<text id="S24A">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:17:24</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Modern Art Museum, London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>The art</topics>
		<activity>A couple discussing modern art at a museum</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0261">so it's getting good sounds I'm going to turn it up okay so let's just see how this goes so erm I I think that he had a very rounded message that er had some interesting things in it that one could explore</u>
<u n="2" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0261">and you know when you see some of his pictures and think erm you know with <unclear>Jenny's</unclear> interest in in <unclear>laser</unclear> and that kind of thing</u>
<u n="4" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0261">and outfit that she works with him for but erm I would have thought in some kind of fashion erm they have an interest in all that kind of stuff that kind of exposure and presumably they come across these people</u>
<u n="6" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="long"/> I'll be <unclear/> surprised if it's all done in isolation</u>
<u n="8" who="S0262">I mean it's a network isn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0262">so I think they actually call it network in the title</u>
<u n="11" who="S0261">they call it traffic one's called traffic and the other one's erm <pause dur="long"/> erm trace network</u>
<u n="12" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0261">mm <unclear>I'm writing this down this is just shocking</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0262">this is exactly why I said do you want to sit here?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0261">oh did you see that coming? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0262">yeah so anyway it's all gonna be on your <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0262">on your <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0261">I'm interested to see how it pans out</u>
<u n="20" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0261">so I mean the idea of following along with someone who does that type of thing and a kind of a erm well a photo journalist way or something like that</u>
<u n="22" who="S0262">I wonder if he works in <unclear/> geography or their their people do</u>
<u n="23" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0262">cos they must have they must have <trunc>pho</trunc>photos cos that would be one way of documenting their work</u>
<u n="25" who="S0261">mm I check I checked out erm Trafford the other day erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> it's it's a network that it's it's been around for a while and it's global erm and so that kind of area is run out of <unclear>K A</unclear></u>
<u n="26" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0261">erm and then there's the Traceman Group and and that is run out of Edinburgh erm and and that is more of a kind of a scientific basis thing DNA tracking and stuff like that I I presume of of species and wildlife traffic and stuff like that</u>
<u n="28" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0261">so erm how how it works I can't imagine that they've got any particular powers to do anything they probably have they probably document evidence in some context which then they put forward erm so that one just seems quite er it's like one particular guy and he seems to be the man who the Traceman Group it so people must work for him but he's not exposed to something else there's a a group of a lot of people <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0262">I'll just see where this coffee went</u>
<u n="31" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="long"/> what happened?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262">oh he's gonna bring it <unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0261">right <pause dur="long"/> so what do you think? what did you think about?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262">well erm yeah I mean you know he's erm he's an interesting talker I mean he <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="35" who="S0261">thank you mm mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262"><unclear/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0261">I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0262">no I think<unclear/> because I want to get his message out there erm I wonder how he actually <unclear>managed</unclear> the whole you know National <trunc>Geoja</trunc>Geographic got its own editorial staff it does what it does</u>
<u n="39" who="S0261">well he he kind of made that clear</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0261">that it's conservative that</u>
<u n="42" who="S0262">and maybe his way of you know fighting to find an audience finding out who is <unclear/> his stuff I mean there was quite a lot of people there today</u>
<u n="43" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0262">so</u>
<u n="45" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">mm but other than that it's appears like well does he go to school does he go to? I mean how does he what what else does he do to support his kind of message? <unclear/> you know like how does he communicate to a big big audience a worldwide audience? that's not a National Geographic you know cos otherwise</u>
<u n="47" who="S0261">yeah well I mean the work that he does is I mean sure he does assignments for National Geographic but he he's effectively his own man he's effectively freelance I would have thought</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">he's not owned by the magazine he's not working for the magazine</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262">no so he's he's basically he's you know he's a freelancer</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0262">but I mean yeah he'll be taking commissions now I would have have thought that is up his street</u>
<u n="53" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262">so he chooses kind of what he thinks is the right kind of assignment for him</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261">yeah mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">but essentially they're not not fully his assignments as in is he driving that idea how is he how is he like putting it together where does that go to?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261">well he's simply told I need a photo of this so he'll carry out whatever research he needs to to understand how he's going to do that with support of a logistics team and contact with <unclear/> scientists erm to get out there erm get the shot get what's important for the magazine somebody else is writing a story about it they could be working with him they could be independent they could be operating out of a library they could be at a university talking to scientists I don't know erm but it would kind of make sense that somehow the people he's working with and people who are writing the story</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262">well I suppose he writes his books doesn't him? that's how he communicates with the with with the</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">yeah and clearly you can see that erm by doing these kind of forums and things like that he's probably thinking longer term that he can't be out doing hefty assignments all of the time and his message kind of sounds like he doesn't like being away from his family but he's doing it</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0261">so he has to balance that whether they're here now with him or not I don't know but</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">well I don't think he was cos he said we're going to <unclear>can't really</unclear> come back because of them so</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261">I suppose the assignments themselves can be for months on end you know they could be a long journey mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">I mean he had he he didn't really talk about it in in concrete terms but you get the impression that he could be away you're right it's not just about being away for a month he could be away for months but you know his wife gets to go with him on some occasions but then who's looking after the kids and that kind of thing but then he he said kids do go with him sometimes so</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262">wherever he can he's making a <unclear/> but also there's risks attached to that because just as he gets Dengue fever and blah blah blah and so could the kids so</u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> he takes on some considerable risks</u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">he does erm and I think that's probably what I admire most about him is that he's a dedicated risk taker</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">he's committed to taking risks I like that</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261">to get what what matters yeah mm <unclear>the shot</unclear></u>
<u n="74" who="S0262">someone's gotta to do it it's him and people like him</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261">mm yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0262"><unclear>like</unclear> you if you wanted to</u>
<u n="77" who="S0261">oh you won't find me climbing up a a a sixty-foot tree with no ropes</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262">I don't think you'd find me <unclear/> tree <unclear/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0261">and you won't find me sitting on top of a hot air balloon</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">when it's really hot</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">no but if you wanted to take photographs of <trunc>li</trunc> of wildlife then you could do it that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">so what do you fancy doing after I've showed you the the giro thing?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">erm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">do you wanna walk back? or get a train? if we get a train we could go well doesn't matter what I was gonna say is we could go past Aldi but we don't need to go to Aldi cos we went shopping on Saturday</u>
<u n="87" who="S0261">we don't have any onions</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262">well if we walk back we could pick up some onions</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">if we take the train we can go to Aldi and get some onions <pause dur="short"/> if you wanna walk I'm happy walking no big digs</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262">yeah <unclear/> we can do that</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">mm okay so you'll show me whatever this particular special thing is?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261">okay <pause dur="long"/> cheers thank you <pause dur="long"/> so today we're at the EMCA</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262">yep</u>
<u n="95" who="S0261">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to show me around</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">ah sorry <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">is that what is that?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">oh maybe it's level two sorry it's level two</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261">so we're just going down the stairs again to level two and hopefully we'll find what we're looking for there</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">yes right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">okay I came to look at this a while back with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0262">yeah?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261">this stuff in here yeah <pause dur="long"/> it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="long"/> what <trunc>i</trunc> what is it?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">it's a piece of string it's a piece of string that's all it is</u>
<u n="105" who="S0261">that and that's just going in a wave</u>
<u n="106" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261">it's not actually spinning round oh it is spinning round as well it's sort of going in a helical wave and then there</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262">it's just a white light</u>
<u n="109" who="S0261">so then <unclear/> it is too so oh that's interesting so then <unclear/> is what creates an impression of the different colours</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261">or something like that</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262">but look inside you can also see like the projection of the string you can see you know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0261">yeah yeah it's like a shadow</u>
<u n="114" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0261">and it travels yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0262"><unclear/> sound you can see more than one <unclear/> you see like the string in the middle and then you see like the <unclear/> and you see the string right in the middle then there's the shadow behind it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0262">so you can see kind of like two or three lines well two lines</u>
<u n="119" who="S0261"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0262">pretty nifty isn't it?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0261">well that's quite cool</u>
<u n="122" who="S0262">well that's just a normal fan</u>
<u n="123" who="S0261">yeah that's just a modified fan</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262" trans="overlap">a fan that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0261">attached a piece of string on it and projected some light in it light in a box</u>
<u n="126" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0261">wow</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
