<text id="S2K6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A car journey from Manchester to Cornwall (going on holiday)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Holiday packing, holidays, weather, decorating/ house, birthday/meal, Indian food, cooking, food</topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on journey to Cornwall (summer holiday)</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">do you want a drink of anything?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0421">yeah I might do <pause dur="long"/> hope I've got everything</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423">well it looks like you've got most things you own in that big bag</u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">yeah pretty much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0423">well I'm surprised I've got three bags clothes the rest of it's like food and bits and pieces I've bought I've bought an iron this time</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0423">I'm just not sure what'll be in these I mean in the last place it had iron and ironing board didn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">well I just like brought quite a lot of stuff</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423">yeah it's better to have it there's plenty of room in the car so you may as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I thought</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423">and if you got a <unclear>clothing</unclear> for each day at least you cos there's probably washing machine on on the site</u>
<u n="13" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">but you'd probably better not have to start washing and stuff isn't it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423">when you can bring enough clothes to the waterpark so <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0421">I always feel like I've forgotten something but I don't think there's anything that I would forget</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423">your toiletries and it looks like you have plenty of clothes that's all you need really isn't it?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah and I mean if I've forgot like and I don't have any toothpaste but I thought you'd bring that</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421">but like if I forgot something like soap or something like I could just buy some</u>
<u n="22" who="S0423">yeah and I've I've bought just clean stuff extra stuff like that cos you don't know what stuff will be there</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421">oh did you yeah did you bring a spray? a side spray and?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0421">oh good good</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423">cos I think last time I gave the place a spray down in the kitchen <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>yo</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah cos you weren't going to and then we were at the shop and I was like let's get one</u>
<u n="28" who="S0423">oh did I not bring one no?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421">no I don't think so and I was like oh wait we should get one and erm I went a bit mad with the spray</u>
<u n="30" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> did you do it?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0421">yeah do you not remember? we had to open all the doors</u>
<u n="32" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I <unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0423">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> so I think <trunc>i</trunc>it's not a bad day for travelling really it's just not too hot</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421">no yeah I thought it was going to be roasting</u>
<u n="36" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> roasting and horrible</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421">because I woke up this morning and I was like <vocal desc="misc"/> I was so warm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0423">yeah it seemed to be quite bright and warm earlier on it's clouded over</u>
<u n="39" who="S0421">but then I went outside cos I heard the cats and I said I better so I went out and I was like <vocal desc="misc"/> it's freezing <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0423">maybe your house holds the heat longer</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421">yeah I think it does <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0423">so your mammy's room it's erm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421">yeah it's done</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">looking good isn't it? it's yours next</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421">yeah I think they were waiting for me to go</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423">it will be nice when you go away and you come back and it'll be much improved won't it?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423">it must be a bit chaotic living there at the moment is it?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421">er yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="50" who="S0423">well especially with your your grandma and grandad having to sleep in the lounge in his boxers on and I mean where do you go when you want to where you can relax and sit down?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0421">in my room</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423">what about when you're eating?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0421">in the kitchen</u>
<u n="54" who="S0423">oh right cos there's nowhere really if you all want to sit down and talk or eat or anything?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0421">we've been in the garden or in the kitchen</u>
<u n="56" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0421">like we never sat in the lounge really in our other house</u>
<u n="58" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> did you not?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0421">no I never really used it I was always in my room anyway <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0423">well your kitchen was a more reasonable size though wasn't it? you could all sit in there and</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh we went out for erm grandad's birthday to that Indian on Saturday</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423">yeah I meant to <unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it was so nice that Indian yeah it was really nice yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423">good</u>
<u n="65" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423">what did you have?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421">I had <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know what it's called it's <trunc>l</trunc> it's like it tasted almost like a korma but I thought wouldn't get a korma it was like a sweeter one it had like mangos and pineapple and coconut or something it was really nice we had it with chicken</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423">oh that's <unclear/> oh so it wasn't vegetarian?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421">no they I don't they didn't really have that much vegetarian stuff I don't know if you can ask</u>
<u n="70" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos proper well proper Indian cooking is <unclear/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0421">yeah yeah it's really nice</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">cos mainly cos most of a lot are vegetarians aren't they? in <unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423">more of it's vegetarian food <pause dur="short"/> I mean what did your grandma have? did she have like English</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421" trans="overlap">she had like a lentils thing she really liked it yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">oh so it wasn't too spicy?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">no well I had a sweet one and she had one that was like well it wasn't spicy at all it said mild</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">and it wasn't spicy cos I tried it and it had like lentils in it or something</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0421">I think grandad had a a balti</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421">and mammy had a korma cos I was going to</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so everyone enjoyed it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">did you have poppadoms and things first?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421">I had a well had poppadoms but we didn't get erm other starters because you you can't</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no it's too filling <unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0421">we barely even ate the curry</u>
<u n="90" who="S0423">yeah but the poppodoms are not too filling are they? always worth having</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423">what time did you go there?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421">about seven</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423">was it busy?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0421">it was actually we almost didn't get a table</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421">yeah because</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423" trans="overlap">why did you not book it?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0421">well no because eh we thought it wouldn't be that busy we were going to go a little bit <trunc>ea</trunc></u>
<u n="100" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah seven's quite busy</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421">yeah we thought it wouldn't be that busy erm and on the website it didn't really you know say like oh book you know cos some of them do they say like oh we're quite busy and whatever so you should book</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">and it didn't say anything like that we went and they were like oh no we've got no rooms and we were like leaving and the guy came after us and was like no no we've found you a table so</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that would have been a bit of a shame what would you have done?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421">I don't know</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423">looked for somewhere else?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421">yeah probably but they probably thought there's like four of them</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we should try and get them in somewhere yeah it was really busy <pause dur="short"/> cos we were thinking like oh is grandma going to like it cos grandma and grandad don't really go out to eat anywhere</u>
<u n="112" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0421">and we didn't know if they would like <trunc>tha</trunc> well we thought grandad would like the Indian but we weren't sure about grandma but she was like oh it's really nice</u>
<u n="114" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0423">well I've I I've brought lots of vegetables for you</u>
<u n="117" who="S0421">have you?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">to practise being a vegetarian <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking about well depending seeing what time they get there cos it's probably not much time to pop out and top up supplies but doing something like a vegetable curry for you but I don't know if you're going to be in the mood for that</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421">mm I'm not really I don't know like I'm quite fussy about curries I don't really like</u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">no I wasn't going to do it spicy</u>
<u n="121" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0423">chilli spicy you can add chilli to it if you wanted to but things like butternut squash aubergines peppers it's really nice one of those</u>
<u n="123" who="S0421" trans="overlap">ah yes do you know I love butternut squash?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423">you know the actual vegetables that I'm I was going to use</u>
<u n="125" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0423">I've done it a couple of times and I've got a <unclear>mangos</unclear> <unclear/> in it as well</u>
<u n="127" who="S0421" trans="overlap">ah butternut squash butternut squash is like the best</u>
<u n="128" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so it's quite different</u>
<u n="129" who="S0421">it's so nice but we never buy it cos I can't peel it and it's <trunc>us</trunc></u>
<u n="130" who="S0423">well no you either put the thing in and what you have to help</u>
<u n="131" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0423">cos the whole point of it is so you can <unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well I've actually found out a good way of peeling butternut squash we just don't but it usually cos it's a bit expensive</u>
<u n="134" who="S0423">well what I do is I I cut it into little smaller manageable chunks and peel it</u>
<u n="135" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it's not like a <pause dur="short"/> well I've found a good way because usually</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423">what's that?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0421">the skin's really hard and I just can't get my knife into it and I end up like cutting my hand open <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you need a small knife though to do it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0421">but I can do it with a peeler now because what you do is I I found this on some cooking website cos I was like I need some help I really like butternut squash but I can't cook it so I looked it up online and it's like right what you have to do is you poke loads of holes in it stick it in the microwave and it softens the skin and you can just peel it off cos it's like it's not it's not like cooked</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423">it just softens</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><trunc>obv</trunc> yeah it's like it gets quite soft so you can peel it</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423">oh right how many? how long do you have to put it in the microwave for?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0421">a few minutes</u>
<u n="144" who="S0423">what? the whole butternut squash?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0421">yeah you just sort of spin it round <vocal desc="laugh"/> but erm cos I put mine in for quite long and it kind of started cooking a bit but it's alright if you're just going to like cook it anyway it's like quite soft and squishy anyway isn't it?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0423">yeah but you don't want to <unclear/> the cooking process in the microwave the best way is if you're cooking something is to you know? like butternut squash it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0421" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0423">cos you get more of the flavours then don't you? and the actual whole dish if you're putting it in with other things</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423">and it's like it's nice like in a curry slow cooked on a low heat and you get <trunc>a</trunc> it just goes soft and there's more flavour if you do it that way</u>
<u n="151" who="S0421">yeah but you're just going to put it in anyway</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423">yeah but <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>it's how you cook things and combine them that makes the flavours if you microwave it you don't get that same</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421">yeah but you don't microwave all of it</u>
<u n="154" who="S0423">well I know yeah but you'll you'll microwave quite an important element possibly</u>
<u n="155" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what? the bit under the skin?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0423">well that's the flesh yeah it's alright if the skin softens a bit but once it starts cooking it's the flesh it's you're changing the cooking process</u>
<u n="157" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0423">it's an exact science to cook things properly</u>
<u n="159" who="S0421">I know but it just</u>
<u n="160" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's like mixing chemicals in the wrong <trunc>e</trunc> order <pause dur="short"/> but erm I use like a you know a paring knife? quite a sharp small one</u>
<u n="161" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I thought <trunc>pe</trunc>people <pause dur="short"/> I can't peel with a knife I have to peel with an a peeler because I just end up cutting my fingers</u>
<u n="162" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but you can't peel everything with a peeler can you?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421">well I've managed alright</u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">yeah?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0423">I didn't bring the peeler</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm just I either I either cut my fingers or I like take off half of the vegetable</u>
<u n="168" who="S0423">ah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0421">cos I'm trying not to cut my fingers</u>
<u n="170" who="S0423">well what kind of? <trunc>w</trunc> is it quite a sharp knife you use?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0423">you just have you're your hand you're holding with away from so you hold it there and peel that way</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0423">so how are you going to cut it if it's not in the vicinity of?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0421">it slips or like it jams into me and the I'm like nearly stabbing myself and</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but if it if it slips it's going to go that way <unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0421">yeah up your arm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0423">well you you have to learn some knife skills</u>
<u n="179" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or I could just use a safe peeler <pause dur="short"/> now don't they usually say cooking is an art but baking is a science</u>
<u n="180" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0421">because baking is like the <trunc>w</trunc>weighing and the measuring and that</u>
<u n="182" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah you have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah and the the <trunc>coo</trunc> the cooking's a bit like</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423">yeah you can have a bit more throwing things together depending on what you want but like the serious chefs you know? you're cooking like <unclear/> these Michelin star <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well it looks art doesn't it? when they put it when they put it on the plate it looks like a painting</u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">well yeah <unclear/> exacting on how they do things</u>
<u n="187" who="S0421" trans="overlap">looks good</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423">we can get away with whatever can't we? <unclear/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">no but I think those Michelin chefs would agree that cooking is an art form</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah maybe</u>
<u n="191" who="S0421">they <trunc>th</trunc>they they're all you know what I mean? you see you see these like</u>
<u n="192" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there is a science to it you have to understand how ingredients go together</u>
<u n="193" who="S0421">yeah well that well you could <trunc>ar</trunc>arguably you could say the same for painting because painting involves chemicals and things but you'd never call painting a science <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0423">erm no cos I mean they're not making the paint are they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0421">no but like the like the when you <trunc>mi</trunc> like mixed media</u>
<u n="196" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0421">mixed forms like you can't erm really like you can't paint over acrylics in watercolours can you?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423">no I mean well I suppose when you get to the down to all the nitty gritty there's there's science in everything really isn't there really?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421">well yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423" trans="overlap">nothing works without science</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> ah we stopping already?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0423">yeah I've got to get fuel we won't get very far with the amount of fuel that I have</u>
<u n="203" who="S0421">oh can I get some Nectar points?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0423">yeah?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0421">oh do you not do Nectar?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0423">no</u>
<u n="207" who="S0421">think I've got a Nectar card <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I've brought it I'll check</u>
<u n="208" who="S0423">I'll start filling it up <unclear/> you can just pass it out to me when I'm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0421" trans="overlap">okay yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0423">or else can I do it at the pump here? no?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0421">can't you?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0423">no</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
