<text id="S2LC">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:57:57</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A car journey from Manchester to Cornwall (going on holiday)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>English language (school subject), university and courses, philosophy, service stations, directions, plans for later, counties and spellings and pronunciation, English language (general and change), spelling, etymology/ words, lightning and storms, organ donations, squeamishness, quinoa, bike race, farmer’s market, pigs.</topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on journey to Cornwall (summer holiday)</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421">cos I like English language but I feel like I might be able to do English language <pause dur="short"/> on my own</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0421">I don't I feel like maybe I don't need a teacher for it I could probably</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh look there's where I work</u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">oh mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well not in there but</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421">I could probably just read the books <pause dur="short"/> erm and get a good knowledge</u>
<u n="8" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">and I mean you know like that that's kind of like the same with creative writing but like I <trunc>wou</trunc> I could do that at home <pause dur="short"/> but erm be alright to do like a for the first year if I've got to do something might be quite good fun</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0421">but like French I couldn't really carry on that by myself because I'm not a good enough standard</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0421">so like it's my extra subjects I should probably pick something <pause dur="short"/> that I will benefit from from having a <pause dur="short"/> a guided thing</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421">cos there's lots of books on English language and I feel like if I read those I'd be alright doing it myself <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0423">yeah it would be good to <pause dur="short"/> kind of link it in to a related subject wouldn't it? to what you're studying <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0421">and if I was studying it myself when I'm in the English department anyway and I had some kind of a question that I didn't understand something I'm sure there'd be someone there to help me</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0421">and they have like erm you can do like world literature <pause dur="short"/> along with English literature but I don't really wanna do that because it's not like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it sounded quite interesting but I don't think I want to do it it's like</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421">erm Greek like I don't know what they do like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0423">what from like classics?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421">yeah I think so maybe not quite classics cos they do have a separate classics course</u>
<u n="24" who="S0423">oh I thought it would be er more modern world literature</u>
<u n="25" who="S0421">no yeah it's like that old stuff</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="27" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it kind of broadens your knowledge of like yeah I suppose like classical things it's not quite classics though because in classics</u>
<u n="28" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well going back to older like</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0423">literature</u>
<u n="31" who="S0421">yeah in different countries because in classics you <trunc>ac</trunc>actually like learn the different languages and things and about culture and things so maybe it's just <unclear>not</unclear> that aspect</u>
<u n="32" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0421">I would have quite liked to do maybe something like philosophy but I don't know what I'd do with philosophy and again that's something that I could do in my own time really</u>
<u n="34" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421">cos I could just read I could read there's lots of books on philosophy that I could do</u>
<u n="36" who="S0423">you could become a full time philosopher</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421">yeah cos there's lots of work for full time philosophers</u>
<u n="38" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0421">philosophising all day</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is there a lot of work for English literature students? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0421">of course there is</u>
<u n="42" who="S0423">is there?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because you can go into anything</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">like what?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421">like <trunc>Engli</trunc> well anything that's not science and you can just get additional training for anything but like to be a philosopher like</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423">well philosophers in theory should be able to go into anything as well</u>
<u n="47" who="S0421">well yeah if you do a philosophy degree</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but you said you could become a full time <trunc>philosoph</trunc> there's like no work for that at all</u>
<u n="50" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0421">like there's no there's</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well if you're good at it and old books then</u>
<u n="53" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0423">I mean there's been somebody on TV who's a <trunc>pai</trunc> a paid full time philosopher</u>
<u n="55" who="S0421">yeah there's like one or two in like</u>
<u n="56" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0421">the world <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't think students who go and do a philosophy degree are planning to go into being a full time philosopher <pause dur="short"/> they'll probably</u>
<u n="60" who="S0423">well how do philosophers come about then? they must start somewhere</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421">yeah well may may I think</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423" trans="overlap">just cos we're in the modern world and we think we know everything doesn't mean <unclear>there's no</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no but yeah there are loads of modern philosophers but the thing is those philosophers probably don't just philosophise all day so like yeah they'll have a book but they'll also do like I dunno research and they'll probably</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well they probably teach don't they?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah they probably teach they <trunc>prob</trunc> they might even be interested in history as well do you know what I mean? they they're not just like sitting round like oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> philosophising all the time</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423">that would be good that that would be a good job</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah there were loads of modern philosophy books not just all the old ones</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421">but you wouldn't be I don't think it would be very rare for someone to be able to live on that full time <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean how many people are buying philosophy books?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0423">mm yeah they have to do other things wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think yeah so like I yeah if you did philosophy you could probably it isn't I think in terms of kind of job prospects people might kind of recognise English a bit more than philosophy</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421">in terms of like employability even though like English <pause dur="short"/> isn't like necessarily gonna be used for the job specifically but English is like a good one a lot of people do it if they don't know what they want to do because</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">but I'm doing it cos I like English</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">well I suppose it demonstrates your level of intelligence if</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you have a degree in most things doesn't it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">well philosophy is kind of quite useful to have like a bit of a knowledge for it cos sometimes I've read books and like I don't understand them because they're like philosophical novels</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0421">and they've got like theories and things in them and I'm just I just don't understand them because I don't know anything about them like I read some Camus and I didn't I didn't realise that he was like I just read it and I was like wow this is a weird book</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">who?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421">Camus</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423">I don't know is he a philosopher?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421" trans="overlap">do you not? yeah well he writes like philosophical fiction</u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421">I don't know if he's got any actual like the pure philosophy things but yeah erm he's quite like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423" trans="overlap">sounds quite interesting</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421" trans="overlap">existential <pause dur="short"/> yeah I read er The Stranger or The Outsider it depends he's French <pause dur="short"/> I didn't</u>
<u n="90" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421" trans="overlap">read it in French though <vocal desc="laugh"/> just read it in English and I I remember I finished reading it and I was like I don't really understand <pause dur="short"/> where this book was going or what it was trying to show or anything</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos it was really short and it was just really strange like well the story wasn't that strange but I don't know and I I didn't really understand it and I feel like if I read it again and read it up a bit more about like some theories that he was trying to employ I think I'd understand it better</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what was he was he coming up with some philosophical ideas which was the theory of some philosopher which is a recognised theory <pause dur="short"/> or was he just making his own stuff up?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0421">no I think it's like because there are like different types of philosophers and I think <pause dur="short"/> because with the thing in like because it's fiction it's not kind of like erm like theories like written out it's kind of incorporated into the story</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421">and he's quite existential so within existentialism it's erm <pause dur="short"/> like about being and well you know like existence like what why are we why do we exist like?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423">so do you have to understand a bit about that philosophy to understand the book?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think so yeah because I mean I kind of like even now knowing a bit more about cos I did I did some research and I do know a bit more about the different branches and things but it's I mean I have to reread the book cos I can't really remember it that well now but even with knowing that I think I'm still kind of thinking about thinking back to the book like not quite sure what he was doing I think I'd have to read it again</u>
<u n="100" who="S0423">I've read er Voltaire</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">one of his novels</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">did you?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and he's like a philosophical writer</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0423">isn't he?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423">yeah but going way back</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421" trans="overlap">did you</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423" trans="overlap">to</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421" trans="overlap">understand it?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0423">no</u>
<u n="113" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0423">so I didn't <pause dur="short"/> you know I don't I don't know whether I particularly enjoyed</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421">and like yeah no I read erm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but like I I mean that was done as I think that's kind of I think I would enjoy more er er reading philosophy in a</u>
<u n="117" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">er knowing that it is just</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421" trans="overlap">in in its purest form yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">yeah well they they're</u>
<u n="121" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0423" trans="overlap">telling you about their theories indirectly rather than in</u>
<u n="123" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423" trans="overlap">written in</u>
<u n="125" who="S0421">it's quite good that</u>
<u n="126" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you you have to</u>
<u n="127" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I've read like extracts and things from certain books</u>
<u n="128" who="S0423">yeah although you</u>
<u n="129" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and they're quite interesting</u>
<u n="130" who="S0423" trans="overlap">having said that it probably is like anything of that kind of <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you know anything that's a bit academic it's probably very hard to get through it <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah cos a lot of them as well a lot of them are erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> like translated if it if they're from different countries and things and then there's like all these like debates over the translation and it's like no this wasn't accurately translated doesn't actually mean this at all and then other people are like no I think it means this so there's</u>
<u n="132" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0421" trans="overlap">all this debate and I'm just like because it there was a bit that I read and then like sometimes I see quotes and I'm like I need to see that in context so I see it in context and I'm like well I've not read the whole book I'll have a look what other people are saying and then there's these people on this like forum or whatever like debating like no well this person says this then this person says that</u>
<u n="134" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0421">yeah I think especially some of the some of the newer ones would be okay to read I think like you can get like philosophy for beginners or like you know</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah something like that might be more <unclear/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0421" trans="overlap">or like quite erm they they like present it in quite like a</u>
<u n="138" who="S0423">simple</u>
<u n="139" who="S0421">a casual way you know what I mean? like you know</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah cos I think to read any of your <trunc>or</trunc>original</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421" trans="overlap">or Aristotle or something</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423">yeah or even or modern ones or something</u>
<u n="143" who="S0421" trans="overlap">or Plato</u>
<u n="144" who="S0423">could be quite like <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah could be yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0423">erm be better to read a book that kind of explains it to you rather than reading it directly</u>
<u n="147" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0423">er what have you ever <trunc>rea</trunc> have you never read one a proper</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I've never read like a yeah I'd quite like to I'd like</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423" trans="overlap">on philosophers or?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos I've read like extracts and I've read all these were quite academic though the ones I was looking at either extracts and then I've read like a critic writing about it or like a discussion on like erm a forum but these forums tend to be like quite high like you know what I mean? they're not just kind of people like discussing</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421">like they are they do know what they're talking about like discussions erm and I I'm quite I I <trunc>fi</trunc> I found those quite interesting because even though the erm discussion itself was <pause dur="short"/> still quite academic it was easier for me to understand just reading it in its its like</u>
<u n="154" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0421">I feel like I'd need the book with kind of someone's like notes next to me like don't understand that that's actually a reference to like you know whatever and I'd be like oh okay</u>
<u n="156" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> so are you are you hungry yet or are you okay?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0421">I'm not that hungry <pause dur="short"/> are you hungry?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0423">no not at all really er cos this there's services here there's something about twenty odd miles I think</u>
<u n="159" who="S0421">oh we can go to those ones maybe</u>
<u n="160" who="S0423">erm cos after that well there probably is some further down this is the <pause dur="short"/> there must be some services if we're going past Bristol area</u>
<u n="161" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> so I mean if you're not hungry it's I don't know <pause dur="long"/> then again we don't wanna leave it too late do we cos?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">I'm just trying to think <trunc>ta</trunc> if you take that thing out of er the what what's the first line on it?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421">Tiverton service area</u>
<u n="166" who="S0423">Tiverton</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421">junction twenty-seven</u>
<u n="168" who="S0423">and that's two hundred and thirty-one miles is it? is there a timing on that to the left?<unclear/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0421">ten eighteen</u>
<u n="170" who="S0423">oh I think it's just timing in each section</u>
<u n="171" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0423">so not an overall time there? er</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0423">each section <unclear/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no I think you asked me this last time and there wasn't</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423">oh cos I've not printed out the whole thing so that's about two hundred miles that we've probably done</u>
<u n="177" who="S0421">that's like a bit further down the page there's Exeter so if you</u>
<u n="178" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's that's coming too <pause dur="short"/> too far down that cos what's the total mileage? so that's about the last two hundred miles of the journey isn't it?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0421">er Exeter is two hundred and forty-seven miles</u>
<u n="180" who="S0423">yeah see that</u>
<u n="181" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and Tiverton is two hundred and thirty-one</u>
<u n="182" who="S0423">yeah no we don't</u>
<u n="183" who="S0421">so Tiverton must be near Exeter</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423">yeah we don't wanna wait till that far down but it might be a bit soon yet I'm just trying to think cos I suppose we should have a little break some time but erm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we could always buy like sandwiches and then eat them later</u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">yeah well we've probably travelled <pause dur="short"/> probably a third of the way I would have thought <pause dur="short"/> so it's took us about two hours to get here and two four six that would be right wouldn't it? so let's shall we leave it another hour of driving?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423">and then we've got probably half of the journey after that it's just sort of to break it up a bit it's probably a bit too early to stop</u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423">erm whether we're hungry or not we'll see what you fancy at the time I suppose we should so say <pause dur="short"/> probably not <trunc>ha</trunc> an hour probably forty-five minutes or something?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0423">er before before half three</u>
<u n="193" who="S0421">uhu <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0423">and then we if we have dinner about eight or something that that's alright isn't it? it's not too late</u>
<u n="195" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0423">it's it's a nice break a long break between it's not getting too late in the day to be eating at that time is it?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423">cos we we won't be eating six'll be too early we wouldn't wanna eat at that time <pause dur="long"/> cos we have to prepare what we're eating so I don't I don't know if we're gonna be going out anywhere by the time we arrive</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421">yeah probably not</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423">check in you want to spray the whole place down with the</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421">disinfectant</u>
<u n="202" who="S0423">antibacterial thing or I think I'd better do that</u>
<u n="203" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0423">unless I'm going out for a walk while you do it have you brought a special mask this time?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0423">so we're the other side of Birmingham now</u>
<u n="207" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="208" who="S0423">the next next town we're gonna come to is Worcester</u>
<u n="209" who="S0421">oh Worcestershire <pause dur="short"/> worcestershire sauce</u>
<u n="210" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0421">or is it Worcester sauce? Worcester sauce isn't it? not Worcestershire sauce or is it Worcestershire?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0423">I think it's Worcestershire</u>
<u n="213" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="214" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you can <trunc>te</trunc> I think it's got either on it</u>
<u n="215" who="S0421" trans="overlap">whatever yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0423">Worcester sauce it think Worcestershire no I think it's Worcestershire</u>
<u n="217" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0423">yeah I'll wait till I'm a little bit more tired I'm still not too bad driving on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0421">what it's weird how Worcester is spelt isn't it? it's like <trunc>Wor</trunc></u>
<u n="220" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0421">cester <pause dur="short"/> it's quite</u>
<u n="222" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah there's few place names like that</u>
<u n="223" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a few yeah a few counties like <trunc>Leic</trunc> Leicestershire? that's quite strange</u>
<u n="224" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah Leicester is really yeah where you don't pronounce it</u>
<u n="225" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0423" trans="overlap">as it's spelt <pause dur="short"/> and there's a few erm there's one <pause dur="short"/> going over towards Hereford there's a place called to to say it as you see it it's spelt Leominster</u>
<u n="227" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="228" who="S0423">but people who are from that area call it Leominster</u>
<u n="229" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="230" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and it's weird cos it's such a different sort of spelling L E O</u>
<u n="231" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0423">M I N S T E R and they say Leominster</u>
<u n="233" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="234" who="S0423">they miss out the O completely <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying to think of one that another one that I've come across <pause dur="long"/> well there's loads like that in like local areas and small places</u>
<u n="235" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="236" who="S0423">well there's one just on the way just outside of <anon type="place"/> on the way to <anon type="place"/> on the main road there's just a little sign for the name of the area and there's a few houses around there and it's spelt <anon type="place"/> so I was chatting to the locals saying oh yeah you know the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0423">which you think it would they say <trunc>Heyr</trunc></u>
<u n="239" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is it <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0423">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0423">they say <anon type="place"/>? you mean <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0423">oh right so that's what it's called</u>
<u n="245" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how did you know that?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0421">it just seemed I don't know it just seemed like it would</u>
<u n="248" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah you always seem to miss out one kind of extreme</u>
<u n="249" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0423" trans="overlap">letter don't you in these words?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0421">it's probably come from Latin <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> or something Gaelic maybe that <trunc>Leo</trunc> like whatever it was sounds like</u>
<u n="252" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Leominster?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0421">yeah <trunc>L</trunc> that sounds like it maybe have a</u>
<u n="254" who="S0423">yeah they probably</u>
<u n="255" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a Gaelic kind of thing</u>
<u n="256" who="S0423" trans="overlap">go back to a long long time ago don't they?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0421">but er English has erm all these silent Bs all over the place like silent letters</u>
<u n="258" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="259" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because of Latin because they had them</u>
<u n="260" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="261" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so when people were like yeah we'll just put them in because Latin has them</u>
<u n="262" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="263" who="S0421">and then you know erm also erm the reason why we have a H after G in some words like ghost</u>
<u n="264" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0421">is because erm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0423">oh they just decided</u>
<u n="267" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0423">okay oh</u>
<u n="269" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because because</u>
<u n="270" who="S0423" trans="overlap">somebody went through the <trunc>di</trunc> to make a dictionary and they said oh no this is</u>
<u n="271" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no it it was</u>
<u n="272" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it was the erm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0423" trans="overlap">because in English they used</u>
<u n="275" who="S0421" trans="overlap">the Flemish</u>
<u n="276" who="S0423" trans="overlap">be a lot more simple didn't they?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0421">it was the</u>
<u n="278" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what was it?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0421" trans="overlap">the the there was a lot of Flemish people in the erm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="281" who="S0421" trans="overlap">printing whatever</u>
<u n="282" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh it as the printing the wasn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah so they all put it in</u>
<u n="284" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0421">but it's not been retained in everything</u>
<u n="286" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0421" trans="overlap">just in some words so like English is like oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> just stick them in there</u>
<u n="288" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0421">cos Flemish has erm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's right I know I heard something like that</u>
<u n="291" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0423">cos er English it used to be a lot more see it is has you see it wasn't it?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0421">well they they</u>
<u n="294" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0421" trans="overlap">didn't have standardised spelling or anything</u>
<u n="296" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="297" who="S0421">so people just used to spell everything however they wanted to</u>
<u n="298" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0421">and spelling only became standardised in seventeen fifty-five with the introduction of Johnson's dictionary</u>
<u n="300" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0421">which took him about eleven years or something to</u>
<u n="302" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="303" who="S0421" trans="overlap">write</u>
<u n="304" who="S0423">I know Johnson's dictionary I didn't know he was the one to standardise it</u>
<u n="305" who="S0421">well he was the first dictionary</u>
<u n="306" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0421">so that's only when <pause dur="short"/> cos then like people would kind of consult the dictionary</u>
<u n="308" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0421">but then <pause dur="short"/> even when that came out there was still a lot of non standard spelling because erm it wasn't widespread and you know like</u>
<u n="310" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah and they thought oh why do we have to go with that?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0421">and there wasn't and you know like local people who like</u>
<u n="312" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0421">not a lot of education and like things like that so it did take a while for it to become like standard but the introduction of that was kind of like the beginning</u>
<u n="314" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0421">of this is how you spell things <pause dur="short"/> and I mean if you look back at that dictionary it probably has stuff spelt differently</u>
<u n="316" who="S0423">well it will do like from that kind of time yeah be a lot of differences so I guess that's as it is when you're when you're kind of alive during times you don't realise how language is developing but you know when you look at it down the ages you see you know so that was his dictionary yeah but language will change all the time</u>
<u n="317" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0423">won't it?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0421">well I mean he made a I think he made more dictionaries over the years well like the Oxford dictionary adds a new word</u>
<u n="320" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0421">when it's been in use for ten years</u>
<u n="322" who="S0423">mm yeah so you get like things that were considered slang and will be entered into it at some point won't they?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0423">if it's still the common use <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0421">I really like etymology dot com and you can put in a word and you can find out its etymology</u>
<u n="326" who="S0423">what does that mean? its history?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0421" trans="overlap">origins it's good it's a fun website <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0423">I don't think many people would say that but obviously has to who's interested in words and English would only say it's a fun website</u>
<u n="329" who="S0421">dictionary dot com is good as well dictionary dot com is really good because it's not just a dictionary it gives you like all sorts of fun facts about language and words and like they have new articles and things coming up about words and stuff it's good</u>
<u n="330" who="S0423">so do you sit in your room all night putting stuff into that saying oh look at that I didn't know that <unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and like I <trunc>rea</trunc> I read the articles on on erm dictionary dot com as well they're really good all about how like words have changed and</u>
<u n="332" who="S0423">do you?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0421">yeah it's good <pause dur="long"/> word of the day on dictionary dot com</u>
<u n="334" who="S0423">well I suppose you're putting your free time to better use than just sitting down and watching telly</u>
<u n="335" who="S0421">I know yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0423">or playing <unclear>sitting on</unclear> video games</u>
<u n="337" who="S0421">it's good entertainment dictionary dot com is</u>
<u n="338" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0423">why do they get somebody on singing and dancing on words <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no they do have a a game on there though that I used to play I've not played it in ages and it was erm it gives you the definition for a word and you have to give the word</u>
<u n="342" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="343" who="S0421">it's harder than it sounds</u>
<u n="344" who="S0423">it sounds very hard to me</u>
<u n="345" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I used to enjoy playing that</u>
<u n="346" who="S0423">did you win?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0421">yeah I was like first in the world</u>
<u n="348" who="S0423">were you?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0421">but probably nobody was playing like</u>
<u n="350" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh somebody's took your crown now you'd better go back on</u>
<u n="351" who="S0421" trans="overlap">probably yeah I was like first in the world for like that month or <trunc>so</trunc> I don't know if I was ever first in the in the world world but yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0423">yeah but can you cheat and look it up?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0421">well it's it's timed</u>
<u n="354" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't think you can can you? oh right</u>
<u n="355" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yeah and how would you look it like you put the definition in like</u>
<u n="356" who="S0423">yeah well you could google that definition and it would come up wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah maybe <pause dur="long"/> cos I used to think something like Scrabble would be good fun and Scrabble's okay but I'm always really annoyed with Scrabble because I'm really limited by the words that I pick out of that pouch the letters</u>
<u n="358" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="359" who="S0421">and it's like I could have fit a good word in there but I just don't have the letters it's just annoying</u>
<u n="360" who="S0423">who you who do you play Scrabble with?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0421">online <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="363" who="S0421">it was good I did play quite a bit of Scrabble for like a while but then I just got bored</u>
<u n="364" who="S0423">who do you play against online? just a computer?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0421">erm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0423">or with other people like?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no they just pair you with someone round the world</u>
<u n="368" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you just play it</u>
<u n="370" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0421">I think it was through Facebook or something</u>
<u n="372" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0421">and you like put in a user name and then you just like you can play with someone</u>
<u n="374" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you don't chat or anything like that?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="376" who="S0423">you just play?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0421">I think you can like able chat if you want but</u>
<u n="378" who="S0423">do what?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0421">I think you can click like if you want to chat with people but you can just have an option to just play <pause dur="short"/> sometimes I would be playing with someone though and they'd put in such like long complicated words then I'm just like I don't even know what that is never mind have the letters for that word</u>
<u n="380" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but er is it is it all in English though?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0423">well how do you know it's a real word? is that checked by?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because the <trunc>compu</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the thing is you could cheat on Scrabble like if you're playing online cos there's all sorts of anagram solvers and things that you can get online so</u>
<u n="384" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="385" who="S0421">yeah I was I was properly against people cheating as well</u>
<u n="386" who="S0423">well there's not much point really is there playing if you're going to cheat against some random stranger?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0423">it's not really what's the point in playing? <pause dur="short"/> you can't come away thinking yes that was a great game</u>
<u n="389" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0423">I beat that person if you just well I don't understand the satisfaction</u>
<u n="391" who="S0421">yeah well they want to go up on the leader board</u>
<u n="392" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0421">I think cos like on the Facebook thing you can like invite your friend to play with you or you can just be paired with like a random person who also wants to play</u>
<u n="394" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0421">but erm <pause dur="short"/> none of my friends ever wanted to play Scrabble <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> or like I'd invite them and they'd like take their go like a week later or something and I'd just be like</u>
<u n="396" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> not as interesting words as you</u>
<u n="397" who="S0421">no <pause dur="long"/> oh and do you know what else I came across? and I didn't realise this was a thing it's like a pronunciation dictionary</u>
<u n="398" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0421">it I saw it in our college library and I was like oh what's this? so I went to have a look and it's basically a dictionary but it it tells you the pronunciation in erm English English and American English</u>
<u n="400" who="S0423">oh right I thought all dictionaries do they not have a thing where it shows you how to pronounce stuff?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it will yeah if you get a good dictionary then it does</u>
<u n="402" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0421">but this was just I don't know why they why that's what I was thinking you can you can get it in a normal dictionary as well</u>
<u n="404" who="S0423">not American though it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I wonder why they have that combination</u>
<u n="407" who="S0421">well because they're both English aren't they?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="409" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they're very</u>
<u n="410" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but the two</u>
<u n="411" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they're the two types of English you can get</u>
<u n="412" who="S0423">yeah but I suppose if you're if they if it's published in English in America I suppose but if it's just published over here you're not gonna need the American one are you?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0421">no but you might want to for like purposes of having a look like get the change <pause dur="short"/> if you're like a linguist</u>
<u n="414" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc>you're not gonna go to well</u>
<u n="415" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no but if you're a linguist then you <trunc>migh</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0423">if you're a linguist you should know already shouldn't you?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0421">well not necessarily <pause dur="short"/> if you're interested in linguistics then you might want to <pause dur="short"/> er it's quite good I don't know I quite want one but I don't think I need one I think just use my regular dictionary <pause dur="short"/> cos that has it in as well</u>
<u n="418" who="S0423">you know you're not gonna need American</u>
<u n="419" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0423">pronunciation are you?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0421">I might like to look at it for the novelty though</u>
<u n="422" who="S0423" trans="overlap">unless when you go over there on holiday you start talking American to everyone</u>
<u n="423" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's quite good for the novelty of it although dictionary dot com provides me with both as well <pause dur="short"/> usually so <pause dur="short"/> and it even speaks it out</u>
<u n="424" who="S0423">does it?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0421">yeah so I don't need to learn the phonetic alphabet but I want to <pause dur="short"/> seems like a good thing to know</u>
<u n="426" who="S0423">is it something you use?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0421">I think I would I'd use it when I'm when I'm doing my dictionary surfing and if I saw a word I could know how to pronounce it as well</u>
<u n="428" who="S0423">dictionary surfing?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what's that?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know I just</u>
<u n="432" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you have to go to the seaside for it?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I just made that up then like people surf the the internet don't they? I can surf the dictionary <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I thought it sounded quite good</u>
<u n="434" who="S0423">yeah <trunc>yo</trunc> it's funny how you just accept expressions like surfing the web</u>
<u n="435" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0423">I mean I wonder where that's come from it's a bit odd really isn't it?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> it's idiomatic</u>
<u n="438" who="S0423">pardon?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0421">it's idiomatic</u>
<u n="440" who="S0423">what are you calling the person an idiot who thought of it?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> but it's weird like they have them in other languages as well like <pause dur="short"/> these expressions and it's just like oh</u>
<u n="442" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="443" who="S0421">and in French we learnt some of them but I've forgotten most of them <pause dur="short"/> but there was like er it was like erm I've got a cockroach sitting on my head and guess what that's a expression for?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0423">what in French?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0423">I don't know</u>
<u n="447" who="S0421">it's erm it basically means that like oh I'm fed up or bored</u>
<u n="448" who="S0423">yeah that is quite interesting other countries' use of expressions I mean that's just weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0423">why would anyone have a cockroach on your head when you're bored? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0421">or er it's raining cats and dogs</u>
<u n="452" who="S0423">well yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0421" trans="overlap">in England <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0423">yeah they're all strange aren't they?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> they have one that makes sense like I'm er in French I'm I'm as hungry as a wolf or something</u>
<u n="456" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0421">that makes sense but what what we would say like</u>
<u n="458" who="S0423">I'm so hungry I could eat a horse</u>
<u n="459" who="S0421">I could eat a horse yeah that's weird as well isn't it? why would you be eating a horse?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you'd think the French would say that though</u>
<u n="461" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0423">they eat horses</u>
<u n="463" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0423">we don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0423">we say it I guess cos it's quite a big animal isn't it a horse?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0423">probably where it'll be coming from <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0421">I think the French one about the cockroaches <trunc>tr</trunc>translates directly to like I have the cockroach or something</u>
<u n="470" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="471" who="S0421">and it it's like basically like I think where it comes from is like as though it's like oh I don't know it's so weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0421">do you want some of these?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0423">yeah if you're dishing some out no wonder we're not hungry</u>
<u n="475" who="S0421">I know yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0423">they are tasty <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0421">you can't taste them?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0423">I said they're tasty</u>
<u n="479" who="S0421">oh right <pause dur="long"/> we had a good thunderstorm not long ago</u>
<u n="480" who="S0423">yeah I was riding my bike home in it</u>
<u n="481" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I was at home <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0423">probably not safe to ride a bike in a thunderstorm really</u>
<u n="483" who="S0421">no you could have been struck <pause dur="short"/> grandma doesn't like thunderstorms</u>
<u n="484" who="S0423">does she scream?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0421">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> but she just generally doesn't like them and I'm like well it's not like you're gonna get struck down are you? and she's like yeah but so many people do</u>
<u n="486" who="S0423">so many people don't</u>
<u n="487" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0423">some people do don't they?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0421" trans="overlap">she's like they're so dangerous <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> like they're not they're not that dangerous <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0423">it's extremely rare</u>
<u n="491" who="S0421">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0423">more dangerous crossing a road</u>
<u n="493" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> aren't you supposed to turn the lights off when there's one? <pause dur="short"/> I never do</u>
<u n="494" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah you're supposed to turn off electrical appliances cos</u>
<u n="495" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0423">cos <pause dur="short"/> they can er be blown up can't they?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't think many people do though they?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0423">no</u>
<u n="499" who="S0421">I don't</u>
<u n="500" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos it's quite a rare thing isn't it? it's like</u>
<u n="501" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I remember when we were at the country house and there was a like a big thunderstorm and they're I really like them over there because you actually get the forks of lightning and over here you only really get the sheet lightning</u>
<u n="502" who="S0423">well you do you get fork lightning here it's just they're probably not as common</u>
<u n="503" who="S0421" trans="overlap">probably and it's probably behind the clouds</u>
<u n="504" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you can't see it yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0421">yeah so I never really see the fork lightning over here and over there you do and I'm like looking it like wow and grandma's like got all the lights switched off and like all the electrical things off and everything and she's like <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0423">did she do that the other night?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="508" who="S0423">oh did she not?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no but she she she did it in the country house I think maybe cos she's worried cos there's loads of trees there and a big forest</u>
<u n="510" who="S0423">well yeah when you when it the sky is clear and it's lightning it's it can be spectacular and you do you people send photos that you get them showing them on the news of</u>
<u n="511" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0423" trans="overlap">er so you do see them the fork lightning it's just like you say it depends on clouds and where you are and</u>
<u n="513" who="S0421">can they not er get electricity from storms?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0423">erm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0421">could they not?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it would be just so unpredictable wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="518" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I guess you can</u>
<u n="519" who="S0421">could they not sometimes?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0423">but it's probably just not worth it is it?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what they would be able to get and store and the effort you'd put into something and what you'd get out of it</u>
<u n="523" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0423">it's probably just not worth it is it? what are you thinking like of Frankenstein's monster when he</u>
<u n="525" who="S0421">I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0423">brought him to life with the lightning?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0421">that would be good wouldn't it? <pause dur="long"/> people aren't really doing experiments like that are they?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0423">Ross-on-Wye it's not far from Hay-on-Wye</u>
<u n="529" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="530" who="S0423">people what?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0421">aren't really doing like experiments anymore are they? well I mean if they <vocal desc="laugh"/> did they ever do experiments like that tried to</u>
<u n="532" who="S0423" trans="overlap">scientists are constantly doing experiments a lot of them are</u>
<u n="533" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0423">experimenting for things like bringing a Frankenstein's monster</u>
<u n="535" who="S0421">yeah no but he wasn't meant to be a monster though was he?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0423">I think from that era when it's er like Victorian they did that have that kind of like idea or we'll</u>
<u n="537" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like and have that that idea of a mad scientist probably because they used to pick up bodies and things to</u>
<u n="539" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0423" trans="overlap">dissect them to understand your body</u>
<u n="541" who="S0421">well I mean they still</u>
<u n="542" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I guess</u>
<u n="543" who="S0421">like</u>
<u n="544" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well they use human bodies</u>
<u n="545" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0423" trans="overlap">just don't yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they just don't dig them up</u>
<u n="548" who="S0423" trans="overlap">just don't well yeah some <unclear/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a legal way</u>
<u n="550" who="S0423">well people donate their bodies don't they? science and <unclear/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah well my my friend was like oh why don't you sign up for organ donation? and I was just like I don't really want to I don't I don't know I'm not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0423">well in some countries it it's erm compulsory unless you sign out of it</u>
<u n="553" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="554" who="S0423">and they were thinking of doing that in this country because there are so few people doing it and it saves so many lives you know</u>
<u n="555" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0423">erm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0421">I don't know I feel like I want to but</u>
<u n="558" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so I've never signed up for it but I I'd be more than happy to give to donate any of my organs cos</u>
<u n="559" who="S0421">yeah cos</u>
<u n="560" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>if it happened</unclear></u>
<u n="561" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's good isn't it for like people?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0423">well yeah if somebody's in need of a a</u>
<u n="563" who="S0421" trans="overlap">an organ</u>
<u n="564" who="S0423" trans="overlap">a liver or a heart or whatever if yours is good but I've erm I mean I think somebody once said oh don't do that cos maybe they won't try as hard to save your life or <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think some people think that you know they think oh they won't be if he dies we can get his heart and we can have <unclear/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they're like oh we can get all his organs oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0423">I dunno have you heard of like that I've I'm sure you've heard of like that exhibition you know where?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0421">yeah that awful one</u>
<u n="568" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the <unclear/> thing yeah I think we've probably spoken about it before I <unclear>can't</unclear> understand people who donate their body to him</u>
<u n="569" who="S0421">for yeah yeah if you say you donate your body to science then that could happen but if you've just donated your organs then they can't do that to you they can just take your organs</u>
<u n="570" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="571" who="S0421">it</u>
<u n="572" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so they could use it for <trunc>anyth</trunc> I don't think it it would end up being in his hands though cos it's not really scientific is it?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0421">yeah well I mean like supposedly</u>
<u n="574" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's like a <unclear/> exhibit</u>
<u n="575" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's a kind of</u>
<u n="576" who="S0423">well yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0421" trans="overlap">educating the public but <pause dur="short"/> not really but yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0423" trans="overlap">not when he's posing and</u>
<u n="579" who="S0421">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="S0423">playing tennis and cards that's doesn't stand up does it you know people just go out of morbid curiosity</u>
<u n="581" who="S0421">oh I couldn't have looked at it like I'm so squeamish like oh <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't have couldn't have done it <pause dur="short"/> but yeah if you donate your body to medical science like you could end up the person like students are dissecting</u>
<u n="582" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0421">but if you just donate your organs I think all they can have is your organs</u>
<u n="584" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and now I guess cos you kind of think well why do they need bodies now? but because we know so much about the body but</u>
<u n="585" who="S0421">but it it yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they need to practise don't they?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the students on</u>
<u n="589" who="S0421">like <trunc>s</trunc> future surgeons</u>
<u n="590" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they want <unclear/> for certain</u>
<u n="591" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I'd rather them be practising on a dead body than like <vocal desc="laugh"/> the first <trunc>go</trunc> the first time going into surgery and they've never seen one before</u>
<u n="592" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0421">but that must be awful like I don't know how doctors do that like oh oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0423">well everyone's different aren't they? <pause dur="short"/> some people don't give it a second thought <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0421">I couldn't even dissect a frog or <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0423">yeah it always seems to be girls that er</u>
<u n="597" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no there was a boy in my <vocal desc="laugh"/> science class</u>
<u n="598" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but they have that reputation of being more squeamish than boys</u>
<u n="599" who="S0421">there was a boy in my science class who was like green in the face when we did the heart dissection I mean I just didn't look but he was like looking and it looked like he was about to faint</u>
<u n="600" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what kind of a heart was it a cow's organs?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think so yeah <pause dur="long"/> most of the class were like okay to look at it though</u>
<u n="602" who="S0423">yeah I don't see why not</u>
<u n="603" who="S0421">I I was like so surprised I was like <vocal desc="gasp"/> how are you doing that?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0423">it's not as though the whole body was there though <trunc>prob</trunc></u>
<u n="605" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0423">it's a bit probably harder to look at when the whole thing is</u>
<u n="607" who="S0421" trans="overlap">then again</u>
<u n="608" who="S0423">is like</u>
<u n="609" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I'm the person who doesn't like touching raw meat so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't even like to look at raw meat <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0423">well would you not be able to prepare it if you had gloves on or something?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no like even looking at it oh <pause dur="short"/> and it smells ah I hate</u>
<u n="612" who="S0423" trans="overlap">shall we stop at the next services?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0423" trans="overlap">thirteen miles</u>
<u n="615" who="S0421">yeah it stinks I hate the smell of raw meat</u>
<u n="616" who="S0423">maybe it's gone off when you're you're</u>
<u n="617" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> I hate the smell of the butcher's it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> I can't go in butchers really</u>
<u n="618" who="S0423">why when was the last time you were there? I don't think you go</u>
<u n="619" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="620" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that often do you? I mean obviously you've got the supermarket</u>
<u n="621" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no but even if you walk past even if you walk past no or like the deli counter <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="622" who="S0423">yeah I think there was something on the news a while ago saying oh there was a butcher and he was told by the <trunc>s</trunc> the shopping centre that he was in</u>
<u n="623" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0423">because he obviously he had meat hung up in the window and stuff</u>
<u n="625" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0423">but I supposedly it was upsetting children and he was told to take it down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well like sometimes they have the whole animal hung there like</u>
<u n="630" who="S0423">yeah but you</u>
<u n="631" who="S0421" trans="overlap">with the fur on it and</u>
<u n="632" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no not with the fur no</u>
<u n="633" who="S0421" trans="overlap">feathers there were in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="635" who="S0421" trans="overlap">there as like rabbits and pheasants hung there</u>
<u n="636" who="S0423">yeah they'll be seasonal won't they? they'll be shot by somebody local probably</u>
<u n="637" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0423">what do you fancy eating?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0421">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="640" who="S0423">actually we'll have to see what's at this services</u>
<u n="641" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0423">I bet they're not that good are they?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0421">there was a Burger King at the last one</u>
<u n="644" who="S0423">well do you fancy a Whopper?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0421">well it's not a bad place to eat is it? we usually go to the Burger King</u>
<u n="646" who="S0423">yeah erm there probably isn't one at this next one <unclear/> probably a different thing I don't like those er Road Chefs</u>
<u n="647" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="648" who="S0423">not good</u>
<u n="649" who="S0421">do you remember that really <unclear>dump</unclear> one that we stopped off at?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0423">that was Scotland wasn't it?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yeah I think so and then the next one</u>
<u n="652" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah with</u>
<u n="653" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we passed had all cool stuff in it</u>
<u n="654" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0421">and we'd eaten some really dodgy sandwich that was horrible</u>
<u n="656" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> it's cos we'd we'd gone for ages as well we'd</u>
<u n="657" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0423" trans="overlap">been waiting and then</u>
<u n="659" who="S0421">and then like the next</u>
<u n="660" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we thought well we'll go in this one</u>
<u n="661" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0423">cos we don't know where the next one will be</u>
<u n="663" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0423">so many fifty mile an hour limits <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0421">what do you think's in that lorry?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0423">which lorry?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0421">that blue one next to us</u>
<u n="668" who="S0423">oh I bet it's full of asylum seekers</u>
<u n="669" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> could be <pause dur="long"/> smuggling them in <pause dur="short"/> what's Coltons? what what mm?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0423">it's an English lorry that isn't it?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0421"><unclear/> yeah oh</u>
<u n="672" who="S0423">Tate and Lyle sugar</u>
<u n="673" who="S0421">oh is that all Tate and Lyle do sugar?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0423">I don't know but it's Colton Commercials <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why they have working in partnership with Take and Lyle it could even be engineering stuff you know for their factories you know if they're working in cos sugar transportation they probably have it in massive containers don't they? you know like you see these tankers they probably have raw sugar in or something</u>
<u n="675" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0423">although that could be coming from the factory and you know the bags of sugar</u>
<u n="677" who="S0421">yeah going to the</u>
<u n="678" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it could be all</u>
<u n="679" who="S0421" trans="overlap">supermarket</u>
<u n="680" who="S0423">pallets in there yeah or the <unclear>little</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0421">did you hear about that erm grain that I don't it's called something it's got a weird and it's like <trunc>quin</trunc> quinoa or something?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0423">yeah I've tried cooking it</u>
<u n="683" who="S0421">have you? well it it's</u>
<u n="684" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think I overcooked it it wasn't nice when I had it</u>
<u n="685" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's rose in popularity in like the western world</u>
<u n="686" who="S0423">yeah it's meant to be</u>
<u n="687" who="S0421" trans="overlap">recently</u>
<u n="688" who="S0423">good for you isn't it?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because it's supposed to be good for you</u>
<u n="690" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0421">and everyone's been buying like you know all the health food</u>
<u n="692" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0421" trans="overlap">people are like oh it's really good and everything but the only problem is that in south America where they grow it</u>
<u n="694" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0421">all the farmers that's like basically what their diet is made of</u>
<u n="696" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="697" who="S0421">and because the demand has rose so high erm the prices are rising and everything and like the normal people there can't afford to eat it anymore</u>
<u n="698" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="699" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so like people are being encouraged to like not you know</u>
<u n="700" who="S0423" trans="overlap">not eat it</u>
<u n="701" who="S0421">yeah because we're all buying it we could be eating anything and we're all</u>
<u n="702" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0421">buying this now and the people over there who have literally like nothing er that's like what they eat</u>
<u n="704" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0421" trans="overlap">all the time that's like their rice</u>
<u n="706" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0421">and <vocal desc="laugh"/> they can't eat anything because</u>
<u n="708" who="S0423">well can't they grow something else?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0421">well maybe but</u>
<u n="710" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well maybe they're getting more wealth out of it if if it's such demand and <unclear/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but like the <trunc>ki</trunc></u>
<u n="712" who="S0423" trans="overlap">charging us higher prices for it</u>
<u n="713" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but the the they're like the poor people</u>
<u n="714" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well no it probably doesn't go to those people yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah like the <trunc>p</trunc> the poor people are like</u>
<u n="716" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0421">got nothing to eat</u>
<u n="718" who="S0423">quinoa</u>
<u n="719" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's got it's spelt weird it's like it's spelt like quinoa</u>
<u n="720" who="S0423">yeah Q I N or whatever else</u>
<u n="721" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is in it</u>
<u n="723" who="S0421">cos I saw I saw I see all these weird and wonderful things in Holland and Barrett's</u>
<u n="724" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="725" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and I've seen people writing about it online and I saw this article and it's like yeah er I mean like obviously they do eat other stuff as well but like they're really like that that's where it grows for them really well</u>
<u n="726" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and that's just what they eat and then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0423">well it's like in</u>
<u n="729" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0423" trans="overlap">our kind of food</u>
<u n="731" who="S0421">in that other place like we would grow potatoes</u>
<u n="732" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's potatoes</u>
<u n="733" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0423">and if people around the world started saying we want potatoes</u>
<u n="735" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> from England</u>
<u n="736" who="S0423">farmers would sell it to the highest bidder</u>
<u n="737" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0423">and er we'd just have to start paying higher prices although we we have so much variety here</u>
<u n="739" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we can eat anything</u>
<u n="741" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yeah but over there like it it must be coming from like poor places and</u>
<u n="742" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0421">they're like well <pause dur="short"/> they probably have other stuff but that was like the main thing that they ate every day and then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0423">yeah it's probably their staple diet isn't it?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah and then <pause dur="short"/> we decided we want it</u>
<u n="746" who="S0423">well yeah over the last couple of years I've heard a lot of like the</u>
<u n="747" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because it's a lot of people</u>
<u n="748" who="S0423" trans="overlap">publicity about it and you know</u>
<u n="749" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a lot of people who are eating it are like maybe like vegan or you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0421">erm and they're like all for like animal rights and everything and it's like well it's hurting somebody out there so maybe you should er <pause dur="short"/> stop eating it <vocal desc="laugh"/> find something else</u>
<u n="752" who="S0423">mm maybe you're gonna start eating that now are you?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0421">no I well I I saw it at the shop I was and erm now that I know that I'm definitely not going to eat it <pause dur="short"/> if the poor people are starving <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0423">yeah I tried it once and I can't remember why it's meant to be good for you but</u>
<u n="755" who="S0421">might as well have rice or something</u>
<u n="756" who="S0423">I think I overcooked it I was gonna put it in salad and it kind of split and just it was kind of mushy I don't think it's meant to be like that so I think I I didn't do it again <pause dur="short"/> we must have passed those services cos I've oh no it's coming up now seems like we've been driving a long time since we saw it <pause dur="long"/> this is down here where we did the bike race</u>
<u n="757" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="758" who="S0423">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0421" trans="overlap">did you win?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0423">no there's about two thousand people racing</u>
<u n="761" who="S0421">yeah and there's all them professionals isn't there?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what did you come did you do better than last year?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0423">well my times all of our times were better</u>
<u n="765" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0423">but we did er a an extra lap so we did more laps this year</u>
<u n="767" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0423">but we're still in a similar kind of position</u>
<u n="769" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="770" who="S0423">in a way er <pause dur="short"/> so I want to I wanna do some more cycling and get fitter so I can do even better next year <pause dur="short"/> I wanna be up there with the fastest</u>
<u n="771" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you wanna win</u>
<u n="772" who="S0423">yeah well no I'm never gonna win but</u>
<u n="773" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0423">but I was the I was the fastest in our team</u>
<u n="775" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="776" who="S0423">so that's good</u>
<u n="777" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="778" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that I was like the fastest in the team</u>
<u n="779" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0423">that's always the challenge and we got a personal trainer on our team</u>
<u n="781" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="782" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and he's pretty fit</u>
<u n="783" who="S0421">really?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0423">yeah well he doesn't only do cycling so he you know</u>
<u n="785" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0423">but he does other stuff you know <pause dur="long"/> and we missed a couple of laps cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bike broke down</u>
<u n="787" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="788" who="S0423">and then erm he said oh I'm not he cos we said oh you can use one of ours and he said no that's it I've had it now just erm me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were talking and said oh we're gonna have to go out sooner and have less of a break</u>
<u n="789" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0423">before the next ride and then the other rider this personal trainer came back in cos he went out after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0423">and he said oh I've just crashed and I'm I've had enough I'm not going out again <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0423">so there was just should be four of us and this was like in the middle of the night as well</u>
<u n="795" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0423">just me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looking at each other then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he went to bed after he decided he wasn't doing any more and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh alright I'll borrow this other bloke's bike then I'll come out and ride so we we probably might have done a couple more <trunc>l</trunc>laps which would have pushed us up a lot higher</u>
<u n="797" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but I think we would have done <trunc>bet</trunc> much better than last year if it wasn't for the problems <pause dur="short"/> and I I crashed I come off once and another rider went into the back of me and crashed into me</u>
<u n="799" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how does that happen?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0423">well the hills you're going down</u>
<u n="801" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="802" who="S0423">and when I went out a little bit of rain and it was like a grassy hill which you can go really quick on</u>
<u n="803" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so I went really quick and got past this rider and then unfortunately though just out of sight at the bottom of the hill</u>
<u n="805" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it comes to a bit of a turning</u>
<u n="807" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0423">so cos you're going so quick you've got to brake then and er take it so you slow down and take the turning but cos there was a bit of rain er that wheel just slid like on the grass and cos I come off he had to brake behind me and then he went and slammed into me <pause dur="short"/> fortunately my bike was okay and I was okay <pause dur="long"/> I think we must have just passed by those original services because</u>
<u n="809" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0423">I feel like we've done more than thirteen miles</u>
<u n="811" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0423">and it's only one mile away now Gloucester services</u>
<u n="813" who="S0421">oh <trunc>Glouc</trunc>Gloucestershire</u>
<u n="814" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that sounds like it should be a posh one</u>
<u n="815" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Gloucester services I should think</u>
<u n="817" who="S0421">yeah Gloucestershire that's not spelt like that's spelt weird</u>
<u n="818" who="S0423">no that's the town Gloucester oh right</u>
<u n="819" who="S0421">Gloucestershire</u>
<u n="820" who="S0423">yeah Gloucestershire is yeah it's another one where</u>
<u n="821" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's not yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0421">why? is Gloucester posh?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0423">I don't know it sounds posh doesn't it?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0421">yeah like gloss</u>
<u n="826" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and see</u>
<u n="827" who="S0421" trans="overlap">glossy</u>
<u n="828" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they've got a farm shop and kitchen</u>
<u n="829" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="830" who="S0423">well there won't be a Burger King here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0423">do you want to try it for a change?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah they might have some nice sandwiches</u>
<u n="834" who="S0423">yeah it'll be different to er to the usual services <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="835" who="S0421">farm shop</u>
<u n="836" who="S0423" trans="overlap">services fully open</u>
<u n="837" who="S0421">is a farm shop nice is that like?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's supposed to be like local produce</u>
<u n="839" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="840" who="S0423" trans="overlap">isn't it? usually it's a nice little quality isn't it?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0421">yeah like farmers' markets they always look so nice where they've got all the cheese and stuff</u>
<u n="842" who="S0423">I love the pig the Gloucester pig</u>
<u n="843" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0423">I think there must be a breed of pig Gloucestershire</u>
<u n="845" who="S0421">oh yeah the Gloucester Old Spot</u>
<u n="846" who="S0423">Old Spot that's the one</u>
<u n="847" who="S0421">ah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0423">well maybe you can have a Gloucestershire Old Spot sandwich</u>
<u n="849" who="S0421">no I don't think they eat them do they?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0423">well yeah what else do you have them for?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0421">are they not in like pig shows for like beauty?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0423">well you can have all animals</u>
<u n="853" who="S0421">oh yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you have these shows</u>
<u n="855" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0423" trans="overlap">for them and compare them but it doesn't mean you don't eat them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0421">oh yeah I suppose pigs</u>
<u n="858" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's what all farming's about</u>
<u n="859" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what else are they for?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0423">isn't it?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0421">no but you get like cows for like milk but I suppose pigs</u>
<u n="862" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="S0421">you just eat them don't you?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0423">yeah I don't think you you milk pigs <unclear/></u>
<u n="865" who="S0421" trans="overlap">did I did I tell you about erm some this girl at college? she lives on a farm and it's mainly like oh no no yeah they do have animals as well but they've got agriculture and they grow like well I dunno like potatoes and stuff but they have a pig and I was like well you don't eat your pig do do you? like</u>
<u n="866" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="867" who="S0421">like you poor pig cos like it's like their pet well not their pet but they they have some pigs</u>
<u n="868" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and they were like erm no there's a farmer not too far away from us so we swap pigs and eat each other's so it's not like you're killing your own pig</u>
<u n="870" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0421">and I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> you <trunc>c</trunc> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos like they they they kill it and then they eat it and so they swap because they don't wanna like be you know killing their own that they've like had</u>
<u n="872" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0421">cos it's it you but yeah they</u>
<u n="874" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I'm not sure</u>
<u n="875" who="S0421">it still gets killed</u>
<u n="876" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there is some kind of sense in it</u>
<u n="877" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but</u>
<u n="878" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but I'm not quite sure</u>
<u n="879" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know I was like oh you eat it? and she's like yeah and I'm just like <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="880" who="S0423">I thought you meant cos there's <trunc>l</trunc>like these <unclear/> things isn't there?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0423" trans="overlap">some people <pause dur="short"/> popular as pets</u>
<u n="883" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they keep them don't they? yeah but no <pause dur="short"/> they're gonna eat it <pause dur="short"/> or the the other one they're gonna eat the other one <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
