<text id="S2QU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:46:32</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0519 S0520 S0522</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Hunsonby, Cumbria</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cheshire, house moving, potty training, children, TV series,  </topics>
		<activity>Morning cuppa with mum and sister</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0519">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Dublin, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith, `</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Recently retired maths teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0520">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, UK`</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>India/Thailand/UK (Hunsoney</hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Transcriber, Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0522">
				<exactage>34</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Chester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>H.R. Consultant</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2>Dutch</l2>
				<fls>French -- GCSE; German -- A-level</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0519">of October erm so dad's organised all the erm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0522">oh</u>
<u n="3" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> which was quite amusing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0522" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it's like mum going to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I want to you to be in charge of <vocal desc="misc"/> and then you just think mm maybe this wasn't the easiest way round</u>
<u n="6" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="7" who="S0520">he's been good in the end</u>
<u n="8" who="S0519">he was in the end but you're right it's you know we hire Anyvan dot com</u>
<u n="9" who="S0520">and they'll have the <trunc>sa</trunc> exact opposite reaction like dad'll be like well this one's only a thousand pounds but the other people want four and mum'll be like no</u>
<u n="10" who="S0519">they <trunc>ca</trunc> if it's</u>
<u n="11" who="S0520" trans="overlap">go with the expensive one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0519">well l I <trunc>ju</trunc> yeah as you very well know I say well what's wrong with it then? <vocal desc="laugh"/> but he had one he he said oh look these are from <trunc>o</trunc> thirty-nine pounds upwards <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're moving our entire house and your grand piano <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0522">dad you <unclear>only</unclear> pay for what you get</u>
<u n="14" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0520">well eventually of course you know whatever brilliant deal is up there it's not really a brilliant deal it's just like pretending to be and then they say oh by the way you know there's tax and this and that and it all adds up to the same doesn't it? it's not like anyone I mean six thousand pounds was a bit over the top but</u>
<u n="16" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah that's right <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0520">yeah so he's got a special guy to do the piano and the rest he doesn't care about really</u>
<u n="18" who="S0519">well eventually we got a good people and I made him do the</u>
<u n="19" who="S0520" trans="overlap">stick it in a warehouse <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0519">so this is the very last thing I said have you checked any reviews? <vocal desc="laugh"/> er so we did and the firm got great reviews so we just went with that but it's three and a half thousand just for the furniture and erm another four hundred for the piano</u>
<u n="21" who="S0520">it's quite a lot isn't it? to be honest but that's including storage for six months</u>
<u n="22" who="S0519">yes I think he put five to six months and they estimated for that so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0520">so that takes you to September October November December <trunc>Nov</trunc></u>
<u n="24" who="S0519" trans="overlap">October November December January February March we won't be done by then I shouldn't think</u>
<u n="25" who="S0520" trans="overlap">well you might be</u>
<u n="26" who="S0519">we could be but</u>
<u n="27" who="S0520">when do people start putting their houses on?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0519">I think probably March</u>
<u n="29" who="S0520" trans="overlap">March probably yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0520">is that what you think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0519" trans="overlap">do you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0522">sorry I didn't hear</u>
<u n="34" who="S0520">do when people start putting their houses on the market like March or April?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0522" trans="overlap">yeah usually it's spring isn't it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0519">because we think it it's gonna</u>
<u n="39" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I mean you could find somewhere in the winter</u>
<u n="40" who="S0519" trans="overlap">we could we could</u>
<u n="41" who="S0520">but and you might get a better deal but erm most people wait don't they? to move in the summer</u>
<u n="42" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0522">so erm what's the next plan then?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0519">so</u>
<u n="45" who="S0522">so you've gotta do you have to store all your stuff somewhere?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0519">we do</u>
<u n="47" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0519">yeah so erm the firm are from Edinburgh and they'll store it somewhere doesn't matter to us and deliver it to the new place</u>
<u n="49" who="S0522">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0519">which we've told them is <anon type="place"/> erm as an approximate we said you know well dad said he's he's the one did did it all and erm so they've given a price for everything</u>
<u n="51" who="S0522">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0519">and the piano firm are from <anon type="place"/> and they're going to store it in <anon type="place"/> erm and it'll be delivered here erm to wherever and we signed up with an estate agent in <anon type="place"/> that had an <anon type="place"/> does that mean anything to you?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0522">yeah I've seen their name</u>
<u n="54" who="S0519">erm and they they've got an a an agent in <anon type="place"/> as well and so they've signed us up in</u>
<u n="55" who="S0522">you realise in the nice places that erm like there's someone at work who er is renting in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0519">and where's that?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0522">er near erm <anon type="place"/> so that kind of where the Lord Binning is where we've been to that pub</u>
<u n="58" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0522">erm and there was a big <trunc>p</trunc> there's a big park outside anyway erm but he's been looking to buy for two years and like the houses don't even get onto the website you know that they go because <vocal desc="cough"/> an agent tells them it's coming and they go and see it before it's even so I <trunc>th</trunc> you know in these nice places I think that's why you need to probably register with more you know agents as opposed to relying on Rightmove</u>
<u n="60" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm mm mm Rightmove they only get to Rightmove</u>
<u n="61" who="S0522">because people want to live in these</u>
<u n="62" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0522">spots and they're just so popular</u>
<u n="64" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's a good point you probably I mean Rightmove is a nice place to sort of feed your dreams and see what you want you know</u>
<u n="65" who="S0522">that's it yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0520" trans="overlap">but it's not the place probably to spot your house cos like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says it's been on for a while</u>
<u n="67" who="S0522" trans="overlap">and if it's been on for two years there's a reason <unclear/> it's just</u>
<u n="68" who="S0519">no that's right</u>
<u n="69" who="S0520">someone doesn't want to live there cos it's like mouldy or something on a road or something</u>
<u n="70" who="S0519">yeah no we just saw a nice one on the A51 you know we said you know that that's why it's still on there cos it <trunc>lo</trunc> you think</u>
<u n="71" who="S0522">but also how expensive</u>
<u n="72" who="S0519">they're crazy prices</u>
<u n="73" who="S0522">the houses are in <anon type="place"/> like we just up the <trunc>r</trunc> here if you go out here and then you carry on straight up that hill</u>
<u n="74" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0522">there's two for sale on the right and they are detached but they're very close to the other ones and the gardens are quite modest I think one's a three-bed and one's a four-bed and I was thinking well I I just I like that road and I like the house and er I looked and it was like nearly five hundred thousand</u>
<u n="76" who="S0520">shit</u>
<u n="77" who="S0522">you just think what?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0520">you're very close to Manchester and Warrington here I wonder if you went a hour south of here you wouldn't have</u>
<u n="79" who="S0522" trans="overlap">oh yeah you've got the luxury of being out</u>
<u n="80" who="S0520">because it's not a commuter distance any more</u>
<u n="81" who="S0519">no er erm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0520">I mean people do commute that far but it's not really needed is it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah no I think that's what we're hoping to do</u>
<u n="84" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you just and you don't want to be too near to Birmingham the other side</u>
<u n="85" who="S0519">is be a little bit more south but then when you when you see like <anon type="place"/> seems a lovely village or a like a almost a mini town isn't it?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0522">yeah a very nice one yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0519">erm but very nice and then erm so we've seen some houses near there just on Rightmove and they always looks lovely but really expensive</u>
<u n="88" who="S0522">oh yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0522">cos that's like family heaven there you know? there's good schools and commuting</u>
<u n="91" who="S0519">that's right</u>
<u n="92" who="S0522">same with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0519">erm and what about erm so I told you did you know <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0519">and is that also still in the super-duper?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0522">it's less isn't it? but yeah I don't know it</u>
<u n="97" who="S0519" trans="overlap">cos that was nicer to us that it was further south</u>
<u n="98" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0519">and a little bit smaller and erm a little bit rolling hills woah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0522">mm yeah it's <unclear/> a bit isn't it?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0520">this is mum I mean mum was saying that she didn't she you know you're more inclined to be south of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> than north of her <unclear/> you didn't like it up there much</u>
<u n="102" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yes I I I love the beautiful area near <anon type="place"/> but all I could think was you know that everything south of you is just an industrial wasteland</u>
<u n="103" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Blackburn and all of the places</u>
<u n="104" who="S0519">you know Blackburn Preston</u>
<u n="105" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Chorley</u>
<u n="106" who="S0519">Warrington Widnes</u>
<u n="107" who="S0522">mum was like where shall we go? I was going to joke that we should take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to Blackpool</u>
<u n="108" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Wigan</u>
<u n="109" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0519">that would be really scary</u>
<u n="111" who="S0522" trans="overlap">Blackpool <trunc>ple</trunc>pleasure beach see what England has to offer</u>
<u n="112" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0520" trans="overlap">he would love it he would love it yeah erm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0519">that little park Brockholds thing looked lovely</u>
<u n="115" who="S0522">it looks lovely doesn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0519">I I've seen the signs to it before</u>
<u n="117" who="S0522">and the weather kind of looks like this at least it</u>
<u n="118" who="S0520">that'll be fine won't it?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0520">I've told him to bring his warm coat</u>
<u n="121" who="S0519" trans="overlap">we'd like a weeny bit of sun if we could</u>
<u n="122" who="S0520">mm well he's going to be happy cos he says he's boiling in Israel and he's tired of it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0522" trans="overlap">Wednesday was gorgeous</u>
<u n="124" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0522">be chilly yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0520">September is a killer in Israel</u>
<u n="127" who="S0522">quite nice that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got two lots of art days I wonder why there must be a reason</u>
<u n="128" who="S0520">yeah she was sweet this morning she came down stairs in like a fully coordinated outfit all white so we were like mm but we went for it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and a frilly skirt</u>
<u n="130" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0519">I don't argue any more</u>
<u n="132" who="S0520">and she was like I need a hairband and she was on she said I'm dressed like a polar bear and she had that that white jumper on with the bear on the front</u>
<u n="133" who="S0519">she erm yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0522">she has a complete strop if I try and change what she's chosen</u>
<u n="135" who="S0520">yeah we we decided not to fight that battle I mean it was fine outfit wasn't it?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0519">it was yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0522">even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has started to bring me clothes it's hilarious and I'm like</u>
<u n="138" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you told me he didn't want the uniform</u>
<u n="139" who="S0520" trans="overlap">he just copies everything that she does <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0522" trans="overlap">can I wear this mummy</u>
<u n="141" who="S0519">I'm two for god's sake</u>
<u n="142" who="S0522">I know poor little lad</u>
<u n="143" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's a bit silly isn't it?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0522">well he's he was having that many accidents last week that I just sent him without uniform anyway</u>
<u n="145" who="S0519">although I that if if it's so many clothes in his bag that that's where I dressed him from this morning</u>
<u n="146" who="S0522">I know yeah well it was you know that it was happening quite a lot and now he's having maybe one</u>
<u n="147" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it was literally mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0520">yeah yesterday he was good wasn't he?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0519">he'd had none</u>
<u n="150" who="S0522">he's really got it</u>
<u n="151" who="S0520">and he didn't resist it any more</u>
<u n="152" who="S0522">no he's kind of just got on with it</u>
<u n="153" who="S0520" trans="overlap">he kind of got on and he and he gets a bit of a reward</u>
<u n="154" who="S0522" trans="overlap">and he's very sweet when we're out he's me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took the boys and walked up <anon type="place"/> lane with the scooters and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> needed a wee so he just went in the bush but he was holding his little winkie and then he just decided to let go and it was all</u>
<u n="155" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0522">I was like no you've got to hold it</u>
<u n="157" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying he was aiming up upwards and she was like mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're gonna hit your face with it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0520">well erm sorry forgotten her name again that lady that we me this morning</u>
<u n="160" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="161" who="S0522" trans="overlap">and I got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying she tried with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but she's given up</u>
<u n="163" who="S0522">yeah loads of people said to me oh don't bother with boys until they're three but I I know he's got it now</u>
<u n="164" who="S0519">oh he's completely got it yeah I don't think it'll be long with him but mind you he does drink such a lot a night but</u>
<u n="165" who="S0520" trans="overlap">he's done well yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0522" trans="overlap">he's two and a half</u>
<u n="167" who="S0522">but it's fine if the he's having accidents if yeah I remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wore the nappy in bed for much for much longer and then just said look why am I wearing a nappy? and I just think it'll be the same</u>
<u n="168" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0519">I was just going to say I don't think he'll I think he'll get up and go</u>
<u n="171" who="S0522">he's still soaking</u>
<u n="172" who="S0519">I know I saw that</u>
<u n="173" who="S0522">yeah so he'd definitely er you know? but</u>
<u n="174" who="S0520" trans="overlap">what does it mean?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0522">so I I remember with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it never got dry because if you know you've got a nappy on you just you know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0519">you just stay in bed</u>
<u n="177" who="S0522">whereas <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said it all happened at the same time with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he would just reject that he didn't want a nappy</u>
<u n="178" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it did with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the only time no that's right</u>
<u n="179" who="S0522">and she says I can hear him going through the toilet so that's sweet at two years</u>
<u n="180" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm you were the same and you were <trunc>y</trunc> really young and it just night as well and we were putting a nappy on you but you woke up and it was dry and you just took it straight off and went to the toilet</u>
<u n="181" who="S0522" trans="overlap">yeah in the day like we went to get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s haircut and it was the end of the day and he was tried and I just thought I can't be doing with him you know there's no toilet there or anything so I just put a nappy on him but I've done it twice doing things</u>
<u n="182" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and it was dry</u>
<u n="183" who="S0522">and it's dry and he's gone as soon as we've got back I need a wee and I'm taking it off and he's done it in there so</u>
<u n="184" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0519">no he's got quite a bit of control actually hasn't he?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0522">yeah but that's all of a sudden it wasn't</u>
<u n="187" who="S0519" trans="overlap">cos it was dry when he woke up at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s the other time</u>
<u n="188" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0519">when I went to get him they'd put it on for him to go asleep on the settee and but it was dry when he woke up</u>
<u n="191" who="S0522">mm that's good and I'm not really giving him unless he asks for it milk at bedtime so trying to sort of</u>
<u n="192" who="S0519">oh right</u>
<u n="193" who="S0522">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0520">he didn't fancy a sleep yesterday did he?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0522">no</u>
<u n="196" who="S0519">we didn't we said do you want a sleep?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0520" trans="overlap">we didn't even</u>
<u n="198" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="199" who="S0520">he was super excited</u>
<u n="200" who="S0519" trans="overlap">don't be ridiculous</u>
<u n="201" who="S0520">to have us</u>
<u n="202" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0520">and he wanted to play with grandma in the garden</u>
<u n="204" who="S0522">yeah I bet</u>
<u n="205" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> set an impossibly high bar from the time before where she pushed him in the tractor</u>
<u n="206" who="S0522" trans="overlap">oh he wanted that again</u>
<u n="207" who="S0519">dug the mud for the entire day and</u>
<u n="208" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0522">yeah she was a very good auntie weren't you?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0522">on Sunday</u>
<u n="212" who="S0519">he just was</u>
<u n="213" who="S0522">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't want to go to her party because they were having so much fun with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> outside</u>
<u n="214" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0519">no I was distraught cos I picked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up and she said where's auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just walked straight past me</u>
<u n="216" who="S0520">no I should have come with you</u>
<u n="217" who="S0519" trans="overlap">don't believe it</u>
<u n="218" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0520">we'll go together today</u>
<u n="220" who="S0519">ah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0520">it's fun when you're when you're just playing with one of them isn't it?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0520">cos you can get proper time not having to resolve arguments all the time</u>
<u n="225" who="S0522">no there's a lot of that going on it drives me bonkers at the moment</u>
<u n="226" who="S0520">yeah yeah they can provoke each other don't they?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0519" trans="overlap">they're vicious aren't they? they're hitting each other</u>
<u n="228" who="S0522" trans="overlap">hit each other and yeah and they both it's when they both want to play physically you know jumping off things</u>
<u n="229" who="S0520">I know we had this yesterday was it yesterday? yeah they were on the trampoline together and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanted to do a competition and I thought oh god this is going to end it tears and they were the competition was that you know if you if you get the other one to fall over you get a point <vocal desc="laugh"/> so they're both like whacking each other</u>
<u n="230" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but no pushing</u>
<u n="231" who="S0520">and I said alright second rule is if you push the other person over you lose a point <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it didn't I mean actually they were fine and it's alright if they play a bit rough but you know that very quickly it can go</u>
<u n="232" who="S0519">it goes wrong doesn't it?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0520">it goes wrong yeah I mean erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s happy to fall over and whack himself</u>
<u n="234" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0520" trans="overlap">quite usually unless you know he's tried whereas <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s very sensitive to it isn't she?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0519">we had to have a ten-minute conversation with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to turn the telly on yesterday</u>
<u n="238" who="S0520">oh god</u>
<u n="239" who="S0522">oh that was making me laugh and Minions he's downloaded it in Chinese or something</u>
<u n="240" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it was in the wrong language</u>
<u n="241" who="S0522">but if you press on the audio button which he won't have told you it swaps it into</u>
<u n="242" who="S0519">no so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told us well daddy can change it to the right well</u>
<u n="243" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0519">look we've already talked to daddy for ten minutes we're just having something else</u>
<u n="245" who="S0522" trans="overlap">forget that that's good enough <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0520">what's my <trunc>boyf</trunc> doing?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0522" trans="overlap">so what shall we do?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0519">something gentle and quiet and peaceful for mummy I haven't even dressed yet I need a wash</u>
<u n="249" who="S0522" trans="overlap">I'm okay I just feel a bit sick</u>
<u n="250" who="S0520">you need to eat have you had toast?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0522">I've had a piece of toast</u>
<u n="252" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0519">we'll just have a very quiet day <vocal desc="yawn"/> we don't need to do anything</u>
<u n="254" who="S0522">well we could go and have a lunch or do something</u>
<u n="255" who="S0520">let's have lunch I want to shop</u>
<u n="256" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm we'll have you puking into it</u>
<u n="257" who="S0520">I have my eye on something on some jeans</u>
<u n="258" who="S0522" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm hoping food'll help as opposed to hinder</u>
<u n="259" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0520">I have <trunc>s</trunc> my eye on a jumper in Jigsaw costs a fortune</u>
<u n="261" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0520">and I have my eye on jeans that I have from Next in in grey</u>
<u n="263" who="S0522" trans="overlap">I bought some from Warehouse and they're really nice</u>
<u n="264" who="S0520">ah can I see them?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0522">yeah they're erm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0520">I would like some grey I'd like a grey pair and the nice thing about the Next ones is that they're twenty-two pounds which is affordable but they look <trunc>ni</trunc> you know they're a good shape aren't they? you have to hoick them up a lot cos of the waistband gets lose but</u>
<u n="267" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0520">er eh because they do long and extra long in Next on all of their styles and that just makes all the difference cos otherwise it doesn't reach your yeah can you get that yours are see you should get petite you well you should try the ones</u>
<u n="269" who="S0519">I know but then they only have those in Markies</u>
<u n="270" who="S0520">well you should try the ones on in Next</u>
<u n="271" who="S0522" trans="overlap">well the Warehouse ones are kinds of just long enough</u>
<u n="272" who="S0520">yeah they can be I mean I can wear sometimes a thirty-two inch if it's generous but I'm actually a thirty-three or four</u>
<u n="273" who="S0519" trans="overlap">these are just regular</u>
<u n="274" who="S0520">inch leg</u>
<u n="275" who="S0519">so I'm just a little shorty</u>
<u n="276" who="S0522">oh cos I was in French Connection and theirs are thirty-one so that wasn't happening</u>
<u n="277" who="S0520">no well I think it can look nice in the summer if it's stops at your ankle even if it's not supposed to</u>
<u n="278" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0520">but most of the time erm the long length not only is better but somehow it's cut better for a tall person not just a longer thing you know it's like</u>
<u n="280" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's the difference that if you think about me the the wide bit of the trouser is too low and the narrow you know everything's in the wrong place</u>
<u n="281" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm well that's why you should get petite and they do that in the <trunc>Ne</trunc></u>
<u n="282" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="283" who="S0520">in that's what I mean in Next that erm for the trousers I was quite pleasantly surprised cos they do so many different</u>
<u n="284" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I think they just do regular and long I don't think they do short</u>
<u n="285" who="S0520">they do petite though if you get petite regular then they're gonna be short</u>
<u n="286" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah enough for me and the right size</u>
<u n="287" who="S0520">petite is for small people not skinny people as well</u>
<u n="288" who="S0519">I know that no I know that</u>
<u n="289" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0519"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0520">I got a message from my boyfriend he's cut his hair</u>
<u n="292" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he does the funniest imitation of the English accent erm so he keeps teasing me that that's how he's going to speak for the whole time that he's here which I hope he doesn't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0519">he's gonna do the imitation of the English accent</u>
<u n="295" who="S0520">well he's you know he's he's <trunc>c</trunc> he's erm learnt it from the films and the telly and stuff but he really like those erm film slice erm Snatch and Lock Stock which are like Londoners you know</u>
<u n="296" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0522" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0520">Americans imitating a cockney so he does all this cockney slang and stuff it's so funny <pause dur="short"/> naughty for going out <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0522">what's in the washing machine?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0519">I put a white wash on with</u>
<u n="301" who="S0522">oh</u>
<u n="302" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0522">ha mum</u>
<u n="304" who="S0520">she did it in secret</u>
<u n="305" who="S0519">I told him I told him I was doing it</u>
<u n="306" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0519">I gave him</u>
<u n="308" who="S0522" trans="overlap">so he's taken a new nana</u>
<u n="309" who="S0519">he's taken clean nana</u>
<u n="310" who="S0522">I know it had to happen but</u>
<u n="311" who="S0520">oh it was grim <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0522">it was so grim</u>
<u n="313" who="S0519">it it was</u>
<u n="314" who="S0520">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were blaming him for spreading the lurgy</u>
<u n="315" who="S0522" trans="overlap">he's had that the whole holiday oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes on about it all the time</u>
<u n="316" who="S0520">she's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0519">but this is only a forty-degree wash it wouldn't even kill germs so I'll I I need to even just throw a boiling water over it when it's finished but he'll be alright</u>
<u n="318" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it was needed it was needed I need to erm decide what I'm wearing today for the airport and I need to wash my black jumper in the sink before</u>
<u n="319" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I need but it won't dry before tonight then</u>
<u n="320" who="S0520">ha</u>
<u n="321" who="S0519">cos it you can't dry it that's the trouble</u>
<u n="322" who="S0520">it's upsetting</u>
<u n="323" who="S0519">you have to buy a we can wash it and hang it but it won't be dry tonight it takes two days to dry the neckline on that jumper</u>
<u n="324" who="S0520">it's it's</u>
<u n="325" who="S0522">and you're better doing it at mum's cos that little room it quite warm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0520">okay fine</u>
<u n="327" who="S0519">erm but you can buy a nice jumper</u>
<u n="328" who="S0520">well yeah I can if we go out I will do so</u>
<u n="329" who="S0519">I'll go and have my shower then erm and get dressed cos I know what I'm wearing I don't have to chose</u>
<u n="330" who="S0520">glad to hear it</u>
<u n="331" who="S0519">erm I could do with wearing a bra I was giving that to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for his nana <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0520">er</u>
<u n="333" who="S0519">I didn't don't worry</u>
<u n="334" who="S0520">snot on it I've got snot as well now I took a vitamin C pill yesterday before I went to sleep</u>
<u n="335" who="S0519">the problem with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is that he can't get rid of the colds but what can I do if I stopped <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from going every time he was snotty he'd never go</u>
<u n="336" who="S0520">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="337" who="S0519">no he was coughing again <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0522">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0519">I don't know is I've sent your lovely son in a pair of pyjamas or a pair of clothes</u>
<u n="340" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0519">to school cos they all look the same to me</u>
<u n="342" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no they were cool he was wearing his trackies</u>
<u n="343" who="S0522">the blue tracky bottoms?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0519" trans="overlap">little trackies blue trackies</u>
<u n="345" who="S0520" trans="overlap">blue trackies</u>
<u n="346" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0520">he was looking fashionable <vocal desc="laugh"/> he had his little train train's on</u>
<u n="348" who="S0519">he had his trainers on he loves his trainers</u>
<u n="349" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and he had like a spiderman</u>
<u n="350" who="S0519" trans="overlap">hang on guys</u>
<u n="351" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0522">his racing shoes that's what they're called</u>
<u n="353" who="S0520">racing shoes well he said he likes yellow so he said yellow is his favourite colour not yellow but lellow I like lellow I said someone's put lellow on your shoes as well he said naughty person <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's funny</u>
<u n="354" who="S0522"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> so where were you out and about?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0522">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0520">did you go just straight from work?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0522">er yeah just drank far too much alcohol</u>
<u n="359" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought you might have</u>
<u n="360" who="S0522">everyone was in the mood</u>
<u n="361" who="S0520">that's good but you organised it so it was a success that's cool so where did you go to dinner?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0522">we went to the <anon type="place"/> which is a church that's converted into a restaurant and a bar</u>
<u n="363" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0522">and erm yeah it was just merriment from the beginning really swigging wine and then er yeah then we started on the cocktails after the meal</u>
<u n="365" who="S0520">ooh</u>
<u n="366" who="S0522">that's when it all started</u>
<u n="367" who="S0520">cocktails are a killer killer killer</u>
<u n="368" who="S0522" trans="overlap">and then at about eleven we were in some dance place and the shots were out and it was all a bit gross</u>
<u n="369" who="S0520">did you do shots?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0522">J채gerbombs</u>
<u n="373" who="S0520">no</u>
<u n="374" who="S0522">going back to my youth</u>
<u n="375" who="S0520" trans="overlap">is there any need? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0522">no need at all</u>
<u n="377" who="S0520">what's a J채gerbomb?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0522" trans="overlap">we're all the same age as well it's like what are we doing?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0522"><trunc>e</trunc>everyone seems better off than me though they're all at work</u>
<u n="381" who="S0520">oh god as well even if I have a couple of glasses of wine I'm <unclear>hung over</unclear></u>
<u n="382" who="S0522" trans="overlap">it was quite sweet actually cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the HR like <unclear> generalist</unclear> and he's always really sensible because I think he feels you're like the face you know people come to you all the time because HR all the queries and whatever and er you know he's kind of feels he needs to be responsible</u>
<u n="383" who="S0520" trans="overlap">representative of the company yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0522">and I always tell him how dull he is and how sensible he's being erm <pause dur="long"/> erm but yeah he's <trunc>ha</trunc>had a terrible time at work er because he his job is not going to be there he's been covering maternity cover and there's nothing for him</u>
<u n="385" who="S0520">oh</u>
<u n="386" who="S0522">and I've been helping him with his CV and stuff but anyway he found out he didn't get a job that he applied for so I think he was in the mood to let his hair down as well</u>
<u n="387" who="S0520">poor thing</u>
<u n="388" who="S0522">but yeah it was him on the J채gerbombs</u>
<u n="389" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> fair enough</u>
<u n="390" who="S0522">I just text him to say you're a bad influence he's like me you <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0520">oh dear J채gerbombs I don't think I've ever done one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0522">oh god they're horrible I don't even know what they are there's something inside the shot and I you know it's like too <trunc>mu</trunc> h</u>
<u n="393" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh dear oh dear dear</u>
<u n="394" who="S0522">it's my worst kind of hangover when I feel sick</u>
<u n="395" who="S0520">oh horrid you have to eat greasy food to soak it up</u>
<u n="396" who="S0522">I know</u>
<u n="397" who="S0520">that's the key</u>
<u n="398" who="S0522">I did have lamb and dauphinoise potatoes</u>
<u n="399" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0522">and then a big waffle with butterscotch ice cream</u>
<u n="401" who="S0520">good decisions all around</u>
<u n="402" who="S0522">so I did definitely line my stomach</u>
<u n="403" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no good that you ate properly yeah otherwise you'd feel even worse but if you mix alcohol in that way then life is not going to treat you well the next day</u>
<u n="404" who="S0522">no</u>
<u n="405" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0522"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like I feel fine</u>
<u n="407" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't understand people who say that I don't know how it's possible even if I drink a few glasses of wine I feel horrible the next day horrible</u>
<u n="408" who="S0522">I know it's cos you don't usually poison your body</u>
<u n="409" who="S0520">no I don't regularly poison mm <pause dur="long"/> yeah so that was fun yesterday trying to put the movie on and er</u>
<u n="410" who="S0522">yeah I was laughing because and then I saw</u>
<u n="411" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and I was like okay we've done it like after half an hour of literally like chaos</u>
<u n="412" who="S0522" trans="overlap">them moaning yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0520">and you know? erm right Minions and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was happy he was on the sofa he was ready to watch Minions and then they're like <vocal desc="nonsense"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0522">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0520">I was like why is not in English?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0522" trans="overlap">what's happening</u>
<u n="417" who="S0520">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was being really grumpy by that point and you know being a little bit mean she was like you can't fix it</u>
<u n="418" who="S0522">oh god</u>
<u n="419" who="S0520">I was oh god go upstairs <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0522">yeah she's not nice when she's a cow</u>
<u n="421" who="S0520">yeah she was a bit mean she was being a bit of a meany so anyway that was that I said right so we put Despicable Me on and after all that they watched it for about five minutes and then they weren't bothered</u>
<u n="422" who="S0522">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="423" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so that wasn't a good move</u>
<u n="424" who="S0522">as long as it's in English you're alright</u>
<u n="425" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0522">I love Despicable Me</u>
<u n="427" who="S0520">anything with erm Minions in it that was the idea</u>
<u n="428" who="S0522">yeah Minions are good</u>
<u n="429" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> likes the Minions</u>
<u n="430" who="S0522">yeah good <trunc>m</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0520">yeah erm it looked good fun the Despicable Me er I think it was the second one that I put on I haven't seen it it looked really funny with that woman</u>
<u n="432" who="S0522" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah it is erm cos Gru isn't in the Minion movie I I like the Minion movie less It's all a bit too much Minions</u>
<u n="433" who="S0520">yeah it's more funny when they come in occasionally and do like a silly thing</u>
<u n="434" who="S0522">that's what I mean but I was like all that <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0520" trans="overlap">but I don't know if I want to watch a two hours of them doing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0522">there were some really funny moments though</u>
<u n="437" who="S0520">and they are really funny</u>
<u n="438" who="S0522" trans="overlap">Inside Out Out you need to watch that that was really lovely</u>
<u n="439" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I know I really want to see it</u>
<u n="440" who="S0522" trans="overlap">it was not <trunc>f</trunc> it wasn't good enough for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos there's no action and it's really like one of those that's more for adult in terms of the what</u>
<u n="441" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah it sounds quite adult themes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying</u>
<u n="442" who="S0522">it's really yeah quite emotional it's kind of er</u>
<u n="443" who="S0520">she has all these her emotions have a kind of</u>
<u n="444" who="S0522" trans="overlap">about a <trunc>fr</trunc> yeah it's all her emotions and erm memories and er you know how how the family and how important the love is you know is from your parents and</u>
<u n="445" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm yeah I've read really good reviews of it I'd quite like to see it in the cinema</u>
<u n="446" who="S0522">it's just an it's clever you know cos it's all the different</u>
<u n="447" who="S0520">yeah it sounds really interesting</u>
<u n="448" who="S0522">each one has a different character</u>
<u n="449" who="S0520" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought even for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was a little bit old</u>
<u n="450" who="S0522" trans="overlap">yeah yeah she liked it but it's just because</u>
<u n="451" who="S0520">she told me a bit about it but she didn't you know go into it she said</u>
<u n="452" who="S0522" trans="overlap">no she didn't know what they mean</u>
<u n="453" who="S0520">she said there was anger and something and then she didn't know the rest</u>
<u n="454" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0520">and then you know she didn't sort of understand the kind of whole thing but that's the idea isn't it? that you can talk you can talk to a child about feelings and stuff</u>
<u n="456" who="S0522">but the clever ones are the ones that appeal to the adult as well</u>
<u n="457" who="S0520">yeah they are that's right well Despicable Me has a lot of like little hidden jokes dome's it? very funny I haven't even seen the end of the first one so I don't know how he grows to like the children and stuff</u>
<u n="458" who="S0522">yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh I see oh right yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0520">yeah like I don't know how it resolves you know? I've gotten about halfway through the first one where he's had to take these children in</u>
<u n="460" who="S0522">well that's what's sweet isn't it he does start to</u>
<u n="461" who="S0520" trans="overlap">he starts to love them yeah <pause dur="long"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are watching Mad Men</u>
<u n="462" who="S0522">what do you think?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0520">I'm slightly bored</u>
<u n="464" who="S0522">yeah it does get a bit boring</u>
<u n="465" who="S0520">but I do like it</u>
<u n="466" who="S0522">yeah we love Don</u>
<u n="467" who="S0520" trans="overlap">erm the third series was quite hard for me to get through I just thought do you know what? I don't care</u>
<u n="468" who="S0522" trans="overlap">it does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has trouble for it</u>
<u n="469" who="S0520">how many times do you need to see them having</u>
<u n="470" who="S0522">affairs</u>
<u n="471" who="S0520" trans="overlap">affairs and drinking er you know it's like</u>
<u n="472" who="S0522">all day long</u>
<u n="473" who="S0520">yeah this is what's amazing about it is that they're just literally drinking all day and smoking which must have been what it was like but I also <trunc>ca</trunc> <trunc>or</trunc> more or less can't stand the wife</u>
<u n="474" who="S0522" trans="overlap">no she's <trunc>ha</trunc> awful but that's the point isn't it?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0520"><trunc>sh</trunc> I mean I know that's the point but I like literally I don't want to watch it because I <trunc>n</trunc> I'm so annoyed by her character</u>
<u n="476" who="S0522" trans="overlap">yeah and how she is with her her children</u>
<u n="477" who="S0520">she's just awful</u>
<u n="478" who="S0522">well she's just <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0520">and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been the same he's been catching up cos I was a bit ahead of him cos we try and watch it in tandem so that when we're together <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0522"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sweet</u>
<u n="481" who="S0520">and erm he's just getting so irritated with this woman and even with the actress you're thinking either she's really doing and good job or she's</u>
<u n="482" who="S0522" trans="overlap">she's very beautiful Elizabeth Jones</u>
<u n="483" who="S0520">she is very beautiful she has lots of nice dresses on all the time</u>
<u n="484" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0520">but she just gets worse and worse</u>
<u n="486" who="S0522">she plays it very well she's like completely emotionless</u>
<u n="487" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh she's like the classic neurotic woman isn't she? high maintenance but erm well now I've only got to the end of the third series so she's just gone off with that erm other man so we'll see what happens <pause dur="short"/> and I'm all for Don breaking free and going out alone</u>
<u n="488" who="S0522" trans="overlap">other man erm I can't tell you what happens</u>
<u n="489" who="S0520" trans="overlap">but there's eight series don't tell me anything there's eight series so god I don't know if I can hack another five series of it</u>
<u n="490" who="S0522">it ends quite well as well like it's not a kind of painful</u>
<u n="491" who="S0520">mm that's good</u>
<u n="492" who="S0522">as in you think how do they end it?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0520" trans="overlap">well I like Don and he does that I mean that's what it all hinges around isn't it? that you like Don and you want to want Don to be happy and he's kind of but the thing is is that the first series it was really interesting cos you start to find out he's not who he says he is</u>
<u n="494" who="S0522" trans="overlap">yeah that's right so there's more too it</u>
<u n="495" who="S0520">it's all really interesting and then that they kind of leave that behind a bit</u>
<u n="496" who="S0522" trans="overlap">no we got bored with it quite a lot it goes up and down</u>
<u n="497" who="S0520">yeah I don't know if I would have kept watching it if it was on the telly</u>
<u n="498" who="S0522">it's obviously</u>
<u n="499" who="S0520">it's really well done isn't it?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0520">and I like that you sort of know see all the historical things happening you know in context</u>
<u n="502" who="S0522">yeah yeah and just how it was like that kind of wealthy how women were treated and</u>
<u n="503" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah yeah god yeah that's so shocking at the beginning I was like oh my god cos you don't they do it really realistic don't they? they do like how they would speak to women and how they would treat them and stuff</u>
<u n="504" who="S0522" trans="overlap">yeah and they're all secretaries</u>
<u n="505" who="S0520">yeah apart from Peggy Peggy's my favourite</u>
<u n="506" who="S0522">Peggy she's brilliant and how attractive is that redhead</u>
<u n="507" who="S0520" trans="overlap">don't say anything god she's gorgeous isn't she?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0520">that's really nice</u>
<u n="510" who="S0522">she's married it's funny she's married to quite a ugly man</u>
<u n="511" who="S0520">yeah he's quite geeky isn't he?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I saw that the other day</u>
<u n="514" who="S0522" trans="overlap">proper geek</u>
<u n="515" who="S0520">erm she's stunning</u>
<u n="516" who="S0522">she is really stunning</u>
<u n="517" who="S0520">and erm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0522">huge boobs</u>
<u n="519" who="S0520"><trunc>ma</trunc> I know that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps saying</u>
<u n="520" who="S0522" trans="overlap">and she always</u>
<u n="521" who="S0520">he's like her boobs are massive</u>
<u n="522" who="S0522" trans="overlap">it's not right is it? but she's my favourite in terms of the clothes as well</u>
<u n="523" who="S0520" trans="overlap">she's like a woman isn't she? I really like her character as well she's got sort of she's quite dignified</u>
<u n="524" who="S0522">so what's happened with her in series three?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0520">she gets married to that bloke the doctor</u>
<u n="526" who="S0522" trans="overlap">who isn't nice</u>
<u n="527" who="S0520">we don't like him he more or less rapes her in the office and then is just a bit self-absorbed and is definitely not her equal in terms of quality of character</u>
<u n="528" who="S0522">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0520">and but she's still married to him and he doesn't get the jobs that he wants so he decides to join the army that's all that's happened so she's still married to him</u>
<u n="530" who="S0522" trans="overlap">and has she had a child?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="532" who="S0522">no</u>
<u n="533" who="S0520">don't worry and er</u>
<u n="534" who="S0522">I thought that was all when she</u>
<u n="535" who="S0520">no she erm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0522">she has a kid with him</u>
<u n="537" who="S0520">well it's on the cards isn't it? she is just back oh what happens at the end of series three is the English firm have taken over and then they're planning to sell again the whole company and Don and the other cronies at the top decide to buy it back and set up their own firm again do you remember?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0522">okay yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0520">so they're going to be like split up broken up and they decide to do a little nifty business manoeuvre and they just start a new business and they get Joanie back on board cos she's not been working there and she becomes like one of their main employees again so she's just join rejoined the firm basically so she wasn't in the third series very much cos she wasn't in the office she was off she was just</u>
<u n="540" who="S0522" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0520">so you wonder what's going to happen to her the old guy what is his name? Stirling</u>
<u n="542" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0520">Roger</u>
<u n="544" who="S0522">Roger he's a character</u>
<u n="545" who="S0520">he is a character who you kind of not sure if you like him but you so</u>
<u n="546" who="S0522">you do yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0520">and he marries that really young girl Jane you're not allowed to tell me anything</u>
<u n="548" who="S0522">I don't remember her so obviously it doesn't last long</u>
<u n="549" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no it doesn't look what happens is he's married</u>
<u n="550" who="S0522">I vaguely remember her yeah she's pretty</u>
<u n="551" who="S0520">to she's really pretty she's Don's secretary and she's twenty and he leaves his wife for her and everyone's like what the are you doing you wally and he's like this is what I want to do this is what's going to make me happy you know so that's his current status but even by now he's starting to she's a bit immature and he's straying to be like mm not sure</u>
<u n="552" who="S0522">not quite as fun as you</u>
<u n="553" who="S0520">not quite what I thought it was going to be</u>
<u n="554" who="S0522">I do vaguely remember that</u>
<u n="555" who="S0520">funny that he so yeah you don't know whether she's not really a main character she's not really in it really she's just pretty as they all are Peggy's pretty as well in a way but yeah Peggy's the main character for me</u>
<u n="556" who="S0522">yeah well she's the one that and erm who what's the redhead's name?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0520">Joanie</u>
<u n="558" who="S0522">Joanie and her are the two women that actually</u>
<u n="559" who="S0520">have a bit of character yeah they're not just wives are they?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0519">who's this?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0520">we're just discussing this show that I was telling you and dad about with that is set in the nineteen sixties Mad Men</u>
<u n="562" who="S0519">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0520">yeah cos they watched it all on telly and I</u>
<u n="564" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you you enjoyed it didn't you?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0519">I did didn't even attempt it I always thought it was just you know</u>
<u n="567" who="S0522">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0520">it's not just</u>
<u n="569" who="S0522">we recommended it to grandad <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I can't remember whether he liked it or not because of it being that era but it's probably a bit slow for him</u>
<u n="570" who="S0520">too slow yeah I think you would quite be interested I mean there is a lot of</u>
<u n="571" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but yeah I think he did watch it I I think he did</u>
<u n="572" who="S0520">they had quite a hedonistic lifestyle so they do just <trunc>di</trunc>drink and smoke and have affairs a lot but that's exactly what they were doing it wasn't erm it's not for the sake of erm entertainment really</u>
<u n="573" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm no just fortuitous</u>
<u n="574" who="S0520">and it's not like explicit in any way and er</u>
<u n="575" who="S0519">you haven't nicked my cream have you?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0520">your BB cream?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0519">no my actual moisturiser I I actually came with nothing I came with two deodorants</u>
<u n="578" who="S0522">handy</u>
<u n="579" who="S0520">she didn't bring her wine or anything</u>
<u n="580" who="S0522">oh dear</u>
<u n="581" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I brought nothing I was absolutely useless no pyjamas</u>
<u n="582" who="S0520">I've got moisturiser in my bag if you want to use mine</u>
<u n="583" who="S0519">and no hand cream nothing hello Jay yeah you're family are here today</u>
<u n="584" who="S0520">Jay slept on my in my nook all night</u>
<u n="585" who="S0519">he erm while dad was here with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he said he kept meowing at me</u>
<u n="586" who="S0520">imagine dad doesn't have a clue does he? what am I supposed to do?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0519">and I said yes he just wanted a bit of love you could have given him a bit of food but he most he probably want oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0520">imagine the horror</u>
<u n="589" who="S0522">I think you should try putting like a grey colour in</u>
<u n="590" who="S0519">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said</u>
<u n="591" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's what I said I think the blonde is kind of out of context</u>
<u n="592" who="S0522" trans="overlap">only very</u>
<u n="593" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I'm going to cut this blonde out anyway</u>
<u n="594" who="S0520">yeah but also</u>
<u n="595" who="S0519">so I'm gonna have it cut and then a lot of that</u>
<u n="596" who="S0522" trans="overlap">that's quite white isn't it? grey which washes you out the hair coming through</u>
<u n="597" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0520">if you go for a dark grey</u>
<u n="599" who="S0519">it's very white but then if you look under there is quite a bit of dark in there</u>
<u n="600" who="S0522" trans="overlap">dark in there</u>
<u n="601" who="S0519">and at the back</u>
<u n="602" who="S0520">you should be</u>
<u n="603" who="S0522">cos it just needs warming up</u>
<u n="604" who="S0520">as a brunette yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it does</u>
<u n="606" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0519">so what I need to do is get rid of the blonde</u>
<u n="608" who="S0520">definitely yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0519">and then find something nice</u>
<u n="610" who="S0522">to put through</u>
<u n="611" who="S0519">to put through as a highlight erm</u>
<u n="612" who="S0522">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but obviously the yellow</u>
<u n="614" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah even if you put a warmer darker grey through</u>
<u n="615" who="S0519" trans="overlap">was clearly not the one</u>
<u n="616" who="S0520">I think it would be better</u>
<u n="617" who="S0522">yellow is not the choice</u>
<u n="618" who="S0519">Goldilocks yellow is not the choice it's fading</u>
<u n="619" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Goldilocks</u>
<u n="620" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0519">it is fading you can probably tell it's not as yellow as it was but er it you know</u>
<u n="622" who="S0522">it's just that you've got such strong eyebrows and pale skin</u>
<u n="623" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0520">the colouring is not right yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0522" trans="overlap">it's not doing you any favours</u>
<u n="626" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0519">no no that's right but hopefully erm I could</u>
<u n="628" who="S0520">I wonder if it would be best just to bite the bullet for a few months grow it out fully and see what your natural colour is</u>
<u n="629" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that see what I've got I'm that's what I'm going to do and</u>
<u n="630" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and then they can dye it from there</u>
<u n="631" who="S0519">then so I've got to get rid of the yellow now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the yellow</u>
<u n="633" who="S0519">and er and then when that's gone which will only be another couple of cuts I might go shorter this time and then that'll be quite a bit of it gone</u>
<u n="634" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0519">I might not but you know I it grows fast anyway so</u>
<u n="636" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="637" who="S0519">but er</u>
<u n="638" who="S0522">right I might have a shower</u>
<u n="639" who="S0519">it's a lovely shower you just want to stand it that shower don't you?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="641" who="S0519"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> recommended this BB cream erm it's just like moisturiser with a bit of foundation in I think did you mention it once before?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0522" trans="overlap">oh mm you've mentioned it</u>
<u n="643" who="S0520">it's good or tinted moisturiser is basically what it is erm but it's gives a bit of foundation coverage but it's also supposed to be I mean you should wear it with moisturiser I think cos it does feel a bit cakey yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0522" trans="overlap">dry</u>
<u n="645" who="S0519">but it looked really nice on you yesterday</u>
<u n="646" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I'm gonna wear it today</u>
<u n="647" who="S0519">er I'm going to put it on now see what it's like without oh and you don't need much do you?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0520">no</u>
<u n="649" who="S0519">I put a big squeeze on and then you don't hardly need any</u>
<u n="650" who="S0520">yeah no it's quite good stuff I think</u>
<u n="651" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0520">I don't want to look like I have foundation on at all it's awful <pause dur="long"/> I quite need some more toast I think <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0519">no it's not quite a nice to put on is it? I haven't already got moisturiser on</u>
<u n="654" who="S0520">well yeah you should put my moisturiser on</u>
<u n="655" who="S0519">I couldn't find anything in your bag</u>
<u n="656" who="S0520">oh</u>
<u n="657" who="S0519">a pile of crud</u>
<u n="658" who="S0520">I carried it all upstairs to the bathroom</u>
<u n="659" who="S0519">ah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0520">yesterday</u>
<u n="661" who="S0519">that'll be it but yeah it didn't</u>
<u n="662" who="S0520">I mean it is quite nice that one it's the right colour anyway for us</u>
<u n="663" who="S0519">mm it didn't look erm it doesn't feel so nice to put on but I bet it soaks cos I told you even last time I didn't like that</u>
<u n="664" who="S0520">no</u>
<u n="665" who="S0519">it <trunc>fe</trunc> it <trunc>fe</trunc> it feels quite dry just now</u>
<u n="666" who="S0520">I'm tempted to try a a professional version and see if there's much difference</u>
<u n="667" who="S0519">put put the moisturiser on first and then it put it on yeah you go and have a shower my love I can do this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was even on the cleaning up this morning</u>
<u n="668" who="S0520">what do you mean even?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0519">yeah I was quite shocked</u>
<u n="670" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0519">it took us erm we did change round the erm the bedroom with the beams we put it back as a bedroom like we used to have it but with the new bed so it looked really nice erm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0520">that looks nice doesn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0519">I thought it would just look horrible anyway but er no it didn't</u>
<u n="674" who="S0522">oh that's good</u>
<u n="675" who="S0520">I'm a bit cold</u>
<u n="676" who="S0522">not putting the heating on</u>
<u n="677" who="S0520">whack the heat</u>
<u n="678" who="S0522">you're not getting any heating</u>
<u n="679" who="S0520">no you're not allowed to put the heating on don't worry we put it on yesterday</u>
<u n="680" who="S0519">I put it on yesterday they said well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't complain</u>
<u n="681" who="S0520">expect a lot a high bill</u>
<u n="682" who="S0519">the cheek of some people <unclear/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0520">it's absolutely freezing in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="684" who="S0519">oh god</u>
<u n="685" who="S0522">still?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0519">it makes me feel ill going to</u>
<u n="687" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so cold</u>
<u n="688" who="S0519">well it you have to put the heating on</u>
<u n="689" who="S0520">it's like when mum goes to choir and</u>
<u n="690" who="S0522">they're like us</u>
<u n="691" who="S0520">mum went on a choir weekend last time and er</u>
<u n="692" who="S0519">there was no heating in the cottage</u>
<u n="693" who="S0520">there was no heating in the house whatsoever</u>
<u n="694" who="S0522">oh dear</u>
<u n="695" who="S0520">dad was I had icicles on my nose</u>
<u n="696" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="697" who="S0520">unimpressed he actually took pity on me and turned it on</u>
<u n="698" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0519"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
