<text id="S2XV">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:33:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0131</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Work, pets, business, beauty products, family, education</topics>
		<activity>Friends catching up about their lives and families.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0131">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0131">erm <pause dur="short"/> cos she was <pause dur="short"/> there were going to be problems with her <unclear/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0018">network yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <trunc>sh</trunc> they're alright <pause dur="short"/> the network as been dismantled and eh <pause dur="short"/> re-mantled?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0131">oh right okay</u>
<u n="4" who="S0018">dismantled and rebuilt on more of a local network <trunc>nation</trunc> at a national level as opposed to a local network at a local level</u>
<u n="5" who="S0131">right</u>
<u n="6" who="S0018">erm <pause dur="short"/> and yeah there are a lot of jobs that are at risk but for the moment she seems to be</u>
<u n="7" who="S0131">she's alright</u>
<u n="8" who="S0018">alright <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0131">Good <pause dur="short"/> right so I heard something <pause dur="short"/> I heard somebody on <pause dur="short"/> where did I hear about it? Some guy on Radio 2 I think was talking about the <pause dur="short"/> he'd done a <pause dur="short"/> somebody who'd done a big erm research project about the organisation of the BBC <pause dur="short"/> and he was talking about getting rid of local radio station which I presume that was <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>bi</trunc> because there was a lot that they were doing that was good <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what the  what the  rationale was for it but I think maybe they were duplicating stuff that was being done elsewhere</u>
<u n="10" who="S0018">right yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0131">so</u>
<u n="12" who="S0018">I wouldn't be surprised</u>
<u n="13" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0018">you're a crazy dog <pause dur="short"/> you are crazy <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0131">so how long is the project for is the project you're doing for?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0018">erm we'll just probably have a month I think so</u>
<u n="17" who="S0131">and then you go back in September hopefully? Will you continue or you don't know?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0018">eh no if I if I went  if I went  back I would go back in January to start the course because the September to January bit I've already done will count <pause dur="short"/> what are you trying to do? Does he want to play?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0131">he does when you do that he thinks you're going to rub his tummy with with your foot <pause dur="short"/> he has a problem with crossed legs <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> if you sit with your legs down he doesn't tend to do it but he's just <pause dur="short"/> we're not sure whether to have his whatsits chopped off</u>
<u n="20" who="S0018">big old softy</u>
<u n="21" who="S0131">Cos he had me over</u>
<u n="22" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0131">recently we were in a car park and he's got an extendable lead which I hate because I don't like the fact that if he takes off and I haven't got it clipped in he's motoring by the time he gets to the end of it <pause dur="short"/> bit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> likes it if we're out walking in the hills <pause dur="short"/> and we were out in Herefordshire walking <pause dur="short"/> and we were just getting him in the car and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> handed the lead to me and I didn't manage to get it hooked in in time <pause dur="short"/> and he spotted three dogs off their lead the other side of the car park and took off and next thing I know I was <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I may I just went head first into the side of the car <pause dur="short"/> he was gone</u>
<u n="24" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="25" who="S0131">I had to let I mean the lead just went out of my hand and I was flat on my face on the front of the car <pause dur="short"/> I thought I'd lost all my front teeth</u>
<u n="26" who="S0018">oh gosh really?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0131">stop it <pause dur="short"/> erm and I was convinced I'd broken my jaw <pause dur="short"/> but actually I'd gone on it it transpired I'd gone in slightly sideways I think so although I was a bit knocked about <pause dur="short"/> tembo stop it <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I was actually alright <pause dur="short"/> erm it was just a shock and it was just well actually he he gets so excited by other dogs and actually I think probably as we sat in the car I said I think we need do have him done</u>
<u n="28" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="29" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0131">yeah so do I</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">and what happened with the the table and the window shut window?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0131" trans="overlap">oh now that's that's my stupid husband</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0131">who honestly who ties a dog this size <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to put you outside cos you're just being a pain <pause dur="short"/> no come on <pause dur="short"/> who ties a dog that size to a table which is movable? It was  It was  windy and the erm the table and chairs were moving were actually it transpired we'd sort of been going round outside Pret in the high street and the chair fell over <pause dur="short"/> and he just took fright when the chair fell over and ran amazingly he didn't take all of the sort of erm surrounding stuff with him there's these sort of canvas sides outside there <pause dur="short"/> he went straight through the gap and straight across the high street <pause dur="short"/> amazing that he didn't catch anybody en route <pause dur="short"/> and came to a standstill with the once the table had smashed the Body Care shop window</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="36" who="S0131">and the people in Body Care shop were <pause dur="short"/> and then not only that he's got a harness on cos we found it easy to walk him on a harness <pause dur="short"/> and then he once the table had stopped somebody grabbed the table and he reversed out of his harness and he was belly down on the floor and he discovered if he put his paws out there so we could actually reverse out of it <pause dur="short"/> and then he raced into the shop <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> by the time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got there from the coffee shop he was</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> inside?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0131"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in the coffee shop just ordering his coffee and somebody said your dog's gone</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">oh my lord</u>
<u n="40" who="S0131">I said to him what why on earth did you tie him to something that moves <pause dur="short"/> he said well I've done it before and he's been alright</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0131">that's a good  That's a good  reason <pause dur="short"/> so yes so when we go down there now he's either tied to us or tied to something like the bike rack which can't be</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">oh gosh</u>
<u n="44" who="S0131">it might not be removed</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">forklift truck</u>
<u n="46" who="S0131">so yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone up to London <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately had a meeting in London this afternoon so</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">oh what's he  what's he  doing?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0131">he's working for himself <pause dur="short"/> he's doing all sorts of <pause dur="short"/> he's got these investments in different companies and <pause dur="short"/> he's got one company down in Fleet that's actually on the back of that he's going to London which we bought about seven years ago <pause dur="short"/> and so he does well I should think four or five days a month he has to go down to Fleet <pause dur="short"/> but other than that he works on the telephone <pause dur="short"/> he's the non-exec chairman <pause dur="short"/> erm and then he's got another company making loft stilts</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">aha that was his idea wasn't it?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0131">that was his <pause dur="short"/> that's taken off <pause dur="short"/> b and Q are now selling them</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">fantastic</u>
<u n="52" who="S0131">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has been working alongside him in it so <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s actually been working two or three days a week on that and only a couple of days work on his own business but that's all sort of working now <pause dur="short"/> so he's now back working more on his own business for the next couple of months so <pause dur="short"/> ah he's got various things <pause dur="short"/> he's got some guy's come to them with this amazing sound erm <pause dur="short"/> what is it? It's a speaker system that is sort of that thick <pause dur="short"/> you can put it in the back of pictures and all sorts and it will both give out sound and record <pause dur="short"/> they want financing <pause dur="short"/> so anybody that wants sort of financing as a computer company he deals with but it's various things</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> so is he investing in?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">is he looking for things to invest in?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">because I've got a friend who's looking for an investor <pause dur="short"/> well eh she makes this amazing natural products like moisturisers facial washes <pause dur="short"/> she teaches at the college actually <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>beau</trunc> beauty therapy</u>
<u n="58" who="S0131">okay</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">and everything she does is without erm preservatives so it has a very short shelf like compared to something you'd pick up in Tesco's <pause dur="short"/> tesco's has actually invited her down to London</u>
<u n="60" who="S0131">really?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">and laid on the the welcome and they wanted to buy her range off her and erm sell it in Tesco's <pause dur="short"/> but they would have wanted to add lots of preservatives to it which was completely against her philosophy</u>
<u n="62" who="S0131">that's somewhat of <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> rather negates the reason of doing it doesn't it?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018">exactly</u>
<u n="64" who="S0131">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually was working with the Peter Jones academy at erm the college <pause dur="short"/> and he's got a guy from there who's got some product <pause dur="short"/> it's a sort of a board a number board for dyslexic people who are dyslexic <pause dur="short"/> and he's dyslexic himself and he and it's it's it's a way of putting numbers together so that it's magnetic and they will on fit together if you've got some right basically</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="66" who="S0131">and he he put this <pause dur="short"/> he's one of the Peter Jones academy students and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went along as a potential investor who was asked if he would go along basically to sort of assess the kids on their what on what they were doing and how they put forward their product and what they needed to do <pause dur="short"/> and actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s quite keen to support this guy</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">brilliant</u>
<u n="68" who="S0131">so I'm surprised it's somebody at the college that's pushing her into looking at that <pause dur="short"/> because they've got various people</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">really? Well I'll get her to look into that</u>
<u n="70" who="S0131" trans="overlap">yeah have a look at Peter Jones Academy</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">I think she's only just started teaching there giving erm talks and demonstrations of her products</u>
<u n="72" who="S0131">oh okay</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">but eh she's already had a business erm she set up herself as a beauty therapist on <anon type="place"/> high street and now she wants to get into the niche market of selling her products at training to spas and hotels <pause dur="short"/> so that's cos she's had a baby in the interim <pause dur="short"/> she's a single mother which doesn't help</u>
<u n="74" who="S0131">well that's hard work</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">but she's just got yeah a few talks and stuff teaching at the tech</u>
<u n="76" who="S0131">I just don't think I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s number</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">well I'll tell her to to ask what was it the <trunc>pri</trunc></u>
<u n="78" who="S0131">Peter Jones Academy</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">Peter Jones Academy</u>
<u n="80" who="S0131">just tell her cos they've got <pause dur="short"/> it's based this academy at the college <pause dur="short"/> and it's Peter is it Peter Jones it is Peter Jones who was the erm Dragon's Den guy</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0131">he's he's sort of been involved with setting it up <pause dur="short"/> so that's why it's got his name</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> well I'll tell her that yeah <pause dur="short"/> because she's <trunc>du</trunc> ripping her hair out <pause dur="short"/> all she needs is five thousand pounds to set up cos she's going live online next week and she got orders and interest but she hasn't got the money to buy the produce to make up the orders and <pause dur="short"/> so she's</u>
<u n="84" who="S0131">I'll mention it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0131">well if I give you <pause dur="short"/> I think you if you had her number I sort of think give me her number and I'll tell him to give her a call or I'll give you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s home number</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018" trans="overlap">okay oh super <pause dur="short"/> brilliant <pause dur="short"/> yeah even just if she could have a chat with him and see ask him if he knows other sources of investment because she's been to the bank and they said no <pause dur="short"/> we're not giving any bank loans out to small businesses at the moment <pause dur="short"/> erm she went to the Prince's Trust who said no because</u>
<u n="88" who="S0131">oh that's interesting cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s involved with the Prince's Trust</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018">oh really <pause dur="short"/> but their reasoning was that it wasn't a new business she was <pause dur="short"/> she had already kind of started it up previously so</u>
<u n="90" who="S0131">right <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit harsh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">I think she actually started it up with a loan from them</u>
<u n="92" who="S0131">oh</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">but eh yeah no <pause dur="short"/> so she was at a bit of a a</u>
<u n="94" who="S0131">my grill's not on is it? In the scheme of things five grand is nothing</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">in business yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0131">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've got I'll give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mobile number</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">fantastic</u>
<u n="98" who="S0131"><unclear/> cos he'd always have a chat with her cos eve if he can't do anything</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0131">he may well have erm ideas about where would be a good place to to look</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">super <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> her produce her products are great <pause dur="short"/> they're so lovely <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> she does this body polish erm that isn't <trunc>act</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> cos most exfoliators are like shower gel based aren't they?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0131">oh okay</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">and this one that she's got is slight jelly oil base that is a moisturiser <pause dur="short"/> so the eh the peach kernel</u>
<u n="104" who="S0131">oh I like peach kernel</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018">it exfoliates just falls off leaving the oil that made it</u>
<u n="106" who="S0131">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> in your skin?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018">lubricate it into your skin <pause dur="short"/> and she makes these candles that are made out of eco wax <pause dur="short"/> but once you've burn them you can rub that into your skin as well</u>
<u n="108" who="S0131">oh blimey</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">Eco wax with essential oils</u>
<u n="110" who="S0131">where do you get  Where do you get  the recipes for all this?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018">she makes them <pause dur="short"/> she's</u>
<u n="112" who="S0131">how do you get into that in the first place?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">she she didn't <pause dur="short"/> she was always a bit of a tearaway at college erm at school <pause dur="short"/> and decided to do beauty therapy instead of going to sixth form <pause dur="short"/> and from that she erm started up as a beautician erm but she's got awful allergies <pause dur="short"/> so she touches for example metal metal cutlery and her hands will flare up and she gets eczema <pause dur="short"/> and so she was finding that as a beautician she couldn't use the products that a lot of <trunc>beauty</trunc> beauty parlours</u>
<u n="114" who="S0131">there must be a lot of people out there that can't <pause dur="short"/> we've got a niece who is now a year old no she's a year and a half <pause dur="short"/> and she was just it was just a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> she seemed to be permanently grisly and sort of didn't want to eat and her skin <pause dur="short"/> she kept coming out in rashes <pause dur="short"/> and she's now they did she's allergic to dairy wheat eggs gluten soya <pause dur="short"/> and various things like tomatoes oranges it's just  it's just  <trunc>ma</trunc> mammoth</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="116" who="S0131">and the problem <pause dur="short"/> one of the worst problems was that the doctor's gave them some <pause dur="short"/> when they discovered that she's got some allergies they gave them some bath oil to try and settle her skin down <pause dur="short"/> and it transpired this had got soya in it and she's allergic to soya so actually was making it ten times worse <pause dur="short"/> poor kid <pause dur="short"/> when when she went to bed she was just <pause dur="short"/> they couldn't <trunc>undersat</trunc> understand why the bath wasn't making her more comfortable <pause dur="short"/> well it wouldn't cos it was actually irritating it even more <pause dur="short"/> so hopefully she will outgrow some of it certainly <pause dur="short"/> but poor little mite <pause dur="short"/> and they said would I make a birthday cake for her? I did manage to make a birthday cake I mean it it didn't taste much like cake <pause dur="short"/> and she didn't but she wouldn't touch it <pause dur="short"/> and you can understand why she wouldn't touch it because she doesn't she hates food because it makes her feel ill</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">shame</u>
<u n="118" who="S0131">it's just she's so fussy but you can understand why</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018">is have they managed to get it under control now?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0131">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean <trunc>j</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is amazing <pause dur="short"/> she's a teacher she works three days a week and she spends the two days a week she's not working preparing food and putting it in the freezer that's stuff that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can eat <pause dur="short"/> and her mum looks after her the two days that she's the three days that she's working <pause dur="short"/> it's so time consuming <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how she does it <pause dur="short"/> she's still breastfeeding her <pause dur="short"/> she she she's a year and a half? And she won't take any of the milk substitutes because they taste horrible <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know how long you can go on <pause dur="short"/> so she's expressing milk to leave with mum <pause dur="short"/> but actually they've had to start giving her vitamins and things cos the milk she's really she's just living on milk and eighteen months is not enough</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0131">but yeah she looks healthy <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> well I'll see her in <pause dur="short"/> we've got a family wedding in June in Amsterdam</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">ah ha</u>
<u n="124" who="S0131">so she'll be out there</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">so when's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0131">potentially next sort of April eh May June time</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018">ah that gives you a a year to</u>
<u n="128" who="S0131">A year</u>
<u n="129" who="S0018">make the cake then</u>
<u n="130" who="S0131">yes <pause dur="short"/> well I've got about four before then</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018">wedding cakes <pause dur="short"/> family wedding cakes?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0131">and eh and others <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've actually got one for a girl who was at school with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she text she put see I'm on Facebook and she sent me a message saying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've got a problem I I <pause dur="short"/> eh excuse me</u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">naughty dog</u>
<u n="134" who="S0131">she said my husband to be wants his mum to make him cakes but she's down in Essex and he wants they want a fruit cake a biscuit cake chocolate biscuit cake and a sponge cake <pause dur="short"/> so I said well that's no problem but you'll have to get the fruit cake <pause dur="short"/> if you get the fruit cake to me a couple of weeks before I can ice it <pause dur="short"/> but then what I'm going to have to do is to put two polystyrene tiers on top and she'll have to the day before the wedding deliver the biscuit cake and the sponge cake to me and I'll ice them and put them in as cutting cakes <pause dur="short"/> cos that's really the only way we can do it <pause dur="short"/> there's no way I can ice everything the day before is it's some sort of <pause dur="short"/> and I don't  I don't  know whether the <trunc>bis</trunc> actually the biscuit cake will stack quite nicely on the fruit cake <pause dur="short"/> it would all stack together <pause dur="short"/> but and she said oh she said you're amazing <pause dur="short"/> I thought it wasn't going to be possible to so anything with it <pause dur="short"/> so we can always do something</u>
<u n="135" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> who is that?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0131">it's erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> they used to live at the end of the road here</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">no I don't</u>
<u n="138" who="S0131">she lives in <anon type="place"/> just round the corner from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> so it's all very exciting</u>
<u n="139" who="S0018">ah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah well this friend I'm telling you about the beautician with her products <pause dur="short"/> her name's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's from <anon type="place"/> and she's just moved to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0131">no we bought a house to downsize to over there <pause dur="short"/> erm thinking that we were going to be abroad and we'd buy something abroad and sort of split out time <pause dur="short"/> and then  And then  actually it didn't work cos we couldn't find anywhere that we really wanted to buy abroad and we weren't sure we were going to get to use <pause dur="short"/> the kids weren't going to get out there at the moment they've got too much else on <pause dur="short"/> so we rented it out and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have bought it off us</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="142" who="S0131">Cos actually it was the wrong size time to downsize</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0131">we've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> here this year <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes back in June <pause dur="short"/> and they're always in fact she might even be back tonight hopefully</u>
<u n="145" who="S0018">Will that be it for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she'll have finished her training?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0131">yeah she starts works in Staffordshire in well in June</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="148" who="S0131">she's got  She's got  a job</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018">oh super <pause dur="short"/> doing what is she?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0131">she'll have she has two years what they call foundation years in Staffordshire <pause dur="short"/> and in the first you have three different jobs in each year <pause dur="short"/> in her first year she's got Burton hospital for a three months doing erm cardiology and three months doing breast surgery which she's delighted about <pause dur="short"/> and then she's got Tamworth hospital where she's going to be doing psychiatry which she's not so bothered about but the only good thing about that is it transpires it's a nine to five unit it's like a clinic unit <pause dur="short"/> it's not a hospital <pause dur="short"/> so that might mean she doesn't have to do nights and things <pause dur="short"/> which could be alright <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't like psychiatry</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it's not a very precise science is it?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0131">A friend of mine has got depression at the moment <pause dur="short"/> and they've said it's a chemically <pause dur="short"/> it her particular depression is chemical imbalance <pause dur="short"/> she's had problems ever since she had the children and she's been on anti-depressants for years on and off <pause dur="short"/> and it's absolutely knocked her sideways and she has one day that's really good and the next day she can't get out of bed</u>
<u n="153" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="154" who="S0131">and it takes a while to get the medication right so it's <pause dur="short"/> and they said you know it's it's a  it's a  medical condition it's not oh well you know <pause dur="short"/> it it it's sort of <pause dur="short"/> people have this thing about mental illness and well you should be able to get over it <pause dur="short"/> but actually you can't and certainly most mental illness is actually a <trunc>ch</trunc> it's a physical condition</u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">yeah it's all about imbalance of as you say <pause dur="short"/> things in your brain</u>
<u n="156" who="S0131" trans="overlap">yeah so it's really tough <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s boyfriend is coming to live with her in Staffordshire</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018">ah ha <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not going to live here and commute to?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0131">no well initially she'll come back here but then erm they want to look to rent somewhere in Staffordshire and he's finishes his law erm training erm in June as well so he's going to be looking in <trunc>Mid</trunc> in the Midlands and Manchester <pause dur="short"/> so hopefully he'll get something but training placements are just so hard to come by</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0131">there's just nothing out there</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="162" who="S0131">so <pause dur="short"/> he's told her he's learning how to cook and he's learnt how to clean</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">he can be a house hubbie</u>
<u n="164" who="S0131">so he can look after her <pause dur="short"/> has he got a womb as well maybe they can start having a family?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018" trans="overlap">having a family</u>
<u n="166" who="S0131">he can take off</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0131">no they'll want to get married I think but <pause dur="short"/> mind you they haven't spent <pause dur="short"/> they've been together for five years but of that time there's three of those years <pause dur="short"/> one year he was in Taiwan and then the last two years she's been in Leeds and he's been in London <pause dur="short"/> so they haven't had a huge amount of time together <pause dur="short"/> but he's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> he's such a star <pause dur="short"/> he just a he's a hunting shooting fishing type but he's not  he's not  sort of pompous or arrogant in any way he's just that's just what he's always done <pause dur="short"/> that's what his family have done <pause dur="short"/> they've got a massive pile down in Hampshire with a river running through it and fishing rights on it <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's <pause dur="short"/> they've got not a penny to rub together but they've got this sort of inherited pile which is crumbling round their ears <pause dur="short"/> they can't actually afford <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ka</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says she'd hate it because you can't afford to actually do it up in any way <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but he's just a sort of rather different background <pause dur="short"/> he was at private school all his life and <pause dur="short"/> but he's actually but and he is a seriously nice guy</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="170" who="S0131">he's such easy company</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018">the the two boyfriend's actually resemble each other a little do you not think?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0131">no <pause dur="short"/> not at all</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> I thought maybe they they looked quite similar</u>
<u n="174" who="S0131">they probably <pause dur="short"/> they are quite different <pause dur="short"/> they get on well they do get on well but erm <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets on well with them so</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018">brilliant</u>
<u n="176" who="S0131">no we're lucky <pause dur="short"/> he's single footloose and fancy free at the moment and thoroughly enjoying it</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018">probably won't be for long</u>
<u n="178" who="S0131">no he's decided he's he's had three long term relationships and he's decided that's it he doesn't want to rush into anything</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">how old is he?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0131">twenty-two</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0131">he's only young <pause dur="short"/> but he's got so much on <pause dur="short"/> he's he's playing hockey at Alton at Alton West Warwick's this year cos he's back here <pause dur="short"/> and they asked him if he would go and coach and play for them as he was back over here</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018">oh super</u>
<u n="184" who="S0131">and he's absolutely loving it <pause dur="short"/> he's got some good mates there so <pause dur="short"/> cos he was worried about living at home this year he wanted to stay in Nottingham <pause dur="short"/> david said well I'm not paying for accommodation if you're not you know <pause dur="short"/> I don't see why I should pay for accommodation if you're not earning anything <pause dur="short"/> and you know you need to come home and live at home <pause dur="short"/> but actually it's turned out really well</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">so has he taken a year out of is studies?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0131">no it's a sandwich course</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0131">so normally you'd have an internship with a big company</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0131">but because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had got his own business which the university had funded <pause dur="short"/> well they'd given him two thousand pounds to help set him up <pause dur="short"/> he went to them and said look I've got this business and I'd like to work in it for the year off rather than so an internship in another company as part of the course <pause dur="short"/> and they said yes he could do <pause dur="short"/> so I mean he's he's got his own business but the reason he's working with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is that erm that also gave it a bit more credence because working with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s business partner <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> eh actually supervises <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so it's not his dad sort of telling him what to do <pause dur="short"/> but he reports to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> he's doing a good job by all accounts they gave him a bonus last month so he was</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">ooh fantastic</u>
<u n="192" who="S0131"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I think you've worked hard and <pause dur="short"/> no that's good</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">excellent <pause dur="short"/> so what what's he in charge of doing like is he marketing and selling?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0131">oh everything everything <pause dur="short"/> I mean his own business he's doing everything <pause dur="short"/> he's just got erm just <unclear/> erm juniors <pause dur="short"/> they do training camps all over the country and they want mouth guards with their own logo on them <pause dur="short"/> it was his idea he sort of approached them and they said oh yes please <pause dur="short"/> so that could be massive</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">wow</u>
<u n="196" who="S0131">what else has he got? He just erm  which is another design a <trunc>co</trunc> a clothing sports clothing company want to use him for their mouth guards <pause dur="short"/> so he's <trunc>go</trunc> he's got  he's got  <anon type="place"/> school he's got King Edward School's girls and boys have said yes they want him to supply not <unclear/> which is the normal supplier <pause dur="short"/> so he's got some big contracts <pause dur="short"/> so he's doing everything in his own business and actually pretty much he does the same with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he does I mean all the yeah marketing sales <pause dur="short"/> he he's been going round the stores checking on stock he's been making <pause dur="short"/> he's even made <unclear/> off to show what these loft stilts do and he's done trade fairs he he <pause dur="short"/> he gets the figures each month and he goes through the figures <pause dur="short"/> yeah they had  they had  a bit of problem because the figures didn't tally with what was in the stalls <pause dur="short"/> it transpired that the stalls have sold out and the figures say there's still some in the stores but there aren't any <pause dur="short"/> so he went out and was walking the shop floors and talking to the managers and things and asking them to move if they'd got sort of what he thought was a poor location <pause dur="short"/> getting them to move it and <unclear/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah he sold a massive amount <pause dur="short"/> he enjoys it</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">super <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> leave more than</u>
<u n="198" who="S0131">oh well I mean he'd have been making the coffee and doing the photocopying wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0131">yeah there's no comparison I don't think so</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">what college is it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0131">he's at Nottingham Trent</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">oh university</u>
<u n="204" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no he loves it <pause dur="short"/> and he's actually got a first in a lot of things <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to him do you think you could come out with a first overall? And he said well it is a possibility but he's he hasn't got firsts in everything so <pause dur="short"/> make his final year fairly tough but he's pretty keen to do it <pause dur="short"/> I think he'll probably come out with a two one but he knows that he can't afford to come out with anything less so</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">that's the problem nowadays isn't it? So competitive out there <pause dur="short"/> I mean in a way I kind of I'm thinking positively and thinking at least I'm trying to get into the job market with experience behind me and eh a two one degree because kids coming out of uni nowadays</u>
<u n="206" who="S0131">we've got a nephew who's been trying for erm since last July <pause dur="short"/> his wife's got a job she's <trunc>ca</trunc> American girl <pause dur="short"/> she's got a job with an em insurance company in London and he's got a thing about going into insurance <pause dur="short"/> cos they want they got married in September and they want to go back to the States to Atlanta where her family are <pause dur="short"/> but and there's big insurance business there <pause dur="short"/> erm so the sort of thinking was if they both got jobs in insurance over here they've then got some experience</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018">mm but</u>
<u n="208" who="S0131">insurance he's going to <pause dur="short"/> it bores the pants of him <pause dur="short"/> she's doing she's got in and she's doing alright <pause dur="short"/> but he has just had he's applied for hundreds and hundreds but he's only got a two two</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0131">so he's always going to be the sort of dodgy candidate <pause dur="short"/> two two and no experience</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018">oh what a shame</u>
<u n="212" who="S0131">and he has he's doing it he is actually <trunc>man</trunc> managed to get some voluntary work with her company at the moment <pause dur="short"/> it's not ideal <pause dur="short"/> I I don't think it's what he should be in anyway so <pause dur="short"/> but he's quite pushy</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah well I'm having this dilemma about cos if you say  if you say  it pays well you said it will bore him to death but at the end of the day it's about survival isn't it? And this is my whole dilemma about the teaching thing <pause dur="short"/> I really do not want to go into teaching after what I've seen</u>
<u n="214" who="S0131">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't miss it</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">I have had I <trunc>m</trunc> I keep meeting teachers who have just retired who've said wouldn't go into teaching if I were you <pause dur="short"/> don't do it <pause dur="short"/> if I  If I  had to start my career at this particular moment in time I wouldn't touch it with a barge pole and erm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0131">that's interesting cos I wouldn't say that <pause dur="short"/> but I don't I I'm happy to be doing other things <pause dur="short"/> and I've I I'm working four days a week pretty much for the college now and it's great because I'm teaching people that want to learn to say</u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0131">but I do enjoy the teaching</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">but that's  But that's  what I come from <pause dur="short"/> my experience as a teacher has always been mostly teaching people who are there because they want to be there or even if they're kids and they don't want to be there the groups are small enough and <pause dur="short"/> there are the targets aren't so stringent that I can use my effervescent <trunc>person</trunc> teacher personality to kind of motivate them</u>
<u n="220" who="S0131" trans="overlap">well maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe FE is the sort of better place for you to be</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="222" who="S0131">Cos I I didn't  I didn't  anticipate enjoying the work from the college <pause dur="short"/> the only problem is it's well I'm I'm lucky I don't need a sort of permanent contract and I roll over from one term the next and I don't know what I'm going to be doing next term and well I generally I've got a pretty good idea but they have to get the numbers to justify the courses I'm doing <pause dur="short"/> erm and actually it just  it just  seems that I tend to get more work rather than less <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I have got two evenings a week which is quite <pause dur="short"/> we went skiing a couple of weeks ago and on Thursday night I'm teaching till half past nine so <pause dur="short"/> we didn't leave till ten o'clock to go down to Dover <pause dur="short"/> but you know there you go <pause dur="short"/> and at the moment I'm at college with the sort of the only day I don't work is Friday and I'm at I do college all day for myself for that <pause dur="short"/> I'm actually canning that this summer cos I just want the day when I'm not working at all</u>
<u n="223" who="S0018">what what are you doing on Fridays then? You're doing college?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0131">I do sugar craft I do the sugar flower work</u>
<u n="225" who="S0018">as a student or?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0131">as a student</u>
<u n="227" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="228" who="S0131">and they and I've also been in cake decorating not not really <pause dur="short"/> I don't really need it <pause dur="short"/> I did it initially because I'd never done any courses <pause dur="short"/> and then the college said well they would pay my fees because the lady I'm working with is the only other cake decorating teacher in the college <pause dur="short"/> and it means that it's professional <unclear/> really <pause dur="short"/> erm but she drives me a bit bit mad with the cakes really <pause dur="short"/> she's she's terribly old it's terribly old fashioned and and I and you know as a teacher when I start off at the beginning of the term and I say to my students okay <pause dur="short"/> this is what I've got planned <pause dur="short"/> but is it's not appropriate to your needs we can change it <pause dur="short"/> so whatever happens I want this to be appropriate to to you <pause dur="short"/> and erm she has this sort of thing that well no we'll do this and we'll do that <pause dur="short"/> and then when they don't bring the <trunc>re</trunc> the resources in she she says well I'm not bringing them in cos you know they've got to be independent <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking well if they don't want to do it if it's not <unclear/> they won't bring the stuff in <pause dur="short"/> I haven't had any of that <pause dur="short"/> I do have two classes Mondays and Tuesdays where I provide all the ingredients but that's because they're special needs so <pause dur="short"/> and I mean actually they they kept coming and they enjoy coming <pause dur="short"/> but even then I had particularly with them actually you have to make sure it's appropriate</u>
<u n="229" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0131">whether it's appropriate to their skills or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and she just <pause dur="short"/> she said well when I did my qualifications and she's basically done the old I think it's called seven two seven two O or something it as called <pause dur="short"/> it was an it's a qualification that enables you to teach adults <pause dur="short"/> that is very basic</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> mm hm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0131">and when you've done what you  it's a bit different <pause dur="short"/> morning Johnny</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">hiya</u>
<u n="234" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> This</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">hi how are you?</u>
<u n="236" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">sorry I was playing with the dog</u>
<u n="237" who="S0131">yeah he'll be pleased with that cos I kicked him out cos he was being a bit of a pain</u>
<u n="238" who="S0018">getting a wet muzzle and</u>
<u n="239" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">imprints everywhere</u>
<u n="241" who="S0131">so yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">you been running</u>
<u n="243" who="S0131">you shouldn't be <unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just <trunc>cha</trunc> just chasing him</u>
<u n="245" who="S0131">ah yes <pause dur="short"/> he'll probably be alright now if you're in here</u>
<u n="246" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Don't know</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">hello big dog</u>
<u n="248" who="S0131">oh no <pause dur="short"/> oh you haven't got cats where you are?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">yeah I've got a cat</u>
<u n="250" who="S0131">you have cats? Oh that's maybe he can</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">maybe that's what he can smell <pause dur="short"/> maybe he just find my leg extremely</u>
<u n="252" who="S0131">there's a shortbread <pause dur="short"/> you can try one if you want to check if they're alright</u>
<u n="253" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0131">that one <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Yeah try it <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't sure whether they were cooked enough but I have a nasty habit of over cooking them</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">is this he wants me to tickle his tummy?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're gonna have to be careful because he want you to tickly his tummy but then eventually he starts thinking that you're a humping post</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">oh right okey-doke</u>
<u n="258" who="S0131" trans="overlap"><unclear/> It's alright to start with <pause dur="short"/> he's alright at the moment but he's a <pause dur="short"/> he's just a he's just <trunc>cro</trunc> he does it when you've got your legs crossed <pause dur="short"/> it's really odd</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">well it's just there at maybe at the right angle for him?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0131">right right yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> go away <pause dur="short"/> that's a pain <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> he's been fed</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">well as long as you enjoy the teaching stuff that you're doing</u>
<u n="262" who="S0131">yeah I do I must admit <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot of preparation</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> always true</u>
<u n="264" who="S0131">but erm <pause dur="short"/> even for what I'm doing I need staff preparation cos it's making cakes and making biscuits and I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but even actually things like putting together lists of equipment they need and perhaps suppliers and then you think well actually don't you know how much you need for a six inch cake? If you ask them to bring in bring a six inch cake it have they got do they know what the recipe for a six inch cake looks like so? It is surprising that <pause dur="short"/> but no it's been fun <pause dur="short"/> I've learnt a lot actually I must admit <pause dur="short"/> it's good</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="266" who="S0131">it's very different to teaching kids</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">and your mum says that you're teaching</u>
<u n="268" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0131">no</u>
<u n="270" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no no</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018"><trunc>Wh</trunc> you're coaching</u>
<u n="272" who="S0131">oh <trunc>coa</trunc> no you</u>
<u n="273" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I did  I did  erm doing a bit of coaching in eh <unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0018">well kind of like teaching isn't it?</u>
<u n="275" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018">sports teaching</u>
<u n="277" who="S0131">actually you you you're good at it with the hockey aren't you? Well he did it  he did it  for a year a school didn't you? When you left school <pause dur="short"/> did it for a year</u>
<u n="278" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah I I quite enjoy it <pause dur="short"/> yeah I quite enjoy the coaching stuff</u>
<u n="279" who="S0131">you are being a pain <pause dur="short"/> stop it</u>
<u n="280" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you want me to put him out?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0131">well he's been out and he was whining at us <pause dur="short"/> ooh <pause dur="short"/>  What was that?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> What was that?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0131">no <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> go away</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">yeah well so I'm at the moment looking for jobs in like the publishing world <pause dur="short"/> tEFL publishing</u>
<u n="285" who="S0131">oh okay</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018">yeah I've I've just <trunc>re</trunc> heard that I haven't got an interview for he first on I went for but it was me I was expecting it <pause dur="short"/> the guy in human resources said apply for all the jobs that come up whether you've got the required requirements or not <pause dur="short"/> which I thought was a bit silly cos if they've got require requirements it's hardly a requirement if you don't have <unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0131">no</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018">erm and it was more of a sales and marketing type roles trying to promote their primary course books and materials to to schools <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so they they they said a requirement was sales and marketing experience which I have but very on a basic level erm doing the advertising for the college that I used to teach at in Barcelona</u>
<u n="289" who="S0131">oh okay</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">but I didn't get an interview because I imagine that they've got sales and marketing professionals who went for that job <pause dur="short"/> but there's another one that's come up with them same company</u>
<u n="291" who="S0131">right</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">that is eh managing their online placement tests <pause dur="short"/> so which sounds quite</u>
<u n="293" who="S0131">is that based in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">no in Oxford</u>
<u n="295" who="S0131">that'll be nice</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so fingers crossed I'm going to do my application for that this week <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="297" who="S0131">that's different isn't it?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0131">and you've got a lot of TEFL experience haven't you?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">yeah well most of the requirements I actually have <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="301" who="S0131">makes a lot of sense</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">be good <pause dur="short"/> what it is about my leg?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0131">I don't know</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">the angle it must be <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0131">I can see that <pause dur="short"/> I think if you go into teaching and you're sort of straight in university where you've sort of your that much you've got a bit more and a a bit more resilience almost</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">you're more malleable</u>
<u n="307" who="S0131">and I think you're also a bit naïve</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0131">so you sort of <pause dur="short"/> whereas you've seen a bit of the real world and you know what it can be like <pause dur="short"/> and you know it doesn't have to be like what you're saying here</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think  I think  that was one of the problems cos there's four of us that have dropped out well with <trunc>de</trunc> deferred the PGCE till next year</u>
<u n="311" who="S0131">really? That's a lot</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">and eh three of us are not straight out of uni</u>
<u n="313" who="S0131" trans="overlap">mature students as it were</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">and the other guy is French <pause dur="short"/> so we're wondering whether it is that that you know you don't <pause dur="short"/> it's not that you're not flexible cos I am as you know <pause dur="short"/> I'm very flexible in the work place erm <pause dur="short"/> it's more that as you say it's like why are they doing it like this? <trunc>Wh</trunc>? I mean it just doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> and if you're used to having high standards and making sure that you're very well prepared and making sure that what you're teaching is the materials are reliable and attractive and will get them talking and that will motivate them <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you can't use materials like that because you have to make every single thing yourself</u>
<u n="315" who="S0131">that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">I mean</u>
<u n="317" who="S0131">that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">it just is ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> it's just not the right way to go about doing it at all</u>
<u n="319" who="S0131">you're reinventing the wheel all the time aren't you?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">exactly</u>
<u n="321" who="S0131">it's completely pointless <pause dur="short"/> the best is to take the best of what's on offer and adapt it if you need to</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018">exactly exactly <pause dur="short"/> which is what I've always done as an ELT teacher <pause dur="short"/> I guess there's a a wealth of published resources for English language teaching cos it's such a big market</u>
<u n="323" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there are for anything  <pause dur="short"/>There is for anything <pause dur="short"/> I remember we had  we had  a problem cos when we moved schools we had all this wonderful computer system <unclear/> computer system <pause dur="short"/> and erm they provided us with some package which had got some on they were erm whiteboard eh sort of you <trunc>we</trunc> <trunc>us</trunc> resources you could use with the whiteboard <pause dur="short"/> and they said this is just wonderful <pause dur="short"/> all these other schools in the Birmingham area were using them and there's these lesson plans on here and there's all the resources are already made for you <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know who was hoodwinked into getting it for us cos if they'd asked us to have a look at it any one of us to have a look at it we'd have said well actually they are completely useless <pause dur="short"/> cos they were totally and utterly useless for our kids <pause dur="short"/> there was nothing that was appropriate <pause dur="short"/> because all the sort of stuff that was level reading age five to six we needed to use with perhaps sixteen fifteen sixteen year olds <pause dur="short"/> well the material wasn't appropriate <pause dur="short"/> the actual content</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0131">even if they could read it the content was totally inappropriate <pause dur="short"/> so that was completely useless <pause dur="short"/> but there was stuff out there if you <pause dur="short"/> it it took a bit of finding but because there were other schools in the position same position as we were there was other stuff out there actually which was appropriate and which did make life a lot easier</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018" trans="overlap">well what <pause dur="short"/> what I found for example with the white with the Smartboards was that teachers had just latched on to them saying oh aren't there Smartboards wonderful <pause dur="short"/> let's use them but let's use them all the time</u>
<u n="327" who="S0131">all the time</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">the kids get so used to them</u>
<u n="329" who="S0131">yes they do</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">and the teachers like oh using smart boards as if this is so you know cutting edge and we'll motivate the kids</u>
<u n="331" who="S0131">but OFSTED has pushed that though <pause dur="short"/> cos we we had we were OFSTED'ed just before we moved schools <pause dur="short"/> and they came in and they'd got a big push on using ICT <pause dur="short"/> fine lesson I was interviewed in I was in a hut <pause dur="short"/> I had no computer in there that actually worked even <pause dur="short"/> there wasn't even a computer that worked <pause dur="short"/> and there was no white board <pause dur="short"/> so I thought well okay the only way I can get any sort of ICT and maybe I'll use an overhead projector <pause dur="short"/> so I used an overhead projector <pause dur="short"/> that was a close as I could get to anything</u>
<u n="332" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0131">and my when I had my lesson review afterwards this woman said it's just <unclear/> I would have liked to have seen more use of ICT <pause dur="short"/> and I said well tell me where I was going to find it because you know I didn't there was nothing in there that I could use</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">what do you want me to do? Buy a computer?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0131" trans="overlap">what do you want me to do? Yeah I you know <pause dur="short"/> their their their if we don't have facilities how are we supposed to use them?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018">well that's a stupid thing to say <pause dur="short"/> if you don't have the facilities</u>
<u n="337" who="S0131" trans="overlap">well it's just <unclear/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">it's like saying I would like to have seen that class taught in Africa <pause dur="short"/> it's like well yeah but we're not Africa</u>
<u n="339" who="S0131" trans="overlap">yeah it's exactly what it <pause dur="short"/> we're not there <pause dur="short"/> if it had been <pause dur="short"/> I think I got a <pause dur="short"/> it was like it was outstanding and then there was very good or whatever <pause dur="short"/> she said if you'd used more ICT it would have been outstanding <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>so</trunc> you know <pause dur="short"/> it was either an outstanding lesson or it wasn't based on what I'd go there <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but then we moved schools and we had all this equipment put in <pause dur="short"/> and as you say people just used it for the sake of using it and they weren't thinking <pause dur="short"/> there was some wonderful stuff you could do with it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">yeah yeah I agree</u>
<u n="341" who="S0131">we bought some erm <pause dur="short"/> overhead projector things which linked to the whiteboard so that you could demonstrate stuff and the kids could see it up there and you could photograph it and then you could do things with it <pause dur="short"/> but nobody ever did the more complex photographing it and using that and they just put it up there so the kids didn't have a to sit round what they were <trunc>do</trunc> sit round the tables <pause dur="short"/> and well actually that's not actually <trunc>gai</trunc> you're not gaining anything out of that</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">well the whole thing of you can arrange things on on the document <pause dur="short"/> the program that comes with the Smartboard</u>
<u n="343" who="S0131">mm hm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">so that the kids can actually come up to the back eh to the Smartboard and with their finger like move it around as if it were a touchscreen <pause dur="short"/> which is great</u>
<u n="345" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">for some things <pause dur="short"/> but I just saw it used all the time <pause dur="short"/> and it wasn't even erm attractive <pause dur="short"/> it was because you have to enter each sentence in as a different entity</u>
<u n="347" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">and then format that <pause dur="short"/> the teacher's just didn't have time to do anything else with it <pause dur="short"/> so they'd just use exactly the same format every time <pause dur="short"/> which was just basically words sentences written on the board in French and then sentences written on the board in English</u>
<u n="349" who="S0131">and match them up</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">and the kids one at a time had to come up</u>
<u n="351" who="S0131">and that's</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">which is another problem</u>
<u n="353" who="S0131">that is a problem</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">like everyone else switches off <pause dur="short"/> but they thought because it was a Smartboard it was fantastic and it <trunc>w</trunc> I was like <pause dur="short"/> kid the kids are not looking at this as cutting edge oh wow I'm motivated I'm engaged because it's a Smartboard <pause dur="short"/> they're thinking I've had death by PowerPoint now I'm having death by Smartboard</u>
<u n="355" who="S0131">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">and you know I I was giving them lots of little conversation cards and</u>
<u n="357" who="S0131">that they've actually got here and they can</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">but they don't know how to behave</u>
<u n="361" who="S0131">no they don't</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">in a <trunc>tw</trunc> one on one situation because all of their eh life in French classes or Spanish classes or whatever has even sitting staring at the board watching as one person goes up and matches the sentence on the board together <pause dur="short"/> and they're not used to actually having to use it <pause dur="short"/> oh it's just horrendous</u>
<u n="363" who="S0131">I had to teach Spanish to we <trunc>de</trunc> they decided in their <unclear/> wisdom that we should teach foreign languages to these kids that can't speak English and <trunc>ca</trunc> certainly can't read or write <pause dur="short"/> so we had a lady who does is she speaks quite good Spanish <pause dur="short"/> she's not a Spanish teacher but she speaks quite good Spanish cos her parents were <unclear/> And but not only did she have to teach it <pause dur="short"/> all the other class teachers have to teach it <pause dur="short"/> they have no Spanish knowledge whatsoever <pause dur="short"/> I was one step ahead cos I'd got other languages <pause dur="short"/> my only problem was I ended up telling them stuff which I subsequently realised was Italian <pause dur="short"/> so there you go <pause dur="short"/> they want to</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">that is a modern foreign language isn't it? Don't have to specify which one</u>
<u n="365" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0131">and they did quite enjoy it in a funny sort of way <pause dur="short"/> they weren't learning a lot <pause dur="short"/> but using the she used a lot of the Smartboard a lot <pause dur="short"/> and actually I discovered that the class I had were just so unruly <pause dur="short"/> and I went back to old fashioned art work and we made a Spanish town out of cardboard and we painted it so we learnt the colours and we peopled it and we worked out what all the shops were and we talked about things happening in this thing</u>
<u n="367" who="S0018">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="368" who="S0131">which was a very traditional way of teaching</u>
<u n="369" who="S0018">works</u>
<u n="370" who="S0131">actually I had them onside because the were occupied and they were  they were  part of it</u>
<u n="371" who="S0018">how old were they?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0131">these guys were year seven</u>
<u n="373" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0131">so first year seniors <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> bearing in mind they'd got mental ages of <pause dur="short"/> I mean they're modelling skills weren't weren't brilliant I have to say cos they were not terribly good <unclear/> It was year seven eight <pause dur="short"/> I do the sevens and the eights <pause dur="short"/> but that was of far more benefit to them than games on the whiteboard</u>
<u n="375" who="S0018">well I I prepared an activity to learn the colours in Spanish whereby erm they had a presentation of Noah's ark but all the different animals were different colours</u>
<u n="376" who="S0131">oh magic</u>
<u n="377" who="S0018">I'd made it look silly different colours <pause dur="short"/> and then what they had to do they each had a little eh print out in black and white and they had to colour their animals different colours and then do like an information gap activity <pause dur="short"/> what colour is your eh elephant? My elephant is pink <pause dur="short"/> what colour is your elephant? My elephant is pink too <pause dur="short"/> whoo we got one the same <pause dur="short"/> and every time they had one the same a bit like battleships</u>
<u n="378" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0018">but she said no no no no you can't get your children colouring in a French lesson <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh for god's sakes <pause dur="short"/> what do you want me to do? Just get them to stare at the Smartboard all</u>
<u n="380" who="S0131">but that's not</u>
<u n="381" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0131">she's completely missed the point of education which is actually you utilise <pause dur="short"/> kids all learn differently <pause dur="short"/> so actually physically doing something whatever it might be if it's colouring so be it it will be a skill that will actually make something stick with some kids</u>
<u n="383" who="S0018">but what I thought she missed the point of was that the colouring was not the end</u>
<u n="384" who="S0131">no</u>
<u n="385" who="S0018">product <pause dur="short"/> it was a vehicle to getting to the actually speaking the language</u>
<u n="386" who="S0131" trans="overlap">to get them to there <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="387" who="S0018">which you know would have worked <pause dur="short"/> would have worked fantastically <pause dur="short"/> erm if I could have managed classroom managed the pair work it would have worked fantastically because that's the kind of thing that they</u>
<u n="388" who="S0131">that's right</u>
<u n="389" who="S0018">they do get into</u>
<u n="390" who="S0131">yes</u>
<u n="391" who="S0018">silly animals <pause dur="short"/> oh look that that pig is blue <pause dur="short"/> ha ha ha</u>
<u n="392" who="S0131">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="393" who="S0018">but no I was told not to  not to  bring <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>ye</trunc> that's the  that's the  thing that annoys me about the training as well is all the different people telling you to do things or don't do different things and it's it's completely arbitrary most of the time it's</u>
<u n="394" who="S0131" trans="overlap">that's just silly isn't it? And when you get out there you do your own thing anyway</u>
<u n="395" who="S0018">yeah true</u>
<u n="396" who="S0131">unfortunately that's the difference <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think  I don't think  people in university who are teaching are necessarily up with what's going on in schools anyway <pause dur="short"/> I mean I that was a problem I had that I found that the tutors who were teaching us actually hadn't been in schools for so long</u>
<u n="397" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="398" who="S0131">that they weren't necessarily teaching us what was appropriate</u>
<u n="399" who="S0018">erm <pause dur="short"/> you see I think if if they got course books and class books <pause dur="short"/> not just books but whole multi media suite of the class book students book the activity book the communicative activity books the smartboard presentations for when you're presenting vocabulary for example and little matching activities when they're first learning the vocabulary <pause dur="short"/> video <pause dur="short"/> if they got it all together as a syllabus</u>
<u n="400" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0018">like there exists for English language teaching and I'm sure that must exist it it must exist in <trunc>mo</trunc> modern foreign language teaching in schools</u>
<u n="402" who="S0131">yeah it does or most most secondary schools use</u>
<u n="403" who="S0018">but then</u>
<u n="404" who="S0131">use textbooks</u>
<u n="405" who="S0018">yeah but they're the most driest of the dry textbooks</u>
<u n="406" who="S0131">but they and they have they will have a well certainly most <trunc>te</trunc> secondary schools that I've worked with and they have a  they have a syllabus <pause dur="short"/> they whether it's their own that they've written or it's somebody else's that they've bastardised they've got a plan and you will be teaching this this week and that <pause dur="short"/> and actually that's <pause dur="short"/> cos David worked when he was at Ninestyles that was exactly what they had there <pause dur="short"/> they had it for everything including foreign language teaching</u>
<u n="407" who="S0018">from what <trunc>y</trunc>they were teaching from the textbook all the time?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0131">pretty much yeah <pause dur="short"/> and if they weren't they were teaching from a set of resources that they had made themselves</u>
<u n="409" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="410" who="S0131">as a  As a  erm department <pause dur="short"/> so it was very prescriptive <pause dur="short"/> more so at secondary than at primary <pause dur="short"/> primary there's a lot more leeway for doing your own thing yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0018">well I wouldn't mind doing mostly someone else's thing <pause dur="short"/> because I don't think teachers have the time to plan as well as teach and mark ad assess and everything <pause dur="short"/> but only if it's good quality stuff</u>
<u n="412" who="S0131">that's right</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018">because I think one of the reasons that they had stopped using course books was that they are so dry and they are so boring <pause dur="short"/> but I think it gives the kids also a focus <pause dur="short"/> that they should be colourful that they should be somewhat you know well designed so that it attracts the eye <pause dur="short"/> that they be clear <pause dur="short"/> that they have you know the vocabulary written down <pause dur="short"/> because these kids that weren't working from the textbook they never did any listening activities <pause dur="short"/> which is awful because before you can start <trunc>tole</trunc> use a language you need a lot of</u>
<u n="414" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">practice listening to it <pause dur="short"/> erm they didn't have a course book so they had no written record or what they'd done <pause dur="short"/> they had these tatty exercise books that they would graffiti all over and rip pages out of</u>
<u n="416" who="S0131"><unclear/> do they?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">write you know change their handwriting every other page and flick ink of the page</u>
<u n="418" who="S0131">this is secondary kids?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">but you know if even if they came to well that's if they came to the lesson with a pen because it wasn't cool to have a pencil case <pause dur="short"/> so you'd start the first fifteen <pause dur="short"/> you'd waste the first fifteen minutes of a class sorting out <pause dur="short"/> miss can I have a pen? Eh haven't you got your pen? No I haven't? No I haven't? Where is it? Oh I didn't bring it today <pause dur="short"/> oh have you got can you borrow it from someone else <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm not going to give you a pen every time you ask for it <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="422" who="S0131">it's crazy <unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0018">but they've just been you know they're spoon fed because all the teachers now just give them pens cos they know</u>
<u n="424" who="S0131">Cos it means they can get on</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018">it that they can get on with it <pause dur="short"/> but that just engenders more <pause dur="short"/> less students taking responsibility for their own learning <pause dur="short"/> and oh it was just crazy <pause dur="short"/> and so they've got no record of what they're doing <pause dur="short"/> they've got no independence and no momentum to learn and it was just <pause dur="short"/> their behaviour was <trunc>pat</trunc> appalling</u>
<u n="426" who="S0131">really?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">the violence <pause dur="short"/> the level of violence was appalling</u>
<u n="428" who="S0131">where was this? Was it <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0018">in <anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="430" who="S0131">I went into <anon type="place"/> school recently <pause dur="short"/> by a mistake <pause dur="short"/> I was actually looking for the primary healthcare trust building over there but it transpires my satnav took me there <pause dur="short"/> but I should've been over the road <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> it was a zoo</u>
<u n="431" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0131">I I stood outside the front door said well I better ask cos it maybe <pause dur="short"/> cos I thought the place I was going to teach might have been within the school school grounds and school complex cos quite a lot of school have that have community outreach centres in them</u>
<u n="433" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0131">so I stood outside the door and there's a women in an abaya in the let me help you desk in the corner who just sat there looking at me <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> she just didn't bother <pause dur="short"/> and then there's a guy talking to the woman behind the who was actually the sort of office administrator lady here and he was talking to her <pause dur="short"/> and he just kept looking at me <pause dur="short"/> now what do I have to do to get into this place?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018">La la la la la</u>
<u n="436" who="S0131">and they knew they all knew I was there <pause dur="short"/> and eventually the headmaster walked passed the door and saw my standing out there and opened the door for me</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">the headmaster</u>
<u n="438" who="S0131">the headmaster as he was going to his office</u>
<u n="439" who="S0018">well at least the led</u>
<u n="440" who="S0131">at least he</u>
<u n="441" who="S0018">by example</u>
<u n="442" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nobody nothing was said to anybody <pause dur="short"/> and then rather than sort of saying ooh it was <unclear/> She this woman had been chatting and it was just chatting to this guy for quite some time <pause dur="short"/> they were all Asian I have to say <pause dur="short"/> and but it probably could have happened if they'd been white anyway but <pause dur="short"/> and eh <pause dur="short"/> instead of sort of saying yeah hang on she she just just made me stand there <pause dur="short"/> and they were just talking about anything and everything <pause dur="short"/> no question of <unclear/> I was thinking I'm going to be late for this thing wherever it happens to be <pause dur="short"/> and then the bell went</u>
<u n="443" who="S0018"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0131"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It was like  It was like  something out of the Lion King <pause dur="short"/> it was just <pause dur="short"/> there was just kids everywhere <pause dur="short"/> and it was complete anarchy</u>
<u n="445" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0131">and there's signs saying walk on the right walk on the left do this do that <pause dur="short"/> it was an absolute bun fight</u>
<u n="447" who="S0018">well I went to a training session</u>
<u n="448" who="S0131">I just thought let me out of here</u>
<u n="449" who="S0018">entitled how we can reclaim the corridors</u>
<u n="450" who="S0131"><vocal desc="gasp"/> What's? Well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <anon type="place"/> was a just a nightmare when he was there <pause dur="short"/> he hated it</u>
<u n="451" who="S0018">oh he was at <anon type="place"/> was he? Oh</u>
<u n="452" who="S0131">yeah he did that <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> are affiliated <pause dur="short"/> and he was sent fairly quickly out to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and that was where he had a chap in the corridor take the scruff of the neck and he's this guy's going you can't do that to me <pause dur="short"/> and he says just watch <pause dur="short"/> and he came home and he said <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I can do this anymore cos I'm going to be in prison if I carry on so</u>
<u n="453" who="S0018">well this is my  this is my</u>
<u n="454" who="S0131">and he handed his notice in the following day</u>
<u n="455" who="S0018">yeah this is my take on it <pause dur="short"/> it's just</u>
<u n="456" who="S0131">it was just</u>
<u n="457" who="S0018">it's an unrealistic situation <pause dur="short"/> and people like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who would be very very very good teachers if you had a class of kids who were used to being taught and who know how you know the the behaviour for learning <pause dur="short"/> that they know how that works and they understand that they've got a responsibility to put their part in <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would be a fantastic teacher</u>
<u n="458" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think teacher's give up <pause dur="short"/> I think you get in the situation like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that they had he <pause dur="short"/> he could understand where the problems were coming from <pause dur="short"/> they were coming from home <pause dur="short"/> eh the boys were treated like sort of princes at home got away with anything <pause dur="short"/> and the parents would come at parents evening and say we can't do anything with him at home</u>
<u n="459" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="460" who="S0131">so <pause dur="short"/> so what so can't you can't do anything in the school we can't do anything at home</u>
<u n="461" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0131">and the girls saw school as a way out of home <pause dur="short"/> so they actually wanted to be there <pause dur="short"/> but then they were sort of preyed on by the boys and it was just <pause dur="short"/> he said it was just an absolute nightmare <pause dur="short"/> and a lot of it was that <pause dur="short"/> but also there was a lot of the Sunni Pakistanis <pause dur="short"/> cos this is very un PC but his mate his business partner's Pakistani <pause dur="short"/> and he said there are a lot of Pakistanis lower down the food chain basically who apparently they came over here from erm I think he said the borderlands when erm they flooded the eh land to make reservoirs for hydroelectric power and they displaced thousands and thousands of basically peasant farmers <pause dur="short"/> and they had to because of the I don't know what what the politics were <pause dur="short"/> but they had to offer them basically asylum here <pause dur="short"/> there was no other option <pause dur="short"/> so they came over here and actually they have no history of education <pause dur="short"/> they have no history of working actually other than subsistence living <pause dur="short"/> and they've been plucked out of there and plonked into central <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="463" who="S0018">gosh <pause dur="short"/> how long ago was this?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0131">we're talking thirty years ago</u>
<u n="465" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> so they're now <pause dur="short"/> we're educating their children</u>
<u n="466" who="S0131">so we're now second and third generation <pause dur="short"/> but they're not they don't they see no reason to to educate <pause dur="short"/> that's why we've now got the the certainly within that particular community <pause dur="short"/> they're not actually educating themselves out of it <pause dur="short"/> they're just there <pause dur="short"/> they don't see any any need for it <pause dur="short"/> and the youngsters don't see any need cos their parent didn't have it so</u>
<u n="467" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0131">it's a bit like <unclear/> and the third fourth generation unemployed over there and my dad hasn't got a job and my mum hasn't got a job but we've got a house and why do I need to world?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0018">yeah and they've been taught that benefits is a career move and having a kid will get you a council house</u>
<u n="470" who="S0131">gets you a flat <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0018">it's a tough situation</u>
<u n="472" who="S0131">we had a sixteen year old girl <pause dur="short"/> she was barely sixteen actually <pause dur="short"/> and there were all sorts of problems at home <pause dur="short"/> and and in the end <pause dur="short"/> she was in with her grandmother for several years in the end the grandmother said I can't cope with her <pause dur="short"/> she's got special needs <pause dur="short"/> grandmother says can't cope with her <pause dur="short"/> so what does the council do? They provide her with a flat <pause dur="short"/> just <trunc>six</trunc> just sixteen <pause dur="short"/> she's going to be <unclear/> So <pause dur="short"/> and you think who in their infinite wisdom thinks that's appropriate <pause dur="short"/> how is that safeguarding this child? I mean she was a nightmare but there has to be a better way than that so <pause dur="short"/> she was actually alright in school because she knew where the boundaries were <pause dur="short"/> but we had lots of kids coming from mainstream where they had just completely fallen by the wayside <pause dur="short"/> they're disruptive they can't <pause dur="short"/> they they they they just they don't find learning easy they can't learn <pause dur="short"/> so basically they've spent all of their time out if the classroom cos that's the easiest thing to do with them <pause dur="short"/> so they've never been in a learning environment and they come to us they came to us and it was like ooh blimey somebody is actually asking me to do something <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0018">you can kind of understand it can't you? You can  You can  see the root of it the root cause of it but</u>
<u n="474" who="S0131">he's being an absolute pain</u>
<u n="475" who="S0018">ah it's cos he wants my leg</u>
<u n="476" who="S0131">he doesn't do it normally <pause dur="short"/> normally he'd have settled down by now</u>
<u n="477" who="S0018">yeah the last few times I've been here he's always been really chilled and <pause dur="short"/> oh maybe it's the spring time</u>
<u n="478" who="S0131">we've walked him he's had about a five mile walk this morning <pause dur="short"/> then I play golf nine holes <pause dur="short"/> it's only nine holes</u>
<u n="479" who="S0018">ooh</u>
<u n="480" who="S0131">and then he needs another walk this evening <pause dur="short"/> so he's definitely going to need it cos he's otherwise he'll be driving us mad</u>
<u n="481" who="S0018">you have to walk him for five miles <pause dur="short"/> well not have to</u>
<u n="482" who="S0131" trans="overlap">we tend to walk him for about an hour and a half <pause dur="short"/> in the morning if will unless we're at work in which case we do it the other way round and then we'll take him out for sort of forty-five minutes and a hour in the evening</u>
<u n="483" who="S0018">that's nice though cos it gets you out</u>
<u n="484" who="S0131">it does well we've given up our gym memberships <pause dur="short"/> it's the first time in thirty years <pause dur="short"/> it's just <pause dur="short"/> and it's just nice to be outside</u>
<u n="485" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> especially when the weather's like this</u>
<u n="486" who="S0131">well I was getting all sorts of repetitive strain injuries in my shoulders and things from swimming <pause dur="short"/> and it was just overuse <pause dur="short"/> and so and actually I haven't got any of that it's been brilliant</u>
<u n="487" who="S0018">ah ha</u>
<u n="488" who="S0131">Cos I walk eight miles <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a thin as I was but there you go</u>
<u n="489" who="S0018">I don't notice a difference <pause dur="short"/> you still look very slim and glamorous</u>
<u n="490" who="S0131">yeah yeah I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> I don't know about glamorous</u>
<u n="491" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0131">in my ski socks and walking trousers</u>
<u n="493" who="S0018">yeah you always have a way of looking glamorous with your earrings and your <pause dur="short"/> have you painted your nails?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0131">no</u>
<u n="495" who="S0018">oh you normally have your nails painted</u>
<u n="496" who="S0131">no they're all shortened <pause dur="short"/> they'd be full of biscuit mix though</u>
<u n="497" who="S0018">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think yeah <pause dur="short"/> this is one of that reasons that I'm just not into teaching <pause dur="short"/> I want to get another career just cos I don't want to work with kids</u>
<u n="498" who="S0131">no I can understand that</u>
<u n="499" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> not just from those backgrounds <pause dur="short"/> just because I don't have that passion for children that I think you need to to</u>
<u n="500" who="S0131">yeah you do</u>
<u n="501" who="S0018">push you a long in that career</u>
<u n="502" who="S0131">I know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said there's his academy in Tamworth</u>
<u n="503" who="S0018">is this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s ex?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0131"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s ex <pause dur="short"/> I mean some of they had the one afternoon they had the police in to break up the fight and then</u>
<u n="505" who="S0018">I had an <unclear/> to remove</u>
<u n="506" who="S0131">and then they had an ambulance man in to because somebody got hit and so badly hurt they had to take them off <pause dur="short"/> it was like well no</u>
<u n="507" who="S0018">yeah I had a policeman come into my class to remove a girl that <trunc>wa</trunc> was kicking off but refused to leave <pause dur="short"/> and then she was kicking off against the headmistress so they got the police in to <trunc>ta</trunc> to remove her <pause dur="short"/> and then another guy who got carted off from one of my lessons in an ambulance because he'd done a runner on my class and the teacher in charge told me to just go and find him <pause dur="short"/> and running away from me he jumped over a wall fell flat on his arm broke his arm <pause dur="short"/> I was like nur nu nur nu nur <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="508" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0131">that was <unclear/> Just let me stamp on the other arm while you're down <pause dur="short"/> it's just shocking</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">it is  It is  and as you say it comes from home</u>
<u n="511" who="S0131">it does come from home</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">lack of <pause dur="short"/> but also the lack of erm because there's so many targets and senior management have got so many targets that they have to achieve</u>
<u n="513" who="S0131">it means that it's not appropriate what you're teaching is not appropriate to those kids <pause dur="short"/> and actually a lot of the kids need life skills <pause dur="short"/> they don't have life skills</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">these guys for example they're all fantastic about shouting their mouth off <pause dur="short"/> and telling everybody what they're doing and what they like and what they don't like <pause dur="short"/> but they they can't listen</u>
<u n="515" who="S0131">listen to save their lives</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">how can you learn a foreign language without having listening skills <pause dur="short"/> even in your own language? And these kids are all brought up on a diet of shouting and reality TV oh look at me  look at me look at me  and <pause dur="short"/> they don't know how to listen <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="517" who="S0131">and actually reality <pause dur="short"/> things like the Jeremy Kyle show <pause dur="short"/> they they would aspire to be on that <pause dur="short"/> being sort of having their private lives put under the spotlight cos they've got on to television you know actually it's irresponsible broadcasting <pause dur="short"/> actually <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and I was in the <pause dur="short"/> I'd taken a school trip away <pause dur="short"/> we'd had this girl with us and I'd I'd said I wanted to take her cos I thought she needed to get away from home actually <pause dur="short"/> it was a bit of a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> and mum was just <pause dur="short"/> I let the have their mobile phones in the coach on the way down <pause dur="short"/> but I said you know if there's any misuse any problem they we will I will collect them in and you will have them for an hour or so each day so that you can phone home let them know you're alright <pause dur="short"/> that would be it <pause dur="short"/> oh and this woman this girl's mum spent every five minutes she was calling her <pause dur="short"/> the mum was actually the one that was sort of was the problem <pause dur="short"/> and in the end we had various problems with phones <pause dur="short"/> so I took them all in at the end of the day and said right okay that's it <pause dur="short"/> you will be able to phone home tomorrow afternoon at this time <pause dur="short"/> well this mother it transpired <pause dur="short"/> the girl did phone her but I think maybe she couldn't get hold of her <pause dur="short"/> so she obviously didn't leave a message or anything cos they've never got any credit on their phones so it's sort of that home they don't have home they don't have landlines because they don't pay the bills so the landlines disappear so <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> I said to the parents categorically before we left that his I would do this if there's problems <pause dur="short"/> I'd also said we will call you if there are any problems <pause dur="short"/> so if you don't hear anything you know they're fine <pause dur="short"/> well I got back at the end of the few days it was a week actually</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">oh oh</u>
<u n="519" who="S0131">and this woman was in the car park absolute guns blazing <pause dur="short"/> and the first thing I knew <pause dur="short"/> she didn't shout at me she shouted across the car park at this poor kid <pause dur="short"/> she was hollering across the car park <pause dur="short"/> david had just got out of the car to come and meet me <pause dur="short"/> he was like what's going on? And you could see why this kid thought it was alright to shout at other people cos she always did shout she always raised she couldn't talk in normal voice <pause dur="short"/> cos this woman was just bawling at her</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0131">and I went over and I said you know I think you've you need  you need  to hear her side of the story <pause dur="short"/> you're you <pause dur="short"/> I know I'm right and I said no <pause dur="short"/> you need to let her you need to listen to what she's trying to tell you <pause dur="short"/> cos the kid was trying to say look mum you know I was alright and I did try and call <pause dur="short"/> but she wouldn't listen her mother was totally incapable of listening <pause dur="short"/> eventually we we sorted it and settled down but <pause dur="short"/> she's never going on a school trip again <pause dur="short"/> this is precisely why this poor kid needs to go away <pause dur="short"/> if you're brought up with that that's the norm</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">yeah yeah and you have to shout to be heard <pause dur="short"/> except no one's listening anyway</u>
<u n="523" who="S0131">no it is it's really <pause dur="short"/> and then the riots in the summer I mean <pause dur="short"/> I could have put I could have named names I'm sure of the kids that I've taught who would have thought that was a good idea to go and join in because <pause dur="short"/> and then there's some parents interviewed <pause dur="short"/> there was one woman she was a teacher <pause dur="short"/> admittedly at a college not at a school <pause dur="short"/> and she said well how am I supposed to know where my sixteen year old son is at night? Excuse me <pause dur="short"/> I know where my twenty-two year old son is <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> he's at home <pause dur="short"/> and then there's another woman who's got several kids she said well there's nothing else for them to do <pause dur="short"/> well if you've got children it's your <trunc>respon</trunc> it's not somebody else's responsibility to find things for them to do</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="525" who="S0131">you've had them <pause dur="short"/> it's your responsibility <pause dur="short"/> to make to sort of</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">totally</u>
<u n="527" who="S0131">and they don't see it as their responsibility to actually perhaps read with the children or do things with the children <pause dur="short"/> even if it's taking them to the park and overseeing a game of football <pause dur="short"/> well somebody else should be doing that not me <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">were these the children maybe that had so the parents could get the council house or single parent benefit</u>
<u n="529" who="S0131">probably <pause dur="short"/> you get very cynical don't you?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">it is such a shame</u>
<u n="531" who="S0131">it is a shame</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">but it's everything I mean it's not just erm <pause dur="short"/> as you say reality TV and what they're fed with on television <pause dur="short"/> it's you know there's there are so many laws of what you have to do what you have to wear what trainer you have to wear what <pause dur="short"/> it's all prescribed for them <pause dur="short"/> so they don't have to develop their own moral compass</u>
<u n="533" who="S0131">no <pause dur="short"/> no that's right</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">so they have no <pause dur="short"/> you know that this muscle that is developed over a thousand years of evolution about what decisions shall I make in the interests of society or in the interests of morality <pause dur="short"/> they don't</u>
<u n="535" who="S0131">no <pause dur="short"/> there's only one person that</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">they never have to do that</u>
<u n="537" who="S0131">it's what suits me</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">it's all prescribed <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="539" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no they don't <pause dur="short"/> and when they do get in a situation where they have to do something that they don't want to do then they just see it as something to fight against</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0131">so yeah school uniform <pause dur="short"/> nightmare <pause dur="short"/> fighting a losing battle I think but <pause dur="short"/> it's part of the whole problem</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0131">no it's it's a really a difficult one <pause dur="short"/> I'm so <trunc>so</trunc> it's a shame that you had that <trunc>experi</trunc> I don't think you <trunc>wou</trunc> there are places where you wouldn't have had such a bad experience but there are a lot of places where you do get that</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I wonder whether it would have been the same had I got a very nice all girls grammar school or something</u>
<u n="545" who="S0131">you get different problems</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">exactly</u>
<u n="547" who="S0131">you get different issues</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">exactly</u>
<u n="549" who="S0131">you get pushy parents <pause dur="short"/> you get yeah you get different issues</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">I guess working with adults in a business environment you get problems there too don't you?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0131">you get politics don't you?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0131">yeah it's interesting</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018" trans="overlap">but I think at the moment I'd like to spend this year at least trying to find</u>
<u n="555" who="S0131" trans="overlap">try something different <pause dur="short"/> so you're not going to back I suppose you can't go back can you? Or can you? Go back out to Spain to do anything else <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing in Spain work wise is there</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">well it's not really worth it because</u>
<u n="557" who="S0131">if you don't do the teaching then</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> the job track there</u>
<u n="559" who="S0131">the job market out there is shocking</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and even when you do get a job you don't get a proper contract you don't get <pause dur="short"/> you know any security in a way that you get over here <pause dur="short"/> I mean I was looking at erm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0131">despite despite the unionisation? Cos I know my brother in law says they're having a real problem with they're actually now shutting office out there but it's taken them years</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0131">to get to the point where they could actually shit it because the employment laws were so favourable to the staff</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0131">that <pause dur="short"/> despite the fact they've been in a rubbish job for so many years losing money hand over fist <pause dur="short"/> they couldn't actually shut the place down</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">well this is what the government changed about six months ago <pause dur="short"/> that it before if you wanted to sack an employee you had to give them a particular amount of erm  do you say?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0131">eh yes <pause dur="short"/> indemnification</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">indemnification <pause dur="short"/> which was based on <pause dur="short"/> they had to you had to pay them one month's salary for each year that they'd worked</u>
<u n="569" who="S0131">right</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">so they'd made it a lot easier for people to sack their employees recently</u>
<u n="571" who="S0131">that must have been why they wanted to shut the office them</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">which <pause dur="short"/> yeah maybe</u>
<u n="573" who="S0131">he said it was just prohibitively expensive to do so before</u>
<u n="574" who="S0018">yeah yeah it would have been</u>
<u n="575" who="S0131">was cheaper to actually keep them working?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0131">at at a loss</u>
<u n="578" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0131"><unclear/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can see it coming from both sides but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's just for example I was looking at a job jobs on the Oxford University Press website <pause dur="short"/> and they had a job advertised in on their Spanish website which actually turns out to be a separate company from Oxford University Press <pause dur="short"/> and if you look at any of the jobs that are on OUPs British website you've got all the requirements all the job description <pause dur="short"/> all what what you would imagine yourself to be doing <pause dur="short"/> all the different responsibilities <pause dur="short"/> the salary brackets</u>
<u n="581" who="S0131">right</u>
<u n="582" who="S0018">the any information please contact this person <pause dur="short"/> eh please full in your online application with a cover letter and a CV <pause dur="short"/> it's all there for you and it's all transparent</u>
<u n="583" who="S0131" trans="overlap">it's all there</u>
<u n="584" who="S0018">okay you look at a job that was going on the OUP Espanya website and it was three lines prod ELT product specialist required <pause dur="short"/> no <trunc>descri</trunc> no job description no description of what the kind of person they're looking for al the key requirements or even the salary bracket <pause dur="short"/> erm apply with CV <pause dur="short"/> so no application process no <pause dur="short"/> and that's <trunc>typ</trunc> typical over there</u>
<u n="585" who="S0131">right</u>
<u n="586" who="S0018">that you don't you know you never find out about</u>
<u n="587" who="S0131">right <pause dur="short"/> literally it's the last minute and actually they'll get you for what they can rather than paying the going rate</u>
<u n="588" who="S0018">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="589" who="S0131">or whatever</u>
<u n="590" who="S0018">yeah it's like a market over there in a different way</u>
<u n="591" who="S0131">it's going down the tubes big time isn't it?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0131">is it going to be the next Greece?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0018">who knows</u>
<u n="595" who="S0131">bit worrying isn't it?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="597" who="S0131">you're probably better off over here in in many respects I suppose from that point of view</u>
<u n="598" who="S0018">well I think so in looking for jobs wise <pause dur="short"/> I'm better off over here <pause dur="short"/> but I just fingers fingers crossed that I find something that erm</u>
<u n="599" who="S0131">so how did you get the <trunc>pla</trunc> what you're doing at the moment? How did you get hold of that?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">oh just eh looking online <pause dur="short"/> cos I always check out eh the big <trunc>pub</trunc>publishing companies that have EL eh English language teaching jobs available <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and this was  this was  up I think back in January</u>
<u n="601" who="S0131">right</u>
<u n="602" who="S0018">and so just luck really that I'd seen it and <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a freelance do as much as you want when you want</u>
<u n="603" who="S0131"><unclear/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0018">it's been perfect</u>
<u n="605" who="S0131">yeah get you back on your feet again</u>
<u n="606" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's nice to have a little project as well <pause dur="short"/> cos there's quite a lot of paperwork involved and</u>
<u n="607" who="S0131">is there?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's nice</u>
<u n="609" who="S0131">yeah but it's an experience isn't it? Which is quite useful for what you</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> and also it</u>
<u n="611" who="S0131">job applications <pause dur="short"/> it's different to experience what you've done before so</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's also erm aside from that just having a little project for me to work on in my own time <pause dur="short"/> and I've got nobody telling me what to do or how to do it which was stifling <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind having managers and stuff but having the mentor at university saying do things this way and having the tutor saying no don't do it like that do it like this <pause dur="short"/> and then there's no rhyme or reason involved <pause dur="short"/> I was just like ah <pause dur="short"/> so now it's like oh yeah just do it however you like but we need this done and we need that done and we need that done</u>
<u n="613" who="S0131">you can cope with that can't you? I mean that's that's fair enough</u>
<u n="614" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0131">you're an adult and</u>
<u n="616" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0131">yeah you should be able to be trusted but</u>
<u n="618" who="S0018">but I do find that they they do <trunc>infa</trunc> infantilise? Teachers</u>
<u n="619" who="S0131">I think though a lot of teacher I think particularly people who come out of university erm <trunc>neve</trunc> and and become teachers never actually are never anything other than a grown up school kid <pause dur="short"/> and they become sort of</u>
<u n="620" who="S0018">do you know what I could see that in the staff room</u>
<u n="621" who="S0131">oh</u>
<u n="622" who="S0018">the cattiness</u>
<u n="623" who="S0131">yeah they never grow up  they never grow up  It's a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> it used to drive me mad managing them sometimes <pause dur="short"/> well she's got this and I should have it</u>
<u n="624" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0131">you know</u>
<u n="626" who="S0018">well I don't know what I'm I'm used to working with teens and teachers who don't actually have to work together but do because they realise that team work is actually very beneficial for everybody</u>
<u n="627" who="S0131" trans="overlap">no they're <unclear/> <trunc>Da</trunc> David had a problem with that <pause dur="short"/> he said he felt that they were incredibly juvenile <pause dur="short"/> so actually that's probably the way you have to <trunc>tre</trunc> you have to treat them I suppose <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0018">I couldn't believe that I you know I expected <pause dur="short"/> in <pause dur="short"/> I have to say in the modern foreign languages department every single teacher without exception was lovely</u>
<u n="629" who="S0131">oh that's good</u>
<u n="630" who="S0018">so supportive so human <pause dur="short"/> very understanding <pause dur="short"/> erm but I was in the <trunc>facul</trunc> the staff room of the faculty of humanities and education ah communication <pause dur="short"/> english modern language music drama <pause dur="short"/> and It was  It was  like being in a playground <pause dur="short"/> people not talking to each other that day like</u>
<u n="631" who="S0131">oh yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0018">completely unprofessional comments being slung across the staffroom I was like <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe that adults</u>
<u n="633" who="S0131" trans="overlap">that's that is  that is  standard <pause dur="short"/> and you are supposed to be</u>
<u n="634" who="S0018">are talking to each other in this way?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> setting an example to the kids but actually going</u>
<u n="636" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0131">I had that particularly over here <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't as apparent when I was abroad at all <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember seeing it over there but particularly over here</u>
<u n="638" who="S0018">but that's the thing I never had that in the TEFL teaching <pause dur="short"/> the you know okay there were the few random people who didn't want to work as a team but everyone was always so much more professional</u>
<u n="639" who="S0131" trans="overlap">they have this thing that <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people have this thing that somebody owes me a living <pause dur="short"/> and and the teachers actually this this is about erm the pensions being changed <pause dur="short"/> I went in to school and someone said I've got to work until I'm sixty whatever and claim my pension it's appalling <pause dur="short"/> and I was thinking well but actually if you were in business you'd probably have to work a damn site longer and you wouldn't be <pause dur="short"/> yes we all say you work very hard during term time yes we all do <pause dur="short"/> but let's face it you get bloody long holidays actually <pause dur="short"/> and I know I've been there and I've worked in business and I've worked in schools and it's not  it's not  a bad deal actually <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah the do have this real sort of I don't know <pause dur="short"/> there is a problem with them just they never grow up <pause dur="short"/> they're permanently school kids themselves <pause dur="short"/> it is a problem <pause dur="short"/> we had people who I'm talking to her and ah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0018">petty</u>
<u n="641" who="S0131">oh it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="642" who="S0018">stupid <pause dur="short"/> but even from erm heads of department and heads of faculties as well it was</u>
<u n="643" who="S0131">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend was one of those <pause dur="short"/> she has <pause dur="short"/> you you can see it because she's none she hasn't known anything else other than really yes she went to university but sort of education in one form or another where you're told what to do <pause dur="short"/> she hasn't known any other way of doing anything <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> she she she will she'll be one of those <pause dur="short"/> she already plan will she'll be one of those <pause dur="short"/> she'll manipulate <pause dur="short"/> she's manipulative so she's likely to side with people that try and work things at <unclear/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0018">she'll probably fit right in</u>
<u n="645" who="S0131">she will</u>
<u n="646" who="S0018">but do you find in general that in business people are more professional</u>
<u n="647" who="S0131">oh <pause dur="short"/> you can't afford to be like that because if you start doing that sort of thing your job's on the line</u>
<u n="648" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="649" who="S0131">we <trunc>co</trunc> it was very very difficult to <trunc>ge</trunc> get rid of poor teachers <pause dur="short"/> and ah the hoops we had to jump through were a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> and so everybody felt really pretty safe there was so <pause dur="short"/> they could say well I can do what I like to some extent because <pause dur="short"/> we had one woman who was on maternity and the young girl they got in to cover her was doing a good job <pause dur="short"/> but she did struggle because this woman who was on maternity hadn't left half the resources that she should have left behind and half the files and the information <pause dur="short"/> and so I was having to chase her up trying to get hold of it <pause dur="short"/> and it's you know she's put some absolutely awful comments on Facebook about this young teacher</u>
<u n="650" who="S0018"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0131">really really</u>
<u n="652" who="S0018">it's worse than the students</u>
<u n="653" who="S0131">on Facebook <pause dur="short"/> and it was just before I was about to leave <pause dur="short"/> and I heard about it and I said  I said  to the head she this is appalling <pause dur="short"/> you can't you cannot have her back from <pause dur="short"/> she will expect to come back from her maternity leave and just slot in as if nothing else has happened <pause dur="short"/> what are you going to do about it <pause dur="short"/> oh I'll have to have a we'll have to have a chat with her <pause dur="short"/> if you <trunc>re</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> and and nothing actually happened <pause dur="short"/> I think there was maybe a chat but nothing ever happened <pause dur="short"/> if you were in business that would be reason for you to be disciplined to the point where you could lose your job <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="654" who="S0018">crikey</u>
<u n="655" who="S0131">yeah well se <trunc>a</trunc> this girl was just completely traumatised <pause dur="short"/> it was horrible the stiff she put on there <pause dur="short"/> it was out in the public domain <pause dur="short"/> nobody has any right to do that about anybody else <pause dur="short"/> but she thought she could get away with it and she did</u>
<u n="656" who="S0018">did this other the replacement teacher find out about it? Was she?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0131">oh she knew all about it</u>
<u n="658" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the only good thing that the head did subsequently was to find her a job at the school next door <pause dur="short"/> cos he made sure that once the maternity cover was up this young girl did have a teaching job somewhere else <pause dur="short"/> it was the least she could so really <pause dur="short"/> really she should have been able to keep that job <pause dur="short"/> the other woman shouldn't have been allowed back but she's back <pause dur="short"/> she's still stirring the whatsit</u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> makes you sick doesn't it?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0131">its staggering absolutely staggering <pause dur="short"/> I used to have a woman she used to come into me on a daily basis moaning about I do so much work here nobody nobody realises how much work I do <pause dur="short"/> if I was working at the school next door I'd get this much money for doing this little work <pause dur="short"/> go and work at the school next door the you know <pause dur="short"/> don't keep laying it in my door <pause dur="short"/> this is <pause dur="short"/> I can't do anything to change that actually <pause dur="short"/> if you want to <pause dur="short"/> and I said to them well if you think life is so much better somewhere else go and try it <pause dur="short"/> and somebody said you didn't say that to her? I said well what else and I supposed to say <pause dur="short"/> I know because I've worked in different places <pause dur="short"/> I knew actually that we were on quite a good number where we were <pause dur="short"/> yeah there was things that used to drive me mad but you know <pause dur="short"/> if you've been around and done other things then you know</u>
<u n="662" who="S0018">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> but did you find you actually had your holidays your holiday time for you? Because a lot of teacher I've been speaking to work through</u>
<u n="663" who="S0131">no I always used to carry on and work through <pause dur="short"/> summer holidays I got <pause dur="short"/> I always worked for at least a week at the beginning of summer holidays and a week at the end of summer holidays</u>
<u n="664" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="665" who="S0131">but that still left me with four weeks actually and at you know Christmas time <pause dur="short"/> I'd always have the time over Christmas off albeit I would <pause dur="short"/> you don't you only get a week or so off <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean I'd be working on stuff and you'd spend a couple of days before term preparing <pause dur="short"/> and certainly over Easter I'd probably do a week out of the two I'd be working <pause dur="short"/> but you'd get six weeks holiday a year which is easily which is you'd easily get that <pause dur="short"/> which is a good holiday for somebody in business</u>
<u n="666" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0131">so <pause dur="short"/> I did work weekends <pause dur="short"/> I did work in the evenings <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean it is  it is  hard work</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0131">but the kids are gone by three o'clock in the afternoon four o'clock in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> so I can understand why people find teachers difficult <pause dur="short"/> I don't people don't understand don't appreciate how difficult it is in the classroom how stressful it is <pause dur="short"/> and there isn't enough down to alleviate that <pause dur="short"/> and there is a problem when you can't exclude kids who are making life an absolute nightmare and it doesn't matter what you do you can't seem to get rid of them <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> it is a problem <pause dur="short"/> and people don't appreciate how hard that it</u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">do you think it's just a problem for this area of <anon type="place"/> or do you think it's country wide?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0131">I should think it's countrywide in the cities</u>
<u n="672" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0131">erm it's definitely easier working <pause dur="short"/> there are easier places that working where you were working in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0018">have you worked in non-city place?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0131">erm <pause dur="short"/> I was out at Henley and Arden when I did my first placement <pause dur="short"/> I've only actual teaching jobs no I've always been <pause dur="short"/> cos I when I came back from abroad <pause dur="short"/> well I worked at <anon type="place"/> and that there there was <pause dur="short"/> there was nothing like the sort of pressure in terms of behavioural needs <pause dur="short"/> but we had a head who was a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> so he was the one that was putting the pressure on <pause dur="short"/> we had lots of pushy parents so yeah I mean I would say that was pretty <pause dur="short"/> they was an okay <pause dur="short"/> I worked hard there was a lot of preparation <pause dur="short"/> I had thirty-three in the class so it was a a big class <pause dur="short"/> and I had everything from <unclear/> kids through to kids who got level sixes in their SATs <pause dur="short"/> so you've got the absolute gamut with no teacher's  in there <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but then I always said when I came that when I came back I should where they need good teachers is the place where it's difficult to teach</u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0131">and the problem is that places like <anon type="place"/> maybe places like the school you were in don't attract good teachers because it's such a difficult environment to work it</u>
<u n="678" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0131">so you've got a no win situation really <pause dur="short"/> we actually ended up with a very good staff over in the school I was in <pause dur="short"/> we we did get some good people in and that snowballed <pause dur="short"/> and we progressively got more good people <pause dur="short"/> but we had some real doors initially <pause dur="short"/> and that we had kids climbing on the roof jumping out of trees well sitting in trees and they couldn't get down</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018">but I saw that that type of behaviour I think jaded the staff to such an extent that even the good teacher's just ended up not being good because for example the guy that I was  I was  attached to his form group <pause dur="short"/> he was a head of department <pause dur="short"/> lovely guy really really really nice really helpful <pause dur="short"/> you could tell he cared about the kids <pause dur="short"/> but they'd come you know they'd be body slamming each other into the room and he <pause dur="short"/> I think so that they <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously these are kids that come from broken families and such a high rate of parental suicide and drug abuse <pause dur="short"/> I think he wanted to give them some kind of person that they could turn to <pause dur="short"/> so he didn't want to be that disciplinarian person <pause dur="short"/> but it was just they ran amok <pause dur="short"/> and I think he could of or he didn't make the effort to be consistent and he said oh I really should be getting them to walk in in a more orderly fashion I'll have to do it I will do it or</u>
<u n="681" who="S0018">that's not going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0131">you're going to change you've lost it <pause dur="short"/> you're gotta do it from day one and keep it going haven't you?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0018">exactly exactly <pause dur="short"/> but they just had him round their little finger</u>
<u n="684" who="S0131">it <pause dur="short"/> and it's it's got to come <pause dur="short"/> it's actually something which has got to sort of systematically come from the top down <pause dur="short"/> you can't do it on your own at the bottom <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0018">well that's another thing <pause dur="short"/> senior management wouldn't wouldn't support the staff</u>
<u n="686" who="S0131"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't bear it any longer</u>
<u n="687" who="S0018">straight to the leg right <pause dur="short"/> I'll uncross my legs</u>
<u n="688" who="S0131">come here  Come here</u>
<u n="689" who="S0018">see what happens when I uncross my legs</u>
<u n="690" who="S0131">yeah I know we do love you we just don't want you being a pain alright? Okay?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0018">who's a beautiful doggy?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0131">cor dear <pause dur="short"/> you've worn yourself out I should think</u>
<u n="693" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="694" who="S0131">ah it's a shame <pause dur="short"/> if you <trunc>fe</trunc> if you felt that traumatised by it though and stressed by it your as well off trying to get something else I'd say</u>
<u n="695" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it was just the course being so intense <pause dur="short"/> I think it was seeing what the job actually was really like <pause dur="short"/> and I mean I'll I'll finish the course if I don't find another job in the <trunc>in</trunc> in interim <pause dur="short"/> but if I finish the course I'll be looking for other jobs afterwards I think</u>
<u n="696" who="S0131">yeah</u>
<u n="697" who="S0018">I can't deal with that amount of <trunc>hy</trunc> hysteria and disorder and hostility</u>
<u n="698" who="S0131">it's no <trunc>nec</trunc> it shouldn't be necessary should it <pause dur="short"/> it really shouldn't <pause dur="short"/> you do feel <pause dur="short"/> I always ended up though I must admit feeling sorry for the kids though because <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>re</trunc> you can the reason they're like that there are reasons why they're like that</u>
<u n="699" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0131">but you can't always take that into account</u>
<u n="701" who="S0018">he's got is paw on my leg</u>
<u n="702" who="S0131">tembo</u>
<u n="703" who="S0018">he's trying to make my leg go</u>
<u n="704" who="S0131">aw</u>
<u n="705" who="S0018">stop with your wet snout all over me</u>
<u n="706" who="S0131" trans="overlap">so yeah it's difficult <pause dur="short"/> oh Tembo <pause dur="short"/> come here <pause dur="short"/> come on</u>
<u n="707" who="S0018">you're such a beautiful boy <pause dur="short"/> but I really don't want to be moist moistened by your snout thank you</u>
<u n="708" who="S0131">so have you got the cats with you?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0018">no they're in <anon type="place"/> but I've been round to my parents <pause dur="short"/> cos I had a driving lesson this morning</u>
<u n="710" who="S0131">ah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0018">so I have been covered in pussy cats</u>
<u n="712" who="S0131">are you going to go out here? Come on away you go <pause dur="short"/> now you can lay that <unclear/> there but <unclear/> alright</u>
<u n="713" who="S0018">yeah in many ways I feel like I just went over to Spain for a gap year and I've come back and I'm trying to do the adult life</u>
<u n="714" who="S0131" trans="overlap"><unclear/> were you?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0018">doing driving lessons looking for work <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But it was a nice long fourteen year gap year</u>
<u n="716" who="S0131">fourteen years</u>
<u n="717" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0131">amazing <pause dur="short"/> so Katy is twenty-seven in eighty-five yeah twenty-seven in April <pause dur="short"/> becca's twenty-five next week <pause dur="short"/> quite scary <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="719" who="S0018">I don't think of the the number <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to be thirty-seven this year</u>
<u n="720" who="S0131">I thought you must be</u>
<u n="721" who="S0018">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> I don't really  I don't really  pay any attention to it</u>
<u n="722" who="S0131">I was thirty  I was thirty  seven actually when I did my PGCE</u>
<u n="723" who="S0018">oh really</u>
<u n="724" who="S0131">Cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> well I was thirty no I was thirty <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of dog"/> Shh</u>
<u n="725" who="S0018">shush</u>
<u n="726" who="S0131">I was thirty-five cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was five going on six <pause dur="short"/> it was a couple of years earlier</u>
<u n="727" who="S0018">he was so sweet when he was a littler wasn't he?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0131">he's huge now</u>
<u n="729" who="S0018">he is he towers over me <pause dur="short"/> I've not seen</u>
<u n="730" who="S0131">he is tall</u>
<u n="731" who="S0018">I've not seen him for must be two or three years <pause dur="short"/> seems like he's grown since then</u>
<u n="732" who="S0131">no he's a good lad <pause dur="short"/> he cooked me a nice curry on Sunday night</u>
<u n="733" who="S0018">how did it turn out?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0131">he's a great cook <pause dur="short"/> he loves <pause dur="short"/> all three of them love cooking so</u>
<u n="735" who="S0018">fantastic <pause dur="short"/> you've brought them up so well</u>
<u n="736" who="S0131">not a problem <pause dur="short"/> yeah I went to the wedding fair with Katy at the NEC and got <event desc="sound of dog"/> Oi stop it <pause dur="short"/> and erm got back and he sort of sat me down with a cup of tea and said I'm making making tea</u>
<u n="737" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="738" who="S0131">but no he likes cooking actually <pause dur="short"/> he'll always cook in the evenings <pause dur="short"/> he said to me last week he said I always cook mum so long as there's something to cook with</u>
<u n="739" who="S0018">he's not so good at shopping</u>
<u n="740" who="S0131">therein lies the problem</u>
<u n="741" who="S0018">oh shall I let him back in?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0131">oh you are just being nuisance</u>
<u n="743" who="S0018">what's wrong?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0131">I want to be with you <pause dur="short"/> I just</u>
<u n="745" who="S0018">aw look at him <pause dur="short"/> god he's heart broken <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to have to go in a bit but</u>
<u n="746" who="S0131" trans="overlap">so you'll have that on tape</u>
<u n="747" who="S0018">sorry?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0131">that'll be on the tape</u>
<u n="749" who="S0018">yeah that'll appear in the British spoken corpus of canine whinging <pause dur="short"/> what are you whining about? Shall I let him in?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0131">yeah if you're alright with him it's just he was a nuisance on top of you all the time</u>
<u n="751" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I'm fine with him <pause dur="short"/> leave my legs alone then <pause dur="short"/> stay in your bed get in your bed <pause dur="short"/> hey in your bed</u>
<u n="752" who="S0131">that's a good boy</u>
<u n="753" who="S0018">Good boy <pause dur="short"/> stay</u>
<u n="754" who="S0131">normally he comes in and he sits in there and just goes to sleep</u>
<u n="755" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> no back in your bed</u>
<u n="756" who="S0131" trans="overlap">oi <pause dur="short"/> bed <pause dur="short"/> bed</u>
<u n="757" who="S0018" trans="overlap">bed bed bed bed bed bed <pause dur="short"/> stop <pause dur="short"/> stay stay</u>
<u n="758" who="S0131" trans="overlap">stay <pause dur="short"/> stay</u>
<u n="759" who="S0018">yeah I think <pause dur="short"/> my mum was chuffed the <trunc>ot</trunc></u>
<u n="760" who="S0131">ah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0018">stay <pause dur="short"/> my mum was chuffed the other day cos erm after so much cooking for me since I've been living there I made soup and took her some soup round <pause dur="short"/> she was very tickled I think</u>
<u n="762" who="S0131" trans="overlap">that was nice <pause dur="short"/> I bumped into your mum and dad actually at the erm garden centre on the <trunc>lan</trunc> the road going out other NEC</u>
<u n="763" who="S0018">ah the <trunc>Bracel</trunc> Bracey's</u>
<u n="764" who="S0131">Bracey's</u>
<u n="765" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's where we took mum for mother's day lunch</u>
<u n="766" who="S0131">oh that's nice</u>
<u n="767" who="S0018">they've got a lovely little restaurant</u>
<u n="768" who="S0131">yeah it's good <pause dur="short"/> I was in there with my mother in law <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's <trunc>sh</trunc> that was November I should think <pause dur="short"/> that was the last time she came here <pause dur="short"/> where are we? Yeah it was November before Christmas <pause dur="short"/> she comes up for the odd couple of week when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister needs a break <pause dur="short"/> actually she's very good <pause dur="short"/> she lives  She lives  in sheltered accommodation but she's only just round the corner from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister</u>
<u n="769" who="S0018">oh super</u>
<u n="770" who="S0131">so we're very lucky we don't have to worry about her <pause dur="short"/> got to phone my brother tonight he was erm made redundant around six months ago</u>
<u n="771" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="772" who="S0131">he worked for <anon type="place"/> council he was their chief surveyor <pause dur="short"/> and he can't find a job <pause dur="short"/> I spoke to mum yesterday and she said he's just tearing his hair out because he's <pause dur="short"/> he's not got a family or anything fortunately he's single <pause dur="short"/> but he just he's not even got any replies to the letters that he send off <pause dur="short"/> she said it's just soul destroying</u>
<u n="773" who="S0018">crikey <pause dur="short"/> is he looking just in surveying or has he got can he transfer the skills?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0131" trans="overlap">no I think that's pretty much what he's looking in <pause dur="short"/> he's looking at <trunc>bui</trunc> he's got some ideas for stuff for his own businesses which he's also working on <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know he's fifty-one now <pause dur="short"/> and really that's not a good age to be looking for another job <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he'll really get anything to be perfectly honest</u>
<u n="775" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="776" who="S0131">so my mum wants a break from my dad so my suggestion was well I will come down and look after dad and you can <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can go off and have a weekend in a hotel somewhere</u>
<u n="777" who="S0018">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> your brother?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0131">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she can take him away <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> and go and have a couple of days away</u>
<u n="779" who="S0018">what a shame</u>
<u n="780" who="S0131">Cos my dad won't go into <pause dur="short"/> mum would like to put my dad into respite care so that she can go off and have a weekend away in September <pause dur="short"/> but he's not mentally  enough to do that</u>
<u n="781" who="S0018">oh right <pause dur="short"/> really?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0131">he doesn't he wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> it would be like he's being pushed out the way when he isn't <pause dur="short"/> he's not very able physically but <pause dur="short"/> and mentally he's got he couldn't tell you what he had for breakfast but</u>
<u n="783" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0131">but he's you can sit and have a conversation with him about all sort of things <pause dur="short"/> generally it's sort of <pause dur="short"/> I mean he he wouldn't know what anybody had said in the budget today or anything couldn't remember that <pause dur="short"/> but you can still sit and chat with him about things <pause dur="short"/> golf and sailing and stuff and have perfectly lucid conversations with him <pause dur="short"/> so he's not at the stage where you can shove him in a home for a few days</u>
<u n="785" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0131">but my mum seems to think she should be able to</u>
<u n="787" who="S0018">where are they based?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0131">Essex <pause dur="short"/> countryside</u>
<u n="789" who="S0018">it's a bit of a bore going down there</u>
<u n="790" who="S0131">oh dear</u>
<u n="791" who="S0018">Katy would like my dad to make the wedding but <pause dur="short"/> every year we go through well I don't know how long he's going to be around for and this year he had a chest infection again so he usually gets chest infection in February <pause dur="short"/> and he refused to go into hospital <pause dur="short"/> and actually he's come through it better than the last two or three years when he's been in hospital and got secondary infections</u>
<u n="792" who="S0131">yes and contracted super bugs and deary me</u>
<u n="793" who="S0018">yeah so</u>
<u n="794" who="S0131">contrary to what we expected he's still around so he might make next May June time if we can sort it</u>
<u n="795" who="S0018">I've heard a couple of stories whereby they you know people who are expected to pass on have kept kept themselves going because they have a particular</u>
<u n="796" who="S0131">well I have to say</u>
<u n="797" who="S0018">celebration or something</u>
<u n="798" who="S0131">it would be nice of them to have something to look forward to <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum's brilliant she's flying out with <pause dur="short"/> she's eighty-four I think and she's flying out with us to Amsterdam <pause dur="short"/> well we're driving she's flying with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother</u>
<u n="799" who="S0018">ah for the wedding</u>
<u n="800" who="S0131">for the wedding <pause dur="short"/> so she she but she's quite good at putting things in the diary and she'll ring and say can I come and see you and we'll book a date and so she's got something to actually look forward to which is good <pause dur="short"/> both my parents do nothing but <pause dur="short"/> my dad sits about all the time cos he really can't he can't even get upstairs now so he lives downstairs <pause dur="short"/> and my mum goes to Waitrose every day <pause dur="short"/> I think that's all she does cos she has to get out of the house to get away from him</u>
<u n="801" who="S0018">oh gosh</u>
<u n="802" who="S0131">he's got a wheelchair but she can't push it that's the problem <pause dur="short"/> she can't actually manage him in it <pause dur="short"/> and he can walk to the car and he can walk some sort of he could walk into a coffee shop if you can park right outside it but he can't walk any further so</u>
<u n="803" who="S0018">does she drive?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0131">yeah she's <pause dur="short"/> yeah she said she'll die if she can't drive <pause dur="short"/> nothing like being melodramatic <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd die if I couldn't drive <pause dur="short"/> oh mum get a life <pause dur="short"/> get a bloody taxi <pause dur="short"/> but it's her lifeline she's she's a bit <unclear/> I think sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I think she's always quite <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't look seventy-nine I have to say <pause dur="short"/> she she looks pretty good for her age but <pause dur="short"/> are you knackered?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0018">snory snore</u>
<u n="806" who="S0131">such a sweety</u>
<u n="807" who="S0018">look at him <pause dur="short"/> right well</u>
<u n="808" who="S0131">well I've got a scarecrow to make for tonight</u>
<u n="809" who="S0018">have you?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0131">A scarecrow cake to make for a child's birthday on Saturday</u>
<u n="811" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> I will  I will  leave you to your scarecrow <pause dur="short"/> or do you need a hand?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0131">no I'm sort of quite</u>
<u n="813" who="S0018">dog <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="814" who="S0131">no I'll take him for a walk <pause dur="short"/> finish him off <pause dur="short"/> so you've got to get the bus back to <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="815" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0131">how do you get over there from here?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0018">thirty-seven down to <anon type="place"/> and the one</u>
<u n="818" who="S0131">oh okay</u>
<u n="819" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> although I might be able to drive soon</u>
<u n="820" who="S0131">oh that'll be nice</u>
<u n="821" who="S0018">pass my test</u>
<u n="822" who="S0131">makes a difference</u>
<u n="823" who="S0018">I've only had four lessons so far</u>
<u n="824" who="S0131">can't imagine what it must be like learning later on</u>
<u n="825" who="S0018">it's actually quite</u>
<u n="826" who="S0131">scary almost I would think</u>
<u n="827" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> I was a bit scared</u>
<u n="828" who="S0131">you're more aware of the what's going on than when you're <pause dur="short"/> when you're eighteen and nineteen you're sort of invisible so</u>
<u n="829" who="S0018">exactly yes <pause dur="short"/> but I think that is that that maybe counts against you</u>
<u n="830" who="S0131">mm</u>
<u n="831" who="S0018">maybe a bit of experience and wisdom as you say makes you scared but helps you make decisions better and be more considerate of other people on the road and <pause dur="short"/> we'll see</u>
<u n="832" who="S0131">do you have lessons round <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0018">no around here</u>
<u n="834" who="S0131">oh yeah cos <anon type="place"/> I think would be quite tricky</u>
<u n="835" who="S0018">yeah I know</u>
<u n="836" who="S0131">lot more traffic there</u>
<u n="837" who="S0018">yes but I was I've been up the <anon type="place"/> the <anon type="place"/> in fourth gear</u>
<u n="838" who="S0131">oh well I'll watch out for you then</u>
<u n="839" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> be warned</u>
<u n="840" who="S0131">steph is out</u>
<u n="841" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
</body>
</text>
