<text id="S32W">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0007 S0018</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A leisure centre café, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Studies, work, sports, relationships, driving</topics>
		<activity>Acquaintances chatting in a café.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0007">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Bartender</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<event desc="sound of background"/>
<u n="1" who="S0007">High-tech bit of equipment</u>
<u n="2" who="S0018">it's very <vocal desc="laugh"/> professional</u>
<u n="3" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0018">it gives really good sound quality as well <pause dur="short"/> fantastic <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>y</trunc> you used to be a sports journalist?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0007">well yeah I'm still trying to <pause dur="short"/> so I am in the loose sense of the word <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I er went to university-six years ago now <pause dur="short"/> and um yeah like er I never grew up wanting to be a sports journalist <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to be a <trunc>s</trunc> a sports athlete or sports performer</u>
<u n="6" who="S0018">yeah? What what sport?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0007">football and tennis were the er</u>
<u n="8" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="9" who="S0007">two big ones <pause dur="short"/> I grew up playing tennis probably before football when I was about four</u>
<u n="10" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="11" who="S0007">and then picked up football about at the age of about ten <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but then when I got to I would say about thirteen fourteen I realized that neither was gonna be er my profession for the rest of my life <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking well what else can I do? And when it came to like deciding your options when you're seventeen I thought</u>
<u n="12" who="S0018">mm mhm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0007">well what could I do?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0007">I could do journalism instead <pause dur="short"/> I'm perhaps if I'm not there like playing on the pitch in the the the major finals well it means I can be reporting on it <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="16" who="S0018">getting free tickets <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0007">getting free tickets <pause dur="short"/> and like yeah <pause dur="short"/> just getting to meet some of these these people you watch on TV</u>
<u n="18" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0007">and that was like the real selling point for me <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I went about it and um studied at <anon type="place"/> University</u>
<u n="20" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0007">did three years on a um honours degree and</u>
<u n="22" who="S0018">is that a <trunc>d</trunc> a specifically sports journalist?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0007">it was <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was one of the things that was a real real appeal <pause dur="short"/> cos er there was</u>
<u n="24" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0007">quite a lot of journalism courses across the country <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="26" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0007">only a handful did did specifically sports journalism so</u>
<u n="28" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="29" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> my er reflections on it is the degree itself wasn't the biggest contributor to me getting a job in sports journalism <pause dur="short"/> I think it kind of taught you <trunc>ab</trunc> about it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0007">didn't really hone your skills as a writer</u>
<u n="32" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0007">only a couple of modules were really kind of <trunc>s</trunc> specific <pause dur="short"/> and they were in the latter year <pause dur="short"/> so you could've almost compacted into one year</u>
<u n="34" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0007">but obviously <trunc>de</trunc> er degrees being degrees and universities being the way they are it's about making money as much as anything so</u>
<u n="36" who="S0018">it is <pause dur="short"/> I agree <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I could've done my degree in two years I think <pause dur="short"/> the first year was like we didn't even have to get more than forty percent</u>
<u n="37" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0018">to get into the second year</u>
<u n="39" who="S0007">that's yeah likewise <pause dur="short"/> and you can drop a module as well</u>
<u n="40" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0007">and just essentially not turn up for it <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="42" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0007">it was like twelve hours a week <pause dur="short"/> and and you did have the reading time to do around it <pause dur="short"/> which I do <pause dur="short"/> but you that'd be thirty hours tops that they'd expect of you to really go on <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>f</trunc> at first cos I was always kind of I've always been competitive and er academically I'd always wanna try and get the highest mark I could</u>
<u n="44" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0007">so I set about trying to obviously get a first <pause dur="short"/> and um in the end it it it wasn't about that <pause dur="short"/> it's about the experience you got <pause dur="short"/> and and</u>
<u n="46" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0007">unfortunately for me on the two er years that they had like had a six-week work placement I had mumps the first year</u>
<u n="48" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="49" who="S0007">so I missed out on that</u>
<u n="50" who="S0018">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0007">and then the second year I got a really good one for cos I'm I am a a <anon type="place"/> lad at heart but my dad's from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="53" who="S0007">so I'm a half-Scouser</u>
<u n="54" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0007">and um yeah I tried to get a job <trunc>f</trunc> well a work placement at their um their website <pause dur="short"/> and I got that one <trunc>s</trunc> you know sorted <pause dur="short"/> provisional sorted <pause dur="short"/> and that fell through er a couple of days before</u>
<u n="56" who="S0018">huh</u>
<u n="57" who="S0007">it was really late notice</u>
<u n="58" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="59" who="S0007">they said oh we can't <pause dur="short"/> we <trunc>c</trunc> really sorry we've double-booked <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so I was kind of left in the lurch so</u>
<u n="60" who="S0018">was that for er <trunc>L</trunc> Liverpool Football Club?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> what a shame</u>
<u n="63" who="S0007">so when it came to me graduating I was really panicking at that point thinking oh I've got no experience whereas everyone else has got</u>
<u n="64" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0007">good good solid foundation <pause dur="short"/> er I was <trunc>qu</trunc> quick to get some some kind of work experience lined up <pause dur="short"/> and it just turned out everything fall fell in place <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>t</trunc> I applied to get on a postgrad <pause dur="short"/> cos at first I thought oh</u>
<u n="66" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0007">I need to maybe have another extra qualification to make me stand out</u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0007">we hadn't learnt shorthand <pause dur="short"/> which er still to this day I've never</u>
<u n="70" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0007">done <pause dur="short"/> which I thought was kind of er an essential thing of doing journalism</u>
<u n="72" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0007">but um yeah from that</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">did you do a postgrad as well?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0007">the postgrads the it was a print journalism based one <pause dur="short"/> there wasn't an online one</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0007">which is what I really wanted to get into</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="79" who="S0007">but I got um a work experience placement um at a website called TEAMtalk <pause dur="short"/> which is a football um site <pause dur="short"/> and they when I got the placement they were being bought out by Sky Sports</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> and they were all putting them in one big office with about five other websites up in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and that was the thing that was surprising <pause dur="short"/> that it was all up in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so I just went back up to <anon type="place"/> after graduating and just went thought oh I'll do the work placement <pause dur="short"/> and um the postgrads were like well that's not really what we were looking for for you to get experience somewhere like an office place unfortunately cos you haven't got enough to get on the course</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> oh no</u>
<u n="83" who="S0007">so I was</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">what what were they looking for then?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0007">they well they were just some some kind of experience in a  in a  press room doing print journalism</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0007">so I couldn't I tried to er er like er here <trunc>u</trunc> up in Leeds</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0007">anywhere <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018">it's so difficult isn't it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0007">and it er you have to know someone in there who who kind of just goes oh put this guy in</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0007">and that's what happened to me when I was at TEAMtalk <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I was up there and did the two weeks <pause dur="short"/> and just thought I'll do it just because just obviously get the experience but to enjoy it <pause dur="short"/> and um I had a great time up there <pause dur="short"/> and in the first week er there was a vacancy at Sky for a freelancer <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/> the editor of TEAMtalk said I'm not gonna beat around the bush <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> like there's some <trunc>d</trunc> I've got like twenty CVs here that I've kept from other people but you're here now so this is your chance <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018">brilliant</u>
<u n="95" who="S0007">put you forward</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0007">so I had another two weeks at Sky</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0007">and then they offered me a contract there like as a like a rolling year contract <pause dur="short"/> and um yeah I spent two and a half years up there <pause dur="short"/> and some ways it was um obviously here with David Lloyd er <trunc>g</trunc> gives you all all you could ever want</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0007">working on the bar but but the that gave me a little bit more <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="102" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0007">some of the stuff I got to do I I in <trunc>m</trunc> in my wildest dreams I thought when I was thinking yeah sports journalism would be great <pause dur="short"/> I'd get to er write about the tennis perhaps</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0007">that'd be one of my main sports <pause dur="short"/> I got to write er the match reports in all four Grand Slam finals</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="107" who="S0007">so while I was there so</u>
<u n="108" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="109" who="S0007">then commentary as well <pause dur="short"/> and like a lot of it was text commentary <pause dur="short"/> not a lot of it was um on the radio or anything</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0007">like that <pause dur="short"/> cos they've got er a radio station there <pause dur="short"/> but but I managed to interview a couple of people as well <pause dur="short"/> and went to er a large football match and did a  did a  thing like er minute by minute commentaries</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018">cool <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah the stuff you can get on er</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">the up updates <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018">that's how I watch the Formula One now it's been sold to Sky <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0007">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> are you a big fan of Formula One?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018">I am <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I do like it</u>
<u n="119" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm er I've I've grown to like it <pause dur="short"/> I I there is something about when Sky get it that they kind of try and make it a bit more</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">tut</u>
<u n="121" who="S0007">er er a bit more than it was shall we say</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0007">but</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018">well they've pretty much doubled the amount of races since</u>
<u n="125" who="S0007">since they've took it on <pause dur="short"/> er well they've got all</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">since yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0007">the all the qualifying now and everything</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0007">but yeah so you know the two and a half years up there <pause dur="short"/> some of the other stuff I got to write was was fantastic <pause dur="short"/> the only</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">and you didn't fancy staying up there?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0007">well er the the only downside was was the pay <pause dur="short"/> it was um the the er the contract they had was so binding in in the sense that you couldn't write for another</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0007">journalist company without their permission</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="137" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> you were only paid six pound an hour with no pay rise</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">you're joking?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0007">it was er just rolling or and and the</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">tut</u>
<u n="141" who="S0007">worst bit of it there was no set hours</u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0007">you were contracted to <pause dur="short"/> so you was er as a freelance they could just turn round and and give you one shift a month and that was it</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0007">and when I  when I  first was up there I used my savings to to um finance me being up there <pause dur="short"/> and I was er I at first it was supposed to be just a two-week trial and you know six week went by and I still hadn't been paid <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like well you know what's going on guys? What? You haven't been paid? Oh sorry <pause dur="short"/> and it was kind of like so I'd been just surviving on my my um savings alone <pause dur="short"/> so when I did get my money the money back that that was owed to me I kind of it was still stuff to pay off overdrafts and</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0007">and and what-not <pause dur="short"/> but yeah and and it huh for two and a half years from where I was when I first started which I think was a really raw and kind of untrained</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0007">journalist to being where I was when I  when I  finished working there <pause dur="short"/> er and I was still on the same wage <pause dur="short"/> and it was a bit disheartening cos er</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">crazy <pause dur="short"/> totally <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's</u>
<u n="151" who="S0007">er</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">and also six pounds an hour and not giving you a set number of shifts so you know how much money you're gonna earn</u>
<u n="153" who="S0007">no <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018">the next month and <pause dur="short"/> I've been in that situation with teaching over in Spain <pause dur="short"/> that you</u>
<u n="155" who="S0007">what was that like?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018">depends on how many students they have as to whether you get work the next month</u>
<u n="157" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018">and well er basically that's why I moved back to England <pause dur="short"/> cos I'd just <vocal desc="laugh"/> had it up to here with not knowing if I was gonna be able to make my rent the next month</u>
<u n="159" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0018">never knowing when I'd have holiday</u>
<u n="161" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018">probably wouldn't have get to have a holiday cos I'd have to be working</u>
<u n="163" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018">you know just getting random classes here and there just to</u>
<u n="165" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can relate to that <pause dur="short"/> cos er it</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">make ends meet</u>
<u n="167" who="S0007">from a <trunc>p</trunc> for a point if you wanna do well in a career and like I'd decided er after uni stuff and I loved like I've always loved sport but I loved writing as well <pause dur="short"/> I love the</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0007">the creative aspect <pause dur="short"/> and I love like er when you do the commentaries I used to love the like er you could get banter with with a lot of the the the members er that come on and would read and would give you feedback and</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0007">and you'd build like rapport and like using like things like Twitter <pause dur="short"/> you could build up like a real like kind of <unclear/> reputation for yourself</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it it was er it like that er aspect it was it's character-building obviously not knowing if you're gonna have enough money to <trunc>li</trunc> and then it made me kind of</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0007">be a bit more astute <pause dur="short"/> cos I got a job at er the David Lloyd's up up there <pause dur="short"/> I worked at the York one for a while</u>
<u n="176" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="177" who="S0007">and I worked at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and it kind of added a lot more strings to my bow <pause dur="short"/> and that was er a really good period <pause dur="short"/> but it kind of all hinged on the huh the difference from from cos I've worked here for um this was my first job at this place when I was sixteen <pause dur="short"/> so I'm twenty-five now</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0007">so I kind of worked here when I was studying and</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="181" who="S0007">came back every now and then <pause dur="short"/> and um I was <trunc>al</trunc> always worked on in the er food and beverage department <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and I really got used to that way of of of working <pause dur="short"/> that you are really interactive with members</u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0007">and really social <pause dur="short"/> and at Sky <trunc>y</trunc> you'd think being a journalist you'd have like a lot of people would er would have a lot to say but it was er in especially the Sky Sports area section</u>
<u n="184" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0007">it was very robotic would the word I'd use</u>
<u n="186" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0007">they would um you'd get <trunc>mem</trunc> er <trunc>st</trunc> members of the team that could happily go a whole shift without talking to you <pause dur="short"/> they would just sit on the computer <pause dur="short"/> and it was like an office-based job</u>
<u n="188" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0007">it was my first experience of that <pause dur="short"/> and there was a lot of cliques <pause dur="short"/> and you'd be like as a freelancer you kind of weren't</u>
<u n="190" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0007">respected <pause dur="short"/> you um you would you'd er er kind of hot-desk a lot of people <pause dur="short"/> and a lot of people would then get er er would give you grief about <trunc>u</trunc></u>
<u n="192" who="S0018">what's hot-desking? I've heard this expression before</u>
<u n="193" who="S0007">hot-desking is where you er it would be the you come in <trunc>t</trunc> and er you'd be the far um desks <pause dur="short"/> you'd have one one desk for the editor</u>
<u n="194" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0007">his deputy and then the er and er it was split into two sections <pause dur="short"/> and all sports which er covered everything apart from football <pause dur="short"/> um and then you'd have two more desks where you'd have the all sports team <pause dur="short"/> you'd have a team of about about there were six or seven of them <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and there'd be one spare that could alwaysbe occupied by <trunc>s</trunc> by a freelancer</u>
<u n="196" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="197" who="S0007">but then um you'd want like obviously they'd rotate who'd be on shift <pause dur="short"/> they'd only need probably four each day</u>
<u n="198" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0007">maybe five depending on how much sport time on that desk <pause dur="short"/> so you'd er go on one of theirs</u>
<u n="200" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="201" who="S0007">and you kind of hot-desking is when you can go round on other people's <pause dur="short"/> and some of them would lock their computers overnight knowing that you'd have to turn their computer off <pause dur="short"/> and  and it and  it just it did make the whole process very kind of</u>
<u n="202" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0007">so there was a lot of cliquey stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<u n="204" who="S0018">what a shame</u>
<u n="205" who="S0007">a football desk was even worse to a degree <pause dur="short"/> cos there was a lot more in football <pause dur="short"/> and the football commanded er er er desks of about ten to twelve</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> and and yeah you had to kind of almost er earn your keep <pause dur="short"/> so the first like year er year to eighteen months was kind of me just trying to fit in <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> being from my background of working here I'd always be like kind of really kind of like blow my own trumpet quite bubbly compared to everyone else</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0007">and a bit more personality</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0007">and that sometimes counted against me <pause dur="short"/> and I would never had ever had a er get told off or had er disciplinary action <pause dur="short"/> but I think I had a reputation as being a bit of a a chatter</u>
<u n="212" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> whereas they I think the editors themselves wanted people to come in <trunc>s</trunc> start you do your job</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018">and be robots</u>
<u n="215" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0007">and then that's it <pause dur="short"/> and um I think  I think  it's quite hard to to be <trunc>p</trunc> put your personalities into your work if you're not like that in</u>
<u n="218" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0007">real life as well <pause dur="short"/> er I dunno <pause dur="short"/> some people <trunc>s</trunc> one of the guys who was the best writer by far he was a quieter guy <pause dur="short"/> er er and didn't talk a lot <pause dur="short"/> but when he did talk he was still er as equally as colourful</u>
<u n="220" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0007">as when er his writing was <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so I don't think they got ever got the balance right <pause dur="short"/> but I got from my I think through being there for two and a half years and being one of the most consistent of the freelancers I got offered er a contract <pause dur="short"/> a better contract <pause dur="short"/> to er cover for one of the guys who went on a er just er I'm trying to think what the word is now <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> he basically went travelling for a while</u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="223" who="S0007">I'm <trunc>tr</trunc> er</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">he had a sabbatical</u>
<u n="225" who="S0007">sabbatical <pause dur="short"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0007">and he er</u>
<u n="228" who="S0018">sounds like he's <vocal desc="laugh"/> joining the Church or something doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's right</u>
<u n="230" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0007">and I think he went to Peru for I think four or five months <pause dur="short"/> so I was covering for him</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0007">so I had regular hours <pause dur="short"/> but I still had my job at David Lloyd <pause dur="short"/> and they made it clear that once er this is my chance to impress but once that four months is up I'd go back to the what I was doing before <pause dur="short"/> and back to the freelance and back to the wage <pause dur="short"/> so I wasn't gonna quit my job at the other David Lloyd</u>
<u n="234" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0007">but I was working quite a lot of hours <pause dur="short"/> and you'd you'd work eight and a half hours there and then at David Lloyd you do eight hours <pause dur="short"/> and I did quite a lot of travelling <pause dur="short"/> and basically I was late for two shifts <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and they sat me down <pause dur="short"/> and they were like Elliot we're gonna have to review the whole system <pause dur="short"/> we're <trunc>w</trunc> we're not gonna keep you on as the um on this sabbatical <pause dur="short"/> don't think it's working for us <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like obviously a bit shocked and stunned <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh well kind of er can I explain? And type thing <pause dur="short"/> er well we've we've made the decision <pause dur="short"/> and I was like okay <pause dur="short"/> er and so what about then the freelancing? I'm afraid we're gonna have to let you go</u>
<u n="236" who="S0018">tut</u>
<u n="237" who="S0007">and that was it <pause dur="short"/> it was just like</u>
<u n="238" who="S0018">what a caring environment <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and er <trunc>th</trunc> they used words like oh it's um there's no malice in this</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0007">but but we need to make an example out of you</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> oh no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0007">so I was just like</u>
<u n="244" who="S0018">tut</u>
<u n="245" who="S0007">that that was er quite I was like well do you realize I said like I've been here two and a half years and</u>
<u n="246" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0007">you you've never once brought up me <trunc>b</trunc> er being late <pause dur="short"/> and I'm the type of person that I wouldn't say I'm er punctual wouldn't be the word er one of my first things that come to mind with me <pause dur="short"/> but when I was at Sky er I'd always make sure that I was like first in last out if you will</u>
<u n="248" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> there'd be odd occasions like anything that you're running late and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and the two occasions like the one was I did fifteen days straight from the way David Lloyd works that their their rotas is done Friday to Thursday so</u>
<u n="250" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0007">if they're gonna give you two days off it might not necessarily be like which is what they should do</u>
<u n="252" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="253" who="S0007">it might roll over into a different week</u>
<u n="254" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0007">so when with the way Sky did it it meant that er I was doing one day where I was did fifteen days one  period where I did fifteen days <pause dur="short"/> and it was on the fifteenth day I was put on the early shift <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> with another guy <pause dur="short"/> the editor who's supposed to always be in <pause dur="short"/> and he booked a day off <pause dur="short"/> so it was just me opening <pause dur="short"/> if they'd told me that I er might I don't know if it would've changed anything but I'd always expect him to be in <pause dur="short"/> so it <trunc>t</trunc> turned out that I was the only would would've been the only one opening <trunc>w</trunc> the like the website content for the all sports section <pause dur="short"/> and er the the main editor turned up at eight o'clock when it was supposed to be a seven A M start and was like where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? My landlord who is a <trunc>f</trunc> a full-time member at Sky Sports in the  in the  <trunc>spor</trunc> in the football desk was like I don't know <pause dur="short"/> and he was like calling me and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and I was just completely conked out <pause dur="short"/> woke up <pause dur="short"/> and didn't didn't hear my alarm or anything like that and</u>
<u n="256" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0007">then I got in at half nine <pause dur="short"/> and I got um er a telling off shall we say</u>
<u n="258" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0007">quite a  quite a  severe one <pause dur="short"/> and he was like okay well I'm gonna speak to the rest of the team and talk about mm mm this <pause dur="short"/> er because this er this is the first time I've known of you being late</u>
<u n="260" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> and just get on with your job type thing <pause dur="short"/> I had a day off er um and then another day off and then was back in on the Sunday <pause dur="short"/> and I'd arranged to go and watch a football match back here in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and my train was delayed on er</u>
<u n="262" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="263" who="S0007">like and I  and I  kinda took took the risk <pause dur="short"/> I thought I'll get the train the next day</u>
<u n="264" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> cos I had an open return <pause dur="short"/> and then the next train I got in the morning it would've meant that I would've been literally two minutes late <pause dur="short"/> and I sent an e-mail out saying I I know I'm on kind of on on thin ice here and I just wanna give you a heads up <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna be literally five minutes late</u>
<u n="266" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0007">however <pause dur="short"/> the train itself got got stuck</u>
<u n="268" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0007">and it got delayed by an hour and a half</u>
<u n="270" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Tut</u>
<u n="271" who="S0007">and I er come in to work <pause dur="short"/> and it it wasn't er er like it</u>
<u n="272" who="S0018">uh</u>
<u n="273" who="S0007">wasn't like er the similar situation where I um tut he was relying on me being in</u>
<u n="274" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0007">however <pause dur="short"/> it was just the principle <pause dur="short"/> and  and the  the all sports editor at the time was just like you he was a quite a malicious person <pause dur="short"/> he was just like well I'm sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna have to tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about it <pause dur="short"/> he was like you've you being late again and you better have a good story prepared</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018">tut</u>
<u n="277" who="S0007">and he didn't even tell them what happened <pause dur="short"/> he just told them I was late <pause dur="short"/> he didn't say er</u>
<u n="278" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0007">the situation <pause dur="short"/> so they were almost like okay that's the final straw <pause dur="short"/> done deal <pause dur="short"/> and um he was one of the guys who was in the who was er there was two er the main editor and him <pause dur="short"/> er yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it it was just er it was quite bitter at the time <pause dur="short"/> and it was just such I was so devastated <pause dur="short"/> and I felt like oh it was such a  such a  great opportunity <pause dur="short"/> but I was er always I planned I was gonna do er do five years there <pause dur="short"/> and er I'd still be there now <pause dur="short"/> and I realize some of the things I I've sacrificed</u>
<u n="280" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0007">like just without thinking about it</u>
<u n="282" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0007">like having a disposable income <pause dur="short"/> like I haven't got a great one here at the moment <pause dur="short"/> but still <trunc>m</trunc> much better off than I was there <pause dur="short"/> like I'd literally have enough</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0007">to get by <pause dur="short"/> if not I'd have to kind of</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018">scrape it together</u>
<u n="287" who="S0007">scrape yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And</u>
<u n="289" who="S0007">delay rent and</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">spending your savings</u>
<u n="291" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0007">and so it er it <trunc>w</trunc> while it er it was like a double-edged sword <pause dur="short"/> while it was a great job and some of the things I did there wasn't the working environment there and the</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> that sounds awful <pause dur="short"/> for them not to be <trunc>sens</trunc> sensitive and sympathetic to</u>
<u n="295" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">someone who they employed on a six pound an hour basis</u>
<u n="297" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">and not let them pursue other avenues of</u>
<u n="299" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">employment while working for you that's working for them <pause dur="short"/> pathetic <pause dur="short"/> it really is</u>
<u n="301" who="S0007">well that that's BSkyB and the er that company I I believe</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">that's Rupert Murdoch</u>
<u n="303" who="S0007">yes</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">isn't it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> We don't like Sky then <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0007">no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> so I've still got Sky membership at the moment <pause dur="short"/> well my mum pays it <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0007">if I could I'd change <vocal desc="laugh"/> to Virgin put it that way</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0007">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm er I'm still er since I've come back cos um that was in happened in May last year</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="311" who="S0007">so I'd um and it in that sense it it the time was quite well because I could quickly make a decision to come back here <pause dur="short"/> and I thought still had my jobs at Leeds and York <pause dur="short"/> david Lloyd's <pause dur="short"/> but I thought er huh I <trunc>m</trunc> I may as well come back here <pause dur="short"/> cos I still had <trunc>th</trunc> I was doing one shift a month here as well</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0007">and I thought um it would be so much er huh so much of a better idea to come back home <pause dur="short"/> er I</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0007">I did make good friends up in Leeds but it I always used to come back here once a month anyway</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0007">so I was never felt like I'd I'd lost my ties here as well</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> did you grow up in the area? <unclear/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0007">um I grew up I I'm from originally Chelmsley Wood</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> not the er most glamorous of places but</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0007">er I lived in Yardley as well so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="325" who="S0007">I've and I've I've that's where I'm back at now <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and then one thing is er I I lost my er you er your independence <pause dur="short"/> it's er it's not the same as what it was when I was up there <pause dur="short"/> but I still can be as independent as I like really <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I've got my mum <pause dur="short"/> I live with my mum at the moment <pause dur="short"/> and she's really flexible <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="327" who="S0007">that's good <pause dur="short"/> and obviously I'm having home-cooked dinner <pause dur="short"/> which is er</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0007">which is nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">I hope you cook your mum dinner too <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0007">I did <pause dur="short"/> for Mother's Day</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="333" who="S0007">so</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">er what did you cook her? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0007">er we had a Sunday roast <pause dur="short"/> I did er</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0007">did chicken for her and and chicken and beef actually <pause dur="short"/> we did a bit bit of a combo of the two and yeah er all all the trimmings so</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">lovely</u>
<u n="339" who="S0007">Yorkshire puddings</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">oh so now are you  are you  trying to get back into the</u>
<u n="341" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">journalism side?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0007">well when I as soon as I er came back I I got in touch with all the newspapers <pause dur="short"/> and just just sent er a few e-mails out to see if there's <trunc>anythi</trunc> any like just get a few weeks work experience just again just to see <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0007">that worked well for me last time <pause dur="short"/> offering your service for free and then impressing there <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0007">I had no no feedback again <pause dur="short"/> and it's er <trunc>y</trunc> wait until you know someone who works there</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">it's soul-destroying isn't it?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">sending out all your CV and you know</u>
<u n="353" who="S0007">er <trunc>y</trunc> you almost have to yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">investing a lot of time and effort into it <pause dur="short"/> and then not hearing anything <pause dur="short"/> it's er</u>
<u n="355" who="S0007">but yeah I've looked at other things and other forms of writing like marketing which is another thing I looked at</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> there's a really good graduate scheme at Jaguar and Land Rover</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0007">I applied for <pause dur="short"/> and I got <trunc>t</trunc> through to er the testing stages but okay I didn't  I didn't  fare too well on the  on the  testing <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't feel I I gave a good account of myself and um yeah like I got knocked back on that <pause dur="short"/> but like I've only just started <pause dur="short"/> I'm really I've seen people cos when I quite fortunate when I graduated I I got into that job <pause dur="short"/> and I know er a lot of my friends had to go through probably eighteen months of that kind</u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0007">of applying to graduate scheme after graduate scheme</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0007">you it's you apply for a hundred and hope you get one <pause dur="short"/> and er and you have to have that attitude of the</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0007">the one yes and a hundred and ninety-nine nos is still a yes so <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">that's a good way of looking at it</u>
<u n="367" who="S0007">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> er I try</u>
<u n="368" who="S0018">I'll remember that <vocal desc="laugh"/> when I send out</u>
<u n="369" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0018">my er my CV again</u>
<u n="371" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">this weekend <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0007">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> you sort of <trunc>s</trunc> when you <unclear/> unfortunately I think if you  if you  dwell on the things you like in the current economic crisis you you won't get anywhere <pause dur="short"/> so I think you have to</u>
<u n="374" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="375" who="S0007">try and be ultra-positive and</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0007">you know <pause dur="short"/> like I've I kind of er after er <trunc>th</trunc> three months of doing it I thought well I'm gonna have a little break and  and just  just concentrate on working here <pause dur="short"/> because this is a job as well <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> bar supervisor <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> if I weren't just full-time in the bar I could um afford more time to do things out er outside <pause dur="short"/> and I can just literally come in and do my job <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="378" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0007">a part of me thought no I'd like a new challenge <pause dur="short"/> and perhaps just distance myself <trunc>f</trunc> for six months er away from the journalism to refresh myself</u>
<u n="380" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0007">and and get in cos I I'd worked here for so long and I I <trunc>ca</trunc> really care about this but it almost feels like I'm <unclear/> my second home</u>
<u n="382" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0007">than <unclear/> and</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018">have you thought about manage getting into management here?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0007">I did <pause dur="short"/> and I er er quickly realized that it's not for me</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="387" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0007">even in my supervisor role that um it's just not my I'm not that kind of person <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm I while I <trunc>f</trunc> I like to lead by example I'm struggle with the kind of the man management of people <pause dur="short"/> and I don't like to er I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it's just I you know when you just realize somethings are aren't for you <pause dur="short"/> or or not yet</u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0007">anyway</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">you wouldn't have sacked someone for being late twice</u>
<u n="393" who="S0007">no</u>
<u n="394" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0007">definitely not <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'll I if if I had had their kind of er <trunc>st</trunc> attitude I'd have sacked pretty much everyone here</u>
<u n="396" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0007">er but um</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0007">yeah it so it like er after after thinking and er again with the competitive side of we wanna try and make this this department the best in the country <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>w</trunc> we're still striving for that <pause dur="short"/> but it it's a long  a long  way down the line <pause dur="short"/> I think you need to er be in it for the long haul <pause dur="short"/> like I thought <unclear/> twelve months like if I could literally get us on the the with my manager get us on the the point where we where it almost there and then then I could could go off and do my own thing <pause dur="short"/> but I've realized six months in now it's  it's gonna it's  gonna be like er <unclear/> two or three years <pause dur="short"/> and and I'm not prepared to to</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0007">and <unclear/> wage and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and as much as I love working here it's I <trunc>n</trunc> I need to do I need to be more fulfilled <pause dur="short"/> so I started writing my own blog er a couple of weeks ago</u>
<u n="402" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="403" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018">excellent</u>
<u n="405" who="S0007">blogger Ball <pause dur="short"/> cos my surname's Ball</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0007">er so Blogger Ball</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0007">is the er my URL and and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and er and yeah like I've just er</u>
<u n="410" who="S0018">what are you writing about?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0007">well it is gonna be predominantly sport <pause dur="short"/> I went to</u>
<u n="412" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0007">Anfield last weekend</u>
<u n="414" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> and I did one on my anticipation <pause dur="short"/> first time I went this year and I was so looking forward to it <pause dur="short"/> and and it my next one's gonna be called Anfield anguish <pause dur="short"/> cos we got beat two one so</u>
<u n="416" who="S0018">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0007">but um yeah <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="418" who="S0018">who do you support?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0007">I'm a Liverpool fan</u>
<u n="420" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="421" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I lost to Wigan <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0007">bottom of the league and never beat us at Anfield ever in the history <pause dur="short"/> and and I go and we've</u>
<u n="424" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not not good <pause dur="short"/> but um but yeah like football and tennis are my kind of my <trunc>m</trunc> my main sport <pause dur="short"/> but er I love I've grown to love I went to Cheltenham Festival <pause dur="short"/> um and I I've never been one for horse-racing but</u>
<u n="426" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0007">and I still don't really completely agree with a lot of the ethics in it <pause dur="short"/> but as a  as a  <trunc>s</trunc> a day out and stuff that's really kind of</u>
<u n="428" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0007">broadened my horizon so</u>
<u n="430" who="S0018">what about things like cricket? Are you a fan? Yeah?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0007">big fan of cricket</u>
<u n="432" who="S0018">really? Ah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0018">Cos my a couple of my friends work for the BBC <pause dur="short"/> the Asian Network</u>
<u n="435" who="S0007">okay</u>
<u n="436" who="S0018">and um one er my best friend's brother worked at he got into the Asian Network um as a broadcast journalist <pause dur="short"/> and then he started specializing in sports <pause dur="short"/> and he was working for Five Live</u>
<u n="437" who="S0007">oh okay</u>
<u n="438" who="S0018">and then he went freelance <pause dur="short"/> and he's living in India now <pause dur="short"/> and covering all the big cricket matches and</u>
<u n="439" who="S0007">oh <pause dur="short"/> cos you've got the <trunc>In</trunc> Indian Premier League <pause dur="short"/> which is like er in football terms like the Premier League for us</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0007">premier football <pause dur="short"/> so er it that's where all the big big stars go <pause dur="short"/> so  that's great <pause dur="short"/> is this one of the people who's borrowed your the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0007">Good stuff</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018">that's the one <pause dur="short"/> no but I mean if it would help for you to get in touch with him and chat with him about</u>
<u n="447" who="S0007"><trunc>S</trunc> maybe advice and stuff</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">you know</u>
<u n="449" who="S0007">or yeah yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">advice <pause dur="short"/> contacts <pause dur="short"/> anything</u>
<u n="451" who="S0007">yeah I I well um I've I've never been one to to look a gift horse in the mouth <pause dur="short"/> and like I've managed to speak to like working here and working at Dave Lloyd's generally is is a great place to</u>
<u n="452" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0007">to network and to meet people</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0007">and I've had a lot of people give me some stuff for marketing <pause dur="short"/> but yeah like I know that I er I I think I would be happiest if I was could get back into some kind of er sports journalism based</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0007">but just just to be creative I think for me <pause dur="short"/> and to be writing is er or or to I dunno cos I feel like I never would I dunno I always willing to try anything <pause dur="short"/> like broadcast journalism <pause dur="short"/> print journalism <pause dur="short"/> even like presenting so <pause dur="short"/> but I dunno if there's er a</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0007">market for too many Brummies there that's the only thing</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Aw <pause dur="short"/> come on <pause dur="short"/> your</u>
<u n="461" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well you got well you</u>
<u n="462" who="S0018">dulcet tones of the Brummie accent</u>
<u n="463" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">well no presenting would be cool surely?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0007">well one of the guys I used to work with as well and <trunc>s</trunc> he was in the Sky Sports News Radio <pause dur="short"/> and because I was like one of the most outgoing there like you er you'd talk to cos they're they'd be the most outgoing people <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> the people obviously in radio cos that's huh kind of you can't be er muted and and then do your radio show I think <pause dur="short"/> so I'd always</u>
<u n="466" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0007">talk to them and we'd have like the the coffee  and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> and one and I saw um a couple of weeks ago he's now on Sky Sport News on the telly</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="469" who="S0007">so I was just like fantastic for him <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">that's great <pause dur="short"/> but you um you're not gonna <trunc>s</trunc> touch Sky with a barge-pole ever again?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> no I I'm never one to to really hold a  hold a  grudge</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0007">er but er they'd have to pay me well put it that way <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Compensate me for</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018">how about contacting him and see if he's made any contacts that you could use?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0007">that's an idea</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">it's always</u>
<u n="477" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">you know it's always um I <trunc>f</trunc> I found especially in Spain that it's always more who you know</u>
<u n="479" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">and the contacts that they know than</u>
<u n="481" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> like I for me like I have felt like um a good break from from doing it <trunc>h</trunc> has kind of I  I just  just write my blog <pause dur="short"/> I just felt like a bit more didn't huh er like it might be er melodramatic bit more alive again <pause dur="short"/> I just feel like I'm back to me again</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0007">being being creative <pause dur="short"/> so while I thought it was good to take a break out <pause dur="short"/> I feel perhaps now I'm just thinking oh why didn't I carry on? I <trunc>j</trunc> probably might've been a bit happier <pause dur="short"/> cos it's been quite a tough six months as well being back here <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> I know the feeling <pause dur="short"/> moving back</u>
<u n="487" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">home <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0007">how's it for you then? How are you finding it?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0007">well er with the weather like this</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">I know</u>
<u n="493" who="S0007">I suppose it's not too bad</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">the <trunc>wea</trunc> when the weather's like this it's gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> it's no <trunc>pro</trunc> there's no problem  <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it's the lack of er dependable income <pause dur="short"/> and not you know <trunc>y</trunc> you're enjoying socializing for example but then you're always thinking fff</u>
<u n="495" who="S0007">should I be out?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">oh I should get home</u>
<u n="497" who="S0007">shall I try this but yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">write my CVs</u>
<u n="499" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">I should be doing this <pause dur="short"/> I should be doing that <pause dur="short"/> have I really got the money to spend on a meal out? Or and it yeah it's</u>
<u n="501" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd like the</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018">but</u>
<u n="503" who="S0007">the time that comes when I've I'm I don't have to think about that <pause dur="short"/> but I always said that I wanted to have a a career that I enjoy and that I don't <trunc>m</trunc> I've never been a money motivated person until</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="505" who="S0007">recently</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018">me either <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="507" who="S0007">so um did you say you lived in Barcelona?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0007">Cos my my girlfriend she's <trunc>sh</trunc> pretty much she doesn't say she's fluent in Spanish but for</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="511" who="S0007">for my opinion I think she's really good um like <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0007">we're talking about going to Barcelona for like a little get-away and</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="515" who="S0007">I've never been  I've I've never been  to mainland Spain so I'd love to</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0007">to check that out</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">do it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0007">have you been anywhere else in Spain?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I lived in Barcelona for eight years <pause dur="short"/> and Murcia for six years <pause dur="short"/> murcia's down south near</u>
<u n="521" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">Alicante</u>
<u n="523" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">but Barcelona's definitely a fantastic place to visit</u>
<u n="525" who="S0007">oh huh</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'd love to go there <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>s</trunc> I suppose you might know <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> cos Danielle my girlfriend she wants to start doing Spanish classes</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="529" who="S0007">do you know anywhere here around like locally or?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> locally? <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> the Brasshouse</u>
<u n="531" who="S0007">brasshouse?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they do language classes</u>
<u n="533" who="S0007">okay</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">and um at the <trunc>Birm</trunc> er <anon type="place"/> University in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> where does she live?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0007">mm <pause dur="short"/> she she lives over <anon type="place"/> way so er</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">is that  is that  north-east?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0007">it's <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">it is isn't it</u>
<u n="539" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">kind of out past <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not too far from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> er it's by er do you know Erdington?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0007">or do know?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="545" who="S0007">near there</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so er</u>
<u n="547" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">Edgbaston's probably a bit too far for her isn't it</u>
<u n="549" who="S0007">or maybe somewhere if there's like the <trunc>cent</trunc> is er Brasshouse in the city centre?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> does she want  does she want  a course?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0007">like well she she wanted ideally something that we could both go to <pause dur="short"/> but I was like well we're at <trunc>com</trunc> I'm know no Spanish virtually</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0007">like um s or er I dunno that's about it to <vocal desc="laugh"/> be fair</u>
<u n="554" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0007">but um yeah she's obviously a lot she did it for seven years <pause dur="short"/> and she got an A in her A-level <pause dur="short"/> but do you think that like there are classes you could go to that could cater for all? Or is it kind of a bit?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> er <trunc>pr</trunc> probably</u>
<u n="557" who="S0007">Cos I just thought er wouldn't it be a bit <trunc>b</trunc></u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">conversation</u>
<u n="559" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">class <pause dur="short"/> but even conversation class <trunc>m</trunc> classes might be streamed</u>
<u n="561" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">has she spoken it at all over the past seven years?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0007">well yeah like and she's er up until a couple of years ago she was doing it like for her A-levels</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="565" who="S0007">so yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">she did it for seven years <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="567" who="S0007">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> seven</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">I thought you said she hadn't hadn't done it for</u>
<u n="569" who="S0007">no no</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">seven</u>
<u n="571" who="S0007">yeah yeah so er er been doing it for seven years</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she'll be at er probably quite an intermediate level <pause dur="short"/> and you're basic</u>
<u n="573" who="S0007">novice</u>
<u n="574" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You're like</u>
<u n="575" who="S0007">amateur</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018">goal</u>
<u n="577" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0018">I can say goal <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0007">I was gonna say any words I probably know is from football-based things so</u>
<u n="581" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Corner <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> then again <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you if she got private classes or something and you found an accommodating teacher who would like let you get along with stuff on the side</u>
<u n="584" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0018">while she was doing her main lessons <pause dur="short"/> and you maybe listening to it <pause dur="short"/> you'd pick up stuff and</u>
<u n="586" who="S0007">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> perhaps</u>
<u n="587" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="588" who="S0007">that'd be good</u>
<u n="589" who="S0018">you er seem to be you seem to possess all the characteristics of a good language learner <pause dur="short"/> it's like</u>
<u n="590" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="591" who="S0018">you know <pause dur="short"/> you're not afraid to talk and</u>
<u n="592" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0007">well maybe that's true</u>
<u n="594" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's er a a lot of the time it's not having the confidence to speak that inhibits you when you're first learning <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you've got a good memory and you do a bit of studying at home there's no reason why you couldn't at least you know</u>
<u n="595" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0018">be there when she was having a class</u>
<u n="597" who="S0007">no <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="598" who="S0018">I've got a friend who works at <anon type="place"/> City University <pause dur="short"/> she's um tut half Spanish half Polish <pause dur="short"/> and she's married to a Spaniard</u>
<u n="599" who="S0007">oh right</u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">um yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0007">so <trunc>sh</trunc> I guess she speak can speak quite a lot of languages then</u>
<u n="602" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she speaks fluent Spanish <pause dur="short"/> fluent English <pause dur="short"/> fluent Polish I imagine <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Being a native <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but yeah no if you're interested in a private class then</u>
<u n="603" who="S0007">yeah well I'll cos I've</u>
<u n="604" who="S0018">I can ask her or</u>
<u n="605" who="S0007">we said at the start yeah this is something we can do <pause dur="short"/> and I know that we've been putting it off <pause dur="short"/> so I just would like to kind of get the ball rolling for her really so she can er <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so perhaps if um I'll have a chat with her and see er what what <trunc>sh</trunc> what ideas she have <pause dur="short"/> if she'd rather do um something that we can both do <pause dur="short"/> the er emphasis or whoever it's about her keeping up the Spanish <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm happy to like I say if it it'd be sitting in and just just learning bits and bobs and just trying to have a a grounding of it</u>
<u n="606" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0007">whereas if she wants to be able to keep it and really use it <pause dur="short"/> cos I just think it is like one thing I regret was <trunc>n</trunc> and <trunc>s</trunc> I think's perhaps something to do largely with um the curriculum is just the the languages er and how early we we learn <pause dur="short"/> cos I started didn't learn er er a <trunc>f</trunc> foreign language until I was twelve <pause dur="short"/> and I did <trunc>l</trunc> I loved learning German and</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="609" who="S0007">it was great <pause dur="short"/> and like I really like embraced it and at first it was just like doing the accents</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0007">like to be a laugh</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0007">but but it was like <trunc>sh</trunc> my German teacher would go no good</u>
<u n="614" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0007">and all this</u>
<u n="616" who="S0018">that is good <pause dur="short"/> ja</u>
<u n="617" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0007">so we'd all like all have really get like get into it that way <pause dur="short"/> and yeah like I'd I'd I'd er happy like <pause dur="short"/> cos I'd love to have have learnt like like one thing is is I remember er it always sticks with me within my mind when I <trunc>w</trunc> used to</u>
<u n="620" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0007">work in when I was like sixteen seventeen got to know a couple of members <pause dur="short"/> um both er foreign and they both came here to <trunc>st</trunc> er to teach</u>
<u n="622" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0007">one to teach French <pause dur="short"/> the other to teach Italian <pause dur="short"/> one was French and one was Italian <pause dur="short"/> and their kids grew up here <pause dur="short"/> and they were all doing some drinks at the bar <pause dur="short"/> and um er the one child I think started to say something in Italian <pause dur="short"/> and he responded in English <pause dur="short"/> and then the mother <trunc>s</trunc> responded in French <pause dur="short"/> and they were all having</u>
<u n="624" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0007">like a three-way conversation with all in different languages <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought that is just so impressive</u>
<u n="626" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0007">and that was one of the first things when I met er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that really kind of made me like ah you can speak another language? Excellent</u>
<u n="628" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0007">but um</u>
<u n="630" who="S0018">what does she do?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0007">she's at the moment she's studying fashion and retail management</u>
<u n="632" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="633" who="S0007">at <anon type="place"/> Uni</u>
<u n="634" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> which one? Which uni?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0007">er the the one at the <anon type="place"/> I think</u>
<u n="636" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="637" who="S0007">the er College of Art I think it is <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="638" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> bIAD?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0007">I think it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that er</u>
<u n="640" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> I work there in the summers</u>
<u n="641" who="S0007">ah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0007">excellent</u>
<u n="644" who="S0018">is she doing er an undergrad</u>
<u n="645" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0018">degree?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0007">undergrad degree at the moment</u>
<u n="648" who="S0018">ah okay</u>
<u n="649" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0018">she's probably on the course with a lot of the Chinese students that I teach in the summer <pause dur="short"/> cos I have to prepare them er in like academic study <pause dur="short"/> like er study skills and</u>
<u n="651" who="S0007">oh okay</u>
<u n="652" who="S0018">make sure their English is brushed up for them to start in September <unclear/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0007">are you er do you speak any Chinese or <trunc>s</trunc>?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="655" who="S0007">I was gonna say</u>
<u n="656" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0007">I was thinking then you you</u>
<u n="658" who="S0018">nothing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0007">I er what language you <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> Spanish obviously</u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">spanish <pause dur="short"/> french <pause dur="short"/> english <pause dur="short"/> and a bit of Catalan <pause dur="short"/> which is the language they use in Barcelona</u>
<u n="661" who="S0007">oh so from Barcelona <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="663" who="S0007">see I think that's just cos I think for a lot of English people it's like we don't I think the perception is that we don't think that we need to learn another language really <unclear/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0007">which is a shame</u>
<u n="666" who="S0018">it is</u>
<u n="667" who="S0007">but</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">people are very imperialistic about speaking languages <pause dur="short"/> even my parents who are very communicative sympathetic people you know they go abroad and they <vocal desc="laugh"/> turn into these English</u>
<u n="669" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>im</trunc> er English <vocal desc="laugh"/> imperialists</u>
<u n="671" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0018">and my dad's favourite is scusi scusi</u>
<u n="673" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0018">I don't know what language he thinks it comes from but</u>
<u n="675" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">he just kind of</u>
<u n="677" who="S0007">it's a generic one just to get attention</u>
<u n="678" who="S0018">er oh no</u>
<u n="679" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0007">oh no <pause dur="short"/> but that's er that's something <pause dur="short"/> but yeah like er she doing er fashion retail management and</u>
<u n="682" who="S0018">fashion and retail management? mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm just trying to think of <pause dur="short"/> fashion design? Or fashion fashion and retail management?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0007">I think it's I er I think it's just one course <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's like a split up of of two</u>
<u n="684" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="685" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> but like for instance at the moment she's doing um a project on three different trends that that they've been given <pause dur="short"/> that that are actual trends that are apparently coming in the next</u>
<u n="686" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0007">next season <pause dur="short"/> and they've gotta do like a board for it and then a presentation and then an essay <pause dur="short"/> and then they've gotta do like er she did one on ASOS as well <pause dur="short"/> where she had to do the whole marketing side of it</u>
<u n="688" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0007">so it's really</u>
<u n="690" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0007">kind of prepping them for that <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="692" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> bIAD is fantastic for you know um vocational type</u>
<u n="693" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0018">training</u>
<u n="695" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0018">I've got a friend there at the moment <pause dur="short"/> she's doing a masters in product design management</u>
<u n="697" who="S0007">okay</u>
<u n="698" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0007">Cos they all sound like er  like er  they could be so</u>
<u n="700" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0007">open-ended couldn't they <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="702" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0007">whereas like not for me like when people said er you can do a degree in sports journalism?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0007">like but they do they can be so specific as well <pause dur="short"/> and um yeah like and she she loves that <pause dur="short"/> and I think <trunc>p</trunc> but she um she's always <trunc>t</trunc> she works as well at um NARS Cosmetics</u>
<u n="706" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="707" who="S0007">in there's a  there's a  <trunc>st</trunc> a stall they've got in in the Bullring in Selfridges <pause dur="short"/> and I think she absolutely loves that <pause dur="short"/> and she's more</u>
<u n="708" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0007">loves loves the beauty side of things <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>sh</trunc> fashion is is um she loves fashion but I think as a profession I think she likes to do the beauty side more <pause dur="short"/> so she's got aspirations to to perhaps</u>
<u n="710" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="711" who="S0007">go down to London and and and like either do like cos she she's someone as well who's quite um</u>
<u n="712" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="713" who="S0007">tut media savvy er and and can write as well</u>
<u n="714" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="715" who="S0007">so um when we er had our our first date we talked about like what our dream job would be <pause dur="short"/> and we'd be like I'd be like an editor of er a successful sport website or something <pause dur="short"/> and she was like oh I'd be an editor of a  of a  magazine <pause dur="short"/> either a fashion or a beauty fashion magazine <pause dur="short"/> so we both kind of we got similar</u>
<u n="716" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="717" who="S0007">er career paths</u>
<u n="718" who="S0018">how about starting a starting up a magazine for sports people who want to be beautiful?</u>
<u n="719" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0007">er the the we talked about that <pause dur="short"/> that's what we we er we come up with on the er <vocal desc="laugh"/> after the end of the first date <pause dur="short"/> so we said well <trunc>w</trunc> why don't we combine them?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0007">we'll have like in one half have yours</u>
<u n="723" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0007">and then the second half and and <trunc>w</trunc> and we'll er</u>
<u n="725" who="S0018">how to be beautiful on the tennis courts</u>
<u n="726" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0007">that's it <pause dur="short"/> your skin'll look great while you hit an ace</u>
<u n="730" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0018">there you go <pause dur="short"/> what with um the press slating what's her face? Stella McCartney</u>
<u n="732" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0018">for</u>
<u n="734" who="S0007">that's right</u>
<u n="735" who="S0018">the design of her sports was it I can't <trunc>reme</trunc></u>
<u n="736" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0018">for the Olympics?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0007">it's er all the for the Olympics <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="739" who="S0018">the uniform</u>
<u n="740" who="S0007">you've got mixed reviews <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> some people were er</u>
<u n="741" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0007"><unclear/> were very er <unclear/></u>
<u n="743" who="S0018">I just can't believe how skimpy the female</u>
<u n="744" who="S0007">yeah like and</u>
<u n="745" who="S0018">uniforms are getting</u>
<u n="746" who="S0007">er and <trunc>t</trunc> some of it as well it doesn't even look like it represents Britain <pause dur="short"/> I just think</u>
<u n="747" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="748" who="S0007">it's not you er you gotta have the colours that we that that makes up the er the the flag <pause dur="short"/> and I thought oh</u>
<u n="749" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> apparently there wasn't enough red on</u>
<u n="750" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0018">her uniforms</u>
<u n="752" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="753" who="S0018">what do you call the <trunc>u</trunc> wouldn't be a uniform would it? The the</u>
<u n="754" who="S0007">um on the</u>
<u n="755" who="S0018">gear</u>
<u n="756" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Sports gear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0007">apparel or  apparel or</u>
<u n="759" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="760" who="S0007">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> there's er um</u>
<u n="761" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But yeah apparently er red is psychologically helpful as well because it puts the enemy off</u>
<u n="762" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0018"><trunc>Com</trunc> opponent <pause dur="short"/> not the enemy <pause dur="short"/> it's not a war</u>
<u n="764" who="S0007">well er</u>
<u n="765" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0007">no as I say you are getting into journalistic terms there</u>
<u n="767" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="768" who="S0007">that's what <vocal desc="laugh"/> we'd do</u>
<u n="769" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0007">we'd try and er dramatic</u>
<u n="771" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like er all of my journalist friends all er all the time they're like terrorists or freedom fighters?</u>
<u n="772" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0007">huh</u>
<u n="774" who="S0018">choose your words carefully <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0018">and where did you meet?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> we met it was funnily enough the <trunc>l</trunc> the last time er I <trunc>c</trunc> when I came back and I went</u>
<u n="778" who="S0018">it wasn't David Lloyd was it?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0007"><trunc>w</trunc> we were on a David Lloyd night out</u>
<u n="780" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="781" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> er but I just met her randomly in a a club we went to <pause dur="short"/> um a place called Bushwhackers <pause dur="short"/> which is open <trunc>ridiculou</trunc> have you been?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="783" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="784" who="S0018">but I've got a friend who</u>
<u n="785" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0018">lives opposite</u>
<u n="787" who="S0007">where it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0018">and er it opens at two P two A M</u>
<u n="789" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0018">or something <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0007">that's right <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and one of her friends who she works with um</u>
<u n="792" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0007">runs the VIP section <pause dur="short"/> so she got in there <pause dur="short"/> and I er was out with a lot of the guys here <pause dur="short"/> and it was like a gym night out <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="794" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="795" who="S0007">traditionally the gym staff er go out and they drink quite early and they can't handle their drink</u>
<u n="796" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> and then they go home early <pause dur="short"/> and me being the a university graduate and</u>
<u n="798" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0007"><trunc>si</trunc> six years up in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so I I could I'm er drink them under the table shall we say</u>
<u n="800" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0007">and um only one guy who was a member here er he he was the <trunc>la</trunc> last guy to stay out <pause dur="short"/> and he was just like we'll just we'll stay out</u>
<u n="802" who="S0018">last guy standing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="803" who="S0007">yeah with me <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And um I was just kind of like I don't really wanna go <pause dur="short"/> and it was like er it was two o'clock and we were or about half two cos they literally we went in and when it opened and they had one drink and they were all ready to go <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like you just paid ten pounds to get in <pause dur="short"/> like well you <trunc>sh</trunc> you may as well stay for another</u>
<u n="804" who="S0018">you have to pay to get in as well?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0007">A tenner <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="806" who="S0018">is it er so what is it?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0007">so it's like er</u>
<u n="808" who="S0018">it's just a bar?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0007">it's not a bar it's er it it is big enough <pause dur="short"/> it's not a club but it's like kind of these <trunc>cr</trunc> hybrid these cross betweens</u>
<u n="810" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="811" who="S0007">that's like it's big enough to have well they've got a dance floor and they've got an outdoor area <pause dur="short"/> and it's VIP <pause dur="short"/> but it's not like a <trunc>b</trunc> a big club <pause dur="short"/> and it they do <trunc>ma</trunc> try and make it quite exclusive</u>
<u n="812" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="813" who="S0007">but yeah so I'm with this guy and the <trunc>g</trunc> the member's fairly um affluent <pause dur="short"/> and he we weren't on the VIP guestlist but he knew <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mate <pause dur="short"/> and um he but he just said just like do what I do <pause dur="short"/> so we just kind of both went like that and just got into VIP</u>
<u n="814" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0007">and we were sitting down and he it he being er he wasn't obviously afraid to to go and say hello to er <trunc>s</trunc> a group of attractive girls <pause dur="short"/> whereas I was kind of a bit like</u>
<u n="816" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="817" who="S0007">mm yes um <pause dur="short"/> and I thought I my experience of VIP is quite um tut snobby shall we say <pause dur="short"/> and er  and er er  kind of it's not about like when you said not not who you are it's what you own perhaps</u>
<u n="818" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="819" who="S0007">so I kind of made that presumption <pause dur="short"/> so I was kind of like okay we'll go in there and but I'm not really in my comfort zone right now</u>
<u n="820" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0007">and then he go over there chatting to them and he calls me over <pause dur="short"/> and I I <trunc>s</trunc> sit next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> first</u>
<u n="822" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="823" who="S0007">and just introduced myself <pause dur="short"/> and I was just a bit like oh my God this is gonna be a</u>
<u n="824" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0007">bit of an awkward conversation</u>
<u n="826" who="S0018">painful <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then when ten minutes later we're doing Borat impressions and</u>
<u n="828" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0007">having a right laugh and and just messing around so <pause dur="short"/> and it just like just kind of grew from there really <pause dur="short"/> and I was still <trunc>st</trunc> I was up in <anon type="place"/> for another two months and um two to three months <pause dur="short"/> but yeah just we got to know each other and then had out first proper date when I came back in er in June <pause dur="short"/> and and yeah like we were talking about our own magazine and</u>
<u n="830" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0007">stuff like that as a joke <pause dur="short"/> and yeah like we've been together now nine months so</u>
<u n="832" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> super <pause dur="short"/> that must've made it easier to move back <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0007">yeah I think that was a definite um</u>
<u n="834" who="S0018">pull <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="835" who="S0007"><trunc>p</trunc> pull factor yes <pause dur="short"/> er so</u>
<u n="836" who="S0018">sorry not that I'm saying that you pulled her but yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0007">no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0018">pull factor to get you back to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0007">yes</u>
<u n="840" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no definitely</u>
<u n="842" who="S0018">cool <pause dur="short"/> and have you been back to Bushwhackers since?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0007">I have had one more night back there and</u>
<u n="844" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0007">to er to reminisce <pause dur="short"/> danielle wasn't there unfortunately <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I was er a <trunc>bi</trunc> a bit drunker that night actually</u>
<u n="846" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="847" who="S0007">so I wasn't as on as er last man standing shall we say <pause dur="short"/> I was</u>
<u n="848" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="849" who="S0007">probably first first faller <vocal desc="laugh"/> that time <pause dur="short"/> so um yeah that's good</u>
<u n="850" who="S0018">you joined the gym</u>
<u n="851" who="S0007">yeah I've er perhaps</u>
<u n="852" who="S0018">the gym staff</u>
<u n="853" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've I've come down to their level unfortunately</u>
<u n="854" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So are they are the different er <trunc>div</trunc> departments within</u>
<u n="855" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>l</trunc></u>
<u n="856" who="S0018">the sports centre like you er do they have different stereotypes? So the people who work in the gym can't drink and the <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0007">that's yeah that's a a <trunc>c</trunc> general consensus for them <pause dur="short"/> you'd probably say the tennis guys in some ways but um cos I'm thinking of going down you know being a tennis coach</u>
<u n="858" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0007">if I'm staying here <pause dur="short"/> I'll start doing um  But I think the view of tennis coaches is they're they perhaps earn the most money like in terms of er er hourly rate if you will <pause dur="short"/> but they're the tightest</u>
<u n="860" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> and then you've got the er F and B team which were were er described as the the louts</u>
<u n="862" who="S0018">is that food and beverage?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> food and beverage</u>
<u n="864" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Are you a lout? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="865" who="S0007">mm <pause dur="short"/> apparently <pause dur="short"/> or or the <trunc>w</trunc> the the party animals</u>
<u n="866" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="867" who="S0007">as well as reception <pause dur="short"/> I think reception get get the similar tag</u>
<u n="868" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="869" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying to think of other departments we've got <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0018">and are the management here are they quite um</u>
<u n="871" who="S0007">sociable?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0018">er</u>
<u n="873" who="S0007">were you gonna say or?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0018">accessible and</u>
<u n="875" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0018">communicative?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0007">I'd say <trunc>c</trunc> <trunc>c</trunc> communication here it's it's a bit of a funny one <pause dur="short"/> in some ways very good</u>
<u n="878" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="879" who="S0007">but in some ways very very poor <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="880" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="881" who="S0007">cos I've had an experience of working at other David Lloyd's</u>
<u n="882" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="883" who="S0007">there's um tut I <trunc>d</trunc> I dunno just er not not an elitist view but there's <trunc>w</trunc> er er huh how to describe it? Like er a lot of people are quite sure of themselves in a certain position shall we say <pause dur="short"/> but then they don't back up with with what not a lot gets</u>
<u n="884" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="885" who="S0007">done here <pause dur="short"/> and and I have noticed as well like we have a tough crowd in in the members here <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot like a lot of people we er we're trying to sell the <trunc>r</trunc> er the rackets dinner dance</u>
<u n="886" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="887" who="S0007">it's an annual event we have <pause dur="short"/> and it's normally one of our big especially food and beverage it's our marquee event <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> er er there was a time cos obviously I've <trunc>d</trunc> been here many years <pause dur="short"/> we used to get a hundred plus <pause dur="short"/> but er it it it's decreased over the years <pause dur="short"/> um at the moment we're only on sixty <pause dur="short"/> and we we need eighty really <pause dur="short"/> but you talk to a lot of members and er they'll they'll find anything to say why they shouldn't come</u>
<u n="888" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="889" who="S0007">but then they do turn up as well</u>
<u n="890" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="891" who="S0007">so it's kind of I think people like to just have their say cos they can if you will</u>
<u n="892" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="893" who="S0007">um but then er it's not really helped that I don't think the management here are that proactive either so <pause dur="short"/> that was another thing for me what I've realized I don't</u>
<u n="894" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="895" who="S0007">doing a managementrole <trunc>h</trunc> at this club specific is for me</u>
<u n="896" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0007">Cos I just don't think er I'm joining in good company <pause dur="short"/> and it's not the right</u>
<u n="898" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="899" who="S0007">atmosphere <pause dur="short"/> where when I was at York er and I went back up there last month to see um see a few friends and stuff I know straight away it'd be so I feel like I'd I'd get more done <pause dur="short"/> and I'd feel</u>
<u n="900" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="901" who="S0007">better about my job so <pause dur="short"/> I don't really get the job satisfaction I was hoping for here so</u>
<u n="902" who="S0018">tut aw</u>
<u n="903" who="S0007">which is a shame <pause dur="short"/> but I still I try and focus on the things I love like like serving er tut er huh trying to think what your mum drinks <pause dur="short"/> she has er sometimes has a latte <pause dur="short"/> and she'll have um</u>
<u n="904" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Does she still have it with soya milk?</u>
<u n="905" who="S0007"><trunc>s</trunc> soya milk</u>
<u n="906" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="907" who="S0007">I was gonna say yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0007">sometimes <trunc>de</trunc> er decaf as well and</u>
<u n="910" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="911" who="S0007">um your mum's very <trunc>ver</trunc> er very um what's the word?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0018">Fizzy <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="913" who="S0007">no no no no no <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say cos er <trunc>y</trunc> clever was the or um resourceful <pause dur="short"/> she <trunc>s</trunc> spotted a few things on the kid's menu that looked oh that looks nice um er rather than pay over the odds on an adult's one</u>
<u n="914" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0007">I probably won't eat all of I'll just get a kid's menu menu one and</u>
<u n="916" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0007">a few times before I realized it was for your mum <pause dur="short"/> I'd bring kid's cutlery <vocal desc="laugh"/> over</u>
<u n="918" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="919" who="S0007">here go you <pause dur="short"/> and she was going oh I'll eat it with the kid's ones and stuff like that</u>
<u n="920" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0007">so</u>
<u n="922" who="S0018">well she is little enough to</u>
<u n="923" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="924" who="S0018">she was a sports teacher <pause dur="short"/> and she used to buy you know all her track suits and shell suits in</u>
<u n="925" who="S0007">like the kid's sizes</u>
<u n="926" who="S0018">kiddies' departments</u>
<u n="927" who="S0007">really?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0007">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="930" who="S0018">you don't have to pay VAT on them either <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0007">oh excellent</u>
<u n="932" who="S0018">then again I can't talk</u>
<u n="933" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="934" who="S0018">I only surpass her by one inch I think</u>
<u n="935" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="936" who="S0007">excellent</u>
<u n="937" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So what shift are you working at the moment?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0007">today? Well I'm done now <pause dur="short"/> done for the day <pause dur="short"/> I'm did an early <pause dur="short"/> I've I've must have annoyed my manager cos she's put me on some horrible run of shifts now</u>
<u n="939" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="940" who="S0007">I'm doing six days straight <pause dur="short"/> and we've got the rackets dinner dance Friday <pause dur="short"/> the big event <pause dur="short"/> that's a long shift that <pause dur="short"/> that'll be three till two in the morning</u>
<u n="941" who="S0018">three o'clock till two in the morning? Woo</u>
<u n="942" who="S0007">and I'm I'm manager that day <pause dur="short"/> so I'm last one in er last one out rather</u>
<u n="943" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="944" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> I've done did a late last night <pause dur="short"/> managed a late so I finished at midnight <pause dur="short"/> I have to be back in today for seven</u>
<u n="945" who="S0018">oof <pause dur="short"/> is it worth going home?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0007">er</u>
<u n="947" who="S0018">you could've just laid out on one of the</u>
<u n="948" who="S0007">er well I wish I did <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0018">sun-chairs <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0007">last <trunc>t</trunc> my dad lives locally here <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> he's only like I cycle to work so it's only like a twenty minute cycle in</u>
<u n="953" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh where does he live?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> lives near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="955" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0007">do you know where er near the Greville Pub?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="958" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0018">I know that area</u>
<u n="960" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he lives just just um er er <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="961" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="962" who="S0007">so it's not too far</u>
<u n="963" who="S0018">that's where I'm learning to drive at the moment <pause dur="short"/> my driving instructor takes me all round there <unclear/></u>
<u n="964" who="S0007">oh are you learning to drive?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="966" who="S0007">you see I'm I don't cos I don't drive yet at the moment</u>
<u n="967" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="968" who="S0007">I've <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> I couldn't afford it when I was up in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="969" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="970" who="S0007">so that's one thing that I'm <trunc>s</trunc> I'm starting <pause dur="short"/> got my provisional again now</u>
<u n="971" who="S0018">cool <pause dur="short"/> well I can <trunc>re</trunc> er recommend a brilliant um instructor</u>
<u n="972" who="S0007">really?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0018">he's super <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's such a nice guy <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="974" who="S0007">okay</u>
<u n="975" who="S0018">I'm sure you'd</u>
<u n="976" who="S0007">I'm definitely er going for that <pause dur="short"/> I've been waiting for someone to recommend a good one to me</u>
<u n="977" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="979" who="S0018">oh brilliant then <pause dur="short"/> he only lives up <anon type="place"/> as well I think</u>
<u n="980" who="S0007">oh wonderful</u>
<u n="981" who="S0018">just opposite um where the old gasworks used to be</u>
<u n="982" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="983" who="S0018">you know the mill pool?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's right</u>
<u n="985" who="S0018">I think he lives down there <pause dur="short"/> but no he's a lovely guy <pause dur="short"/> he used to be a builder and er he's a real kind of like Brummie Brummie kid <pause dur="short"/> brummie ain't it</u>
<u n="986" who="S0007">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0018">and his two daughters play football <pause dur="short"/> and he takes them out playing football every weekend <pause dur="short"/> and he's</u>
<u n="988" who="S0007">oh wonderful</u>
<u n="989" who="S0018">he's a really nice guy</u>
<u n="990" who="S0007">and how many lessons have you had so far then?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0018">I've had five <pause dur="short"/> five or six</u>
<u n="992" who="S0007">have  have you have  you drove never before?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0018">never</u>
<u n="994" who="S0007">no?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0018">apart from one</u>
<u n="996" who="S0007">wow</u>
<u n="997" who="S0018">time when I um a friend of my brother's was said oh do you want do you wanna have a go then? And so I had a go and I reversed his car into a tree <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And er</u>
<u n="998" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="999" who="S0018">it warped the body of the car so he couldn't open the <trunc>f</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> open the passenger door</u>
<u n="1000" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0007">oh no</u>
<u n="1002" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1003" who="S0018">so yeah no I've never really learnt to drive <pause dur="short"/> cos one as you say I couldn't afford it <pause dur="short"/> um I always preferred to spend my money on going away and</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0018">travelling and</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0007"><trunc>S</trunc> well that's been the thing for me er as well <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>w</trunc> has there</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0007">been any other defining factor or?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0018">no not</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0007">have you never really needed to?</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0018">well no <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I've never really needed to <pause dur="short"/> cos after after university I I moved straight out to Spain <pause dur="short"/> and like living in cities like Barcelona you just don't need you know having a car is a liability</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0018">Cos you you have to pay for it to er pay for a parking tut space for it <pause dur="short"/> and you never really use it <pause dur="short"/> the traffic's so bad in the city that it's easy to catch the er the metro <pause dur="short"/> the underground <pause dur="short"/> which is so convenient</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0018">and</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0007">I can imagine</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0018">a good price <pause dur="short"/> and so no I just never really wanted to learn <pause dur="short"/> and in Spain as well you have to pass the theory exam before you can even get behind a</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0007">A wheel</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0018">a wheel</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0007">I think that's a good idea in some ways</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it is <trunc>c</trunc> although er the that put me off in Spain</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0007">oh okay</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0018">just because I couldn't er <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="1024" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you feel like a bit too much</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0018">well no it's just the motivation really</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0018">if you've got the motivation of knowing that oh I'm actually gonna be learning the skill of driving <pause dur="short"/> that's quite motivating <pause dur="short"/> but then when you  when you  <trunc>h</trunc> sign up <trunc>f</trunc> for a twenty-week course to learn how to drive but you're stuck sat in front of a computer learning how to drive</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0018">it's not as motivating</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0007">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0018">really</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0007">I suppose not</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0018">but</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0007">so why why have you why are you learning to drive now then? Is it just because you're moving back here or <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0018">well it's basically cos I think it's a skill that if I don't use it I'll lose it <pause dur="short"/> if you <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0018">not but if I don't learn now I think it will be more difficult to learn in the future</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0007">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos my dad doesn't drive <pause dur="short"/> and he</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0007"><trunc>tr</trunc> he tried when he was in his forties and he well he claims that he was just unlucky but no I know that it is just he's <trunc>t</trunc> I think he isn't</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0007">he's he's like I say he he'd lost the er appetite to learn stuff</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0007">and I think he just found it a lot more challenging than he would've if he was younger <pause dur="short"/> and I was like I'm never going down that avenue <pause dur="short"/> but then I again I've er it's through I have er I've never really been someone who's I have to learn to drive type thing <pause dur="short"/> and I've always thought well I'm quite happy using other forms of transport and cycling</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0007">it's been fine <pause dur="short"/> but now it's I've grown so restless of</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0007">like I don't mind cycling but for me living in Yardley and trying to get to Danielle's <pause dur="short"/> like tonight for instance I've gotta cycle home from here <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>j</trunc> well jump on train anyway to er to cut out um some traffic and to save er save some time <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> but then I've gotta jump on more trains <pause dur="short"/> and it still means even with a bike I've gotta</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0007">an hour and a half of going back home then going out to Sutton</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the time</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0007">but</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0018">most of er all isn't it <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it  and it  is <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> time's precious isn't it <pause dur="short"/> so it's</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I'm if it what's the name of this guy then? The</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0018">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0007"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> has he got like a does he?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0018">I've got his er mobile number here <pause dur="short"/> I'll give it to you actually <pause dur="short"/> wait there</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0007">I'll see if I've got still got battery</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0018">let's see <pause dur="short"/> oh gosh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thank you <vocal desc="laugh"/> so much for sending me that text this morning</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0007">no I just thought well just</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0018">I thought oo gosh shall I  shall I  send him a text back? He hasn't got much battery <pause dur="short"/> shall I save his battery or? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0007">no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's all good</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0018">let's see <pause dur="short"/> contacts <pause dur="short"/> nuh nuh nuh nuh <pause dur="short"/> I nearly gave you Jake's number then</u>
<u n="1066" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1067" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no he's such a lovely guy <pause dur="short"/> I've um actually cancelled this week's driving lessons cos we did emergency stops and going over a lot of speed bumps last week and I've got a bit of a neck injury</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0007">oh have you?</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0018">from before</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0007">from doing it? Oh right</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0018">no from</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0007">oh from?</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0018">a few  a few  years ago <pause dur="short"/> and it's been setting off my neck again <pause dur="short"/> so I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you mind if we cancel? What's your cancellation policy? Er do I still have to pay? And he was like no <pause dur="short"/> don't worry <pause dur="short"/> no problem <pause dur="short"/> don't you don't have to pay <pause dur="short"/> he's a really nice guy</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0007">that's nice</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0018">okay so it's O seven</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0007">two seconds <pause dur="short"/> o seven</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0018">eight two three</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0007">eight two three</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0018">three three</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0007">three three</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0018">two eight</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0007">two eight</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0018">O four</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0007">O four</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0018">so O seven eight two three three three two eight O four</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0007">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> put</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0018">er <pause dur="short"/> what's his surname? Oo</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0007">for now I'll put <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the driving instructor</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That can be his surname</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0007">so I did er I've had one lesson <pause dur="short"/> and um <unclear/></u>
<u n="1093" who="S0018">how did that go?</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0007">I managed to turn get into second gear and turn constantly turn left</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0007">that's  start <pause dur="short"/> but it was so um kind of random the way it come about <pause dur="short"/> like I was just looking into er</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0018">oh er</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0007">it was just kinda one of these things you know</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0018">that's his card <pause dur="short"/> I've got all my appointments on the back though <pause dur="short"/> but if you wanna look at it</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0007">okay <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0018">so it's I I paid a hundred and seventy quid for ten lessons <pause dur="short"/> so it works out quite cheap</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0007">and that's <trunc>w</trunc> something cos I've I've got a bit of a wager going with one of my friends who said oh he never thinks I'll ever drive</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1104" who="S0007">and and the challenge is to do it by um by the time the Olympics starts</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0007">so I was gonna have ten lessons <pause dur="short"/> that was my plan <pause dur="short"/> and then perhaps do um an intensive course afterwards <pause dur="short"/> cos I <trunc>f</trunc> I feel while if you could do an intensive course and pass straight away <pause dur="short"/> which I <trunc>th</trunc> I I think I could do</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0007">I still think having those ten lessons over a longer period of time</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> would you?</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0007">is better</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0018">would somebody that you know be up for taking you out to practice while you're having lessons?</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0007">er a few of the guys here have as well <pause dur="short"/> they've said they'll do that so</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0018">Cos er I reckon if <trunc>y</trunc> cos some people Darren was saying some people can pass in ten lessons</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0018">if you've got the aptitude for it and</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0007">see that  that if  if I could do that then that'd be great</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0007">rather than do the intensive as well</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0018">maybe you wouldn't even need to do an intensive <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0018">I wanna take more lessons <pause dur="short"/> cos I wanna get quite confident in the car</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0007">Cos I think one thing I've got which would suit me cos I've cycled now for about five years <pause dur="short"/> I've er I've got like kind of I know roads and I know like kind of the the the Highway Code <pause dur="short"/> and I know kind of got that kind of</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0007">instilled upon me cos if if not I'd probably be dead now</u>
<u n="1125" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1126" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you're probably quite good at managing traffic</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0007">but yeah</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0007">um</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0018">that's one thing that freaks me out <pause dur="short"/> I'm fine I'm so confident when I'm the only one on the road <pause dur="short"/> and then as soon as I see a car in the rear-view mirror</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0007">you're just ah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0018">I'm like huh <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> there's a car behind me</u>
<u n="1133" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1134" who="S0007">see I've not had that experience yet</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's called a road</u>
<u n="1136" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1137" who="S0018">there usually is more than one car on the road <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1138" who="S0007">no <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so I've gotta  I've gotta  pass before then as well <pause dur="short"/> and I just think that I'd still be someone who cycles quite a lot</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0007">Cos I I I don't really do a lot of cardio upstairs if I use the gym and I play football as well now <pause dur="short"/> but yeah but <trunc>j</trunc> just cycling it just means</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0007">that <trunc>y</trunc> and I've got it's got like a purpose <pause dur="short"/> I don't feel like I ever <trunc>n</trunc> I have to think I need to  I need to  do more cardio type thing <pause dur="short"/> I only</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0007">have to go up um if I wanna do weights or</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0007">dunno like just get in shape for something then that's all I have to do so</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0018">do you get free membership here?</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0007">you do</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0007">not just for you but for another person as well</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0018">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0007">so my dad's been the beneficiary for the last er nine years so</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0018">oh I bet he's happy that</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0018">he's got you as a son <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> He's like no you don't wanna be a sports journalist son</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0007">yeah er</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0018">you carry on working at David Lloyd <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1158" who="S0007">yeah well he er he's he's he's made sure that I kept sort of keep it <vocal desc="laugh"/> for him as well</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1160" who="S0007">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean er he's well that's the thing like this job it's I don't wanna ever <trunc>s</trunc> feel like I'm ungrateful <pause dur="short"/> cos I am grateful for it <pause dur="short"/> but it's just you know when there comes a point when you think I <trunc>n</trunc> I need to</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0018">it's holding you back</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I need to  I need to  progress now <pause dur="short"/> and I think um once I get my driving underway and er <trunc>th</trunc> er me and Danielle have talked about potentially moving to London <pause dur="short"/> and I'd happily get to start to <trunc>st</trunc> get myself started get a job at a David Lloyd's in London and</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0018">have they got er many down there?</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've got quite a lot actually <pause dur="short"/> and there's there's quite a few <pause dur="short"/> and some of them are really like the top exclusive ones and</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> I imagine you could network like crazy in places like that</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0007">and I I think there's er the head office is near there as well and</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0007">I've never said <trunc>t</trunc> that I I couldn't see myself forging a career <pause dur="short"/> like if I was kind of head of marketing here</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0007">for David Lloyd company <unclear/> or like <trunc>d</trunc> like <unclear/> an impact manager for the food and beverage type thing <pause dur="short"/> and if er part of his team like that that'd be something I'd I'd be interested in so</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0007">so we'll see <pause dur="short"/> but but for now it's just plodding on here <pause dur="short"/> I host the quizzes here</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0018">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1174" who="S0007">so that's why I</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0018">when's that?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0007">so I'm used er do it er every second Thursday and every fourth Thursday <pause dur="short"/> I tried to get your mum to come to the last one but I think she went away to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1178" who="S0007">they went away so um</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1180" who="S0007">we um did A Question of Sport quiz so</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0018">she loves A Question of Sport <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1182" who="S0007">so but when er the er how successful it was we're gonna do a sports quiz now every every month as well</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0007">so we do two a month so</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0018">maybe that's something you should do online</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0007">doing my own like an online</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0007"><trunc>qui</trunc></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0018">you know <pause dur="short"/> like Pagebet and all that <pause dur="short"/> all the betting websites <pause dur="short"/> they're really taking off <pause dur="short"/> bingo</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0018">you could do like Question of Sport <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1192" who="S0007">ah <pause dur="short"/> that's an idea actually</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0007">oh <pause dur="short"/> good stuff</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0018">do you write your own questions?</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0007">I do <pause dur="short"/> not for didn't do it for the Question of Sport one because that was um I managed to find one on the Sport Relief website</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0007">um <pause dur="short"/> but yeah generally I I kind of I use like some um internet sites that some quiz sites and and just kind of tailor the questions to to to the <trunc>b</trunc> members here <pause dur="short"/> cos I they've had a few quizmasters over the years here and I've never thought of myself as being a quizmaster but I just thought well I know what the members would like to see</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0007">and read and like listen out for <pause dur="short"/> so I kind of make it like mentally stimulating</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0018">cool <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1202" who="S0007">so</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0018">have you invented your own catchphrase?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0007">not yet <pause dur="short"/> I'm</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1206" who="S0007">still working on that</u>
<u n="1207" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1208" who="S0007">so er</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You haven't got any er possibles?</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0007">I was just trying to think of something then <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1212" who="S0007">no <pause dur="short"/> really haven't yet <pause dur="short"/> I've I'm I've I think I've er this is I've done seven now er that I've been doing I've of the monthly ones <pause dur="short"/> so I think perhaps this is the er the end zone now where you you kind of hone in your catchphrase</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1214" who="S0007">so I'll have to think of it</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0007">by next month <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1217" who="S0018">and is er <trunc>s</trunc> this something that you proposed to them or that they</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0007">it was er</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0018">kind of?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0007">it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually who who</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0007"><unclear/> he he come up with the idea and I think he run it by <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who er my manager <pause dur="short"/> and she was like oh actually</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1224" who="S0007">and then when I was asked I was like I really don't fancy that <pause dur="short"/> cos er just I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I just didn't</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1226" who="S0007">didn't think it'd be for me <pause dur="short"/> but but I do love it <pause dur="short"/> it's one of the best things I do here</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0007">I think <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0007">mhm</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0018">so is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> your manager?</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0007"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is kind of my opposite in the um tut er upstairs in the  in the  gym</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0007">he's the um lead coach</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0007">so like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s the sports manager and er oversees obviously all those areas <pause dur="short"/> where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like food and beverage <pause dur="short"/> but um yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s kind of my my opposite in that sense so</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0007">but I think er like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> compared to me like he er cos er as a supervisor I'm I'm I'd like to think I'm I'm very lenient <pause dur="short"/> and perhaps they they they take advantage of that <pause dur="short"/> whereas <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they wouldn't dare like take the mick with him</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0018">is he wuh chush?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0007">he no</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0007">he's so friendly and like so like</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0007">personable <pause dur="short"/> but I think he he kind of draws the the line with them <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0018">oh right <pause dur="short"/> it takes a strong personality to be able to do that in a</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0007">mm</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0018">nice</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0018">nice way isn't it</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>s</trunc> I salute him for that</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0018">so where am I going to be able to find <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0007">that is a good question <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? Um have you seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> anywhere?</u>
<u n="1253" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's just doing his one to one with <unclear/></u>
<u n="1254" who="S0007">oh he's in a one to one there so</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0007">there we are <pause dur="short"/> no just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1257" who="S0018">what's a one to one?</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0007">just to sit down and chat about he like that's probably what he's doing now cos the personal trainers are very much like numbers based about how many um clients they get and</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0007">how much money they can bring in <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s role like he's such a good inspirational person <pause dur="short"/> like he'll he will like give them all a lift and give them some good feedback</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> so he's having a one to one with staff</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0007">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0018">and stuff?</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0007">with staff to do that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0018">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> well thanks ever so much</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0007">you're very welcome</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0018">it's been a pleasure chatting with you <pause dur="short"/> and yeah I mean if you want any <trunc>con</trunc> if you want me to get that er the e-mail of my mm best mate's brother to you or?</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0007">I er yeah that absolutely love that <pause dur="short"/> like even if it's just an like I say like a share a conversation and cos I did speak to someone who was um well also worked for Five Live <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0007">when I first started doing my degree <pause dur="short"/> and he gave me some good advice and said about when I was concentrating on my degree basically he was like no try and get your experience <pause dur="short"/> that's the most important thing</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0007">and he er offered to help me out and stuff so <pause dur="short"/> um yeah so</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er so I maybe he could even give you advice about freelancing?</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos that well like if I am gonna go to London um which is what we're planning to do in a couple of years it'll be  it'll be  something that I need to perhaps</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0007">like if I got a job at Dave Lloyd's to start with <pause dur="short"/> maybe doing the tennis coaching <pause dur="short"/> but then to start freelancing <pause dur="short"/> that's how you really get your</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0007">repertoire really and getting your</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0007">reputation so</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0018">or find out where all the the bigwigs in that world train</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0007">er yeah</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0018">and go and find go and get a job at the bar there and really?</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0018">are you?</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0007">yeah</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0018">I'm a sports journalist</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0007"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1289" who="S0018">fancy that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1290" who="S0007">check out the blog</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1292" who="S0007">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0018">check out my blog</u>
<u n="1294" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1295" who="S0018">do you wanna <trunc>s</trunc> Question of Sport quiz?</u>
<u n="1296" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1297" who="S0007">yeah</u>
</body>
</text>
