<text id="S346">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:56:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0255 S0319</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Women’s clothes/shoes/boots sizing and styles, wearing glasses, spam phone calls, perfume, Internet problems, recent night out, Decoupage, online shopping. </topics>
		<activity>Chatting with close friend while online shopping.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0255">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Boston, Lincs</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Boston/London/Peterborough</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>account manager - sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0319">
				<exactage>43</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wisbech</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0319">oh they weren't cos it's round here</u>
<u n="2" who="S0255">yeah cos that's I I'm wondering if you're wearing I mean they they're too big for you</u>
<u n="3" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="4" who="S0255">the ones you're wearing now</u>
<u n="5" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0255">so what size are those ones?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0319">these are</u>
<u n="8" who="S0255" trans="overlap">let's have a look</u>
<u n="9" who="S0319">yeah these are are we on?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0255">yeah erm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0319">can you see?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0255"><trunc>si</trunc> yeah sixteen</u>
<u n="13" who="S0319">right so I could get a fourteen then really</u>
<u n="14" who="S0255" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0319">at Primark</u>
<u n="16" who="S0255">and what <trunc>s</trunc> what size did you say?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0319">oh there was a fourteen but are we on? oh right erm but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bought me off from Ebay er rather than get me cos I he says have some Levi's I</u>
<u n="18" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0319">so he went on the internet and what he done was is he actually just bought me a pair of Levi's er that have been chopped down into shorts</u>
<u n="20" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="21" who="S0319">er so they was <pause dur="short"/> er oh gosh I think he said a thirty thirty-four waist</u>
<u n="22" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="23" who="S0319">er but obviously the leg length and what have you they were supposed to be a size fourteen</u>
<u n="24" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="25" who="S0319">but when I put them on they looked nice but this bit here at the back there was plenty of room</u>
<u n="26" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0319" trans="overlap">but I'm this is my bone hip oh I'll come this side this is my bone now I haven't gotten I haven't got the excess</u>
<u n="28" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0319">baggage that I had on top of it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay so fourteen or a thirty-four waist</u>
<u n="31" who="S0319">I'm sure it was a <trunc>tho</trunc> <trunc>thir</trunc> well we'll have to ignore the waist fourteen</u>
<u n="32" who="S0255">yeah I mean it's easier to <trunc>ac</trunc> it's just some of some of the <trunc>thi</trunc> oh I need my glasses some of the erm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0319">oh I ought to have mine as well erm it's it's a pink case in my handbag <pause dur="short"/> please and thank you <pause dur="short"/> mind you ah thank you saying that is there any <trunc>gla</trunc> oh there is crikey mikey</u>
<u n="34" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0319">that's a first it's normally glasses case and no glasses</u>
<u n="36" who="S0255">well I have a I have a I have a pair I keep at work and a pair I have at home but I'm cos I'm finding I need them more and more now I don't want to take them room to room</u>
<u n="37" who="S0319" trans="overlap">yes I am</u>
<u n="38" who="S0255">and I'm always like oh where are they where are they?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0319">I am er and I went and checked while <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was here before he went back when our eye tests were</u>
<u n="40" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0319">er and they said it's not till next year and I'm thinking crikey I really am struggling at times but I'm finding it's cos</u>
<u n="42" who="S0255" trans="overlap">if you're struggling go and get them done earlier</u>
<u n="43" who="S0319">well it's cos I'm so tired as well</u>
<u n="44" who="S0255">yeah that doesn't help</u>
<u n="45" who="S0319">er and it doesn't does it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="47" who="S0319" trans="overlap">and if I start wearing them at the beginning of the day come the end of the day if I take them off I'm like <pause dur="short"/> I can't see anything</u>
<u n="48" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0319">but looking at them <event desc="sound of phone"/> <pause dur="long"/> oh that's erm a big one innit?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0255">what the screen?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0255">yeah well you know me biggest is best</u>
<u n="53" who="S0319">er well this is it but I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't get anything bigger than what he's got I hope</u>
<u n="54" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0319">er <pause dur="short"/> he's got a fifty-inch one now</u>
<u n="56" who="S0255">exactly it's just junk it comes through about this time every day</u>
<u n="57" who="S0319">yes I keep getting them</u>
<u n="58" who="S0255">do you get the government ones saying that you're entitled to a new boiler and</u>
<u n="59" who="S0319" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0255">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0319">get all that crap and sometimes when I'm there I get it and I'll answer it and then it's the <trunc>au</trunc>automated</u>
<u n="62" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0319">but it's filling up my answerphone</u>
<u n="64" who="S0255">yeah I know I find that you come in and there's a message and you know what it's gonna be</u>
<u n="65" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0255">it's just it's annoying so annoying</u>
<u n="67" who="S0319" trans="overlap">er but I rang up to find out how I could stop it er and BT were like oh yeah we can stop that I'm like I mean no problem it's gonna cost you I think it was like something three pounds something or whatever more a month</u>
<u n="68" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0319">er and I'm thinking but it's getting that bad now where I think I might do it</u>
<u n="70" who="S0255">the trouble is though it it comes up as international calls and withheld numbers and unavailable numbers so actually <trunc>ho</trunc> they can't block all those cos that would mean you wouldn't be able to get any phone calls say if the council rang you for something or if something a lot of places businesses ring and their numbers are withheld</u>
<u n="71" who="S0319">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0255">and then they can't ring the people because it's all on</u>
<u n="73" who="S0319">yeah ah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0255">are you on the telephone preference service?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0255">yeah yeah cos we're on that as well</u>
<u n="77" who="S0319">but it's a waste of time</u>
<u n="78" who="S0255">mm well I I think the ones when if it comes through with a number I mean I've got on my actual phone I can block numbers</u>
<u n="79" who="S0319">yeah I can on my mobile</u>
<u n="80" who="S0255" trans="overlap">so if anything comes through with a number no on the actual phone phone on this one</u>
<u n="81" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0255">I've got it on here look I can go in and just on the settings <pause dur="short"/> caller barred</u>
<u n="83" who="S0319" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0255">so if anything comes up with a number I <trunc>a</trunc> I can just put it in that</u>
<u n="85" who="S0319">and then it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0255">so that blocks it</u>
<u n="87" who="S0319">oh mind you our phones are old so that's probably why but I could do it on my mobile</u>
<u n="88" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but a lot of the time now it just but it just comes through with the <trunc>un</trunc>unavailable or international or withheld</u>
<u n="89" who="S0319" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0255">so actually that wouldn't stop because you can't stop the erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0319" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="92" who="S0255">the things</u>
<u n="93" who="S0319">there used to be something years ago though cos I done it for nana and grandad when they was both alive so I am going back a while</u>
<u n="94" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0319">er that <pause dur="short"/> your phone number</u>
<u n="96" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0319">for you to be able to ring certain people if they'd got this thingy on you had a code that you had to put in front when you rang the number</u>
<u n="98" who="S0255" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="99" who="S0319">so then that way the call would then come through to that person</u>
<u n="100" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="101" who="S0319">because they'd got like a block on their phone</u>
<u n="102" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0319">but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know they don't seem to do that now but I remember doing that cos we used to have to put a number like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know four eight and then put nana and grandad's number and then the call would go through to them</u>
<u n="104" who="S0255" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> oh right that's good <trunc>s</trunc>so it's only certain people could read them</u>
<u n="105" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0255">that's good yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0319">er so then like all them businesses you see they couldn't get through because they haven't got the number in front er</u>
<u n="108" who="S0255">no that's a good idea</u>
<u n="109" who="S0319">anyway deary me</u>
<u n="110" who="S0255">right so ahem</u>
<u n="111" who="S0319">I've had a shower this morning mind you I've been into the market</u>
<u n="112" who="S0255">you don't smell</u>
<u n="113" who="S0319">no don't I can't you even smell my perfume oh Christ that's bad</u>
<u n="114" who="S0255">no I can't smell your perfume</u>
<u n="115" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="116" who="S0255">what is it you're wearing?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0319">Kylie Minogue</u>
<u n="118" who="S0255">oh I don't wear perfume not at all</u>
<u n="119" who="S0319">er</u>
<u n="120" who="S0255">sounds daft but I get fed up of the smell</u>
<u n="121" who="S0319">now you see I can never smell it so I I'm like this and I'm like</u>
<u n="122" who="S0255">you put more and more on</u>
<u n="123" who="S0319">yeah sometimes I can be a bit</u>
<u n="124" who="S0255">people say oh put different ones on different days but I <trunc>a</trunc> what I mean <trunc>i</trunc> I spray <trunc>perfu</trunc> if I spray perfume on about an hour later I think god I can still smell that smell and it annoys me that I can smell it so I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't wear it at all</u>
<u n="125" who="S0319">well I have to spray it so it's on my clothes</u>
<u n="126" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0319">cos if I do it round the neck and what have you</u>
<u n="128" who="S0255">yeah do you get a rash?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0319">it yeah er and cos I used to do it they used to tell you to put it here and here and rub together</u>
<u n="130" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0319">and then I got told that you should put it behind the backs of your knees as well</u>
<u n="132" who="S0255">yeah the idea is you put it on a pulse so you put it on the wrist but you shouldn't even rub perfume because it breaks down the erm the thing of it changes the smell</u>
<u n="133" who="S0319">oh <unclear/> like this</u>
<u n="134" who="S0255">so you should just just spray it on and just</u>
<u n="135" who="S0319">I started them coming up and what have you and everything so I thought oh I'll erm spray it on my clothes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0255" trans="overlap">spray it on your clothes mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0319">so</u>
<u n="138" who="S0255">okay so jeans</u>
<u n="139" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0255">erm so where do you normally get your jeans from?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0319">well I haven't bought jeans well apart from those ones I've done on Ebay</u>
<u n="142" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0319">I couldn't tell you how many years ago it was that I bought jeans cos I went into Primark er and I just get these jeggings</u>
<u n="144" who="S0255" trans="overlap">jeggings yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0319">and that's all I've been really having</u>
<u n="146" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="147" who="S0319">erm so the jeans that I had in my wardrobe I wouldn't even know where I'd got them from how long I'd had them</u>
<u n="148" who="S0255">no that's fine what we'll do is we'll start on ASOS because I tend to buy things off ASOS erm Mango Oasis places like that and then I look out particularly if they've got sales on because the they can be quite expensive erm I'll tell you another Wallis I get <trunc>alo</trunc> my skinny jeans are from Wallis and you can get them in black erm <trunc>bl</trunc> all different <trunc>blu</trunc> all different blues and different colours as well so they might be worth looking at as well</u>
<u n="149" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0255">and with Wallis if you when you send for it it's sort of I think I'm not sure if it's about three pound for delivery but it's free return and</u>
<u n="151" who="S0319">oh that's good</u>
<u n="152" who="S0255">so that's yeah that's the thing you want to watch up cos if you start buying like I buy everything online and then I send loads of stuff back</u>
<u n="153" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0255">but I always look and find the people that give you free returns</u>
<u n="155" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0255">er like ASOS which isn't loading with ASOS I pay I think it's about fourteen pound a year but that means I get free next day delivery free returns erm and also get a like advance of different sales and extra money off things et cetera so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> uses it as well she will</u>
<u n="157" who="S0319">I was going to say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s told me about them and what have you and I've had a look on theirs</u>
<u n="158" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0319">er and one of my dresses that I've got is erm <pause dur="short"/> from them as well</u>
<u n="160" who="S0255">yeah they're good</u>
<u n="161" who="S0319">actually I think I got two dresses summer dresses</u>
<u n="162" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0319">but see it's now going into winter and I got no winterwear</u>
<u n="164" who="S0255">yeah well it's up to fifty percent off sale jeans</u>
<u n="165" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0255">so let's let's start on that then and er okay let's go size fourteen do that do that go on yeah let's make this even bigger mind you it's a bit deceiving you do that and actually it's just white at the sides so that's gonna make my eyes go buzz eyed</u>
<u n="167" who="S0319">well</u>
<u n="168" who="S0255">do that if that's alright that's the easiest easy enough to see isn't it? okay so that</u>
<u n="169" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0255">erm and how many is that two hundred and thirty-one styles so we'll look at them all and just see so I mean stuff like that is no good with the rips and stuff in and like unless you want rips to me I just think that's a bit</u>
<u n="171" who="S0319">well you can do that yourself and I mean like round here and what have you men it tends to rip quite easy cos they're forever scratching aren't they?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> so like those ones</u>
<u n="173" who="S0319">oh they're yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0255">see they're nice they're slim</u>
<u n="175" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0255">and they're quite high waist</u>
<u n="177" who="S0319">and high</u>
<u n="178" who="S0255">so I always do middle high waist because the low rise ones that's fine for kids but I don't think that's right so</u>
<u n="179" who="S0319">no</u>
<u n="180" who="S0255">I'll tell you what we'll this with ASOS I I'll just get <trunc>thi</trunc> I'll just get them and then they'll come tomorrow erm you can try then and <trunc>the</trunc> then whatever you want to keep or don't I can send back and you just pay me for anything you want to keep</u>
<u n="181" who="S0319">okey-dokey</u>
<u n="182" who="S0255">I think that'll be the easiest way to do this cos then</u>
<u n="183" who="S0319">do they have like leg lengths?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0255">er no just the size</u>
<u n="185" who="S0319">ah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0255">but but I <trunc>te</trunc> oh yes they do</u>
<u n="187" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="188" who="S0255">okay sorry take it back</u>
<u n="189" who="S0319">oh crikey where's the right</u>
<u n="190" who="S0255">trouble is when you get into the sale thing is quite a lot of things aren't available so erm thirty we were saying thirty-four see thirty-four inch waist</u>
<u n="191" who="S0319">is sixteen</u>
<u n="192" who="S0255">that's a sixteen</u>
<u n="193" who="S0319">so it can't be so I want a</u>
<u n="194" who="S0255">so you really want to be a thirty-two</u>
<u n="195" who="S0319">ah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0255">yeah?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0255">so if you're thirty-two</u>
<u n="199" who="S0319">and the thirty-two leg</u>
<u n="200" who="S0255">thirty-two length that's the <trunc>nor</trunc> that's a like a standard</u>
<u n="201" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0255">see these are these are a thirty-two</u>
<u n="203" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0255">yeah? and how long are your legs compared to mine?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0319"><unclear/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0255">stand up and be counted yeah hip to hip so we're about the same length of leg so a thirty-two would be fine for you because then it's just sort of here so it means if you're wearing it even with Converse trainers or your Doc Martens that would be fine</u>
<u n="207" who="S0319">hopefully then yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0255">but with heels as well cos when you when you're up with your heels it sort of goes</u>
<u n="209" who="S0319">over the</u>
<u n="210" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0319">it goes over it</u>
<u n="212" who="S0255">right so what we'll do is we'll just go yes yes yes yes then we can look at the <trunc>bas</trunc> the bag at the end and knock out anything and then</u>
<u n="213" who="S0319">I was gonna say cos some of them other ones were thirty-four</u>
<u n="214" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="215" who="S0319">er so but I can see can't I? try them on and</u>
<u n="216" who="S0255">yeah see again made from stretch cotton denim so that's another thing I usually look for stretch cotton <trunc>demin</trunc><trunc>den</trunc><trunc>de</trunc><trunc>de</trunc>denim</u>
<u n="217" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="218" who="S0255">because that gives it's like it's like these are they're just just that little bit</u>
<u n="219" who="S0319">yeah I like that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0255">of give in it</u>
<u n="221" who="S0319">I find that's that's more flattering as well</u>
<u n="222" who="S0255">and I like it as well if I can normally get T-shirts with it in because they keep their shape a lot better</u>
<u n="223" who="S0319">yeah yeah yeah okay see if there's something</u>
<u n="224" who="S0319">so oh</u>
<u n="225" who="S0255">well I was just gonna have look</u>
<u n="226" who="S0319">it doesn't give you they're in blue ah so it's that blue</u>
<u n="227" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0319">that's alright</u>
<u n="229" who="S0255">there you go that's them bigger look</u>
<u n="230" who="S0319">how did you get that up there?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0255">I pressed the zoom underneath it</u>
<u n="232" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="233" who="S0255">yeah? so now I've found when I send for jeans sometimes it'll be a size ten and I can't get it up over just over my knees and I can't get it any higher and I'm thinking what? and then other times a ten it fits fine and sometimes it's big so this is why I tend to order a lot of stuff and it's like when you're at a shop remember we went to Primark that time and you went in with about six trolleys worth to try on and you went home with about five trolleys worth of stuff</u>
<u n="234" who="S0319">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0255">when I get loads of them and I'll <trunc>li</trunc> try on try on try on and out of eight pairs of jeans I might send for I'll keep one or maybe two and then but you've got the choice rather than getting them oh they're no good send them back try another pair send them I just think right it's like are you</u>
<u n="236" who="S0319">so it's with ASOS</u>
<u n="237" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0319">er do you pay for them all</u>
<u n="239" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0319">and then you get them er</u>
<u n="241" who="S0255">pay for them send them back and then</u>
<u n="242" who="S0319">and then if whatever you send back and then they credit you</u>
<u n="243" who="S0255">so <trunc>ho</trunc> do they credit you or do they put the money back into your bank?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0319">erm well I pay with PayPal you got PayPal?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0319">yeah I pay with PayPal and they just put it back into PayPal and then you go into PayPal and you draw it</u>
<u n="247" who="S0255">ah and then you yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0319">et cetera I've usually spent it I'd spend it on other stuff so I tend to just</u>
<u n="249" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0319">unless I if I if I bought a lot if I bought sort of three hundred pounds of stuff and then I send loads of it back and I've got two hundred pound credit I'll go into PayPal and get it back out but if it's twenty thirty quid it just tends to</u>
<u n="251" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0319">ah so some of these places then they do use PayPal</u>
<u n="253" who="S0255">yeah ASOS almost almost all the places I've shopped through again they use PayPal</u>
<u n="254" who="S0319">yeah I like using PayPal</u>
<u n="255" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0319">yeah oh look normal jeans that go round your waist</u>
<u n="257" who="S0255">see exactly yeah this this is what I</u>
<u n="258" who="S0319">you see cos that's really difficult to find them in the shop</u>
<u n="259" who="S0255">yeah I know I know it's just a fashion of what it actually is but see look these are twenty-one pound now</u>
<u n="260" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0255">so add that to the bag okay so that's in my bag and we'll go back and then see what else there is so right so there's those ones just shout if you spot any or I'll just like some of these like the tight skinny ones I I find normally things like that they'd be the ones you struggle to get on cos I</u>
<u n="262" who="S0319">yeah I wouldn't want tight skinny ones</u>
<u n="263" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="264" who="S0319">I have skinny jeans but tight skinny jeans I you might as well just wear tights so</u>
<u n="265" who="S0255">right so that's</u>
<u n="266" who="S0319">that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0255">those ones you were looking at or which ones</u>
<u n="268" who="S0319">oh oh I just saw them I thought that was pretty but you can do that</u>
<u n="269" who="S0255">oh yeah yeah with rhinestones down the side</u>
<u n="270" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0319">I'm gonna get a hot fix gun so I can do that anyway</u>
<u n="272" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0319">then but they're enough the same colour as what them other ones were aren't they?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0255">yeah but but there might be an option for a different colour in two colours</u>
<u n="275" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="276" who="S0255">light or dark but to be fair if you if you send for this and the others only one of them might suit or might fit so out of the two you'd probably keep one although these are fifteen quid and the others are twenty so actually if they're both right you might think okay I've got two decent pairs of jeans now</u>
<u n="277" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0255">you know and so</u>
<u n="279" who="S0319">this pair looks darker denim that what over to the other</u>
<u n="280" who="S0255">it does yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0319">er</u>
<u n="282" who="S0255">so</u>
<u n="283" who="S0319">fourteen</u>
<u n="284" who="S0255">fourteen size guide see what it says UK fourteen oh I see that's just and it's all how to measure you</u>
<u n="285" who="S0319">inside leg right so what is?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0255">actually I've got a thing right hold on I've got a thing that ASOS sent me it's a tape measure which actually measures you to show you the ASOS sizes I've never used it but let me see if I</u>
<u n="287" who="S0319">ah well this could be fun <pause dur="short"/> measure from the top of inside leg at crotch to ankle bone <pause dur="long"/> put it oh that's a petite that bit at the bottom there there's a size guide underneath but that petite</u>
<u n="288" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0319">is only up to five foot three it's probably a bit more than I am but about me <trunc>s</trunc> height</u>
<u n="290" who="S0255">so what are you?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0319">it says model's height on that picture</u>
<u n="292" who="S0255">yeah that's what I find's good with ASOS as well</u>
<u n="293" who="S0319">it <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="294" who="S0255">it tells you how big how what size the model is</u>
<u n="295" who="S0319">is that five foot nine and a half inches?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0255">so eight hang on let me put the thing on yeah five foot nine and half so she's quite tall</u>
<u n="297" who="S0319">yeah she is so</u>
<u n="298" who="S0255">yeah right now I've not used this I don't quite know how it works</u>
<u n="299" who="S0319">oh this I gonna be good</u>
<u n="300" who="S0255">so women's colour code hips bust bust <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0319">oh why is the</u>
<u n="302" who="S0255">okay the I've got no idea</u>
<u n="303" who="S0319">there's no numbers on it is there?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0255">I haven't I've not actually looked at this so I don't know mm womenswear colour code that doesn't make any sense then</u>
<u n="305" who="S0319">no because there's no numbers on it where's the?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0255">well it's probably something came with it it says how to use it</u>
<u n="307" who="S0319">I was gonna say where's the instructions? did it come with anything?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0255">maybe but I wouldn't have kept them</u>
<u n="309" who="S0319"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's really good so</u>
<u n="310" who="S0255">alright so my bust is orange</u>
<u n="311" who="S0319"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0255">okay right let's look I'll open another thing and see whether there's a thing on here how to use it</u>
<u n="313" who="S0319">there's there's nothing on here</u>
<u n="314" who="S0255">ASOS</u>
<u n="315" who="S0319">hips hips bust</u>
<u n="316" who="S0255">tape measure oh that's different languages</u>
<u n="317" who="S0319">er like I say it's got hips and <trunc>bu</trunc></u>
<u n="318" who="S0255">ASOS tape measure guide</u>
<u n="319" who="S0319">bust but there's nothing on there anyways with regard to legs</u>
<u n="320" who="S0255">we're all out of them I don't know if that'd be easier I dunno ASOS tape click here to size tape watch the video to see how to use your ASOS tape</u>
<u n="321" who="S0319">right okay</u>
<u n="322" who="S0255">this could be interesting</u>
<u n="323" who="S0319">yeah they might erm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0255">it just came in with something it was like here it is and <trunc>wha</trunc> and I thought oh yeah yeah and I just chucked it in the in the drawer but because I know what sizes on here fit me pretty much on ASOS now</u>
<u n="325" who="S0319">well yeah no</u>
<u n="326" who="S0255">it's it's useful if erm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0319">it had numbers so you could measure cos you can't measure your inside leg with this</u>
<u n="328" who="S0255">no but I bet you probably measure round and it'll say if you're green blue blue then you're a size ten or twelve or whatever let's see what it says</u>
<u n="329" who="S0319">er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0255">it's on the right side <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0319">oh trust me I'm in the middle of the blue and the white underneath there</u>
<u n="332" who="S0255">go round here</u>
<u n="333" who="S0319">oh I'm on the middle on that of blue and pink er green and pink</u>
<u n="334" who="S0255">I don't know we'll see what this is but if not then</u>
<u n="335" who="S0319">I was gonna say you can see what's gonna happen</u>
<u n="336" who="S0255">the thing is though if we if we send for something that's a fourteen and it's too big we'll you know we'll send it back and get a twelve</u>
<u n="337" who="S0319">twelve too big? mind you I need to shift this half a stone that I've put back on</u>
<u n="338" who="S0255">alright no we'll add that anyway so</u>
<u n="339" who="S0319">no cos this is we'll just discard that</u>
<u n="340" who="S0255">yeah we'll probably just throw that away the computer's just going really slow</u>
<u n="341" who="S0319">you see cos that colour as well</u>
<u n="342" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0319">they're nice like she's got the heels and that and then you've got a nice top and what have you they're you can use them for going out</u>
<u n="344" who="S0255">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="345" who="S0319">like you do</u>
<u n="346" who="S0255">yeah yeah that's right</u>
<u n="347" who="S0319">cos you have a nice pair of jeans on then with your top and your shoes and whatever</u>
<u n="348" who="S0255">yeah yeah come on add to bag</u>
<u n="349" who="S0319">whereas the ones which are lighter aren't so</u>
<u n="350" who="S0255">no they're not dressy are they?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0319">they're not <trunc>dre</trunc> no</u>
<u n="352" who="S0255">whereas a dark pair of jeans</u>
<u n="353" who="S0319">and black</u>
<u n="354" who="S0255">black or dark jeans</u>
<u n="355" who="S0319">you have to watch it because the black and what have you I mean these I ought to throw these out they're miles to big</u>
<u n="356" who="S0255">alright I'm going to go back in again cos somehow this seems to have got mixed up</u>
<u n="357" who="S0319">has has it got erm lots of things running on the background?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0255">well no there's nothing going I don't know what's going on it's just having a moment it could be there's there's nothing on that</u>
<u n="359" who="S0319">I sometimes like with my phone I think what's going on? erm cos it's not erm working and then or it's really slow and then I notice a little arrow up here which keeps coming down</u>
<u n="360" who="S0255">oh and it's er doing data</u>
<u n="361" who="S0319">which means it's updating and that and I'm like oh that's why</u>
<u n="362" who="S0255">er there's something going on here</u>
<u n="363" who="S0319">ah when was the last I don't remember that</u>
<u n="364" who="S0255">oh that's that's from the meal</u>
<u n="365" who="S0319">excuse me</u>
<u n="366" who="S0255">that's actually one it was</u>
<u n="367" who="S0319">excuse me sorry</u>
<u n="368" who="S0255">taken with a few other people and I've cut it down that's why it's a little bit blurry really it's a bit sort of too zoomed in for erm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0319">looks alright</u>
<u n="370" who="S0255">let me just see it might be Google so I just if I put in ASOS on try this other search engine if not I'll shut the computer down and start again</u>
<u n="371" who="S0319">oh look there's a bit of me there</u>
<u n="372" who="S0255">looks like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got blond extensions on his</u>
<u n="373" who="S0319">I was gonna say yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0255"><trunc>be</trunc> on his beard right I'm going to quit Firefox Safari</u>
<u n="375" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="376" who="S0255">no that's me</u>
<u n="377" who="S0319">oh I was gonna say all of a sudden that blue thing went across but now it's stopped</u>
<u n="378" who="S0255">this is it you sometimes find sometimes it just gets a bit stuck it's alright I'll just I'll restart it and that'll that'll wipe it start it and start again</u>
<u n="379" who="S0319">yeah start from the beginning</u>
<u n="380" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0319">that was lovely that well what I can remember</u>
<u n="382" who="S0255">oh you were fine until you had your tablets and then you zoned out slightly</u>
<u n="383" who="S0319">mm and that's where I can't remember anything</u>
<u n="384" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0319">er</u>
<u n="386" who="S0255">you you were very well behaved</u>
<u n="387" who="S0319">cos I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and what have you I said oh lord I says did I say anything? do anything? <event desc="background talk"/> he said no you was fine</u>
<u n="388" who="S0255">no you you were fine you were just really slightly</u>
<u n="389" who="S0319">mm gone</u>
<u n="390" who="S0255">well <trunc>ju</trunc> no just not I was gonna say not quite in the room but you know what I mean it's not you were just just a little bit zoned out and a bit quiet but it's nothing to worry about</u>
<u n="391" who="S0319">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that he thinks that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a bit concerned he says cos he was going hop over he and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said no you were alright you know me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were used to it and that he says but I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was sort of a bit worried he says with how you'd gone</u>
<u n="392" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0319">er he said but you know he said I said to him well you know this is what happens and that when she's had her last lot which is true it does</u>
<u n="394" who="S0255">yeah or no cos you</u>
<u n="395" who="S0319">that's why I try to leave them as late in the evening as I can</u>
<u n="396" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> can you take them as you go to bed or is that too late?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0319">er I like to take to them probably an half and hour an hour before I go to bed cos then they start kicking in</u>
<u n="398" who="S0255">then they start working yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0319">er I mean like left here last night took the girls outside</u>
<u n="400" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0319">er went and had a tiddle and everything got myself ready for bed</u>
<u n="402" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0319">er girls all came in and I had to count that I'd got all of them in</u>
<u n="404" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0319">yeah cos Imogen when it's nighttime and with her moving so quickly you tend to miss her</u>
<u n="406" who="S0255">yeah she's in and out in and out and actually which way did she end up being?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0319">erm so I count and it's like yeah oh I've got something in the bag</u>
<u n="408" who="S0255">yeah that's the first part that we put in</u>
<u n="409" who="S0319">oh right</u>
<u n="410" who="S0255">it stays in there I think for two hours so</u>
<u n="411" who="S0319">oh right but erm and then I said come on we're going to bed well cos like Trudy was there a bit worried so I put her on the bed and then she started whinging and what have not whinging but whinging because the next thing Page had jumped on the bed cos I'd go the quilt on and if they know that quilt's on you see over the top of my bed linen then they can come on the bed</u>
<u n="412" who="S0255">oh right yeah they don't go on until that's on there</u>
<u n="413" who="S0319">so no and erm then cos Holly came waddling through and looked at me and sort of so I had to try and pick her up and that's like a miniature pig</u>
<u n="414" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0319">er so I picked her put her on Maddie then wanted to be on so the dogs were all on the bed before me so then I was trying to get in bed and Trudy trying to get snuggled in to me like she does</u>
<u n="416" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0319">er</u>
<u n="418" who="S0255">these are these are jeggings black high waist jeggings I just thought they might be nice with heels</u>
<u n="419" who="S0319">those yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0255">right let me do it bigger sorry cos er</u>
<u n="421" who="S0319">that's nice</u>
<u n="422" who="S0255">they're like denim ones aren't they? I could see you in them with your heels</u>
<u n="423" who="S0319">mm I like them</u>
<u n="424" who="S0255">yeah?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0255">oh right what we'll do oh right so there's a ten to twelve or a fourteen to sixteen oh that's gonna be a problem I think cos you'll be sort of in between we'll get both sizes but I think you'll find one'll be too big and one'll be too small</u>
<u n="427" who="S0319" trans="overlap">big and one's gonna be too small</u>
<u n="428" who="S0255">but we'll put them in now and we can always go back later on</u>
<u n="429" who="S0319">oh them other ones went</u>
<u n="430" who="S0255">oh I put I just put them in</u>
<u n="431" who="S0319">oh you just put them in</u>
<u n="432" who="S0255">yeah oh I shop at the speed of lightning</u>
<u n="433" who="S0319">well yes I can't see this</u>
<u n="434" who="S0255">okay hold on so</u>
<u n="435" who="S0319">erm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0255">you see there they were those ones I've just put them in</u>
<u n="437" who="S0319">there's those ones</u>
<u n="438" who="S0255">erm yeah so there's I just thought they looked nice so I think we're on the lookout for some straight leg ones as well cos I mean they're straight leg but they're quite shabby sort of look whereas they're not</u>
<u n="439" who="S0319">yeah no I don't</u>
<u n="440" who="S0255">they're a bit scruffy erm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0319">they're straight leg they're not bad</u>
<u n="442" who="S0255">those ones? they're quite tapered in though let's have a look they're forty-three quid as well G-Star they're <trunc>qui</trunc> no they're you'll <trunc>fi</trunc> they're all they're sort of pulled up over the knee do you see? all scrunched up</u>
<u n="443" who="S0319">they've yeah they've got a dart in them haven't they? they've</u>
<u n="444" who="S0255">yeah yeah they're they're like for kids really cost they're sort of scrunched all round your knee</u>
<u n="445" who="S0319">yeah no they're <pause dur="short"/> what on earth are them ones?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0255">those ones they look like you've got wet legs at the bottom don't they?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0319">they the well yeah it looks like they've took the bottoms off from one jeans and sewn them on the other</u>
<u n="448" who="S0255">I know you get all sorts here it looks like you're been wading through bleach with those ones</u>
<u n="449" who="S0319">yeah don't you remember though and I never did do it but I knew somebody she used to get her jeans</u>
<u n="450" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0319">and she'd get in the bath of water</u>
<u n="452" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0319">to shrink them so they'd then fit her</u>
<u n="454" who="S0255">really hot yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0319">yeah er but she would also then sort of stick them stones around them and elastic bands and that er and then put bleach on so she could get the</u>
<u n="456" who="S0255">yeah the stonewashing or tie-dye right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0319" trans="overlap">tie-dye or yeah and I used to think why don't you just go and buy them? cos you could get them like that</u>
<u n="458" who="S0255">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="459" who="S0319">you see now that says that that's a skinny jean but to me looking from here that looks like a bootleg the way that it kicks out at the bottom</u>
<u n="460" who="S0255">yeah that's it that's what it looks like to that's bootleg</u>
<u n="461" who="S0319">and I don't like bootleg</u>
<u n="462" who="S0255">no I don't right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0319">yeah no I put the telly on and I'd got my Ipad so I thought right I'll get moving on this the next thing I knew I woke up so I don't think the girls probably was erm watching the telly and I didn't do anything on my Ipad I just went out like a light</u>
<u n="464" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0319">see they're not bad but they don't say what</u>
<u n="466" who="S0255">which? those?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0319">oh they're printed paisley those but they don't say <pause dur="long"/> oh no</u>
<u n="468" who="S0255">it's alright for a bedspread</u>
<u n="469" who="S0319">yeah no</u>
<u n="470" who="S0255">not to wear</u>
<u n="471" who="S0319">no no no no no</u>
<u n="472" who="S0255">right mm mm mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0319">it must be the fashion there's another one there look</u>
<u n="474" who="S0255">yeah I think they sort of run out of things to do don't they? and then they just</u>
<u n="475" who="S0319">mm oh no they're skinny</u>
<u n="476" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="long"/> looking for some straight ones</u>
<u n="477" who="S0319">have they got an option at the top? put it so it's straight legs</u>
<u n="478" who="S0255">yeah yeah but I'm just looking we're nearly at the bottom look and you see that's down there now so</u>
<u n="479" who="S0319">oh right yeah now what's the boyfriend jeans?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0255">they're I think they're sort of like when they're meant to be like blokes' jeans so at the top it's a different cut so they're more slouch a bit slouch and a bit looser and they've got this stupid thing at the knee again</u>
<u n="481" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0255">but no they're weird</u>
<u n="483" who="S0319">cos I've I've <trunc>se</trunc></u>
<u n="484" who="S0255">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sometimes gets boyfriend ones cos they suit her shape but then she never really likes jeans she says jeans generally don't suit her so get back to where we were erm no jeans generally don't really suit her that's why she always wears the jeggings</u>
<u n="485" who="S0319">there's that mind you they're in red and that but I mean either are they? no they say skinny don't they? they're not</u>
<u n="486" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0319">no no no <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've seen it in the shops boyfriend I'm thinking what's boyfriend jeans when they're at home?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0255">well the <trunc>id</trunc> the idea is it's like you you know you get out of bed and pull your boyfriend's jeans on and you wear them like you wear a boyfriend shirt and stuff like that so do you like the the red ones?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0319">erm yeah they look better there are them blue ones</u>
<u n="490" who="S0255">they're nice different high leg</u>
<u n="491" who="S0319">and they're different</u>
<u n="492" who="S0255">yeah you you got a big thing on the back there though Monkey Jeans so it's whether you'd whether you wanted that on there</u>
<u n="493" who="S0319">that oh I can soon take that off</u>
<u n="494" who="S0255">what even with those stud things?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0255">ah right no it's not available in your size</u>
<u n="497" who="S0319">ah not available ah got to be a skinny minnie</u>
<u n="498" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right oops oh nearly at the bottom</u>
<u n="499" who="S0319">oh she's back</u>
<u n="500" who="S0255">I know you always hear she walks in the door and goes er</u>
<u n="501" who="S0319">no it means she's back all in one piece</u>
<u n="502" who="S0255">that's it yeah <pause dur="short"/> come on</u>
<u n="503" who="S0319">there's nothing on yours that sort of whirls to let you know that it's still processing is there?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="505" who="S0319">ours has a oojiwhatsit going round and round and round so you know that it's thinking still that's strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0255">don't know what is going on</u>
<u n="507" who="S0319">press one of them and see if it comes up and then there's a picture in there</u>
<u n="508" who="S0255"><pause dur="long"/> mm it's just reloading it all <pause dur="long"/> no right let me have a look light skinny skinny skinny boyfriend</u>
<u n="509" who="S0319">no</u>
<u n="510" who="S0255">no skinny straight leg there G-Star straight leg ones might be alright</u>
<u n="511" who="S0319">she's huffing and puffing though is she alright?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0255">yeah that's normal</u>
<u n="513" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="514" who="S0255">just when she's bending down to do stuff and you forget she's eighty</u>
<u n="515" who="S0319">oh I know</u>
<u n="516" who="S0255">I know you don't think it but you know what I mean it's this is just doing my head in the Mac is meant to be so much better <pause dur="short"/> what have we got here</u>
<u n="517" who="S0319">well there's something somewhere adrift</u>
<u n="518" who="S0255">there is have a go on this one</u>
<u n="519" who="S0319">oh but those are the only ones down the bottom there that said erm straight leg</u>
<u n="520" who="S0255">yeah I think we'll look on somewhere else for the straight leg let's just get these</u>
<u n="521" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0255">and then er we'll look somewhere else do you like that? that's erm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0319">that's erm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0255"><unclear/> cosmetics the one you know I'm having the party</u>
<u n="525" who="S0319">yes</u>
<u n="526" who="S0255">November the twenty-sixth</u>
<u n="527" who="S0319">did I put it in here? I did say yes I need to make sure I've shoved it in here so I don't go and do anything</u>
<u n="528" who="S0255">I'm gonna go on on my Ipad cos it's</u>
<u n="529" who="S0319">yeah mistletoe kiss is you Ipad connected so then you can see it on there?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0255">no it's erm I probably could but I'll just I'll just go here now and just buy these I don't know what's going on I'm gonna</u>
<u n="531" who="S0319">Wednesday the twenty-sixth of November</u>
<u n="532" who="S0255">just shut it down yes Wednesday the twenty-sixth of November</u>
<u n="533" who="S0319">try another place</u>
<u n="534" who="S0255">I just I think it might be because I had that that was in there but it's sort of saying that the internet's not working but they are both the things are going</u>
<u n="535" who="S0319">was gonna say try a if it's ASOS or whatever try Next or something and see if they work okay</u>
<u n="536" who="S0255">yeah the twenty-sixth of November is that what we just you said?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0255">right I need to put it in there Wednesday night yeah cos you'd got it on there but I couldn't see anywhere a time</u>
<u n="539" who="S0319">no</u>
<u n="540" who="S0255">no I think nothing's working I'm gonna have to shut this down again this is ridiculous</u>
<u n="541" who="S0319"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bomb party</u>
<u n="542" who="S0255">bomb party just be careful how you say that</u>
<u n="543" who="S0319"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bomb yeah that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bomb party er what <trunc>ti</trunc> it was eight o'clock weren't it? here</u>
<u n="544" who="S0255">I think there's a problem with erm with the internet</u>
<u n="545" who="S0319">oh right let's see if we can find a candle or smelly things cos I bought one of those er cream thingys that erm I use in the shower raspberry and something er it's taking ages cos you only have to have a little bit on use a sponge and</u>
<u n="546" who="S0255">oh yeah that's that thing it's it just takes absolutely ages</u>
<u n="547" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0255">to use it</u>
<u n="549" who="S0319">oh there's no candles or anything there's a present I'm not quite sure what they're supposed to be</u>
<u n="550" who="S0255">are they maracas?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0319">well I don't know nature oh I like to put little things so then when I see it I think oh it's something exciting it's nothing to do with food</u>
<u n="552" who="S0255">you know what it is</u>
<u n="553" who="S0319">mm oh well so I'll put it so it's drinks cap thingy that's all that I can do</u>
<u n="554" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> poo pants</u>
<u n="555" who="S0319">er there you are <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bomb party</u>
<u n="556" who="S0255">shame there wasn't a picture of a bomb mind you it'd get swooped on by the terrorist squad then if you weren't gonna weren't careful would you?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0319">this is it erm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0255">I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> alright welcome to my new Ipad I don't want to do that I don't want to do that I just want normal day-to-day internet come on behave <pause dur="long"/> okay so I don't want to do that yeah I'm just wondering whether it's because I've plugged that new Ipad in it was erm yeah look there you go it was waiting to try and do something for that rather than do what I wanted it to do on the screen</u>
<u n="559" who="S0319">ah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0255">technology</u>
<u n="561" who="S0319">right bag</u>
<u n="562" who="S0255">right seventy-four yeah so that's all in</u>
<u n="563" who="S0319">right</u>
<u n="564" who="S0255">so it means so it's</u>
<u n="565" who="S0319">we didn't get</u>
<u n="566" who="S0255">do you want to have a look at that second page of jeans?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0319">yeah will that come up?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0255">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0319">no this is</u>
<u n="570" who="S0255">reserved for sixty minutes</u>
<u n="571" who="S0319">so it that still working now or have you had to abort it?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0255">no no it's all still going</u>
<u n="573" who="S0319">oh right</u>
<u n="574" who="S0255">fourteen see two hundred</u>
<u n="575" who="S0319">see technology erm I really am a bit of a dunce when it comes to it nowadays</u>
<u n="576" who="S0255">page two</u>
<u n="577" who="S0319">right they was at the bottom weren't they? boy</u>
<u n="578" who="S0255">yeah just get it on right so yeah these are page two straight leg jeans they're quite faded on the knee bit so no don't worry we'll just get this and the we'll look on somewhere else</u>
<u n="579" who="S0319">na na na na</u>
<u n="580" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="581" who="S0319">I was doing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s one of her Christmas presents weren't I the other night?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0319">er the next thing hiya I'm like oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> looked at me and like it's too late it's all out</u>
<u n="584" who="S0255">oh no</u>
<u n="585" who="S0319">she probably forgot about it</u>
<u n="586" who="S0255">did she see it or <trunc>di</trunc></u>
<u n="587" who="S0319">well no</u>
<u n="588" who="S0255">she didn't know what it was?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0319">well no she didn't sort of say anything and what have you erm didn't ask what I was doing I was doing decoupage and that er</u>
<u n="590" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="591" who="S0319">picture frame and you sit there really it's daft you have lovely paper which you then <trunc>re</trunc>rip to pieces and then you glue it back on</u>
<u n="592" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="593" who="S0319">yeah I know I know you see her room's purple isn't it? you see</u>
<u n="594" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0319">so I've done it in different purple colours of paper</u>
<u n="596" who="S0255">I know when I used to work at Ideal World and I was doing the stock control on Create and Craft and there was a lot of stuff there that had erm that used to do the <trunc>dec</trunc> decoupage the shows and all the stuff and</u>
<u n="597" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="long"/> right so that's</u>
<u n="599" who="S0319">you see I can't get to do much sewing or anything at the minute with being such a mess</u>
<u n="600" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0319">but I need to put heating actually back on in my shed</u>
<u n="602" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0319">now I go down there but</u>
<u n="604" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0319">come on PayPal PayPal PayPal</u>
<u n="606" who="S0255">going thinking about it</u>
<u n="607" who="S0319">mm he's whizzing</u>
<u n="608" who="S0255">sometimes this goes slower when it's backing up to the time machine or something which is erm</u>
<u n="609" who="S0319">oh hang on</u>
<u n="610" who="S0255">oh that's why eleven thirty-three that's why cos it was backing up <pause dur="short"/> it's the the settings erm the time machine is something <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got installed which means everyday it it backs everything up that's on the machine and at different times during the day and the night so if ever we had a problem and lost something on here you could go back to yesterday or three days ago when it was on there in the version you wanted before it got trashed and disappeared</u>
<u n="611" who="S0319">oh right</u>
<u n="612" who="S0255">so it's great but when it was that's what was slowing it down I think I don't know why it was doing it then cos normally it does it at night time so right there we are so that's that's ordered</u>
<u n="613" who="S0319">order received thanks</u>
<u n="614" who="S0255">so Wallis as well they do really nice erm skinny jeans they're the dark skinny jean and the black skinny jeans that I wear out they're from Wallis</u>
<u n="615" who="S0319">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0255">so we'll have a look on those it's a shame they had a thirty percent off the other night from five till eleven at night but it's not on now but erm and I bought two pairs they just arrived today so I'm gonna try those that's a dark pair</u>
<u n="617" who="S0319">er I want to have a look and see so where do you shop online for your shoes?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0255">erm <trunc>ha</trunc> trying to think really often ASOS again I tend to get a lot of stuff from ASOS</u>
<u n="619" who="S0319" trans="overlap">so I need to the boots that I'm wearing today they need to be thrown</u>
<u n="620" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0319">erm because if it is a bit slippy out there and damp they've got no grip on them whatsoever erm and I have on a few occasions cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said get rid of them but I haven't done</u>
<u n="622" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0319">erm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0255">let's have a look in the sale on ASOS for shoes while we're on the thing what size are you?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0319">well I seem to be a five and a six</u>
<u n="626" who="S0255">five and a six</u>
<u n="627" who="S0319">er so do five and a half</u>
<u n="628" who="S0255">there you go</u>
<u n="629" who="S0319">this is it some shoes I've got at home I've got them bloody new shoes are sitting there for you I've got sixes which fit me fine and I've got fives that fit me fine</u>
<u n="630" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0319">er some sixes are too big</u>
<u n="632" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0319">and I'm having to put two lots of inner soles in them</u>
<u n="634" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0319">I cos they're too big</u>
<u n="636" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0319">erm yet other sixes I've got they're fitting me fine but I've got some fives as well which I I can get in and wear and I'm fine</u>
<u n="638" who="S0255">that's strange cos with me I'm a five and I just buy a five and put them on and it's either I like it or not basically and I've got if they've got pointy toes they might squeeze my toes a bit but I don't like them anyway so</u>
<u n="639" who="S0319">yeah but five and a half I didn't realise that you <trunc>do</trunc> that you could still get halves in shoes</u>
<u n="640" who="S0255">so what sort of thing?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0319">I don't like those no I would like just a nice pair boots with a heel</u>
<u n="642" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="643" who="S0319">cos those ones that you have with the open toe</u>
<u n="644" who="S0255">oh yeah the shoe boots</u>
<u n="645" who="S0319">they they was nice</u>
<u n="646" who="S0255">try I'll try five and a six and just see and then <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0319">she's got the deep fat fryer on I haven't heard the noise of one of them for donkey's</u>
<u n="648" who="S0255">no it's not she's probably just frying in a frying pan then</u>
<u n="649" who="S0319">oh I was going it sounded like our old deep fat fryer which I loved</u>
<u n="650" who="S0255">mm <pause dur="long"/> this is definitely going slow and it's annoying me now it's one of these things I like to just get on get on get on press the button happens press the button</u>
<u n="651" who="S0319">yeah erm well what else came up?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0255">nothing</u>
<u n="653" who="S0319">something another screen popped up didn't it?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0255">no no there's nothing on it</u>
<u n="655" who="S0319">no oh I thought there was another one that opened up well that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0255">not fast enough for me</u>
<u n="657" who="S0319">no it's not me either but it was running okay</u>
<u n="658" who="S0255">yeah it was and then it stopped</u>
<u n="659" who="S0319">now it's gone wonky donkey again</u>
<u n="660" who="S0255">but then if you think years ago you'd put the computer on and it used to be de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de</u>
<u n="661" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0255">while it was actually getting going de de de de de de de de while it was actually getting going de de de de de de de de de this is it and then you'd put something in and you'd quite happily sit for five minutes cos you knew it was going to bring something up that you wanted to look at</u>
<u n="663" who="S0319">yeah but nowadays it's click of a button and things tend to go and</u>
<u n="664" who="S0255">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="665" who="S0319">you want it to go just work</u>
<u n="666" who="S0255">instantly yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0319">right</u>
<u n="668" who="S0255">okay so eleven and six okay so there's over a thousand styles so let's do</u>
<u n="669" who="S0319">oh crikey</u>
<u n="670" who="S0255">no well boots</u>
<u n="671" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0255">what else? erm what's Chelsea boots?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0319">no nor do I</u>
<u n="674" who="S0255">well look at those so just do boots</u>
<u n="675" who="S0319"><trunc>na</trunc> yeah hang on is there got heeled boots or what what are they</u>
<u n="676" who="S0255">heeled shoes sandals shoe boots</u>
<u n="677" who="S0319">we want shoe boots like mine is that what they're called shoe boots</u>
<u n="678" who="S0255">shoe boots the ones that are sort of like boots but they got the toes out and the heels out they were they were the ones that I've got</u>
<u n="679" who="S0319">yeah those are nice</u>
<u n="680" who="S0255">yeah okay</u>
<u n="681" who="S0319">right</u>
<u n="682" who="S0255">so now there's</u>
<u n="683" who="S0319">so how many have we got now?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0255">there's four hundred and sixty-nine so that's two pages and two hundred a page</u>
<u n="685" who="S0319">right</u>
<u n="686" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="687" who="S0319">er oh god grandma's slippers no please but Chelsea <unclear/> not not these</u>
<u n="688" who="S0255" trans="overlap">those are not</u>
<u n="689" who="S0319">slippers</u>
<u n="690" who="S0255">yeah I know they're weird</u>
<u n="691" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="692" who="S0255">oh my word look at those</u>
<u n="693" who="S0319" trans="overlap">made in yeah that's they're just up there they've made them erm grandma's slippers no but look with heels in them now look</u>
<u n="694" who="S0255">oh yeah yeah still doesn't work still grandma's slippers</u>
<u n="695" who="S0319">still don't float my boat</u>
<u n="696" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="697" who="S0319">right see they're not too bad them ones but then</u>
<u n="698" who="S0255">those?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0319">but then I don't like the heel so</u>
<u n="700" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="701" who="S0319">oh crikey they're disgusting</u>
<u n="702" who="S0255">they have to cater for every case</u>
<u n="703" who="S0319">I know</u>
<u n="704" who="S0255">it seems to be very much sort of chunkier heels now for the boots</u>
<u n="705" who="S0319">it is</u>
<u n="706" who="S0255">for this season she says sounding like a fashion queen this season back in trend</u>
<u n="707" who="S0319" trans="overlap">well yeah no you are you're far more trendy than me</u>
<u n="708" who="S0255">but I don't follow fashion I don't wear things because they're in fashion I just I'll look through all this and I'll think oh I like them and then I buy them</u>
<u n="709" who="S0319">mm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0255">is that your phone</u>
<u n="711" who="S0319">yeah it's just a base or something oh look little kitten heels</u>
<u n="712" who="S0255">these ones do you like them?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0319">no</u>
<u n="714" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0319">I know but it was just like seeing those little kitten heels</u>
<u n="716" who="S0255">yeah so they're not yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0319">but no</u>
<u n="718" who="S0255">yeah but no</u>
<u n="719" who="S0319">yeah you erm yeah you always look lovely and what have you and whenever I see you you know</u>
<u n="720" who="S0255">oh thank you</u>
<u n="721" who="S0319">you're erm those but they're suede aren't they?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0255">I'd just yeah pretend suede as well so you don't want pretend suede</u>
<u n="723" who="S0319">no you see I just but I spend my time whizzing through the ASOS sale Mango Oasis and all things like that and I don't always buy stuff out the sale but I just go on and think oh I want this or this flick through and pick out something I like and just wear it it's nice a lot of people say that what I wear looks nice</u>
<u n="724" who="S0319">you always yeah you always seem to be up you know as though you are up in with the fashion and stuff where I'm like miles behind oh my lord how and earth I know I wear heels and</u>
<u n="725" who="S0255">I think you wear those when you're sitting down and you have to get someone to carry you out the room <vocal desc="laugh"/> right next page</u>
<u n="726" who="S0319">oh dear I won't get any what on earth is that? ah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0255">snow heaven trainers trainers with a baggy white booty bit</u>
<u n="728" who="S0319">oh please</u>
<u n="729" who="S0255">I think in a way they've done so many different things they're running out of ideas</u>
<u n="730" who="S0319">of ideas</u>
<u n="731" who="S0255">and that they're trying to mash things together</u>
<u n="732" who="S0319">it's</u>
<u n="733" who="S0255">it doesn't work</u>
<u n="734" who="S0319">well not unless you live down London and you're sort of nineteen or something but</u>
<u n="735" who="S0255">oh yeah well but oh and look at them with the bits sticking up</u>
<u n="736" who="S0319">I know sticking up you get cramp in your toes</u>
<u n="737" who="S0255">it yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0319">well so far there isn't anything that floats my boat</u>
<u n="739" who="S0255">no I was thinking there might be the one my boots or the shoes boots they might still be though they might not be in the sale we'll have a look in the non-sale ones</u>
<u n="740" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0255">in fact actually we'll look at the non-sale jeans as well because we might find there'll be some straight ones</u>
<u n="742" who="S0319">straight ones</u>
<u n="743" who="S0255">yeah I just fine ASOS so easy because you just you joist look on it click click click bye it comes the next day if you don't like put it back in their bag with their label and send it back again</u>
<u n="744" who="S0319">de de see looking at them they're all suede which is no good</u>
<u n="745" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="746" who="S0319">cos if it's rain or whatever you're knackered you end up with wet feet</u>
<u n="747" who="S0255">come on don't do this to me again</u>
<u n="748" who="S0319">and them ones that I had on yesterday and what have you they're comfortable and they were those cheap things in Primark</u>
<u n="749" who="S0255">right just gonna look on the standard things then not looking in the</u>
<u n="750" who="S0319">no</u>
<u n="751" who="S0255">the normal sale</u>
<u n="752" who="S0319">no but they're like quilted inside so they keep my feet warm and well</u>
<u n="753" who="S0255">de dum let's do the jeans and finish off with those so cos we sort of know what we're looking for don't we?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0319">so you had to go into denim on that one?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0255">yeah so jeans are are denim or what did we say thirty-four?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0319">thirty-four regular</u>
<u n="757" who="S0255">yeah okay so we want jeans</u>
<u n="758" who="S0319">jumpsuits and playsuits</u>
<u n="759" who="S0255">do you want a jumpsuit or a playsuit?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0319">no they're no good for me no I wouldn't be able to get it off quick enough and that when you go to the loo</u>
<u n="761" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="762" who="S0319"><unclear/> sets in and you're like help</u>
<u n="763" who="S0255">I like your hair tied back like that it suits you off your face</u>
<u n="764" who="S0319">does it? thank you I should have seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and what have you cos I've had it sorted the other day but <trunc>sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was poorly and she had it as well so she's coming tomorrow morning now cover up my grey and it needs thinning out and what have you badly</u>
<u n="765" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0319">it's been long well you can see it's been a long long while but I've tried not to pester her and that because you know what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now? six months er so</u>
<u n="767" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0319">I mean you know she wants some time with the baby</u>
<u n="769" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0319">so they look bootleg I don't like them</u>
<u n="771" who="S0255">yeah no that's it kick flare jeans well they're coming back in but I you know</u>
<u n="772" who="S0319">no I don't I never have liked them</u>
<u n="773" who="S0255">de de de oh well these are with your ankles all exposed</u>
<u n="774" who="S0319">I yeah I'm doing that now I'll have them boots on cos these are not long enough</u>
<u n="775" who="S0255">er er er er just keep looking cos somewhere in here they'll be some straight leg jeans she says somewhere</u>
<u n="776" who="S0319">there's some ones I think they're probably the other ones</u>
<u n="777" who="S0255">they're the boyfriend ones or the skinny ones</u>
<u n="778" who="S0319">yeah</u>
<u n="779" who="S0255">the skinny ones I think they were the ones that we'd done <pause dur="short"/> g-Star midge sculptured bum lift skinny jeans they have them sort of pulled up to make your bum more pert</u>
<u n="780" who="S0319">ah dear</u>
<u n="781" who="S0255">it's like oh give us a break</u>
<u n="782" who="S0319">they'll be doing jeans next with them gel pads in them like the cyclists have</u>
<u n="783" who="S0255">yeah yeah well you can get pants like that can't you?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0319">oh god I didn't know that please</u>
<u n="785" who="S0255">you get pants with the bum implants</u>
<u n="786" who="S0319">no</u>
<u n="787" who="S0255">to give you a bit of booty toosh</u>
<u n="788" who="S0319"><vocal desc="laugh"/> god no thank you</u>
<u n="789" who="S0255">actually I'm gonna knock off the skinny I think cos oh no but you see that's the thing you can't <trunc>e</trunc> you can't do by you can just do jeans so we'll going to have to trawl a bit</u>
<u n="790" who="S0319">so they don't give you them when you get in that side the option of</u>
<u n="791" who="S0255">so they're straight but they're straggly at the bottom so you don't want those cos you'll be hemming them up</u>
<u n="792" who="S0319">no</u>
<u n="793" who="S0255">no with this bit it doesn't and they're slim but they're a bit not a nice colour <pause dur="short"/> it's fine that all the skinny side's in at the minute but you want to have an option cos the straight leg ones are just they're really flattering for us not teenage ladies boyfriend boyfriend oh there's straight legs</u>
<u n="794" who="S0319">you're as old as you feel number doesn't matter how old you are it's how you feel and at the moment I feel older than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="795" who="S0255" trans="overlap">that's it right shoes</u>
<u n="796" who="S0319">she's got more get up and go er</u>
<u n="797" who="S0255">let's try five and a half boots right that's it in the five and a half try the five there'll be masses in the five</u>
<u n="798" who="S0319">oh that oh no they're suede</u>
<u n="799" who="S0255">cor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dinner smells nice</u>
<u n="800" who="S0319">I was going to say what's she been</u>
<u n="801" who="S0255">I don't know</u>
<u n="802" who="S0319">I'll go and pinch it off her</u>
<u n="803" who="S0255">I don't know she's always eating she eats well to be fair she's a <pause dur="long"/> so what sort of heel do you like more of a pointed stiletto heel? or?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0319">I don't I I don't really want a chunky chunky one</u>
<u n="805" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="806" who="S0319">but it doesn't have to be a stiletto one</u>
<u n="807" who="S0255">yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="808" who="S0319">that you know I want it so it's</u>
<u n="809" who="S0255">yeah that's nice</u>
<u n="810" who="S0319">that's a nice sort of a heel</u>
<u n="811" who="S0255">yeah yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="812" who="S0319">I mean they're they're just gross look yuck</u>
<u n="813" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0319">what on earth are them things?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0255">you don't want to know</u>
<u n="816" who="S0319">see they're nice but they're suede them Karen Millen suede ones</u>
<u n="817" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0319">lovely colour</u>
<u n="819" who="S0255">you see now they're the ones I've got but they're suede but I wear them because they're only thirty-eight quid I think if they get ruined this winter I'll just buy more next year</u>
<u n="820" who="S0319">oh</u>
<u n="821" who="S0255">see if the thing is working</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
