<text id="S36Z">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:42</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-09</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home, China</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>babies </topics>
		<activity>couple takes a walk round their house</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0024">she's not drinking her camomile tea she's just chewing the top</u>
<u n="2" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah what does it feel like when your teeth are coming through? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0024">well I can't remember</u>
<u n="4" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0024">but I know the wisdom teeth kill</u>
<u n="6" who="S0144">yeah but why would it help to put pressure on it? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0024">it helps them break the gum which is why erm my mum said erm make some dry biscuit things like really hard biscuits for them to chew on to break the gum literally</u>
<u n="8" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0024">to help the tooth through must really hurt</u>
<u n="10" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0024">wisdom teeth really hurt don't they?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0024">oh actually I think I've only got one but the others keep pretending to grow and that hurts enough</u>
<u n="14" who="S0144">I don't know if I've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0024">I've got one I need it out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I need it out I've decided</u>
<u n="16" who="S0144" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0024">yeah I'm gonna go</u>
<u n="18" who="S0144">that's quite a big er operation</u>
<u n="19" who="S0024">it's er it's going it's er <vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't care I'm sure it affects my nerves sometimes and it's I hate it</u>
<u n="20" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0024">it feels like it doesn't belong</u>
<u n="22" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0024">what? I'm not supposed to be wise she likes her camomile tea look <pause dur="short"/> it's only a weak one it's only <trunc>r</trunc>really weak</u>
<u n="24" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0024">do you like it? <pause dur="short"/> better than just water er oh it's don't start her on juice though because then she gets a taste for it she won't have just plain water any more</u>
<u n="26" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0024">this is only camomile tea's only a hint of flavour <unclear/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm yeah it's not strong is it?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0144">what about marshmallow tea? is she allowed that?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0024">I don't know if people have er allergies to that and do you know ever since we had that marshmallow tea? that was lovely wasn't it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0024">erm I haven't seen it sold anywhere <unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0144">where did you get it from?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0024">we got it from where were we living? it was a little shop that suddenly had all these weird fruit teas <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0144">was it here?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0024">no not here <trunc>marshma</trunc> oh the you're spilling it my lovely <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>w</trunc> oh she has to get changed she's soaking wet I thought my <trunc>s</trunc> I thought a sippy cup was supposed to be so that they didn't spill it</u>
<u n="38" who="S0144">oh she <trunc>l</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> she looks cute like that</u>
<u n="39" who="S0024">you look cute in your little Labyrinth outfit <pause dur="short"/> oh she's soaking no she can't go out like this the wind is too strong oh my god her belly's soaking wet what have you been doing? oh well camomile tea is good for your skin erm yeah where were we? <pause dur="short"/> erm a little <trunc>s</trunc> corner shop</u>
<u n="40" who="S0144">was it <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0024"><trunc>w</trunc> I don't think it oh I I think it was quite a long time ago we were drinking marshmallow tea <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0144">mm?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0024"><anon type="place"/> it was ages ago it really was ages ago</u>
<u n="44" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it wasn't</u>
<u n="45" who="S0024">it really was ages ago it was <pause dur="short"/> well anyway what were we <trunc>s</trunc>? that was a funny texture ain't it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0024">I liked it I'd like to get it again I wonder if they've got it in that foreign shop cos they had all sorts of stuff didn't they? but I just didn't spend I felt quite rushed</u>
<u n="48" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0024">with just one hour to nip round wasn't kind of browsing</u>
<u n="50" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well it took us an hour as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0024">yeah well we weren't browsing</u>
<u n="52" who="S0144" trans="overlap">only got there with a few minutes to spare</u>
<u n="53" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we had to just focus on the meat <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the end yeah so I didn't really look at all those special vitamins and stuff they'd got and the teas but these fruit teas are so expensive</u>
<u n="54" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0024">and I'm sure they do the flowers for camomile at the supermarket but then I bought the wrong ones last time that look exactly the same as a camomile flower</u>
<u n="56" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0024">er so <pause dur="short"/> do you like that? do you like those?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0144">so what could we use instead of Bonjela?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="60" who="S0144">cos that's just aniseed isn't it?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0024">cloves</u>
<u n="62" who="S0144">cloves?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0024">cloves and aniseed but it's in a really minute quantity I'm guessing I don't really know what they put in Bonjela but I know that if you put clove when er we when your teeth come through when you're a bit older I remember we I put clove oil on but it's so strong that a baby can't have that can it?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0024">don't think</u>
<u n="66" who="S0144">don't know</u>
<u n="67" who="S0024">let me ask the girls they've all they've got four-month-old babies and the their teeth have already come through let me ask them what they've got</u>
<u n="68" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0024">whether they've got anything spare I'll put it on that <unclear>Mama's Wechat</unclear> thing <pause dur="short"/> nobody ever talks to me I <trunc>d</trunc>don't think people don't talk to each other unless you ask a question <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0024">you can't just put like a comment</u>
<u n="72" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0024">like when I was telling people where their that that the nurse told us you couldn't get vitamin D only in the hospital and stuff but that but then they just ignore me and talk between themselves because they're asking each other questions</u>
<u n="74" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0024">it's weird I don't know if I like it yet <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0144">mm but if you're not asking a question what what are they supposed to say?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0024">well I'm giving them answers to questions</u>
<u n="78" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="79" who="S0024">and</u>
<u n="80" who="S0144">and they don't say thank you?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0024">nobody cares no they say thank you to other people</u>
<u n="82" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><unclear>why are you stop dripping that everywhere</unclear></u>
<u n="83" who="S0024">oh oh my goodness you're dripping you're soaking wet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you'll get catch a cold like that did you enjoy that? did you? right we'll have to take this off now tut you look so cute</u>
<u n="84" who="S0144">are her trousers wet as well?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0024">only a little bit they'll be alright with erm they'll be alright with a different <trunc>t</trunc>top underneath oh my goodness come here Labyrinth baby oh and you've got a little hat on you really look like a Labyrinth baby I wanted a photo <pause dur="short"/> oh I might dress her up in erm the you know the dress that erm? tut oh I've forgotten her name <vocal desc="gasp"/> oh my god erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> S begins with an S the little pretty dress that we got given the other day by the girl who works in the first year office</u>
<u n="86" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tut I don't know why I forgot that I was gonna ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was gonna ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to put her in the dress and bring her to uni <vocal desc="laugh"/> bring her to uni for lunch and then I'll take her up to the first year office</u>
<u n="88" who="S0144">yeah cos I said you'll send her a photo</u>
<u n="89" who="S0024">yeah yeah I know I need a photo but I thought I'd just bring her instead yeah? <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I'm gonna put her in the dress and say erm at one o'clock come and meet me at <anon type="place"/> university yeah we'll go go to see our friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she'll like to see you yeah especially if you're wearing the pretty dress she bought you yeah? <pause dur="short"/> let's hope <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't made any arrangements for</u>
<u n="90" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0024">because well er <trunc>es</trunc>especially if the building work's going on all day I told her go make arrangements go round people's houses go go on play dates <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0024">like she can't stay here with</u>
<u n="94" who="S0144">no it was awful <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="95" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0144">give her a one it'll give her a headache and two it'll make her in put her in a bad mood</u>
<u n="97" who="S0024">yeah put you in a bad mood doesn't it? can you?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0144">you don't want that that's noisy for us</u>
<u n="99" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'm gonna just</u>
<u n="100" who="S0144">it must be you know? her her ears are gonna be a lot more sensitive than ours</u>
<u n="101" who="S0024">yeah they are they're at their peak right now I'm just gonna</u>
<u n="102" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah well not after all that noise today they're not</u>
<u n="103" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0144">can you turn that thing off now? with the</u>
<u n="105" who="S0024" trans="overlap">she's probably got really</u>
<u n="106" who="S0144">er I think the recorder's on you need to turn it off if you're <unclear/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0024">I'm just running to get a top</u>
<u n="108" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="109" who="S0024">cos she's cold I'll be two seconds</u>
<u n="110" who="S0144">okay <pause dur="short"/> you can talk to me can't you? eh? ah? well what have you been doing today then? huh? what you been up to? huh? where did you go? who did you see? who did you meet? what trouble did you get into? huh?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0024">well I thought I was gonna be two seconds but <unclear/> moved</u>
<u n="112" who="S0144"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0024">thought I was gonna be two seconds but it's all moved around everything's moved</u>
<u n="114" who="S0144">what's moved?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0024">the the long sleeved tops</u>
<u n="116" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="117" who="S0024">everything's been reorganised so</u>
<u n="118" who="S0144">you're getting too heavy missy</u>
<u n="119" who="S0024">right head put your arms in put your arms in there good girl there you go you gotta keep warm after that her tummy got really cold</u>
<u n="120" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0144">we're not going to be able to do this erm recording any more <trunc>on</trunc>once she starts speaking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0024">no it'll really interrupt things won't it? <unclear>here you go</unclear></u>
<u n="124" who="S0144">when she can actually say words it's gonna</u>
<u n="125" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that matches your dress <unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0144">unless we can get her to sign the er consent form</u>
<u n="127" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0144">put a little X on it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0024">right shall we wander down to the shop?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0024">hat</u>
<u n="132" who="S0144">do you wanna go down the shop <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? or is that a no? shall we stay here and chill out while mummy goes down the shop? yeah? oh that look no no come on</u>
<u n="133" who="S0024" trans="overlap">er yeah you can actually you can</u>
<u n="134" who="S0144">huh?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0024">you two you can stay together and I'll run down the shop that's alright</u>
<u n="136" who="S0144">well no cos then we were gonna go for a walk after I was only teasing you</u>
<u n="137" who="S0024">we don't need any cold stuff do we? milk or anything? we've <trunc>s</trunc> even stopped eating those yogurts <unclear/> they're er we loved those yogurts</u>
<u n="138" who="S0144">I don't really like the plain ones</u>
<u n="139" who="S0024">get rid of them then I think they're out of date now anyway</u>
<u n="140" who="S0144">er <trunc>d</trunc> you need to straighten her hat a little bit</u>
<u n="141" who="S0024">why? she looks nice wonky</u>
<u n="142" who="S0144">no at the front it's the the <unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah here you go oh this is this hat's quite small we need a new hat for the winter it's cute ain't it? look how cute that hat is <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0144">mm come on then <vocal desc="misc"/> I'm absolutely knackered</u>
<u n="145" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I think really should we do a pram because she looks quite tired? we can always lift the pram over</u>
<u n="146" who="S0144" trans="overlap">er yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> we can do that</u>
<u n="147" who="S0024">we could always yeah we could always lift the pram over the stupid railings that they've put there</u>
<u n="148" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0024">in you get <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0144"><vocal desc="sigh"/> what else do we need to get then?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0024">bananas and tomatoes and can you just check the onions?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0144">yeah we always need onions</u>
<u n="153" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <unclear/> they don't always have good onions there</u>
<u n="154" who="S0144">no we've got one</u>
<u n="155" who="S0024">one good onion?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0144">no we've got a couple <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0024">oh oh oh left <unclear/> shoes in front of the cupboard</u>
<u n="158" who="S0144">sorry we've got a <trunc>coup</trunc> we've got a couple of onions but I don't know how good they are</u>
<u n="159" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that was my fault I <unclear/> might just wear these flat shoes should I wear? I don't know if she's in the pram I could wear high heels couldn't I? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> talking about shoes again</u>
<u n="162" who="S0144">gonna be like er a milf in the supermarket <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0024">what's a milf?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0144">mm?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0024">oh yeah milf yeah yeah that's what I wanna be</u>
<u n="166" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that your ambition?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0024">yeah yeah that's what I'm <trunc>w</trunc> I'm I'm working towards</u>
<u n="168" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0024">that's why I've bought all the high heeled shoes and stuff</u>
<u n="170" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0024">but then I <trunc>h</trunc>I haven't bought enough flat shoes for work <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0144" trans="overlap">to get some little have to get you some little hot pants or some mini skirts <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0024">where?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0144">are we going now?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0024">we need a blanket just er no we've got blanket I've got no money no phone</u>
<u n="176" who="S0144">I've got money</u>
<u n="177" who="S0024">erm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0144">and a phone</u>
<u n="179" who="S0024">I've got no key</u>
<u n="180" who="S0144">and I've got a key</u>
<u n="181" who="S0024">oh you're organised</u>
<u n="182" who="S0144">well what would you do without me?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> do I need anything then? I'm not gonna take anything</u>
<u n="184" who="S0144">no has she got her socks on?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0024">she's got socks on <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> yeah she looks happy in her pram today</u>
<u n="186" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well if I pass you the key</u>
<u n="187" who="S0024">I really wanted to do a walk with erm her in the thing but we'll just have to do a walk with her in the pram instead it's a bit windy anyway isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0144">yeah can I grab one of these pieces of wood?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0024">I can't lock the door <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0144">ah grab that</u>
<u n="191" who="S0024">did you <unclear/> that with a hammer?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0144">no someone else broke it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="194" who="S0144">I think the cleaner must be as pissed off as we are <pause dur="short"/> so she smashed it</u>
<u n="195" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> slowly smashing it to pieces</u>
<u n="196" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="197" who="S0024">can't believe the landlady</u>
<u n="198" who="S0144">every time I'm going out I'm trying to take a piece</u>
<u n="199" who="S0024">yeah?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0144">but there's so many left</u>
<u n="201" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0144">it's crazy</u>
<u n="203" who="S0024">well that</u>
<u n="204" who="S0144">just gonna be doing it for the next ten months</u>
<u n="205" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what are you gonna do? smash that whole cupboard? you need to buy you a hammer</u>
<u n="206" who="S0144">unless I spent a couple of hours one evening just doing it but</u>
<u n="207" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0144">I've got better things to do really <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0144">I mean er how how much does it annoy you?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you're not allowed to smash things with a hammer past seven o'clock</u>
<u n="212" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0024">that's <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0024">that's what they <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="216" who="S0144" trans="overlap">look she's falling asleep already</u>
<u n="217" who="S0024">yeah are you tired? yeah I think she is she can have a little <unclear/> nap er oh</u>
<u n="218" who="S0144">er oh</u>
<u n="219" who="S0024">er oh are you alright? we're gonna get moving soon look there's the man the man in the lift <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0144"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0024">there</u>
<u n="222" who="S0144">sorry</u>
<u n="223" who="S0024">that's alright <pause dur="short"/> oh have you got the other card to get back in too?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="225" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0144">yeah think so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0024">otherwise we'll have to press all the buttons <pause dur="long"/> right what do we need?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0024">did you check the onions?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0144">mm?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0024">did you check onions?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0144">onions? yeah we got two I said</u>
<u n="233" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="234" who="S0144">she's got a big bogey on her face</u>
<u n="235" who="S0024">oh dear <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0144" trans="overlap">were you saving that for later? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0024">oh it's stuck now tut oh</u>
<u n="238" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0024">tissue</u>
<u n="240" who="S0144" trans="overlap">rub it on that leaf up there <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0024">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0144">why?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0024">I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0144">what difference does that make?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> dunno <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0144">so it's okay rub to rub it on the floor but you won't rub it on a leaf on a tree</u>
<u n="247" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that wasn't on the floor that was on a <trunc>l</trunc>on a leaf on the floor there you go a caterpillar can eat it</u>
<u n="248" who="S0144">a caterpillar can eat it? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno I dunno</u>
<u n="250" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? are you gonna grow up this silly?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I think people'll think that I'm just disgusting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0144">you can rub a bogey on a leaf</u>
<u n="253" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0144">especially when it's a baby's bogey <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> where are the tissues <trunc>anyw</trunc>? oh we must buy boxes of tissues we're out</u>
<u n="256" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="257" who="S0024">oh somebody has to run upstairs then</u>
<u n="258" who="S0144">I'll run upstairs</u>
<u n="259" who="S0024">you know erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that she <trunc>snea</trunc> she goes in erm and walks straight to the back of the supermarket and gets in the lift and you end up in the storeroom bit and they're all eating their lunch</u>
<u n="260" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what? what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0024">erm to get up</u>
<u n="262" who="S0144">you can do that?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0024">you <trunc>c</trunc> well apparently because I said erm I took I've taken her before and they've never let me go in the lift so I've left the pram downstairs and gone up the escalator</u>
<u n="264" who="S0144">you don't wanna leave that that's like four hundred quid or whatever it is</u>
<u n="265" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well I left it with with the helpers with the people working there the one that's working behind the cigarette counter</u>
<u n="266" who="S0144" trans="overlap">right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0024">I've said can you look after the pram? she was like oh</u>
<u n="268" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0024">and then <trunc>s</trunc>and then she said yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0024"><trunc>s</trunc> and then I couldn't get back on the escalator cos I'm a bit scared of them aren't I? getting down</u>
<u n="272" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0024">and I had the shopping trolley and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I had to get someone to help me lift the basket anyway onto the escalator</u>
<u n="274" who="S0144">oh <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0024">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she just wheels the pram on the escalator</u>
<u n="276" who="S0144">on the escalator?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0024">yeah she's got a double pram with two babies in it god knows how she does that? she reckons she's a pro</u>
<u n="278" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah you could go up the escalator</u>
<u n="279" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0144">yeah we'll do that</u>
<u n="281" who="S0024">shall we try?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0024">well we've gotta try it one day so <trunc>sh</trunc> they they've been going up and down escalators if they can't find lifts</u>
<u n="284" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0024">with a pram</u>
<u n="286" who="S0144">I just don't know with the basket on the bottom of the pram with the lips with the the stairs</u>
<u n="287" who="S0024">ah yeah that might</u>
<u n="288" who="S0144">I don't know if it'll work</u>
<u n="289" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well we don't have haven't got much in it now <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0144">but will it snap it? I mean</u>
<u n="291" who="S0024">no it should just lift it up</u>
<u n="292" who="S0144" trans="overlap">or does it move? oh okay</u>
<u n="293" who="S0024"><vocal desc="cough"/> oh excuse me</u>
<u n="294" who="S0144">that was</u>
<u n="295" who="S0024">oh where did that come from? <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0144"><unclear>want me</unclear> to answer that?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0144">your question</u>
<u n="299" who="S0024">what? where did it come from?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0024"><unclear>think the</unclear> camomile tea <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="302" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0024">eh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0144"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0024">oh she looks a bit grumpy now</u>
<u n="306" who="S0144">she always looks grumpy at this time of night</u>
<u n="307" who="S0024" trans="overlap">are you alright? <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0144">it's cos she's looking more chubby now</u>
<u n="309" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0144">not as cute looking is she?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0024">I don't know what she looks like any more cos erm it's weird isn't it? can you see? cos I can't see myself in her can you see yourself in her?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0144">dunno she looks a bit like the milkman <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0024">she she used to really look like you but now I don't know I dunno she's just got such a mixture of features</u>
<u n="314" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0024">that er I can't tell <unclear/> she's still got your eyebrows</u>
<u n="316" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0024">and the shape of your your eyes hasn't she? your eyelids</u>
<u n="318" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0024">but she's got brown eyes like me now</u>
<u n="320" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0024">and she's got my lips and <unclear/> what <unclear>nose</unclear> she's got</u>
<u n="322" who="S0144">she's got a baby <unclear>nose</unclear> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0024">yeah I guess cos she's quite chubby you just people look very different when they've got puffy cheeks</u>
<u n="324" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I can't tell what she's gonna look like at all</u>
<u n="325" who="S0024">I hope she's pretty</u>
<u n="326" who="S0144">I think she'll be pretty</u>
<u n="327" who="S0024">a little bit pretty anyway <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0144">mm you're not bad looking are you?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I think we <trunc>g</trunc> I think we're alright</u>
<u n="330" who="S0144">yeah so and our families are quite good looking I'd say</u>
<u n="331" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0144">so she's in good good hands with her genes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0024">ah did you hear that? yeah especially if we buy you some more cute hats like that where did you get that one from?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0144">mm?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0024">I like the little fluffy bit on the side</u>
<u n="336" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0024">it looks kind of like a beret <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like the way she does that with her hands she looks like a French philosopher</u>
<u n="339" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0024">I wonder if she's looking at like the energy that you use you get around like your hands and stuff</u>
<u n="341" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0024">I wonder if she looks at that and can see it</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144">maybe</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">or can see the colours of people's auras or anything like that</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0024">do you think?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144">well I used to watch the energy coming out of my fingers</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024">mm like cos babies are so pure they wouldn't know any different</u>
<u n="349" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024">they might be able to see things that we just can't see</u>
<u n="351" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0024"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0144">I wonder if she sees <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0024">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0024">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144">he's my shadow</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">he walks three metres behind me</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh <unclear>don't</unclear> it's like Twin Peaks <unclear>it's horrible</unclear></u>
<u n="361" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hang on let me turn this</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
