<text id="S376">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:33:46</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-03-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0187 S0188 S0200 S0387</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Bristol, home of all speakers</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Experiences, Celebrities, Work, Other family members, Living arrangements, Internet, Other people, university.</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about their current and future situations</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0187">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Fishponds</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2.5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>e_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0188">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wrexham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Ellesmere</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0200">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Enfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0387">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bridgewater</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southwest</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bristol</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0187">who did you bump into?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0200">our mate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0187">so did so did we actually</u>
<u n="4" who="S0200">do <trunc>a</trunc> did he say?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0187">er hey you guys are from <anon type="place"/> er come over it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and it's when we left when they left you two to come back to meet me cos I was going home and er he was I was like no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go and walk and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> felt sorry for him so we went and said hi</u>
<u n="6" who="S0387">he just said to us have you voted? and I was like I haven't voted but did any of you vote? it's like nah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0200" trans="overlap">hey guys <pause dur="short"/> I said yeah we voted and he was like ah well damn shame</u>
<u n="8" who="S0387">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I should have said made you pose for me in our er</u>
<u n="9" who="S0187">yeah I know</u>
<u n="10" who="S0200">that looks like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from the back</u>
<u n="11" who="S0187">should have said something I I think I said something but like something not great but but I can't remember what it was it was something like I wouldn't vote for you or something</u>
<u n="12" who="S0200"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0187">but I do it was like one of those things that I mumbled under my breath but wanted him to hear at the same time <pause dur="short"/> it was like we were never friends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't</u>
<u n="14" who="S0200">yeah like let's not start pretending now</u>
<u n="15" who="S0387">he was weird wasn't he? for me it's like normally like oh like you know me so you get my vote I'm like no I know you and that's why you're not going to get my vote and can't blag it off for some like manifesto</u>
<u n="16" who="S0187" trans="overlap">I think that's what I said <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0200" trans="overlap">I just that's no claim to anything</u>
<u n="18" who="S0387">I was surprised I've literally not been to see him I've only been there two days but no one's come up to me with anything</u>
<u n="19" who="S0187">I've had stuff</u>
<u n="20" who="S0387">cos in second year someone came up to me shook my hand was like alright mate I'm er blah blah blah blah I'm running for</u>
<u n="21" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0200">they gave me sweets</u>
<u n="23" who="S0187">yeah that you know the girl <pause dur="short"/> that like she like looks l like Spanish in her like colour and everything but she I think she's Iranian or something like that <pause dur="short"/> like a bit taller than me probably not even taller than me</u>
<u n="24" who="S0387">is she running or something?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0187">she's yeah she's running for something but she did it last year as well and she came up to me and some other people last year and was like basically took us through her whole policy on immigration or</u>
<u n="26" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0187">or integration or something like that</u>
<u n="28" who="S0200">it's all the same innit?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0387">did you vote for her?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0187">er I can't remember I did vote for someone last year I can't remember whether she was the one or</u>
<u n="31" who="S0200">I just voted for them to stop emailing them and they have I'm going to stop voting don't email me anymore</u>
<u n="32" who="S0187">what do they email you on your UE one?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0200">no my private one as well</u>
<u n="34" who="S0187">I only check that every so often</u>
<u n="35" who="S0387">no I had that like you er you voted last last year we really need your vote this year</u>
<u n="36" who="S0200">yeah just vote and then get them out the way I was sick <unclear>of listening</unclear></u>
<u n="37" who="S0387" trans="overlap">I said last year they actually did really well like I really liked the we <trunc>s</trunc> you said we did</u>
<u n="38" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0387">that was good I l liked the printer credit <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>i</trunc> other than that I don't really know what they do</u>
<u n="40" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0200"><unclear/> who still has those?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0187">I might have a look at the erm I've got shitloads of printing credits left cos I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't use them</u>
<u n="43" who="S0200">do you just not print?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0187">I don't need to</u>
<u n="45" who="S0387">I top up like fifty quid every now and again</u>
<u n="46" who="S0187">fifty quid?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0387">I go through that in like nothing</u>
<u n="48" who="S0200">yeah <unclear/> I do mine</u>
<u n="49" who="S0387">I mean you printed what did you print today?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0200">I printed about a hundred and seventy pages today</u>
<u n="51" who="S0387">did you do that on my account?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0200">no my account</u>
<u n="53" who="S0187">I've probably printed about ten pages all year maybe I don't even think I've I've spent a quid</u>
<u n="54" who="S0387">at the beginning at the end of last year just to use up my allowance I put about a hundred quid in</u>
<u n="55" who="S0187">I don't know what</u>
<u n="56" who="S0387">and it's gone</u>
<u n="57" who="S0187">I don't know cos I don't have anything to <vocal desc="cough"/> I don't have anything to print what are you lot printing?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0387">I've got reports and cases to read</u>
<u n="59" who="S0200">journal articles</u>
<u n="60" who="S0187">I just read everything online</u>
<u n="61" who="S0387">I can't</u>
<u n="62" who="S0200">that's probably why</u>
<u n="63" who="S0187">yeah I don't</u>
<u n="64" who="S0387">I like to annotate it highlight it write in the margin</u>
<u n="65" who="S0187">sometimes I have an issue with not being able to yeah sometimes that bothers me but like I printed <pause dur="short"/> tell a lie I probably printed about fifteen cos I for my dissertation on I had to <pause dur="short"/> yeah for my dissertation I had to transcribe interviews and stuff and I needed them but and I I needed to annotate it but apart from that</u>
<u n="66" who="S0200">like even even an essay I will probably print out seven times proofread it go over it and go over it and go over it</u>
<u n="67" who="S0187"><unclear>god</unclear></u>
<u n="68" who="S0387" trans="overlap">I really like this film</u>
<u n="69" who="S0187">I wanted to watch that mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0387">it's really really good <pause dur="short"/> he won an Oscar for this didn't he?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0200">no he got nominated didn't win it</u>
<u n="72" who="S0187" trans="overlap">no er I saw the I saw the picture like the poster in some in <anon type="place"/> Oscar-nominated</u>
<u n="73" who="S0200">it's just the thing he's just like erm the camera went up to him afterwards and he was just like oh piss off</u>
<u n="74" who="S0187">really?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0200">acting like a he was he was only joking</u>
<u n="76" who="S0187">oh right</u>
<u n="77" who="S0200">but er yeah acting pretty pissed</u>
<u n="78" who="S0187">Benedict Cumberbatch <pause dur="short"/> the Maze Runner?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0200">yeah it's alright</u>
<u n="80" who="S0387">it's Hunger Games-esque so if you like The Hunger Games watch it if not don't</u>
<u n="81" who="S0200">I don't think it's that it's like that but</u>
<u n="82" who="S0387">if you're into that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="83" who="S0200">oh yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0387">watch it if not don't</u>
<u n="85" who="S0187">I might get involved at the weekend actually</u>
<u n="86" who="S0200">it's worth a watch it's alright it's not bad at all</u>
<u n="87" who="S0187">yeah I might get involved mate I might get involved</u>
<u n="88" who="S0200">nice mate nice</u>
<u n="89" who="S0387">when does Alzheimer's generally strike? like sevent eighties? <pause dur="short"/> he's been on the news far too much for my liking like he's not that big much of a big deal</u>
<u n="90" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0187">three hundred and fifty million viewers</u>
<u n="92" who="S0387">I saw that thirty different countries</u>
<u n="93" who="S0200">and then what was it? fifty million pound a year for the BBC bearing in mind they don't advertise so</u>
<u n="94" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0200">that's a lot of money although I saw we have a TV licence letter downstairs</u>
<u n="96" who="S0187">oh really have we? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0387"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has</u>
<u n="98" who="S0187"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it expired the other day</u>
<u n="99" who="S0200">yeah so I don't know what we do with that?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0387">as long as we don't watch live TV we're good</u>
<u n="101" who="S0187">it's always TV's always on downstairs</u>
<u n="102" who="S0200">is it?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0187">yes</u>
<u n="104" who="S0200">I don't fucking watch it</u>
<u n="105" who="S0387">but generally we we only watch Netflix so and <trunc>Sk</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> and Sky on demand</u>
<u n="106" who="S0200">yeah you <unclear/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0387">you do</u>
<u n="108" who="S0200">but <trunc>i</trunc> it on the other side of the coin though it is only twenty quid</u>
<u n="109" who="S0387">twenty quid</u>
<u n="110" who="S0200">between us for the year</u>
<u n="111" who="S0387">I'm not getting it this year</u>
<u n="112" who="S0187">yeah but what's the point in paying it for? I watch it I wouldn't it wouldn't be a loss to my life if I stopped watching it but</u>
<u n="113" who="S0200" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0387">from now until September</u>
<u n="115" who="S0200">but the other thing is they don't know the only thing is is that the living room TV is connected to an aerial and if they come in they'll go you've obviously been watching TV</u>
<u n="116" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0200">so that's</u>
<u n="118" who="S0187" trans="overlap">you're allowed to you're allowed to tell them no once aren't you? and then if they come back with a warrant</u>
<u n="119" who="S0387">yeah cos I said no last year and then we paid it</u>
<u n="120" who="S0200">yeah we paid it before he came back round</u>
<u n="121" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0200">but you can stream and stuff but you can just put the laptop on or an Xbox or whatever</u>
<u n="123" who="S0187">yeah you see I think watching is just the ease of I <trunc>ha</trunc> I've got my dinner I put it on the table and I eat like watching TV but</u>
<u n="124" who="S0387" whoConfidence="low">eat we eat in here generally don't we? <pause dur="short"/> pretty much</u>
<u n="125" who="S0187">yeah I like eating either either in the kitchen or in there</u>
<u n="126" who="S0387">I I never watch live TV</u>
<u n="127" who="S0200">yeah you don't need it if you stream like BBC Iplayer or</u>
<u n="128" who="S0187">mm a lot of the time I think though <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got it on like he'll be in there and have it in the background while he's doing something or whatever and it'll be on I'll come in and sit with him and just watch whatever shit's on TV I like having it but I'm not really arsed</u>
<u n="129" who="S0387">I sit and watch I sit while we've been watching on demand I miss live TV I like to flip through the channels</u>
<u n="130" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0387">sometimes you <trunc>wa</trunc> you watch stuff you wouldn't normally watch</u>
<u n="132" who="S0187">yeah I think when I just end up streaming everything or like net if we're on Netflix or whatever there's there's an odd feeling about it like it's just unlimited like I could just be sat here all day whereas yeah I don't feel like that with TV</u>
<u n="133" who="S0200" trans="overlap">yeah it's too much it's too much really</u>
<u n="134" who="S0387">I was reading on erm ten ways recently erm if you've got Sky broadband if you ring them up and say you wanna cancel</u>
<u n="135" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0387">they say why? and I think the person said oh I've found a better offer with Virgin or something and they're like oh we'll match it and he said oh I want to cancel anyway cos I get a voucher when I join with them and they said we'll give you twelve months free</u>
<u n="137" who="S0187">fucking hell</u>
<u n="138" who="S0387">twelve months that's a massive</u>
<u n="139" who="S0200" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0187">mum's on the verge of signing well mum and dad are on the verge of signing up to Sky broadband</u>
<u n="141" who="S0200">see it's shit where I am and no one has it</u>
<u n="142" who="S0387" trans="overlap">it's great where I am</u>
<u n="143" who="S0187">we're we're on AOL and we're supposed to be getting eight megabytes like we get sixty here don't we?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0200">a hundred and twenty</u>
<u n="145" who="S0187">oh did we up it?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0187">yeah well yeah we were supposed to get an eight and we were getting one point four or something like that it's essentially fucking dial-up</u>
<u n="148" who="S0387">we were on IO AOL with dial-up I used to love the noise <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0187">it's ridiculous it's so <trunc>r</trunc> it's so ridiculous ah dial-up's fucking quicker than the shit we were rocking at home</u>
<u n="150" who="S0200">I I have no signal <unclear/> for the last three days <pause dur="short"/> I have to wait until we go into <anon type="place"/> to get signal</u>
<u n="151" who="S0187">I warned you bruv</u>
<u n="152" who="S0200">it's a fucking shambles</u>
<u n="153" who="S0387">I thought you said my house my house is fine for signal the one thing with dial-up that used to piss me off is I used to play online gaming and then mum'd be like oh I'm going to call nan now so they put the phone back in and I'm like no no</u>
<u n="154" who="S0187" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I used yeah we trying to play on the Xbox <pause dur="short"/> I don't I can't even remember whether that was even just the wifi was the wifi used to fuck with the the phone used to fuck the wifi up as well at one point <pause dur="short"/> it's not even it's not even funny I've</u>
<u n="155" who="S0200">I've never ever had a problem with internet</u>
<u n="156" who="S0187">genuinely fallen out with dad about it at times like</u>
<u n="157" who="S0200" whoConfidence="low">get it fixed</u>
<u n="158" who="S0387"><unclear/> the one thing that really annoys me with this place is if you've got no internet you deal with it if you've got internet it's great but this it's it'll be on it'll be off it'll be on then flip off</u>
<u n="159" who="S0187">I don't really have that problem I had it last night before I went to bed and I was like well that was only really with my Xbox for some reason and then it came back and I was like well I'm going to sleep anyway</u>
<u n="160" who="S0200">that's the thing like he moans about it but look how far away we are from the box</u>
<u n="161" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0200">and there are at least twenty-one things hooked up to that thing</u>
<u n="163" who="S0187">so much innit?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0387" trans="overlap">I said to you I was downstairs in the living room and it wasn't connecting</u>
<u n="165" who="S0187">I never have a problem with it really</u>
<u n="166" who="S0200">me neither like cos <pause dur="short"/> my things have got this <unclear/> as well so if I never really have an issue</u>
<u n="167" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0387">that's the good thing about next year there's gonna be less of us less devices</u>
<u n="169" who="S0187">yeah still get the same kind of deal or a similar deal</u>
<u n="170" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0187">and have shit hot internet</u>
<u n="172" who="S0200" trans="overlap">just less people to divide the bills by is what that means</u>
<u n="173" who="S0187">true but that's what we get a job for</u>
<u n="174" who="S0387">let's take a look at the energy rating in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are going to stay overnight just to make sure it's not cold I said I'm running the shower and then flushing the toilet I'm not having a house that <pause dur="short"/> that does that again</u>
<u n="175" who="S0187" trans="overlap">that's fair that's fair enough <pause dur="short"/> this does piss me off here like you have to have very conscious of what times I have a shower and stuff</u>
<u n="176" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0387">that's it if we get up late and someone starts like cleaning and washing up we're screwed but it's our own fault for getting up late</u>
<u n="178" who="S0187">yeah your time your your times screw you over</u>
<u n="179" who="S0200">yeah but to honest with you it only it happened to me the first time today since I've been back</u>
<u n="180" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0200">and I've been back a a week tomorrow I think <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="182" who="S0387"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has been shouting a lot recently I've heard</u>
<u n="183" who="S0187">he's always fucking shouting</u>
<u n="184" who="S0200">he just needs to get on with it like</u>
<u n="185" who="S0187">just move the shower out the way and</u>
<u n="186" who="S0200" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="187" who="S0187">wait</u>
<u n="188" who="S0200">you do that though</u>
<u n="189" who="S0187"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>si</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sits in sits in there and just takes it</u>
<u n="190" who="S0200">that's what he does and he's like ah it's like fucking move it then</u>
<u n="191" who="S0187">yeah it's not like it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0200">oh it's really hot it's burning me</u>
<u n="193" who="S0187">take it off you</u>
<u n="194" who="S0387">oh cos it takes ages I just want to get clean</u>
<u n="195" who="S0200">it is literally moving the shower head</u>
<u n="196" who="S0387" trans="overlap">yeah but you've got to wait and you get cold</u>
<u n="197" who="S0200">or you can burn</u>
<u n="198" who="S0187">or you burn or you get frozen</u>
<u n="199" who="S0200">that that's what I hate</u>
<u n="200" who="S0387">I can embrace the cold</u>
<u n="201" who="S0200">I can't handle that cold I cannot handle</u>
<u n="202" who="S0187">I just yeah I get frustrated but</u>
<u n="203" who="S0387">your body numbs after a while and you can't feel it</u>
<u n="204" who="S0187">yeah but I don't want my body to numb</u>
<u n="205" who="S0200">exactly like and when it gets hot again you you just have to itch and stuff</u>
<u n="206" who="S0187">I just I just put it off me</u>
<u n="207" who="S0200">yeah exactly a simple thing to do even in Barbados that shower was cold and it was hot I fucking hated it I was so relieved when I <unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0200">have a nice hot shower</u>
<u n="210" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0387">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think I told you in erm before I came to uni I had my gap year <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had a house and her shower like it was ice cold and it had its own generator it would as it would make a noise to generate heat but it'd be pure hot so it would literally be in like maybe ten seconds every sixty that you'd have to jump in and jump back out</u>
<u n="212" who="S0187" trans="overlap">so shit <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0200">where was that?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0387">huh?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0200">where was that?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0387">don't know where it was it was in a block of flats</u>
<u n="217" who="S0200">no where were you?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0387"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="219" who="S0200">oh right I didn't I didn't hear the rest of the story cos I was</u>
<u n="220" who="S0387">that I couldn't handle</u>
<u n="221" who="S0187">what?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0387">ten seconds every sixty like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0187">yeah it's a joke</u>
<u n="224" who="S0200">we <unclear/> the shower generates its own hot water</u>
<u n="225" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0200">you can flush the toilet you can <pause dur="short"/> you can run a million taps in the house it never makes a difference</u>
<u n="227" who="S0387">the worst thing they had for a year was over Christmas when everyone went home and I was here for work and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had turned off the heating when I was out so I got up for work there was no cold water so I had to I had like five pans on the stove had the kettle going trying to fill up a bath</u>
<u n="228" who="S0187">yeah it's not it's not great to be honest I think we we had we've got it at home where <pause dur="short"/> because of the farm like dad got the water sorted out I think but we've got an electric shower because of the farm sometimes like if they're power washing or something we just get horrendous water pressure so</u>
<u n="229" who="S0200" trans="overlap">oh like a dribble</u>
<u n="230" who="S0187">so yeah it comes out a dribble and it's really hot and it'll go stronger if you put it round down to the cold but yeah it's</u>
<u n="231" who="S0387">and when the pressure is right it's freezing cold</u>
<u n="232" who="S0187">yeah it's fucking minging but he's got it sorted now cos <unclear/> but if if they are power washing we're still still fucked</u>
<u n="233" who="S0200">I I the worst I had here was the downstairs toilet wouldn't stop flushing</u>
<u n="234" who="S0187">oh yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0200">and I was upstairs I'd just woke up I was so angry</u>
<u n="236" who="S0187">I think I remember that</u>
<u n="237" who="S0200">I came downstairs like who the fuck <pause dur="short"/> is running that tap?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0187" trans="overlap">yeah anytime anyone I think that was I might I thought it was me but it wasn't me or something we spoke about that I can't remember what it was</u>
<u n="239" who="S0200">I I remember some I remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> being in the kitchen or something I</u>
<u n="240" who="S0187" trans="overlap">you ripped his head off didn't you?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0200">I ripped somebody's head off</u>
<u n="242" who="S0187" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you ripped <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s head off</u>
<u n="243" who="S0200" trans="overlap">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s head off</u>
<u n="244" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0200">I came out was like is that fucking you? he was like what? <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="246" who="S0387">hello mate</u>
<u n="247" who="S0188">I thought you were still at <anon type="place"/> I saw your door</u>
<u n="248" who="S0187" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0188">open and your light off can't still be at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0200">they're going to terrorise each other</u>
<u n="251" who="S0188">have you seen the demonstration on the news?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0187" trans="overlap">of what? what?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0188">at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0387">what?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0187">it's been on the news?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0188">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0387">what demonstration?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0187">what the one that we went past earlier? ha is it actually?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0188" trans="overlap">yeah you know you know where you turn left it's on it's like you know you turn left at the lights?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0188" trans="overlap">and you got there they were building constructions I don't know they've got fucking tree houses in the thingy</u>
<u n="263" who="S0187">I haven't looked at it properly cos every time I look every time I go past I've driven</u>
<u n="264" who="S0188">you know as you go towards <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0188">and you turn left at the lights don't you?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0187" trans="overlap">you know where the <trunc>hi</trunc> where the hippies go?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0387">ah we saw the police and that?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0188">yeah you know that thing over there?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0188">like on the right that woodland bit?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0188">well they've been demonstrating for fucking weeks ain't they cos they want to knock it down and build summat</u>
<u n="274" who="S0200">I haven't seen that's on an M <unclear>though</unclear> innit?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0387">cos we saw construction there we've seen police</u>
<u n="276" who="S0188">yeah that's</u>
<u n="277" who="S0200">is it the allotments?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0188">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0200">ah yeah that's where the new stadium's gonna be innit?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0188">that's what er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0387">cos there's that massive sign you know like <trunc>sa</trunc>save our allotment</u>
<u n="284" who="S0200">ah shit yeah maybe yeah cos they are building aren't they?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0188">I was just standing at the <unclear/> and looked up and then that's fucking <anon type="place"/> on the on the telly</u>
<u n="286" who="S0187">that's it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0188">and it's just some fucking bloke in a tree going ah fuck ah ah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0387"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0187" trans="overlap">what time was it?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0188">just <unclear/> like that in the in the fucking tree there's somebody in the</u>
<u n="291" who="S0200">probably fucking living up there ain't he?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0188">yeah no they are ain't they? they're sleeping up there they look rough as fuck mind <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0187">fucking idiots</u>
<u n="294" who="S0387">you'd take turns wasn't it? like I stay here tonight you guys go home</u>
<u n="295" who="S0188">yeah go home</u>
<u n="296" who="S0200">mind you home's probably a bush somewhere else though innit?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0188">what?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0200">home's probably a bush somewhere else</u>
<u n="299" who="S0387" trans="overlap">they probably live in the shed in their allotment that's why</u>
<u n="300" who="S0200">that's a <unclear/> bus innit?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0187">no that's just the first bus they're all over the country</u>
<u n="303" who="S0188">they're nice very Christmassy they are</u>
<u n="304" who="S0187">someone laughed at me today</u>
<u n="305" who="S0188">why?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0187">this girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on my course turned round and literally started laughing and we were like <pause dur="short"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought she was being weird but she was actually she was laughing at my socks cos I didn't have any shoes on</u>
<u n="307" who="S0188">yeah you I've noticed that you take your shoes off don't you?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0387"><unclear/> get comfy</u>
<u n="310" who="S0188">yeah aye yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0187">yeah aye yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0387">I do it if I'm staying there for a while</u>
<u n="313" who="S0187">yeah I did it earlier I was sat in that room in <anon type="place"/> just with no shoes on</u>
<u n="314" who="S0188">I can't my feet stink and my shoes stink as well that's why my room stinks to a degree I've all my shoes in there ain't I? and they all fucking stink</u>
<u n="315" who="S0387">that whole bag of shoes you brought up I threw out</u>
<u n="316" who="S0187">thank fuck for that we were going to throw them out anyway</u>
<u n="317" who="S0188">we did want to try them out but I thought we can't throw shoes out</u>
<u n="318" who="S0387">no you can throw them out</u>
<u n="319" who="S0187"><trunc>moul</trunc>mouldy shoes</u>
<u n="320" who="S0200" trans="overlap">I knew they hadn't been worn in a while to be fair</u>
<u n="321" who="S0387">I ain't worked in a while that's why</u>
<u n="322" who="S0188">you can't you can't fucking work in those fucking massive fucking brick things with mould on them</u>
<u n="323" who="S0187">clodhoppers you called them</u>
<u n="324" who="S0188">yeah fucking clodhoppers</u>
<u n="325" who="S0187">have you show have you shown <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the the houses?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0188">I had a look at them yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0187">tidy innit? what's the one we're looking at on <trunc>Fr</trunc></u>
<u n="329" who="S0188"><anon type="place"/> road pictures don't look great but I just though it's just a viewing innit?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0188"><unclear/> innit? we</u>
<u n="332" who="S0187">and you can you can drive so if it's a shithole it's your petrol we waste</u>
<u n="333" who="S0188">fine</u>
<u n="334" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0387">sound I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> earlier like as long as there's three of us to go somewhere and as long as that's not including me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0200">what I was going to say but the thing is is there's five of us looking at a four bedroom house</u>
<u n="337" who="S0188">I've thought of this like what are we gonna say if they you can't share a room</u>
<u n="338" who="S0200">I think maybe one of us should go and the other one should stay</u>
<u n="339" who="S0188">at the end of the day it's gonna be hard to get us all in place for all viewings</u>
<u n="340" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0188">if we really like a place then we should just say like we really like this you should you know</u>
<u n="343" who="S0187">get there if you can</u>
<u n="344" who="S0188" trans="overlap">arrange another another viewing and then</u>
<u n="345" who="S0387" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0187">is that GCHQ? jinx</u>
<u n="347" who="S0187"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives like seven minutes around from there</u>
<u n="348" who="S0387" trans="overlap">it's <anon type="place"/> innit?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0200">does he live that close?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0200">fuck that</u>
<u n="352" who="S0187">that's what he said he was like</u>
<u n="353" who="S0200">when the Russians are coming that's the first place they go</u>
<u n="354" who="S0187">yeah he said that literally you know where that obviously the <trunc>ci</trunc> you got the circle things and then out it's like and obviously big circle circular fence around it afterwards</u>
<u n="355" who="S0188">right yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0187">he used to live literally in the block of flats next to it in his old house when he left uni</u>
<u n="357" who="S0200">fuck when the Russians are coming</u>
<u n="358" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0200">that's the first place they're going</u>
<u n="360" who="S0187">that's the first place they nuke</u>
<u n="361" who="S0200"><unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0187">yeah he's just down the road from it now?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0200">it's those mattresses innit?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0387">as I say</u>
<u n="365" who="S0188">I'd like to go home sleep on a memory foam mattress</u>
<u n="366" who="S0200">what were you gonna say?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0387">of all the ones I've looked at it just said four beds they didn't say four people</u>
<u n="368" who="S0200">no but that</u>
<u n="369" who="S0188">they'll be like no couples and stuff like that won't they?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0200">yeah I know that was on some of them</u>
<u n="371" who="S0188">yeah you've just got to ask</u>
<u n="372" who="S0200">it's not even worth asking is it? like don't give them the opportunity to say no</u>
<u n="373" who="S0187">it's one of those things though that</u>
<u n="374" who="S0188">you <unclear/> landlord comes round for summat</u>
<u n="375" who="S0187">but you have to you have to give a day but</u>
<u n="376" who="S0188">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0187">still I've known people to be caught</u>
<u n="378" who="S0188">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0187">and they've kicked off about it but still it's like well you were subletting that was what they put it as cos a girl and her boyfriend</u>
<u n="380" who="S0200">but that's <unclear/> came round like everyone's entitled to have</u>
<u n="381" who="S0387" trans="overlap">a friend</u>
<u n="382" who="S0200">friends but not like another <trunc>an</trunc>another like another half</u>
<u n="383" who="S0188">you'll have to hide under the bed</u>
<u n="384" who="S0187">yeah fucking</u>
<u n="385" who="S0200">but I know but I'm well within my rights to be there</u>
<u n="386" who="S0187" trans="overlap">R Kelly it in the closet</u>
<u n="387" who="S0200">as far as he knows as far as he knows I don't he never actually <unclear/> like he can just assume we're together <unclear/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0387">I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like in <anon type="place"/> they said you're allowed like a friend for two nights a week by saying</u>
<u n="390" who="S0188" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah you just let them know that you're here</u>
<u n="391" who="S0387">I was saying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> could be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friend for two days then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friend for two days then</u>
<u n="392" who="S0200">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="393" who="S0187">I remember that yeah I remember actually thinking like shit we're going to have to actually register people that are going to stay around <pause dur="short"/> what the fuck?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0387"><unclear/> even if they were to get it</u>
<u n="395" who="S0200">they were useless anyway</u>
<u n="396" who="S0187">they didn't give a shit that that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> guy cracker</u>
<u n="397" who="S0200">apparently it pay pays fifteen grand</u>
<u n="398" who="S0187">really?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0200" trans="overlap">they reckon</u>
<u n="400" who="S0187">I'd go for that</u>
<u n="401" who="S0200">I don't know I'd have done it for fifteen grand in a heartbeat</u>
<u n="402" who="S0187">just sit around and fuck around with students</u>
<u n="403" who="S0200">but I don't know whether they give you like your tuition fee free and then your accommodation <pause dur="short"/> even so I'd so that</u>
<u n="404" who="S0387" trans="overlap">gonna go to the toilet</u>
<u n="405" who="S0200">that makes perfect sense doesn't it?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0187">we're talking about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> being a warden</u>
<u n="407" who="S0387">I said that he no way he'd get to the top floor</u>
<u n="408" who="S0187">no no</u>
<u n="409" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">if he had a <unclear/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0187">saying that though he got up to the top floor when he lived there</u>
<u n="411" who="S0188">just about</u>
<u n="412" who="S0200">very very occasionally</u>
<u n="413" who="S0387"><unclear/> backed up he said he <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like what floor are you on? what's the bling? just aside of the fact that</u>
<event desc="0387 leaves"/>
<u n="414" who="S0187">yeah how serious is it?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0188">yeah how serious is this?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0200" trans="overlap">you you get your post once a week wouldn't you? and you are a fat fucker weren't climbing up the stairs</u>
<u n="417" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0188">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0187">parody huh</u>
<u n="420" who="S0200">but <unclear/> what he was doing?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0188">I wouldn't know I won't see him before him leaves</u>
<u n="422" who="S0187">apparently he piped up on Facebook recently</u>
<u n="423" who="S0200">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0188">about the death of thingy weren't it?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0188">he wasn't very <unclear/> today there was this other guy</u>
<u n="428" who="S0187">that's the thing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not nothing to do with <unclear/> if <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't you know <unclear/> here there's gonna be it'll be five of us in a place for four it needs to be tidy cos you two are a main a main culprits for mess</u>
<u n="429" who="S0200">oh mm I dunno</u>
<u n="430" who="S0187">you're you fucking are <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0188">it's just like the the the amount of stuff you have</u>
<u n="432" who="S0187">it's yeah it's a lot of stuff</u>
<u n="433" who="S0188">if we go to a smaller place</u>
<u n="434" who="S0200">yeah but the rooms'll be bigger</u>
<u n="435" who="S0188">yeah but we we we dunno that do we?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0200">I assume so</u>
<u n="437" who="S0188">well this is this is this is the biggest room in this house I mean our rooms might be bigger but like kitchen and just general stuff it would be <trunc>sm</trunc> could be smaller</u>
<u n="438" who="S0200">yeah but I mean everybody else'll just leave all their shit and then occasionally go for a big blitz</u>
<u n="439" who="S0188">no no it's not it's not just you you two</u>
<u n="440" who="S0200">cheers</u>
<u n="441" who="S0188">but as as as a lot of us</u>
<u n="442" who="S0200">there are two of us though</u>
<u n="443" who="S0188">yeah I know and you two are the messiest</u>
<u n="444" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0188">but next year cos we'll be working young professionals</u>
<u n="446" who="S0200" trans="overlap">mm yeah we'll be working in fucking Topman</u>
<u n="447" who="S0187">cos I think I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like</u>
<u n="448" who="S0200">young professionals nothing</u>
<u n="449" who="S0187"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s messy kind of thing but I remember he eh said to me he was like I stopped being so messy cos I saw how annoyed you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were getting with it so cos if he's like if I lived on my own I would be an absolutely fucking state</u>
<u n="450" who="S0200" trans="overlap">state</u>
<u n="451" who="S0187">and like that's fair enough</u>
<u n="452" who="S0188">where is this then?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0200">the the three girls who went to Syria just left fifteen years old</u>
<u n="454" who="S0188">oh this is a while ago though</u>
<u n="455" who="S0200">three weeks?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0187">do what they want did you hear about that that guy in Manchester that fucked off? he was trying to fuck off to Syria and his family</u>
<u n="457" who="S0188" trans="overlap">yeah he <unclear/> here didn't he?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0187">is he? before he went to prison he was a teacher or something</u>
<u n="459" who="S0188" trans="overlap">oh one of them one of them some of them where went</u>
<u n="460" who="S0387" whoConfidence="low">oh yeah I did hear about he got what was it? he got arrested and stuff</u>
<u n="461" who="S0187">yeah his family like hid his passport and stuff</u>
<u n="462" who="S0200">fucking idiot</u>
<u n="463" who="S0387">like as if people are going to say to you oh right mate enjoy Syria</u>
<u n="464" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0188">yeah are we still going to the gym in the morning? I was thinking like eight o'clock</u>
<u n="466" who="S0187">yeah mate erm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0188">eight quarter past half past</u>
<u n="468" who="S0387">how is your <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0188">hey?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0387">did you go for a drink in the end?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0188">yeah we had one group well two groups if you count <unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0387" trans="overlap">how d'you go?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0200">no it has to be your nose <unclear/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0188">yeah I don't like going out there</u>
<u n="475" who="S0387">I haven't been there in ages</u>
<u n="476" who="S0188">cheaper in there innit?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0387">that's Thursday night as well do they still do the</u>
<u n="478" who="S0188">I don't know mate it was fucking dead</u>
<u n="479" who="S0387">since they bought in that pool table I haven't been there</u>
<u n="480" who="S0200">the <anon type="place"/> I haven't been in no I like the <anon type="place"/> though it's just pricey</u>
<u n="481" who="S0188">I like it in there yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0387">the pool table has <unclear/> a whole floor</u>
<u n="483" who="S0200">yeah but no one is ever up there it's always closed</u>
<u n="484" who="S0188">I've never played pool in there <unclear/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0187"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0387">have you not?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0187">I played it I been up there once I went there <trunc>ba</trunc></u>
<u n="488" who="S0188">that's a fast car bloody hell</u>
<u n="489" who="S0387" whoConfidence="low">you have to <unclear/> mate</u>
<u n="490" who="S0187">what did I what did I went there? er</u>
<u n="491" who="S0188">that'd make you dizzy wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0187">amaretto sours was that in there?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0387">nice nice</u>
<u n="494" who="S0187">well nice</u>
<u n="495" who="S0188">where?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0187">in <anon type="place"/> that's the last time I went</u>
<u n="497" who="S0387">they make a nice drink in there</u>
<u n="498" who="S0187">I haven't been this year I don't think</u>
<u n="499" who="S0200">you have to go mate cos it's got a nice garden in the back and all</u>
<u n="500" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0188">on a summer's day</u>
<u n="502" who="S0187">I need to start my tablets soon</u>
<u n="503" who="S0387">tablets?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0187">hay fever tablets</u>
<u n="505" who="S0387">mm</u>
<u n="506" who="S0188">my mate back home right he's a fucking moron like <trunc>cri</trunc> cos erm one of my cricket boys from back home said ah pre-season drinks next weekend and I put ah you know it's a week too late I'm coming back this weekend if anyone want a drink so</u>
<u n="507" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">my mate automatically took that as I'm going out when I go back home</u>
<u n="508" who="S0187">ha</u>
<u n="509" who="S0188">and he told my brother apparently my brother goes out doesn't he? with his fake ID</u>
<u n="510" who="S0187">brilliant</u>
<u n="511" who="S0188">he's like cos he gave me some shit about ah cos if I if he can get a fake ID for my other brother they're going to come to town <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm like and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says you're you're you're out already I'm like no I'm fucking not</u>
<u n="512" who="S0187">coming back for my brother's birthdays and and Mother's Day</u>
<u n="513" who="S0188" trans="overlap">just come I'm back doesn't mean I'm I mean he hasn't he hasn't been out not been out on a weekend since October</u>
<u n="514" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0188">he loves it he lives for it</u>
<u n="516" who="S0200" whoConfidence="low">who your little brother?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0188">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my mate I'm like just cos I'm home doesn't mean I'm going to spend it out</u>
<u n="518" who="S0187">you say</u>
<u n="519" who="S0188">I probably will</u>
<u n="520" who="S0200">I was about to say you'll have a night out</u>
<u n="521" who="S0188"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but every time I go I'm like I won't go out I don't want to</u>
<u n="522" who="S0387">if you had the money <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you'd be out every week</u>
<u n="523" who="S0200">he is out every week</u>
<u n="524" who="S0188">I've been out</u>
<u n="525" who="S0187">you have yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0387">since when?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0188">since I've come down</u>
<u n="528" who="S0187">I've never seen you look so rough than like this weekend</u>
<u n="529" who="S0188">oh mate don't I haven't been that bad</u>
<u n="530" who="S0387">I wanted to I wanted to see all of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends not like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that</u>
<u n="531" who="S0188">a fucking long time</u>
<u n="532" who="S0200">did you not all go out when <unclear/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0188">yeah two of them were were the miserablest bitches I ever met in my entire life</u>
<u n="534" who="S0200">what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends? chatty <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0187">yeah mate</u>
<u n="536" who="S0188">she never made any effort to talk talk to me either</u>
<u n="537" who="S0200">who how many came up?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0188">five</u>
<u n="539" who="S0200">where'd they sleep? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0188">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0187">I thought it was less than that I only saw two in the morning it was it was initially supposed</u>
<u n="543" who="S0188" trans="overlap">yeah two she fucked off quite early</u>
<u n="544" who="S0387">two were in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room</u>
<u n="545" who="S0200">yeah in that big double bed</u>
<u n="546" who="S0187">it was initially supposed to be two two of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mates and then maybe one that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> brought round weren't it?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0188">it was it was mm yeah it was going to be two of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mates but then two more came</u>
<u n="548" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="549" who="S0188">god they were as miserable as sin</u>
<u n="550" who="S0387">I thought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like in I thought he was definitely going to pull that night</u>
<u n="551" who="S0188"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0387">five females under the same roof</u>
<u n="553" who="S0200">all you have to do literally to a pissed girl at the end of the night is say I have a double bed like you can sleep on the floor</u>
<u n="554" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0188">they were yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0200">or come up to my room</u>
<u n="557" who="S0188">come up to my double duvet and my memory foam mattress</u>
<u n="558" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0387">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s Egyptian cotton sheets</u>
<u n="560" who="S0188">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0200">and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets to offer them a single bed and a room that smells like feet</u>
<u n="562" who="S0187">that's freezing cold</u>
<u n="563" who="S0188">with a mattress that's made of knives</u>
<u n="564" who="S0387">it's not going to go down as <unclear/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0187">no wonder you slept alone</u>
<u n="566" who="S0387">cos it's ice cold so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s definitely in with a chance</u>
<u n="567" who="S0187">yeah true</u>
<u n="568" who="S0387">cos there's the body heat</u>
<u n="569" who="S0187">get nice and close</u>
<u n="570" who="S0188">well I'll just put my little heater on and then you know it'll be like a sauna <pause dur="short"/> until we turn it off</u>
<u n="571" who="S0200">I I fucking smash that <unclear>yo</unclear> be nothing left of it</u>
<u n="572" who="S0187">ah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0387"><unclear/> wake up in the morning now you haven't needed to have it on <unclear/> warm now</u>
<u n="574" who="S0200">I've been fucking boiling</u>
<u n="575" who="S0187">yeah I've been alright now I was surprised was the heating on tonight?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0200">yeah we came in we turned it off as soon as we got in it was boiling up</u>
<u n="577" who="S0187" trans="overlap">yeah I was surprised when it when I got home I was like oh</u>
<u n="578" who="S0188">I've been putting it on all this week apart from tonight</u>
<u n="579" who="S0387">I'm excited I thought that bill would be here by now</u>
<u n="580" who="S0200">god fucking forbid when that bill comes in</u>
<u n="581" who="S0387">so unless it came and someone's hid it</u>
<u n="582" who="S0200">hid it never to be seen again</u>
<u n="583" who="S0188" trans="overlap">just fucking burned it <pause dur="short"/> have you been using the barbecue again? fucking</u>
<u n="584" who="S0187">bye bill</u>
<u n="585" who="S0200"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s name he's not living with us next year you never know</u>
<u n="586" who="S0187">stitch him</u>
<u n="587" who="S0188">he wouldn't know if he had fucking mail anyway would he? he thinks it it gets brought here by fucking owls like in Harry Potter</u>
<u n="588" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0187"><trunc>St</trunc>stork</u>
<u n="590" who="S0188"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0200">I'm <trunc>wai</trunc> I'm literally waiting for an <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> email to come through like hey mate</u>
<u n="592" who="S0387">got some work for you mate</u>
<u n="593" who="S0200">there are ninety-two shifts on offer</u>
<u n="594" who="S0387">yeah exam period</u>
<u n="595" who="S0200">cheers bud</u>
<u n="596" who="S0387"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s having ninety of them but you can have the fucking rest go fight for them</u>
<u n="597" who="S0188" trans="overlap">did any of you did any of you get the the emails for the work at <anon type="place"/> helping the nursing things out?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0187">I didn't get one no</u>
<u n="599" who="S0188">it might just be me cos it's a <anon type="place"/> thingy</u>
<u n="600" who="S0200" trans="overlap">are you working Saturday?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0188">ah I've got rugby keep I keep getting emails <trunc>co</trunc> I I could not do it but</u>
<u n="602" who="S0200">cos it's</u>
<u n="603" who="S0387">not this Saturday it's a week Saturday innit?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0200">oh yeah it's a week Saturday</u>
<u n="605" who="S0187">still only still only forty quid I hear</u>
<u n="606" who="S0188">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0200">it's a week Saturday not this Saturday coming next</u>
<u n="608" who="S0188">yeah but yeah I've got rugby that week I've got rugby all next weekend</u>
<u n="609" who="S0200">sack it off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos <unclear/> seventy quid like for a go</u>
<u n="610" who="S0188">yeah I know</u>
<u n="611" who="S0200">which aint bad</u>
<u n="612" who="S0188">yeah <unclear/> wells but I've</u>
<u n="613" who="S0200">the wells</u>
<u n="614" who="S0188">and I've got the only problem is I've got the bag so I'd have to drive to</u>
<u n="615" who="S0200">go and give it someone</u>
<u n="616" who="S0188">yeah but fuck that I dunno I just yeah it's it's fine cos I'll <pause dur="short"/> I'm doing the <anon type="place"/> ladies game on on the Sunday as well hopefully Stereophonics that night Saturday night</u>
<u n="617" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0188">if I can get on the fucking tickets in the morning</u>
<u n="619" who="S0387">have you got anyone coming with you?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0188"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is coming come up come down from home</u>
<u n="621" who="S0200">it's a long fucking way to come</u>
<u n="622" who="S0188">yeah but he's a</u>
<u n="623" who="S0200">and a lot of money to pay</u>
<u n="624" who="S0188">he likes his gigs</u>
<u n="625" who="S0187">we were talking about it though it's not it's not a huge amount of money if you <pause dur="short"/> if you love it</u>
<u n="626" who="S0188" trans="overlap">for someone who doesn't go to gigs like people will spend hundreds of pound going to see someone</u>
<u n="627" who="S0200">oh yeah definitely but I don't think they're I don't think they're that big to be warranting like forty quid</u>
<u n="628" who="S0188" trans="overlap">it's it's because I like them and I</u>
<u n="629" who="S0200">oh yeah I get why I get why people go</u>
<u n="630" who="S0187">I was thinking cos I was thinking that's fucking expensive and then it's like well I have no interest in them I paid sixty-five quid to go watch the Watch The Throne tour</u>
<u n="631" who="S0188">the the it's the only thing that they're in <anon type="place"/> I can get a bus into town and where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0200"><anon type="place"/> yeah it's it's not</u>
<u n="633" who="S0187">no it's</u>
<u n="634" who="S0188">exactly I'll get a fucking bus in and I'll get a taxi back it's happy days</u>
<u n="635" who="S0200">yeah you know which stop the bus opposite the start of the bus pretty much</u>
<u n="636" who="S0387">no it's not</u>
<u n="637" who="S0200">yeah it is</u>
<u n="638" who="S0387"><anon type="place"/> is by the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0188">I don't know where it is</u>
<u n="640" who="S0200">yeah you can go that way but it's still round the back of that way</u>
<u n="641" who="S0188" trans="overlap">is it big or is it is it big?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0387">it's big enough I think</u>
<u n="643" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0200">it's a good few thousand seats in there</u>
<u n="645" who="S0188">I reckon I'll have to be pretty sharp on the tickets in the morning</u>
<u n="646" who="S0187">you're getting up for fucking <trunc>Ste</trunc>Stereophonics</u>
<u n="647" who="S0387">what time they go on sale?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0188">ten</u>
<u n="649" who="S0200">ten</u>
<u n="650" who="S0188">hey?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0200">see what?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0188">they're fucking big mate</u>
<u n="653" who="S0187">I know I know they are I don't know</u>
<u n="654" who="S0188">they're big time</u>
<u n="655" who="S0387">Rihanna was fifty quid that's what I can't understand like Rihanna's like up there</u>
<u n="656" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah that's</u>
<u n="657" who="S0187">that's about as it gets what between fifty and seventy for like that upper echelon</u>
<u n="658" who="S0387">oh the Beyonc tickets were like a hundred plus</u>
<u n="659" who="S0187">ah yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="660" who="S0200">they're like they're like rocking horse shit aren't they? if you get one of them</u>
<u n="661" who="S0187">Drake was like sixty I didn't bother with them he was in <anon type="place"/> at one point oh no he weren't in <anon type="place"/> he was</u>
<u n="662" who="S0200">thingy was in <anon type="place"/> though wasn't he? Snoop Dog</u>
<u n="663" who="S0187" trans="overlap">he was in <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="664" who="S0188">really?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0200">yeah he was at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0188"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0187">fucking hell</u>
<u n="669" who="S0200">where <anon type="place"/> is</u>
<u n="670" who="S0187">has been <pause dur="short"/> give up lad</u>
<u n="671" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="672" who="S0387"><unclear/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0200">Lethal Bizzle can stay where he is he couldn't give me a fucking Lethal Bizzle ticket</u>
<u n="674" who="S0188">I want to make you sweat <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0200">who who sings that?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0387">he he bored me</u>
<u n="677" who="S0188">who Snoop?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0187">I've never really been a fan of him</u>
<u n="680" who="S0188">I think he's a bit of a tool to be honest</u>
<u n="681" who="S0200">is a <unclear/> his name's Snoop <unclear/> innit?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0188" trans="overlap">he's fucking too thin isn't he?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0188">he is borderline fucking</u>
<u n="685" who="S0200" trans="overlap">he's the world's biggest fucking dope head isn't he?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0188"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he is so thin</u>
<u n="688" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm I do want to see like I said to you I missed Joey Badass like in January</u>
<u n="689" who="S0188">that's like you know erm er <pause dur="short"/> it's just like you're at school and you want to call yourself something innit? oh Joey Badass over there</u>
<u n="690" who="S0387">Badass innit?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0187">he'll probably change his name cos he was I think like seventeen when he started</u>
<u n="692" who="S0188">yeah he can't be going round</u>
<u n="693" who="S0187">he's younger than us</u>
<u n="694" who="S0188">called Joey Badass</u>
<u n="695" who="S0387">Joey lies</u>
<u n="696" who="S0187">but he's making a lot of money so he can do what he fucking wants</u>
<u n="697" who="S0188">well he can to be fair</u>
<u n="698" who="S0200">oh my god she's proper pregnant isn't she?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0187">hevo pregnant</u>
<u n="700" who="S0387">I'm impressed with her actually</u>
<u n="701" who="S0187">with a pointless child</u>
<u n="702" who="S0200">any reason in particular?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0387">she drinks so much</u>
<u n="704" who="S0187">she has got a pretty important role though</u>
<u n="705" who="S0188">yeah what what else is she gonna do? she wasn't doing fuck all would she if she wasn't doing all this shit</u>
<u n="706" who="S0200">that is a fair point</u>
<u n="707" who="S0187">work work for her money</u>
<u n="708" who="S0188">ah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0200">she's got to <unclear/> to do something doesn't she?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0187">did they win?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0387">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0200">cool they won did they? I saw it was one all</u>
<u n="713" who="S0387">I was over the moon the other day in uni I bet on er Blackburn versus Bolton Blackburn to win they scored in the ninety-fourth minute</u>
<u n="714" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mental that's a big game as well</u>
<u n="715" who="S0188" trans="overlap">Lukaku</u>
<u n="716" who="S0187">fuck me</u>
<u n="717" who="S0188">Romelu</u>
<u n="718" who="S0187">so strong beating his way through</u>
<u n="719" who="S0188"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0200">he's a bit of a racist noise to make innit?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0187">no it isn't mate it's a grunt same grunt that toothless same grunt that toothless Joe makes in the gym</u>
<u n="722" who="S0200">toothless Joe</u>
<u n="723" who="S0188">ha</u>
<u n="724" who="S0187">that's a handball why is his his hand doesn't need to be there</u>
<u n="725" who="S0188">yeah he did yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0187">shocking that</u>
<u n="727" who="S0188">Romelu</u>
<u n="728" who="S0387">I hate placed penos down the middle</u>
<u n="729" who="S0200">it's a brave decision innit?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0188">I like <unclear/> over there</u>
<u n="732" who="S0200">look how fucking <unclear/> though</u>
<u n="733" who="S0387">he's been there for years</u>
<u n="734" who="S0188">ha</u>
<u n="735" who="S0387"><unclear/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0188">oh they went up in thirteen seconds didn't they?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0387">how many?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0188">thirteen seconds</u>
<u n="739" who="S0200">great ball</u>
<u n="740" who="S0188">oh <unclear/> ooh</u>
<u n="741" who="S0200">that's great play innit?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0387">that'll be UE UE <unclear/> next week</u>
<u n="743" who="S0200">yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0188">what picking the ball out the back of the net?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0187">probably <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm gonna play next week though <pause dur="short"/> gonna try try and make a bit of difference</u>
<u n="746" who="S0387" trans="overlap">that was Kevin De Bruyne weren't it?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0187">he played shit from what I saw</u>
<u n="748" who="S0188">he got two goals though</u>
<u n="749" who="S0187">did he?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0200">they word <unclear/> fucking innit?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0187">he was playing awful when I was there</u>
<u n="752" who="S0188" trans="overlap">Nicklas Bendtner's there isn't he? at Wolfsburg</u>
<u n="753" who="S0387">is he?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0200">what's he doing there?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0188" trans="overlap">he's fucking todge</u>
<u n="756" who="S0200">yeah todge</u>
<u n="757" who="S0187">todge</u>
<u n="758" who="S0387"><unclear/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0187">you want to lay down mate?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0188">no it's alright I'm gonna and get <unclear/></u>
<u n="761" who="S0187">no you lay down mate</u>
<u n="762" who="S0200">I was meant to get through a hundred and twenty-six pages when I came home ph</u>
<u n="763" who="S0187">nah mate ain't happening</u>
<u n="764" who="S0200">I'm through one</u>
<u n="765" who="S0187">have you have you seen the new tech they've got</u>
<u n="766" who="S0188">who?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0187">these two</u>
<u n="768" who="S0200">our flash new toy</u>
<u n="769" who="S0187">can I show him on my phone?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0200">you can show them on the phone</u>
<u n="771" who="S0188">what have you fucking got now? Mr Mr and Mr I've got no money but I'll buy the fucking</u>
<u n="772" who="S0187" trans="overlap">this is with vouchers</u>
<u n="773" who="S0387">this is with our vouchers</u>
<u n="774" who="S0200">Mr and Mrs er</u>
<u n="775" who="S0188">I said Mr and Mr didn't I?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0387">so you enjoy your few pints at the pub and I'll be here doing nothing this this came free of charge mate</u>
<u n="777" who="S0187">we spent a fiver <pause dur="short"/> I want it to work but I don't know whether it's cos <pause dur="short"/> oh here we go</u>
<u n="778" who="S0200">give it a go</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="779" who="S0200" whoConfidence="low">he fucking does</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
