<text id="S37F">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0251 S0252</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living room in Malton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>TV and history</topics>
		<activity>Russian princesses TV programme discussion</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0251">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>North Ferriby, East Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>GCSE Maths Examiner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0252">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>York</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0251">what have you been watching on the television recently then?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0252">erm I think the er latest thing was the erm a programme about the er Russian princesses</u>
<u n="3" who="S0251">oh yes I saw that as well did you enjoy it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0252">yes I thought it was very interesting I like seeing things erm you've already had an insight into er because I did that period erm as my AS course</u>
<u n="5" who="S0251">yes you quite liked that actually didn't you?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0252">I did yes</u>
<u n="7" who="S0251">more than the er English did you? English history</u>
<u n="8" who="S0252"><trunc>a</trunc>absolutely</u>
<u n="9" who="S0251">yeah it was quite interesting we saw the film one film about it didn't we?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="11" who="S0251">so I think it gives you a good idea of the atmosphere of the period I don't think it'll help you write a better essay</u>
<u n="12" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0251">or get more marks but it shows you a bit more about what it was like in those days doesn't it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0252">it does it does have you found anything particularly in the erm <unclear>programme</unclear>?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0251">one thing that I didn't realise was when the erm family were held captive and they were trying to escape that George the fifth said that they could actually get a pass to England but they were unable to do that because the girls had gotten measles and were not well enough to travel and that was the reason why they did not take up the offer immediately</u>
<u n="16" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0251">then he withdrew the offer and when the girls were well enough so they were unable to go so that's how they missed out the chance</u>
<u n="18" who="S0252">yeah backfired on them really</u>
<u n="19" who="S0251">yeah it did didn't it? but I don't suppose anybody ever thought that it would come to that that all those people would be shot</u>
<u n="20" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="21" who="S0251">I suppose it was quite unheard of really that the whole family would get killed</u>
<u n="22" who="S0252">I think in the end it shocked er George the fifth so I believe the reason he er decided to erm withdraw his offer was because er he was with that the er rising presence of erm the Bolsheviks in erm England would have greater effect if the er Russian royal family were in the UK</u>
<u n="23" who="S0251">mm <unclear/> cos they were actually family weren't they?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0252">they were</u>
<u n="25" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0252">having said that er the kaiser did not make an offer but obviously that would have been because er Germany and Russia were at war at the time</u>
<u n="27" who="S0251">mm was there anything that you think could have been added to the film from your knowledge? that would have made it a bit more</u>
<u n="28" who="S0252">I think one they did talk about erm the strikes erm I don't I don't think they really looked at specific examples of strikes they just acknowledged that there were some</u>
<u n="29" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0252">but they didn't look at some sort of er how the strikes were er initiated</u>
<u n="31" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0252">one example is the er Lena Goldfield's massacre erm where the er gold miners were on strike</u>
<u n="33" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0252">but erm the reason that it holds such a prominent infamous position er today is that that er the Russian erm Cossacks opened fire on the er miners that was apparently by accident because erm they <unclear>felt</unclear> that the miners were trying to attack the Cossacks</u>
<u n="35" who="S0251">and how many people were killed?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0252">I think it was a few hundred</u>
<u n="37" who="S0251">it was some accident wasn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0252">it was yes</u>
<u n="39" who="S0251">mm one thing that was very good about the programme was that there was a lot of footage from the time which is quite surprising because it's when was the revolution? about nineteen seventeen is it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0252">mm yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0251">erm some of it was film and a lot of it was photographs because apparently all the four princesses had these box Brownie cameras</u>
<u n="42" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="43" who="S0251">so there's a lot of photographs of the period and some of them are absolutely lovely</u>
<u n="44" who="S0252">mm they've done well to er manage to survive that length of time yes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it's good that yeah that they're still preserved because even when they were held captive there's a photograph of them all when when they had the measles all their hair fell out</u>
<u n="46" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="47" who="S0251">and there's photographs of them then so they must have had them even when they were held captive</u>
<u n="48" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0251">I don't know whether they were developed then or whether they were subsequently</u>
<u n="50" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="51" who="S0251">developed I thought it was quite good</u>
<u n="52" who="S0252">I was not aware that er they made er two separate journeys erm from er St Petersburg that er there was more than they stayed in more than one place</u>
<u n="53" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="54" who="S0252">and I thought they just erm stayed at one place in Siberia</u>
<u n="55" who="S0251">right so first of all there seemed to be er not a strict rule wasn't it? it was more like a house arrest</u>
<u n="56" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="57" who="S0251">but the second place seemed to be more severe didn't it?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0252">it did yes</u>
<u n="59" who="S0251">mm it's a sad story though isn't it?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0252">it is</u>
<u n="61" who="S0251">I suppose they wanted to kill the whole family because they didn't want the monarchy to come back</u>
<u n="62" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="63" who="S0251">so when we had the civil war in this country for instance Charles the first was killed but his son later Charles the second restored the monarchy and came back</u>
<u n="64" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0251">so they might have tried to learn from history that they needed to eradicate the whole family</u>
<u n="66" who="S0252">yes but in some ways it's whilst that was a very horrific thing to occur I think Russia at that time it was facing massive industrialisation</u>
<u n="67" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0252">but it wasn't really changing politically to erm to <unclear>counteract</unclear> the erm massive industrialisation that was occurring because it wasn't until eighteen sixty-one that the <unclear/> were emancipated</u>
<u n="69" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0252">so that is almost a feudal system</u>
<u n="71" who="S0251">yes it was</u>
<u n="72" who="S0252">in what would almost be considered almost Victorian er period</u>
<u n="73" who="S0251">yes yes it was another thing is in that programme they were saying how isolated the princesses were around the whole family but I think if you look at any equivalent monarchy say in England the families would be very isolated they weren't going out to the shops or mixing with ordinary people</u>
<u n="74" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="75" who="S0251">I think people in that position at that time would be very isolated and er they wouldn't have gone to school particularly I don't think they would have had governesses er come to the house for their education and they would have just have had their little court circle probably</u>
<u n="76" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="77" who="S0251">I don't think they're very integrated so</u>
<u n="78" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0251">I don't think that was much different to any other monarchy of that time</u>
<u n="80" who="S0252">no I think had er the tsar followed the route of erm a constitutional monarchy</u>
<u n="81" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0252">I think Russia potentially could have still had its monarchy today because I think especially when things go wrong like er firing at erm strikers</u>
<u n="83" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0252">and also because the tsar went to the front line in the First World War</u>
<u n="85" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0252">erm that meant that he was seen as personally responsible</u>
<u n="87" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="88" who="S0252">for any failures</u>
<u n="89" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="90" who="S0252">the fact that erm the majority of people didn't have a vote that really counted because er the current <unclear>Dumas</unclear> that were introduced were just merely consultative</u>
<u n="91" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="92" who="S0252">so I think had they just gone one step further made it constitutional I think that would have it would have meant that it would have only been the very radical er people that would have considered erm revolutionary activity</u>
<u n="93" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0252">I don't think the er the more politically erm centred people would really have considered revolutionary activity</u>
<u n="95" who="S0251">mm I think actually it was very popular I think they had a lot of respect</u>
<u n="96" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="97" who="S0251">from a lot of people and I think the tsar was looked upon as a father figure to the country</u>
<u n="98" who="S0252">he was</u>
<u n="99" who="S0251">but I think the social conditions the poverty that people experienced just became so grinding and he was the boss he had to take the blame if he'd tried to be a bit more understanding and had some measures put in place to try to alleviate that he could've still have er pulled it round I think</u>
<u n="100" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0251">I think in those days he was very involved even for instance if people wanted divorce they had to write to the tsar</u>
<u n="102" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0251">to get his express permission</u>
<u n="104" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0251">so he was very much in control of people's lives</u>
<u n="106" who="S0252">I think he was involved and in some ways he seemed very interlinked with the the church the Russian Orthodox Church</u>
<u n="107" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="108" who="S0252">which was a fundamental part of many Russian people's lives</u>
<u n="109" who="S0251">yes I think they had a big following</u>
<u n="110" who="S0252">yes I think his reputation was brought down erm further along the line I think one thing that really did damage it was the Rasputin scandal</u>
<u n="111" who="S0251">yeah that was a real wild card wasn't it?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0252">it was</u>
<u n="113" who="S0251">mm that he had all this influence I think that wouldn't have happened had they not had that son who had the haemophilia</u>
<u n="114" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0251">it made them really vulnerable</u>
<u n="116" who="S0252">it did</u>
<u n="117" who="S0251">because they were so desperate</u>
<u n="118" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0251">to get any help because there <trunc>j</trunc> was just no known cure</u>
<u n="120" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="121" who="S0251">and so they turned to him I think possibly coincidentally the child had got better at one point and they er credited him with influencing that recovery</u>
<u n="122" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0251">but he just seemed to get a stronger and stronger hold on the family didn't he?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0252" trans="overlap">he did really if they were seeking erm sort of medical expertise</u>
<u n="125" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0252">they'd have been better off with er a group of erm physicians rather than er you know someone of Rasputin's character</u>
<u n="127" who="S0251" trans="overlap">a mystic I think they'd tried the doctors but they hadn't had a lot of success and</u>
<u n="128" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="129" who="S0251">they were rather mystified about what to do they couldn't</u>
<u n="130" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="131" who="S0251">find anything to help them</u>
<u n="132" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="133" who="S0251">and also they were trying to keep it secret</u>
<u n="134" who="S0252">I know</u>
<u n="135" who="S0251">because I think in those days probably the life expectancy for someone with that condition would be say sixteen years of age</u>
<u n="136" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0251">so that meant that the dynasty was not secure</u>
<u n="138" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="139" who="S0251">because it was possible that the son would erm die before the father did</u>
<u n="140" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm but it definitely would've been a more legitimate</u>
<u n="141" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0252">erm approach</u>
<u n="143" who="S0251">route yes it would</u>
<u n="144" who="S0252">which I think would've been accepted</u>
<u n="145" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0252">by the Russian people</u>
<u n="147" who="S0251">yes it would so they'd already had four daughters and then this one son so they'd had five children</u>
<u n="148" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0251">but er that all was from queen Victoria's blood stock I think that problem</u>
<u n="150" who="S0252">it was mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0251">it's a shame and then apparently on the site where they got massacred they built the church I found that quite surprising really and there was the little mosaic pictures of the</u>
<u n="152" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="153" who="S0251">was it all the family? or just those four girls?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0252">erm I think as far as I'm aware I think it was the four girls</u>
<u n="155" who="S0251">four girls and they were worshiped by I think they were Greek Orthodox people as some kind of martyrs</u>
<u n="156" who="S0252">yeah but what it would have been interesting to know when that was built because you wouldn't think that a communist rule would really allow that</u>
<u n="157" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no that's a good point it didn't look that new so</u>
<u n="158" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="159" who="S0251">it appeared as though it had been going on some time but I as you say I don't know when that would happen and how it was allowed I wouldn't have thought it would have been allowed really</u>
<u n="160" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0251">in communist Russia</u>
<u n="162" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="163" who="S0251">but obviously it was</u>
<u n="164" who="S0252">I think they did their best to erm scupper any attempts to er find the er remains of the Russian royal family</u>
<u n="165" who="S0251">oh yes</u>
<u n="166" who="S0252">by pouring acid and burying them under a railway line</u>
<u n="167" who="S0251">yes absolutely</u>
<u n="168" who="S0252">that sort of thing</u>
<u n="169" who="S0251">well they've only just been discovered recently haven't they?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0251">and then that put paid to the myth that it was always said that Anastasia had managed to escape</u>
<u n="172" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0251">and er but I think they had found all the remains hadn't they for the whole family?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="175" who="S0251">for somebody was pretending to be Anastasia erm in America I think? and any question that she was asked about the royal family in Russia she always knew the answer</u>
<u n="176" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0251">and they was never quite sure whether it was her as she claimed or whether it was an imposter so it seems that she was an imposter but how she knew so much about the er tsar's family I don't know whether she'd just read a lot of history books I'm not sure and that historian Orlando <unclear>Baigs</unclear> said why would they let one teenage girl run away? cos apparently there was just one person shooting at each member of the family so there was a whole group of soldiers there'd be five children and mum and dad so that's seven and I don't know whether they had any <unclear/> or</u>
<u n="178" who="S0252">mm uh</u>
<u n="179" who="S0251">well</u>
<u n="180" who="S0252">as you pointed out it er you would have expected a shooter per person rather than one for all</u>
<u n="181" who="S0251">yes well that's what they did have wasn't it?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0251">they had one person to shoot each member of the family I think one reason for letting her go was because somebody didn't want be a murderer that would be one good reason wouldn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0251">because it would be a lot to have on your conscience wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0252">I know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0251">for the rest of your life you'd never forget it would you?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0252">no cos the er from a Russian Orthodox background</u>
<u n="189" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0252">it probably would contradict the erm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes the morale er morals</u>
<u n="192" who="S0252">yes the moral and ethics</u>
<u n="193" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0252">that the church</u>
<u n="195" who="S0251">whether they thought there were working for the good of Russia or whether they were just operating under instruction it's still it's a big thing to do isn't it?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0252">absolutely</u>
<u n="197" who="S0251">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's a shame that there was only two episodes</u>
<u n="198" who="S0252">I know quite a number of er programmes were I don't think there is erm sufficient episodes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0251">no no there's only erm programmes that you're not so bothered about probably</u>
<u n="200" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0251">seem to go on for a lot longer don't they? <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="202" who="S0252">and have you er enjoyed the Bake Off?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0251">yes I have I've liked all the Bake Offs really I found it quite fascinating to watch did they put all the recipes on the internet for you to find out how to make the things that they make?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0252">I think the er challenge where they are given a recipe to follow the surprise challenge</u>
<u n="205" who="S0251">oh yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0252">I think that is one of the erm either Paul or Mary's er</u>
<u n="207" who="S0251">yes specials</u>
<u n="208" who="S0252">specials so obviously I think they will be on as far as I'm aware of the rest of them that's just selected er recipes that are put on</u>
<u n="209" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0252">the internet</u>
<u n="211" who="S0251">yes I think that <unclear>Martha</unclear> seems very er steady she's not very erm nervous or she appears not to be very nervous even though she's the youngest I think she's doing well isn't she?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0252">mm it's surprising how she's managed to fit in</u>
<u n="213" who="S0251">I know</u>
<u n="214" who="S0252">that with her AS levels</u>
<u n="215" who="S0251">I don't know how she's done it? she said it's relaxing compared to doing chemistry and mathematics</u>
<u n="216" who="S0252">yeah still</u>
<u n="217" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0252">I would personally find that quite stressful so I don't like working to such a precise <unclear/> time</u>
<u n="219" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0252">they only have half an hour to make their one</u>
<u n="221" who="S0251">there never seems to be enough time to</u>
<u n="222" who="S0252">I know</u>
<u n="223" who="S0251">you know finish the job does there?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0252">absolutely not</u>
<u n="225" who="S0251">of course there's been the controversy this week it's been on the front page of The Times and The Telegraph</u>
<u n="226" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0251">about when somebody allegedly took out somebody else's ice cream out of the freezer and it melted</u>
<u n="228" who="S0252">mm I'm not sure how fairly that was really done because whilst they did say that erm well he could have presented the cake or</u>
<u n="229" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0252">something on those lines</u>
<u n="231" who="S0251">oh it looked a complete mess</u>
<u n="232" who="S0252">it wouldn't have looked right</u>
<u n="233" who="S0251">no it wouldn't</u>
<u n="234" who="S0252">and you would still be considered er the worst entry</u>
<u n="235" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="236" who="S0252">so therefore I don't think any additional er consideration would be implemented in that case</u>
<u n="237" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no <unclear>certainly</unclear> not but that's the first time somebody's stormed out of the tent bit of a storm in a teacup isn't it?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I know yeah indeed</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
