<text id="S38V">
	<header>
		<rec_length>2:00:48</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0192 S0198</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In my new flat, Sussex</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Smoking cigarettes, moving apartments, future plans, university, family, inventory, music, extended family, marriage, living in South Korea, friends, ELT methodology, language, cooking, alcohol, making arrangements, driving, travelling.  </topics>
		<activity>First day in the new apartment</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, complaining, advising, requesting, announcing, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0198">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Gillingham, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Easten</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>27</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0198">I don't know how cold it's gonna be out on this balcony for the beer</u>
<u n="2" who="S0192">might be a bit chilly</u>
<u n="3" who="S0198">it's not actually in the sun but shall we see?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0192">oh it's locked at the top there</u>
<u n="5" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="6" who="S0192">so this top one locks and this middle one locks don't pull that off</u>
<u n="7" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh all locked up so that doesn't doesn't work</u>
<u n="8" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah but that doesn't</u>
<u n="9" who="S0198">that's the one I looked at</u>
<u n="10" who="S0192">we don't have a chair unfortunately</u>
<u n="11" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="12" who="S0192">how are we going to do this?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0198">I mean we just sit well on the windowsill or do we <pause dur="short"/> should have bought up those rugs to sit on the floor with really</u>
<u n="14" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah where are the rugs?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0198">they're not here I don't think they're in Kent erm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0192">I'm up for a cigarette and a and a beer on the balcony if you are</u>
<u n="17" who="S0198">yeah is there anything else that we could sit on?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0198">that you can think of that would be useful there isn't really is there?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0192">pillow or</u>
<u n="21" who="S0198">no I didn't really want to dirty anything though</u>
<u n="22" who="S0192" trans="overlap">something an old curtain or a towel</u>
<u n="23" who="S0198">ah maybe a curtain <pause dur="short"/> got plenty of those haven't we?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0198">oh the wind's picking up</u>
<u n="26" who="S0192">yeah it is it's cos we've opened the through flow</u>
<u n="27" who="S0198">yeah shall we shut one of the windows?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0192">yeah we can do</u>
<u n="29" who="S0198" trans="overlap">maybe the kitchen cos we're not gonna be out here for a while are we?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0192">yeah we might be if we smoke another cigarette in here</u>
<u n="31" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh yeah well whatever there's a breeze it doesn't really matter does it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0192">no yeah it's fine we'll just shut this door</u>
<u n="33" who="S0198">so I'll grab a curtain for us to sit down on</u>
<u n="34" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you think it's okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0198" trans="overlap">on there</u>
<u n="36" who="S0192">to sit on a curtain?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0198">yeah I mean we'll sit on a curtain on a thing <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe some of these curtains are a little bit different</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192">no I know <pause dur="short"/> we should have paid attention to that a little bit</u>
<u n="39" who="S0198">that one see I think like that's</u>
<u n="40" who="S0192">lighter</u>
<u n="41" who="S0198">that's darker than that isn't it?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that one's slightly darker</u>
<u n="43" who="S0198">oh well whatever</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">are you sure you wanna sit on a curtain?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0198">well</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192">I forgot we got this cable</u>
<u n="47" who="S0198">we <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="48" who="S0192">so we can see if the sound works</u>
<u n="49" who="S0198">we'll sit on the inside of the curtain not the outside</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="51" who="S0198" trans="overlap">fold it up and make it look a bit like a rug</u>
<u n="52" who="S0192">that'll be fine where's the beer then?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0198">although I think there's another blanket we can sit on out there</u>
<u n="54" who="S0192">oh if you've got a blanket that would be great</u>
<u n="55" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah that would be better wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0192">where's the beer in the fridge?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0198">yeah I left the beer in the freezer</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192">I've got the tobacco are we just sharing the bottle?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I wasn't yeah <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't in the fridge at the supermarket so I thought it would go colder quicker in the freezer</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">yeah and it's</u>
<u n="61" who="S0198">but I don't know if it's been in there long enough</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192" trans="overlap">doesn't need to be cold</u>
<u n="63" who="S0198" trans="overlap">do we need glasses or do we just share from a bottle?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0192">yeah we can have glasses would you prefer glasses?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0198">maybe</u>
<u n="66" who="S0192">yeah do you wanna grab them then?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0198">yeah they're behind you</u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">where?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0198">there's two behind you</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192">okay is that the only two glasses we've got?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and just give yourself a little bit more of the beer</u>
<u n="72" who="S0192">how do we open this do we have a bottle opener?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0198">there's a bottle opener in the drawer</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">yeah there's one</u>
<u n="75" who="S0198">there's two actually</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192">so there is oh look we've got <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0198"><event desc="unintelligible"/> yeah we've got those in <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0192">oh nice we've got a bunch of stuff <pause dur="short"/> our family do know how to <pause dur="short"/> equip us</u>
<u n="79" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">pornographic ashtray</u>
<u n="81" who="S0198" trans="overlap">handy isn't it?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0192">are we taking that out?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you can't really <unclear>find</unclear> a house when you first move in unless you've already bought a bunch of stuff for it you can't move in and then go and buy the you've got to buy everything on the first day</u>
<u n="84" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0198">it would be a nightmare how do you get it home again?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no there needs to</u>
<u n="87" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I suppose if have a car but <pause dur="short"/> don't have a car</u>
<u n="88" who="S0192">most people have been living in England so they have lots of stuff</u>
<u n="89" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0192">we're not those people</u>
<u n="91" who="S0198">it's true a lot of assumption going on there</u>
<u n="92" who="S0192">people accumulate a lot don't they? <pause dur="short"/> nice afternoon beer we haven't got into study mode yet</u>
<u n="93" who="S0198">no it's coming <pause dur="short"/> wednesday is coming</u>
<u n="94" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we've got three weeks for our study</u>
<u n="95" who="S0198">yeah well crack on starting from Monday as far as I'm concerned</u>
<u n="96" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do you want to take this?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0198">there's erm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0192">I'll take the beers</u>
<u n="99" who="S0198">Sunday obviously we're still just going to be sorting stuff out</u>
<u n="100" who="S0192">what do you need that for?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0198">I don't know it's just rubbish isn't it er Sunday we'll still be sorting stuff out so Monday <pause dur="short"/> that's the day really</u>
<u n="102" who="S0192">Monday will be our first proper <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0198" trans="overlap">wake up</u>
<u n="104" who="S0192">try and do a bit of studying</u>
<u n="105" who="S0198">study studying</u>
<u n="106" who="S0192">oh don't knock that bike over</u>
<u n="107" who="S0198">too small is it big enough for us to both sit on?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">I was gonna sit on the windowsill</u>
<u n="109" who="S0198">alright I'll sit here then yeah can you get out there?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> oh you do feel you're on view</u>
<u n="111" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192">on show</u>
<u n="113" who="S0198">I might this a little bit more comfortable</u>
<u n="114" who="S0192">but you're also definitely outside</u>
<u n="115" who="S0198">yeah which is a nice thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0192">yeah which is good</u>
<u n="117" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0192">erm you might want to put that on something there's a little book to put it on here</u>
<u n="119" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I can see erm why the neighbours partitioned it a little I suppose <pause dur="short"/> cos erm <pause dur="short"/> just gives a slighted added sense that that's part you know part owned do you know what I mean? rather than</u>
<u n="120" who="S0192">but is it part-owned?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="122" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's directional by the way so</u>
<u n="123" who="S0198" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> well yeah I suppose we don't</u>
<u n="124" who="S0192">I think it's our balcony</u>
<u n="125" who="S0198">maybe they just want the privacy of a</u>
<u n="126" who="S0192">I mean most likely they didn't do it and it's been there for ages</u>
<u n="127" who="S0198">yeah that's true well if the landlady owns the whole building she may have done it herself just so the people on that side <pause dur="short"/> can't claim that</u>
<u n="128" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0198" trans="overlap">none of the others are like it are they?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0192">no none of them really</u>
<u n="131" who="S0198" trans="overlap">either you have it or you don't basically</u>
<u n="132" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0198">I imagine it causes some dispute <pause dur="short"/> or ideally you own both rooms</u>
<u n="134" who="S0192">yeah I mean if you have both both sides that would be nice</u>
<u n="135" who="S0198">so it would be nice if this if this was</u>
<u n="136" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that person might they've got potted plants on both sides</u>
<u n="137" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I feel like they have</u>
<u n="138" who="S0192">if we started using their windowsill would they be alright with that?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0198">no I don't think so I reckon they do own both of the it's like another flat</u>
<u n="140" who="S0192">we saw the guy that lived there though and he didn't look too normal are we both having a cigarette?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0198">yeah I'll roll one as well</u>
<u n="142" who="S0192">yeah mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0198"><trunc>s</trunc> oh the sun's on that side this time of the day isn't it?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it is</u>
<u n="145" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's shining on the back of the building</u>
<u n="146" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't think we ever get the sun here on the <unclear>back</unclear> or</u>
<u n="147" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah no that's fine</u>
<u n="148" who="S0192">you'd dry clothes up here pretty quick</u>
<u n="149" who="S0198">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="150" who="S0192">if you just put a hobbyhorse on this balcony</u>
<u n="151" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0192">you need a small enough hobbyhorse</u>
<u n="153" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you don't want to you'd want erm pegs though because you don't want them to actually blow off</u>
<u n="154" who="S0192">I mean they shouldn't blow over this railing er</u>
<u n="155" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it gets pretty windy here but yeah I guess not</u>
<u n="156" who="S0192">no I'm gonna direct it this way cos I talk louder then maybe I</u>
<u n="157" who="S0198">erm <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> I feel like er I feel like if you just rig something or just stands if you stand a hobbyhorse in the kitchen with the kitchen window open it would dry really fast</u>
<u n="158" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh I mean that would dry really quickly and there's the sun</u>
<u n="159" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the sun on that side as well</u>
<u n="160" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the natural sun on that side as well</u>
<u n="161" who="S0198">I feel like we could do I'm gonna try and get one in Dorset cos I don't really wanna carry one up the hill here</u>
<u n="162" who="S0192">what a hobbyhorse?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0198" trans="overlap">if I can get a cheap or a cheaper one at a boot fair I'll get one in Dorset <pause dur="short"/> if not that shop sold them for twelve ninety-nine</u>
<u n="164" who="S0192">yeah <trunc>wh</trunc></u>
<u n="165" who="S0198" trans="overlap">cos we are gonna</u>
<u n="166" who="S0192" trans="overlap">which shop?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0198">cos I don't know where we're gonna have a a rope up constantly</u>
<u n="168" who="S0192">which shop <trunc>t</trunc> sold them for twelve ninety-nine?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0198">er what shop was it? Robert Dyer I think the one we</u>
<u n="170" who="S0192" trans="overlap">a Dyas or whatever it is</u>
<u n="171" who="S0198">yeah Robert Dyas Dyas or whatever it's called the one we first went into to get erm <pause dur="short"/> curtain hooks</u>
<u n="172" who="S0192">hooks yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh we'll have to go back there and have a look then</u>
<u n="173" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0192">mm it's a nice tree it's gently sloping down</u>
<u n="175" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I can see hills in the distance over there</u>
<u n="177" who="S0198">there are hills around there</u>
<u n="178" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you can see in the far distant <pause dur="short"/> erm apart from the crazy neighbour earlier</u>
<u n="179" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she seemed</u>
<u n="180" who="S0192">I'm not sure what that was all about</u>
<u n="181" who="S0198">you didn't like her did you? definitely was a</u>
<u n="182" who="S0192">well she was slagging off the neighbours wasn't she?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah criticising people <pause dur="short"/> but I felt like I don't know I don't know what I thought she was talking about</u>
<u n="184" who="S0192">because people sit out on their balconies shouldn't be nosy it should be seen as being neighbourhoody</u>
<u n="185" who="S0198">neighbourhoody yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0192">like community</u>
<u n="187" who="S0198">well it's the point of people living in <anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0198">becomes <unclear/> for on-show part of the the vibe around here isn't it?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0192">see these ones all have conversions those ones have conversions on both windows can you see?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0192">it's got those two front windows but this has only got one and so does that one</u>
<u n="193" who="S0198">yeah so that house has been more divided than this one then</u>
<u n="194" who="S0192">yeah it has <pause dur="short"/> you don't get too much traffic over here which is nice it's not like a constant road <trunc>dri</trunc> like with cars driving past</u>
<u n="195" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0192">because you could easily live on a busy road</u>
<u n="197" who="S0198">yeah you could which would be weird seeing people in traffic going by all the time</u>
<u n="198" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm you're definitely a bit on show here but you're bound to be it's</u>
<u n="199" who="S0198">it looks better now there's curtains hanging up a reckon</u>
<u n="200" who="S0192">it does</u>
<u n="201" who="S0198">well just from the outside as you said it's a clear indication that the it's not vacant</u>
<u n="202" who="S0192">yeah somebody's there</u>
<u n="203" who="S0198">quite a few people don't bother with nets some people do</u>
<u n="204" who="S0192">and they've got nets I guess over there now</u>
<u n="205" who="S0198">that's another thing you can do which sometimes people do just have it around the bottom section and not round the top for privacy</u>
<u n="206" who="S0192">where's that? oh yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the house on I mean they have blinds as well but</u>
<u n="208" who="S0192">how do we get all that installed? that is hooks and rope and like</u>
<u n="209" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0192" trans="overlap">hooks and elastic chord or whatever it is</u>
<u n="211" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's just a little bit of hook though isn't it?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0198">that might hold it more</u>
<u n="214" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I <trunc>mi</trunc> I mean my mum said she'd spend up to fifty quid so if there's things we need at that point we just say yeah it would be nice to have some drapes</u>
<u n="215" who="S0198">so</u>
<u n="216" who="S0192">so people</u>
<u n="217" who="S0198">the shelves might be still in need at that point</u>
<u n="218" who="S0192">pardon me</u>
<u n="219" who="S0198">so you don't need a pub garden on a day like today</u>
<u n="220" who="S0192">no you don't this is our pub</u>
<u n="221" who="S0198">mm it is</u>
<u n="222" who="S0192">cheers to the new house</u>
<u n="223" who="S0198"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="225" who="S0198">it's like <foreign lang="fre">Santé</foreign> and <foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0198">then there's</u>
<u n="228" who="S0192">how many others do we know? <foreign lang="jpn">Kanpai</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="kor">geonbae</foreign></u>
<u n="229" who="S0198"><foreign lang="kor">geonbae</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="ita">salute</foreign></u>
<u n="230" who="S0192"><foreign lang="ita">cin cin</foreign></u>
<u n="231" who="S0198"><foreign lang="ita">cin cin</foreign></u>
<u n="232" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">arriba abajo adentro al centro</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="spa">al centro adentro</foreign> that was it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0198">yeah it it was</u>
<u n="234" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><foreign lang="spa">arriba abajo</foreign></u>
<u n="235" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><foreign lang="spa">abajo</foreign></u>
<u n="236" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">adentro adentro</foreign></u>
<u n="237" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><foreign lang="spa">adentro</foreign> yeah so <foreign lang="spa">arriba abajo adentro</foreign></u>
<u n="238" who="S0192" trans="overlap">er above below</u>
<u n="239" who="S0198">in the middle</u>
<u n="240" who="S0192" trans="overlap">in the centre</u>
<u n="241" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0192">and down</u>
<u n="243" who="S0198">oh down</u>
<u n="244" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and in yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah mm above below <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0192" trans="overlap">rolls off the tongue nicely</u>
<u n="247" who="S0198">do you miss Latin America?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0192">no I do we'll go back</u>
<u n="249" who="S0198">I know that was a good trip</u>
<u n="250" who="S0192">not many people get to take a year out and travel there</u>
<u n="251" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="252" who="S0192">I think people are might be a bit envious if we do another year in Africa or something</u>
<u n="253" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0192">I don't see why we can't do another year it would be good to travel for at least one more year</u>
<u n="255" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0192">just got to raise the money want to chuck us the lighter?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0198">parents have got a year to get used to the idea of us going to Saudi or the Middle East</u>
<u n="258" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0198">and then</u>
<u n="260" who="S0192">cos we <trunc>w</trunc> we might be potentially working there for a while <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0198">wouldn't rule out Turkey still if a good position came up just to still have a</u>
<u n="262" who="S0192">they're two years in those contracts now aren't they?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0198">they're all of them two years I mean you don't even really wanna work at <unclear/> anyway</u>
<u n="264" who="S0192">I'd only wanna work at like a uni or an equitable uni I've seen quite a few jobs there that pay quite considerable less</u>
<u n="265" who="S0198" trans="overlap">less typical ESL positions</u>
<u n="266" who="S0192"><unclear>we've just</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> again especially if we're going to go and visit them</u>
<u n="267" who="S0198">yeah once our internet's up and running I'm gonna give them a call</u>
<u n="268" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if we've got the money we should definitely try and go</u>
<u n="269" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah we should I agree cos er it's just a good trip to do</u>
<u n="270" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0198">and also especially if by that point <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s back out on her boat</u>
<u n="272" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0198">which she might she may or may not be by she should be by the end of July</u>
<u n="274" who="S0192" trans="overlap">depends when we go I guess if we go in August or something <pause dur="short"/> I mean we can always</u>
<u n="275" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I imagine the flights might be a bit cheaper in July</u>
<u n="276" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we can always do a erm <pause dur="short"/> summer programme somewhere to earn some quick hard cash</u>
<u n="277" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah that's true they kick off you could do that first two weeks of July and then leave</u>
<u n="278" who="S0192">it depends how your dissertation</u>
<u n="279" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah it really does depend on the dissertation <pause dur="short"/> er like I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her sister <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had just finished her dissertation that day but she hadn't edited yet it has to be in this Friday but she'd like she'd got to her <unclear/> she felt pretty comfortable with it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0192">what was it on?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0198">given herself I didn't actually ask given herself a week to edit it yeah I didn't ask her</u>
<u n="282" who="S0192">you girls ask different questions don't you so</u>
<u n="283" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah we do we</u>
<u n="284" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0198">we jump about topics so frequently</u>
<u n="286" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0198">it's incredible but I mean conversation goes that way doesn't it?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0192">yeah it really does</u>
<u n="289" who="S0198">one thing reminds you of something else but you know</u>
<u n="290" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there is a module on discourse analysis I think in the second semester</u>
<u n="291" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah there's a there's a consideration towards that but <pause dur="short"/> I think I like I don't know</u>
<u n="292" who="S0192">psycho-linguistic</u>
<u n="293" who="S0198">I think I like the likes learning the core aspects of it but not necessarily going too deep into the <pause dur="short"/> the serious side of it or whatever</u>
<u n="294" who="S0192">so much</u>
<u n="295" who="S0198">but maybe I don't know</u>
<u n="296" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cos that's more my cup of tea it's not bad if we take different modules is it?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0198">no no</u>
<u n="298" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is if we specialist slightly differently <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0198">there will be of all the ESL students well anyway imagine second language acquisition is gonna be busy</u>
<u n="300" who="S0192">yeah there might be quite a few people in there I imagine it'll be mandatory</u>
<u n="301" who="S0198">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping that doesn't open it up to changing times or anything</u>
<u n="302" who="S0192">no I wondered if they're set now</u>
<u n="303" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean they've got to be set right? I guess they could get a different class</u>
<u n="305" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did say as well within the first like few weeks you can change your modules</u>
<u n="306" who="S0192">you can</u>
<u n="307" who="S0198">so it's not a big deal <pause dur="short"/> she said you can but maybe she said after the first week</u>
<u n="308" who="S0192">so we have like a drop period?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0198">kind of I suppose I'm sure we did in Bath Spa I don't know I can't remember</u>
<u n="310" who="S0192">I mean I got on some other modules</u>
<u n="311" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0192">ended up doing those English modules</u>
<u n="313" who="S0198">I know in the very very first week I did I took a class in history and I didn't have a I just was so what? I didn't know what she was talking about</u>
<u n="314" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0198">I can't remember what the module was which is random for an undergrad module I just remember thinking this is too hectic</u>
<u n="316" who="S0192">no I don't wanna do this</u>
<u n="317" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="318" who="S0192">certainly in your first year</u>
<u n="319" who="S0198">changed it to something else <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>wasn</trunc> like yeah it was in the first semester</u>
<u n="320" who="S0192">I just did like the history of <unclear>drama</unclear> one-o-one and one-o-two pretty much</u>
<u n="321" who="S0198">pretty much yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0192">the first year</u>
<u n="323" who="S0198">the American equivalents</u>
<u n="324" who="S0192">theory of drama theory dramaturging <pause dur="short"/> no <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0198" trans="overlap">first first of <unclear/> do get plenty of seagulls around here</u>
<u n="326" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0198">it's cos the sea's just down the hill</u>
<u n="328" who="S0192">it's not far is it?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0198">we might get family there actually come and visit</u>
<u n="330" who="S0192">I mean if there's one place that they might come and visit it would probably be <anon type="place"/> wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might bring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up on the train that's if he ever has the money</u>
<u n="332" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0192">it's crazy it's</u>
<u n="335" who="S0198" trans="overlap">he would like to</u>
<u n="336" who="S0192">faster for your parents to drive up to the M25 than it is to just drive across</u>
<u n="337" who="S0198">across yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not <trunc>cau</trunc> they don't he they're not on the M twenty-<trunc>fi</trunc> they're on the M23 longer than the M25</u>
<u n="338" who="S0192">yeah you're only a small portion of it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah it is a small potion</u>
<u n="340" who="S0192">well that's the</u>
<u n="341" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but it's quicker going the motorway way</u>
<u n="342" who="S0192">they have to take quite a big portion</u>
<u n="343" who="S0198">then going through the only thing is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it's just the only problem is it is quicker but it's touch and go because it only takes one accident on the motorway</u>
<u n="344" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0198">and then it's built up it's like and then you're two hours later</u>
<u n="346" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0198">whereas if you go the other way it's just all A roads and whatever and you can if there's an accident you just go through a different you go through the town a little bit more</u>
<u n="348" who="S0192">yeah yeah it's alright not a problem</u>
<u n="349" who="S0198" trans="overlap">so so it depends on the risk cos he has to he's had to travel quite a bit for work</u>
<u n="350" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="351" who="S0198">he went up to erm yeah like I think did he say to you? he was saying to you he's gone up as far as er Milton Keynes and that kind of area</u>
<u n="352" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah you've seen his job</u>
<u n="354" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he knew my area a little bit mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but now he doesn't like now</u>
<u n="356" who="S0192">it's a little bit chilly on the old feet</u>
<u n="357" who="S0198">yeah I've got goose pimples</u>
<u n="358" who="S0192">my feet</u>
<u n="359" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well I'm wearing slippers</u>
<u n="360" who="S0192">my feet are changing colour</u>
<u n="361" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0192">they are genuinely they don't look healthy</u>
<u n="363" who="S0198">it might be warmer the other side of the sun</u>
<u n="364" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0198">although I think the sun's</u>
<u n="366" who="S0192">I think it is warmer</u>
<u n="367" who="S0198">behind the cloud now</u>
<u n="368" who="S0192">it's no good</u>
<u n="369" who="S0198">it's never just blue actually quite a few mornings I woke up at my parents and the very first thing in the morning between like around seven it was like it was a nice clear morning</u>
<u n="370" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0198">but by about nine the clouds had started patching in and then it was like this for the rest of the day <pause dur="short"/> and it was hard to tell whether or not it was gonna stay like this or whether it's gonna get really dark and start raining</u>
<u n="372" who="S0192">it's very changeable isn't it that's it</u>
<u n="373" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0192">it just goes all over the place</u>
<u n="375" who="S0198">it's cos clouds are often the clouds that oh it's <unclear/> the clouds that run in are</u>
<u n="376" who="S0192">this could be a neighbour</u>
<u n="377" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="379" who="S0198">oh he has got a young lady</u>
<u n="380" who="S0192">oh someone from <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> could be</u>
<u n="381" who="S0198" trans="overlap">could be like inventory</u>
<u n="382" who="S0192">you alright there?</u>
<u n="383" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hiya</u>
<u n="384" who="S0198" trans="overlap">hello</u>
<u n="385" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">are you flat three?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0192">yes we are yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yes we are</u>
<u n="388" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've got your inventory</u>
<u n="389" who="S0198">inventory?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0192">brilliant</u>
<u n="391" who="S0198" trans="overlap">brilliant</u>
<u n="392" who="S0192">I'll come down and grab that</u>
<u n="393" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="394" who="S0198">thank you</u>
<u n="395" who="S0192" trans="overlap">thanks very much <event desc="recording skips"/> yeah okay so he just dropped that off</u>
<u n="396" who="S0198">off the inventory</u>
<u n="397" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh so they were just gonna post it through the door they were never</u>
<u n="399" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they were never gonna come in then</u>
<u n="401" who="S0192">well they've already done it haven't they?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0192">shall we bring the stuff round and go</u>
<u n="404" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I've got this bit left on my roll-ups</u>
<u n="405" who="S0192">do you wanna just smoke it out the back?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0198">alright then</u>
<u n="407" who="S0192">yep</u>
<u n="408" who="S0198">yeah bring it round</u>
<u n="409" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do you wanna take that thing?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0198">yeah and then we can do this then</u>
<u n="411" who="S0192">oh that's definitely a bit chilly on my feet</u>
<u n="412" who="S0198">yeah these slippers I'm so glad I packed them</u>
<u n="413" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0198">yeah <unclear>I'm going to the bathroom</unclear></u>
<u n="415" who="S0192">wonder what this inventory says</u>
<u n="416" who="S0198">don't know bits of <unclear/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's pretty dirty</u>
<u n="418" who="S0198">it's a big weathered isn't it?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0192" trans="overlap">could put something like permanently there</u>
<u n="420" who="S0198">and replace this <unclear>door handle</unclear>?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0192">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="422" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0192">shall I open a window? it's</u>
<u n="424" who="S0198">yeah that would be good</u>
<u n="425" who="S0192">do you think just keep the air going through?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> good idea</u>
<u n="427" who="S0192">the old sash windows</u>
<u n="428" who="S0198" trans="overlap">keep the air keep the damp old air maybe</u>
<u n="429" who="S0192">doesn't have to be open much does it don't think anyone can get in through there</u>
<u n="430" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="431" who="S0192">right cool</u>
<u n="432" who="S0198">he was <unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0192">he did have a little <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> bag</u>
<u n="434" who="S0198">yeah have to all look dapper these estate agents don't they?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0192">I know yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0198">for the time that they are</u>
<u n="437" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's a bit it's a bit OTT <pause dur="short"/> for an estate agent not entirely sure why oh wow</u>
<u n="438" who="S0198">oh it's gonna be a problem this side of the building you don't notice it out on the balcony</u>
<u n="439" who="S0192">I'm sure if we point this in it won't be too bad</u>
<u n="440" who="S0198">yeah that door should be already as it is for now</u>
<u n="441" who="S0192">yeah it should be alright for now</u>
<u n="442" who="S0198"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if we're going to smoke another rollie maybe we should have <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> says an inventory</u>
<u n="444" who="S0198">how many pages is it then?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0192">oh they've got a photo</u>
<u n="446" who="S0198">oh there you go are they taking photos for us?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0192">I don't know</u>
<u n="448" who="S0198">which is fine that's fine</u>
<u n="449" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no I think just er any retrieved photographs accompanying the report will be noted adjacent to the relevant copy something like that we've got seven days to check it when does that leave us until?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0198">Wednesday I suppose I think it's seven days</u>
<u n="451" who="S0192" trans="overlap">complaints</u>
<u n="452" who="S0198" trans="overlap">is there seven days for a delivery?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0192"><event desc="unintelligible"/> condensational mould you've got to wipe surfaces daily</u>
<u n="454" who="S0198">I mean</u>
<u n="455" who="S0192">fixtures should be</u>
<u n="456" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there's no damp yet is there?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0192">no there really isn't all items of furniture well there aren't any <pause dur="short"/> oh wow they're pretty yeah they tell you about the front door</u>
<u n="458" who="S0198">do they describe everything like officially then?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0192">number three <unclear>grass</unclear> Yale lock chrome mortise lock deadlock between two</u>
<u n="460" who="S0198" trans="overlap">how about the windows in like the bedroom cos they were pretty filthy?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0192">it's it even says stuff like the hooks on the back of the door</u>
<u n="462" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0192">one white plastic hook to interior of door one hook to interior rope hook appears missing replaced with metal hook paint markings to fitments door closing mechanism working minor paint mark and tarnishing door closing we need to really go through all this</u>
<u n="464" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0192">skirting flooring doorbell chime untested discoloured paint marked</u>
<u n="466" who="S0198">I mean we have paid for this company to do this they should be thorough</u>
<u n="467" who="S0192">yeah they've even tested the door living room balcony door <pause dur="short"/> rusting to some fitments could be tarnishing glass seasonably mark to interior</u>
<u n="468" who="S0198">seasonably marked</u>
<u n="469" who="S0192"><unclear/> so heavy chipping throughout all paintwork paintwork cracking</u>
<u n="470" who="S0198">yeah good</u>
<u n="471" who="S0192">balcony <pause dur="short"/> they count that as the living room then bathroom</u>
<u n="472" who="S0198">what about the bedroom windows?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0192">yeah I know that's not everything walls flooring extractor fan working but very noisy</u>
<u n="474" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it says it yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0198">that's good so they can't come around and be like what have you done you left this on</u>
<u n="477" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no it says it here bedroom door ceiling walls skirting flooring heating windows heavy mildew surrounding edge of glass panes at edge of glass panes heavily paint and scratch mark both sash chords in place but paint marks tarnishing to brass fittings cable protruding to bottom left yellow stained <unclear/> so <pause dur="short"/> so they're definitely erm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0198">how about the cleanliness of the window? are they not commenting on that?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0192">doesn't really say no</u>
<u n="480" who="S0198">no well</u>
<u n="481" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just says heavy mildew surrounding edge of glass panes I mean if we're gonna take some photos I mean er <pause dur="short"/> and talk about it</u>
<u n="482" who="S0198">well they have taken photos it's in the back</u>
<u n="483" who="S0192">it does say only one door shelf present to the fridge usage is marked yellowing and discolouration</u>
<u n="484" who="S0198">oh really?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0192">yeah which then I mean it's the number of smoke alarms</u>
<u n="486" who="S0198">so if they just if we just accepted it as it is and the landlord won't actually because where do you get a shelf from for a fridge?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0192">yeah I don't know</u>
<event desc="sound of children screaming"/>
<u n="488" who="S0198">those children</u>
<u n="489" who="S0192">do we shut the window?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0198">yeah that's probably a good idea</u>
<u n="491" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we can leave the other window open</u>
<u n="492" who="S0198">because it's just ridiculous isn't it?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0192">it's very noisy</u>
<u n="494" who="S0198">as you said in the winter they shouldn't be out there should they</u>
<u n="495" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they shouldn't be out there no <pause dur="short"/> oh they do have pictures they've got pictures of the electrics why do we have four different electrics?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0198">what are they pictures from?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0192">these pictures are rubbish anyway</u>
<u n="498" who="S0198">what is that even of where is that?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0192">it's the electric wherever that is there's four different ones they've got a reading here rate one rate two rate three rate four electricity</u>
<u n="500" who="S0198">well where are our electricity meters?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="502" who="S0198" trans="overlap">is that downstairs in that cupboard?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0192" trans="overlap">should in they've taken a picture of the fridge</u>
<u n="504" who="S0198">oh good look the stove</u>
<u n="505" who="S0192">the stove top</u>
<u n="506" who="S0198">good</u>
<u n="507" who="S0192">it's not very clear though <pause dur="short"/> oh well you can see he's got his building tools in here whenever they did that that was the day before</u>
<u n="508" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0192">oh he's got a whole</u>
<u n="510" who="S0198">things very patched up there</u>
<u n="511" who="S0192" trans="overlap">table up here <pause dur="short"/> didn't do a very good job of that though did he?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no they didn't and they fixed one little bit basically</u>
<u n="513" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0198">and no pictures of how dirty the windows are that must be cos that's like a you know if it's a <unclear/> stupid thing or not</u>
<u n="515" who="S0192">yeah well I'll agree with them anyway</u>
<u n="516" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0192">and disagree where is necessary we've got to go round and do that thoroughly then soon</u>
<u n="518" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah maybe all the markings and stuff</u>
<u n="519" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0198" trans="overlap">feel like it could happen easily and is that is that more markings or is that just where it's</u>
<u n="521" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just dirt or just wear wear and tear</u>
<u n="522" who="S0198" trans="overlap">scuffs on that as well</u>
<u n="523" who="S0192">absolutely no idea looks a bit like that</u>
<u n="524" who="S0198">cos I don't know yeah we definitely need to check carpets cos they charge you a fortune to clean a carpet</u>
<u n="525" who="S0192">yeah I know it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="526" who="S0198">like three hundred pounds for a professional carpet cleaner on this carpet and the carpet didn't cost that much I doubt</u>
<u n="527" who="S0192">no it didn't</u>
<u n="528" who="S0198">for this cheap bit of rug</u>
<u n="529" who="S0192">do you wanna move those speakers over there and see if they work?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0198">yeah okay what attach it to there</u>
<u n="531" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if we plug it up use a laptop or something</u>
<u n="532" who="S0198">laptop maybe we can get some music</u>
<u n="533" who="S0192">don't even need to have a laptop going really just a er MP3 player or anything</u>
<u n="534" who="S0198" trans="overlap">MP3 player yeah that's true anything that'll plug into it</u>
<u n="535" who="S0192">alright if I rest this keyboard</u>
<u n="536" who="S0198" trans="overlap">are they wired up now the speakers then?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0192" trans="overlap">not quite no just move them over there and then erm I'll wire them</u>
<u n="538" who="S0198">no but you have one you have to stick it to the back</u>
<u n="539" who="S0192">not both of them I don't think maybe one of them I'm not sure</u>
<u n="540" who="S0198">oh alright then</u>
<u n="541" who="S0192">I've got a good old cable going on here so</u>
<u n="542" who="S0198">so this one this one isn't attached okay</u>
<u n="543" who="S0192">it was just from Poundland this cable though wasn't it?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0198">no yeah it was but I mean it's just a basic jack lead isn't it?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0192">yeah you don't need much else</u>
<u n="546" who="S0198">doesn't have to be too technical</u>
<u n="547" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so this is <unclear/> and move this over</u>
<u n="548" who="S0198">don't know where this one is attached</u>
<u n="549" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do you want to carry that?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah one of them I attached <pause dur="short"/> we're going to have some permanent music set up</u>
<u n="552" who="S0198">absolutely</u>
<u n="553" who="S0192">in here</u>
<u n="554" who="S0198">and something probably er don't need to plug it in yet do we?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0192">if you just get an MP3 player</u>
<u n="556" who="S0198">just to make sure it works and put this away</u>
<u n="557" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah so</u>
<u n="558" who="S0198">so you can charge your your MP player via this as well you don't need to I mean you can do it on your computer obviously does that have</u>
<u n="559" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh does that work for both of them?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0198">it works for a plug socket yeah just anything that's a Samsung device will use the same connector</u>
<u n="561" who="S0192">alright do you wanna grab an MP3 player?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0198">yeah put it on here</u>
<u n="563" who="S0192">alright we should have some sound minimum maximum some speakers</u>
<u n="564" who="S0198">get some music going then</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">where's the MP3 player? where's that little cable as well?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0198">you threw it as it's it's between your feet</u>
<u n="567" who="S0192">it's got a plug here</u>
<u n="568" who="S0198" trans="overlap">for some reason</u>
<u n="569" who="S0192">right this whole</u>
<u n="570" who="S0198" trans="overlap">now these speakers haven't been used for about six years</u>
<u n="571" who="S0192">where does this I always struggle to formulate again using</u>
<u n="572" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0192">yeah this one goes</u>
<u n="574" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's a good</u>
<u n="575" who="S0192">here</u>
<u n="576" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's good news</u>
<u n="577" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0198" trans="overlap">obviously not the volume too loud at first</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">no got to choose an artist just whoever or whatever comes up first</u>
<u n="580" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the power's on so that's the half promising</u>
<u n="581" who="S0192" trans="overlap">hopefully it'll work</u>
<u n="582" who="S0198">that's promising</u>
<u n="583" who="S0192">can't be sure though we need to check both speakers</u>
<u n="584" who="S0198">oh they're working they're both working</u>
<u n="585" who="S0192">are they both working?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0192">see if it's <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0198">that's fine isn't it?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0192">it's not very loud or</u>
<u n="590" who="S0198">I mean you can go louder but yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0192">it's erm it works</u>
<u n="592" who="S0198">it's some speakers isn't it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we'll just make</u>
<u n="594" who="S0198" trans="overlap">we just need to clean them up</u>
<u n="595" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so therefore that</u>
<u n="596" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and once they're hooked up to the I mean we can't have music too loud here anyway</u>
<u n="597" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="598" who="S0198">we've got all kinds of neighbours that we have to think about</u>
<u n="599" who="S0192">we've got some sound there so that's good so hopefully they won't pop round anymore</u>
<u n="600" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="601" who="S0192">at least we won't have people round</u>
<u n="602" who="S0198">he was going to post it through the door weren't they</u>
<u n="603" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0198">bit lazy in the car unless he's doing a few rounds which I hope he is</u>
<u n="605" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0198">to kind of do it on their way out to doing something</u>
<u n="607" who="S0192">he's only just round the corner isn't he</u>
<u n="608" who="S0198">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0192">I wonder how many properties you can have round here</u>
<u n="610" who="S0198">I know probably a few</u>
<u n="611" who="S0192">shall I make another rollie?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there's a <trunc>cou</trunc> yeah there's a couple down the road that have got the young the er <unclear>Ford</unclear> outside of their apartments so</u>
<u n="613" who="S0192">there are</u>
<u n="614" who="S0198">erm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0192">that's useful shall I just make one of my lists?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0198"><unclear>over here</unclear> just need to get and this will see what your dad brings up see how that because I mean we're gonna he's gonna have a bit of stuff I think I think we're probably gonna want as least another bookshelf or something erm to put some book to like to make it tidier basically</u>
<u n="619" who="S0192">no definitely</u>
<u n="620" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0192">what</u>
<u n="622" who="S0198" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0192">on top of what we're getting?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think so</u>
<u n="625" who="S0192">so we need to buy one I mean maybe Argos has a cheap bookshelf or something</u>
<u n="626" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it probably does</u>
<u n="627" who="S0192">write it down here</u>
<u n="628" who="S0198" trans="overlap">should have probably grabbed at Argos catalogue while we were there</u>
<u n="629" who="S0192">oh were they free?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0198">I think so I don't even know if they even do you remember you'd be able to go in and there'd be a pile of them but</u>
<u n="631" who="S0192">is Argos</u>
<u n="632" who="S0198" trans="overlap">everything's online now isn't it?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0192">yeah is it the cheapest of places? until we get the internet we're in a bit of limbo really and until you get back form Dorset</u>
<u n="634" who="S0198"><trunc>Dors</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0192">typical you going to Dorset just after we move in</u>
<u n="636" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I know sorry darling</u>
<u n="637" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's rubbish</u>
<u n="638" who="S0198">it's the one time of the year there's the bloody steam fair</u>
<u n="639" who="S0192">I'm sure that's important the steam fair</u>
<u n="640" who="S0198">well my dad's pretty excited about it they would have been pretty gutted if I couldn't have gone</u>
<u n="641" who="S0192">they don't seem bothered that I can't go then</u>
<u n="642" who="S0198">no I mean my mum was would have quite like it of course she does she's like she's a bit more like your mum I suppose they'll hopefully get to spend some time with with you as well as me this year I suppose</u>
<u n="643" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah if possible</u>
<u n="644" who="S0198">just to build a relationship or whatever</u>
<u n="645" who="S0192">my mum wants you up for Christmas if that's possible</u>
<u n="646" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but erm yeah obviously I'll come up maybe the week before Christmas</u>
<u n="647" who="S0192">yeah or the week after</u>
<u n="648" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and then or the week afterwards Christmas day Boxing day Christmas Eve they're</u>
<u n="649" who="S0192">for your family</u>
<u n="650" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they're a no-go</u>
<u n="651" who="S0192">no of course I'm not expecting you to come</u>
<u n="652" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but no yeah no</u>
<u n="653" who="S0192">I don't think they're expecting you to come up either erm bearing in mind that I've got two families as well</u>
<u n="654" who="S0198" trans="overlap">where are you going is it your mum's for Christmas?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0192">yeah I can't really</u>
<u n="656" who="S0198" trans="overlap">just for sentimental that that's</u>
<u n="657" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I can't really disappoint my mum too much by not going to hers</u>
<u n="658" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm I think she'd be a bit upset</u>
<u n="659" who="S0192">I'll probably have to</u>
<u n="660" who="S0198">why isn't any we don't have any like pieces of er cable attachments for cameras that we don't use that we can string across that that erm oh it's all attached isn't it?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0192">yeah I don't think they're thin enough or long enough</u>
<u n="662" who="S0198">that we can put through the</u>
<u n="663" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that cable we just bought would've worked</u>
<u n="664" who="S0198">what about this to hang across the thing to attach the curtain rail net to?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0192">that's much too thick to go through a curtain</u>
<u n="666" who="S0198">oh right to actually go through the curtain <trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> er <pause dur="short"/> no it wouldn't go through the curtain the curtain would still have to have something to hook it to hook onto this</u>
<u n="667" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but if you've just got one piece of rope that went through the curtain</u>
<u n="668" who="S0198" trans="overlap">this would just be the wire</u>
<u n="669" who="S0192">is it possible to go through the curtain is there like a</u>
<u n="670" who="S0198">I don't know I'll have a look</u>
<u n="671" who="S0192">have a closer look</u>
<u n="672" who="S0198">they're big old curtains</u>
<u n="673" who="S0192">if you were to get just a piece of rope of a piece of string would it go through?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="675" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="676" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no the curtain needs to attach to something everything's er</u>
<u n="677" who="S0192">those little bits for the thing</u>
<u n="678" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it it's not horizontal it's <pause dur="short"/> long width ways</u>
<u n="679" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we'll figure something out I need to see what my dad's got maybe the curtains that he's got are different</u>
<u n="680" who="S0198">slightly different</u>
<u n="681" who="S0192">I didn't look at anything too closely before so I should do that</u>
<u n="682" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I think they do yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then I guess the wire needs to what we just need like you said is a little piece of wood that goes along there basically a little bannister that's so little that it hooks into those hooks</u>
<u n="683" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0198">yeah don't know if that makes any sense</u>
<u n="685" who="S0192">I'm not gonna sleep in there until we get something sorted cos it's too bright and I'll see what it's like with the curtains closed tonight</u>
<u n="686" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0192">but I can't see it'll be</u>
<u n="688" who="S0198">well not with that other door exposed</u>
<u n="689" who="S0192">no it's pretty bright with the street lamp just there</u>
<u n="690" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0192">you need like blackout curtains you need something thick blinds would definitely help can we shut that door if we're gonna smoke inside?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0198">yeah I suppose we should we've still got a window open in here though haven't we to air it?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0198">yeah it'll be fine</u>
<u n="695" who="S0192">if we just sit at the back window?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0198">yeah sun's gone in now anyway</u>
<u n="697" who="S0192">it has</u>
<u n="698" who="S0198">more or less</u>
<u n="699" who="S0192">of course it is it's England it's fleeting and</u>
<u n="700" who="S0198">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> doesn't last long</u>
<u n="701" who="S0192" trans="overlap">won't last you long</u>
<u n="702" who="S0198">enjoy it whilst it lasts</u>
<u n="703" who="S0192">are we gonna prepare the chilli con carne after?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0198">I mean yeah it doesn't we can just get it on can't we see how that beef mince is</u>
<u n="707" who="S0192">can I borrow your glasses?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0198">it's probably not as erm they're in the bathroom</u>
<u n="709" who="S0192">it's twenty percent fat so it's not too bad</u>
<u n="710" who="S0198" trans="overlap">is this is this too</u>
<u n="711" who="S0192">no no that'll be fine</u>
<u n="712" who="S0198">too big?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0192">that'll be fine</u>
<u n="714" who="S0198">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's certainly cheaper than the mince we were buying that's five hundred grams for two pounds</u>
<u n="715" who="S0192">that's pretty good isn't it?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's really good</u>
<u n="717" who="S0192">it's like the same as it was in Lidl's</u>
<u n="718" who="S0198">I thought like we'll be getting our beef from there from now on regardless <vocal desc="laugh"/> of quality still probably a step up from expat marts like <unclear>sketchy</unclear> beef</u>
<u n="719" who="S0192">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="720" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I mean that was a bit on the one side wasn't it</u>
<u n="721" who="S0192">gonna finish this beer for first</u>
<u n="722" who="S0198">yeah mine's always erm was a little bit smaller but I have been drinking more than you recently</u>
<u n="723" who="S0192">yeah I haven't been drinking very much at all</u>
<u n="724" who="S0198" trans="overlap">although I didn't drink from I drank last time I drank was Friday before I came here</u>
<u n="725" who="S0192">that's pretty good</u>
<u n="726" who="S0198">or smoked a cigarette</u>
<u n="727" who="S0192">do we</u>
<u n="728" who="S0198" trans="overlap">Saturday Sunday<unclear/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0192">that's really good are <trunc>w</trunc> do we sit on the floor out here?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0198">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="731" who="S0192" trans="overlap">alright battery's still full on this thing</u>
<u n="732" who="S0198">yeah is it?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0192">wow</u>
<u n="734" who="S0198">seems to have done quite a few hours <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty good where's the lighter?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0192">pretty good er</u>
<u n="736" who="S0198">oh think I've got one</u>
<u n="737" who="S0192">oh there's two over here now</u>
<u n="738" who="S0198">oh all the boxes are here though for sitting on</u>
<u n="739" who="S0192">no they're not you're not gonna be able to sit on that</u>
<u n="740" who="S0198">no I know but it's kind of in the way of</u>
<u n="741" who="S0192">oh being able to get it <pause dur="long"/> move it</u>
<u n="742" who="S0198">move it out the way</u>
<u n="743" who="S0192">you can really hear those children here can't you?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="745" who="S0192">I'll just leave that there I'm sure it'll be fine</u>
<u n="746" who="S0198">it'll be good when we get a couple of the chairs</u>
<u n="747" who="S0192">that glass there you get it</u>
<u n="748" who="S0198">I'll get that <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0192">sit there just on the floor?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0192">no-one out here is there?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0198">get out of your way</u>
<u n="753" who="S0192">don't think there is</u>
<u n="754" who="S0198">you see did you ask him about the rubbish that we've got?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I did he said he didn't know</u>
<u n="756" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0192">but one of the people <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who lives around here she might know so we'll just have to go into the office <pause dur="short"/> well he said to ring them I said I'd probably just</u>
<u n="758" who="S0198">pop in</u>
<u n="759" who="S0192">pop in yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0198">save myself the credit thanks that's a point where</u>
<u n="761" who="S0192">pretty pretty close</u>
<u n="762" who="S0198">thought my parents would have phoned by now so I suppose I'd better have it I bet he wants to he just hasn't</u>
<u n="763" who="S0192">yeah trying to let you settle in your mum's like oh leave her alone is she working today?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0198">yes eight till eight</u>
<u n="765" who="S0192">oh she is?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0192">that's a long old shift</u>
<u n="768" who="S0198">it's a bit really long she doesn't come back very happy</u>
<u n="769" who="S0192">no I'll after doing twelve hours</u>
<u n="770" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and she's tired and she's just trying to do her best to function</u>
<u n="771" who="S0192">I'd say she hasn't been used to working but she's been doing a lot for them well she as doing a lot for your nan</u>
<u n="772" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah that yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0192">and for the grandchildren</u>
<u n="774" who="S0198">if only she could get paid to do that</u>
<u n="775" who="S0192">yeah definitely wouldn't be a bad job would it</u>
<u n="776" who="S0198">she can't</u>
<u n="777" who="S0192">she was being paid for your nan though wasn't she?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0198">yeah about fifty pound a week</u>
<u n="779" who="S0192">mm it's not a wage</u>
<u n="780" who="S0198">not a wage no</u>
<u n="781" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="782" who="S0198">but you also get <pause dur="short"/> she also got additional help in other ways through other benefits and things to being a for being a carer</u>
<u n="783" who="S0192">so there were benefits to it?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0198" trans="overlap">wasn't major though but now that</u>
<u n="785" who="S0192">she's</u>
<u n="786" who="S0198">she's earning more money now like she like the other month she's like got eight hundred pounds and she's like you know that's what's incredibly useful that's a massive boost to my monthly income</u>
<u n="787" who="S0192">yeah it really is to not have that and then to have it</u>
<u n="788" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0192">fifty quid a week is only two hundred quid so</u>
<u n="790" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="791" who="S0192">she knows the difference</u>
<u n="792" who="S0198">so she needs to keep working</u>
<u n="793" who="S0192" trans="overlap">was that after tax that then?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I think so</u>
<u n="795" who="S0192">yeah sounds about right if she got about a grand</u>
<u n="796" who="S0198">yeah and she's not full time but she keeps doing all this full time hours</u>
<u n="797" who="S0192">my mum's on that contract</u>
<u n="798" who="S0198">oh is she like?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0192">so you know like in in America where they</u>
<u n="800" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh yeah there's no</u>
<u n="801" who="S0192">that's mine</u>
<u n="802" who="S0198">oh sorry</u>
<u n="803" who="S0192">where they erm they keep them on part time job forms</u>
<u n="804" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0192">like I'm one hour away from being full time so they don't give me</u>
<u n="806" who="S0198">we do the same</u>
<u n="807" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0198">and my brother doesn't get any sick leave full time job no sick pay</u>
<u n="809" who="S0192">what a joke</u>
<u n="810" who="S0198">Specsavers <trunc>re</trunc> retracted it because too many people took liberties</u>
<u n="811" who="S0192">well you would never take</u>
<u n="812" who="S0198" trans="overlap">so he doesn't actually get sick pay</u>
<u n="813" who="S0192">oh that isn't good</u>
<u n="814" who="S0198" trans="overlap">said I think that's illegal in England isn't it?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0192">what did he say?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0198">don't know apparently not they're not gonna be breaking that law</u>
<u n="817" who="S0192">it's perfectly fine</u>
<u n="818" who="S0198">so he said he went in once and he was clearly so ill that they sent him home but like the last week he had a flu type thing like he said he was really ill but he still went to work still kind of went through it and I said that's great so now that everyone you came in contact with for a week is going to go home and get sick</u>
<u n="819" who="S0192">yeah has got the flu</u>
<u n="820" who="S0198">because your company won't pay for you to have a day off work</u>
<u n="821" who="S0192">it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="822" who="S0198">it's terrible</u>
<u n="823" who="S0192">stuff just seems to be getting tighter and tighter doesn't it jobs don't seem to be getting better</u>
<u n="824" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="825" who="S0192">they seem to be cutting back on everything after the recession there was like you know</u>
<u n="826" who="S0198">like the</u>
<u n="827" who="S0192">want a job in a hotel? need to speak three languages</u>
<u n="828" who="S0198">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0192">have a degree in hotel management or something ridiculous</u>
<u n="830" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I know and if you're gonna take away people's sick pay well then just be like look we'll meet you in the middle and we'll give you six days sort <trunc>o</trunc> extra vacation</u>
<u n="831" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0198">paid leave</u>
<u n="833" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0198">cos that's what you would have I suggest you keep that as a sick pay</u>
<u n="835" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="836" who="S0198" trans="overlap">people wouldn't but then they can't call in sick so it's up to them isn't it?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0192">yeah sometimes you really are too sick to work though</u>
<u n="838" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0192">teaching especially when I had some <trunc>ser</trunc> basically migraines I'm pretty sure</u>
<u n="840" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0192">it's pretty horrible just teaching when your head is pounding and you've got to perform and you've got to talk to people</u>
<u n="842" who="S0198">it's terrible</u>
<u n="843" who="S0192">not nice</u>
<u n="844" who="S0198">I guess it's in an ideal world is that class that they do but you can't really do that in our job</u>
<u n="845" who="S0192">depending the class or the course that you're running</u>
<u n="846" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah it does depend on the class and the course <pause dur="short"/> got through it though and the conversation programme came and went didn't it?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0192">it really did yeah six weeks of that was pretty quick</u>
<u n="848" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah really quick</u>
<u n="849" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0198">they weren't difficult days were they?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0192">no three hours a day</u>
<u n="852" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="853" who="S0192">of work most people can't confess to that <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty good</u>
<u n="854" who="S0198">it was pretty good <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="855" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0198">well probably won't have that in our next job</u>
<u n="857" who="S0192">no probably won't in any job for a while</u>
<u n="858" who="S0198" trans="overlap">or the job after that</u>
<u n="859" who="S0192">by the sounds of things in Saudi they make you work full days</u>
<u n="860" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0192">and we're gonna be at different institute so</u>
<u n="862" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="863" who="S0192">it's we're not gonna see each other in the day</u>
<u n="864" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="865" who="S0192" trans="overlap">not at all I was saying to my friend some of my friends have asked about our marriage and stuff and like are you actually married and it kind of annoyed me a bit that like apparently in my dad's house <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="866" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah the doctor</u>
<u n="867" who="S0192">missus they're married now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and somebody else <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> all asked my dad like within a day of me us posting that is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> married? like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wrote it up or something and so did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="869" who="S0192">and he said no we're not married</u>
<u n="870" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0192">and I was a little bit like well</u>
<u n="872" who="S0198">that's what my I'm looking at that sort of thing</u>
<u n="873" who="S0192">I said it you know I explained that in our eyes we are and I said think about it I've lived with her for nine years I said we've basically or we haven't quite got but we're getting a joint bank account we work together</u>
<u n="874" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0192">teach together pretty much and have always lived together how more married can you be other than having children?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0198">I know I don't know why people are so it surprises me that some people still that I thought were more not open-minded just they don't care themselves about married but still ask and get excited and</u>
<u n="877" who="S0192" trans="overlap">don't deem it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="878" who="S0198">they still think of it as being significant if you've actually gone and done it</u>
<u n="879" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0198">signed the paper</u>
<u n="881" who="S0192">guess people must think that we do to have done it</u>
<u n="882" who="S0198">I I guess so</u>
<u n="883" who="S0192">that would try to explain that <pause dur="short"/> but no I <pause dur="short"/> we're not that traditional</u>
<u n="884" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="885" who="S0192">got a wooden ring</u>
<u n="886" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0192">you were wearing it earlier oh you're still wearing it now</u>
<u n="888" who="S0198">I'm still wearing it it's been er scratched and dented quite badly oh my god</u>
<u n="889" who="S0192">has it?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0198">yeah look at that side</u>
<u n="891" who="S0192">let's have a look</u>
<u n="892" who="S0198">that might have been from</u>
<u n="893" who="S0192">oh wow yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="895" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it is</u>
<u n="896" who="S0198">it's got a bit of wear to it I quite like it</u>
<u n="897" who="S0192">do you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0198">yeah sorry it's damaged through</u>
<u n="899" who="S0192">oh it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="900" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that side's been seems more pristine</u>
<u n="901" who="S0192" trans="overlap">doesn't bother me just when it's too damaged for you <pause dur="short"/> we'll get you another one</u>
<u n="902" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> say that was a bit of a fart wasn't very girly</u>
<u n="904" who="S0198" trans="overlap">shut up whatever</u>
<u n="905" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="906" who="S0198">it is really scratched</u>
<u n="907" who="S0192">let's have a look</u>
<u n="908" who="S0198">I wondered if I maybe I've been wearing <trunc>ca</trunc> er carrying too many boxes and stuff <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0192">I can see that <trunc>scr</trunc> scratch</u>
<u n="910" who="S0198" trans="overlap">probably wasn't the best idea</u>
<u n="911" who="S0192">oh I do see a few there</u>
<u n="912" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah there's a real impact spot isn't there?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh wow that's really worn yeah and scratched</u>
<u n="914" who="S0198">and do you know what I haven't even been wearing it at home very much</u>
<u n="915" who="S0192" trans="overlap">maybe you can buff it</u>
<u n="916" who="S0198">I've done that I did that yesterday</u>
<u n="917" who="S0192">did you?</u>
<u n="918" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0192">maybe you can buff it and give it a polish</u>
<u n="920" who="S0198">yeah that's true shine it back up</u>
<u n="921" who="S0192">but erm I'll just replace it for you</u>
<u n="922" who="S0198">I mean as long as the ring itself remains intact I don't mind</u>
<u n="923" who="S0192" trans="overlap">maybe if we actually sign in <anon type="place"/> next year then er we'll get each other</u>
<u n="924" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh what was that?</u>
<u n="925" who="S0192">we'll both get each other one</u>
<u n="926" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's an earwig where's that come from?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0192">it's like an ant with an extra</u>
<u n="928" who="S0198">mm I can see an ant being battered by an earwig</u>
<u n="929" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's an elongated thorax <pause dur="short"/> do you know that's called a thorax?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0198">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0192">it's the head and the <unclear/> and then the abdomen and then the thorax</u>
<u n="932" who="S0198">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0192">I don't know why I remember that or where I learnt that but</u>
<u n="934" who="S0198">yeah I was gonna ask</u>
<u n="935" who="S0192">I I've known it since I was a child</u>
<u n="936" who="S0198">mm oh just did a little <pause dur="short"/> it looks kind of angry</u>
<u n="937" who="S0192">yeah it doesn't look too happy</u>
<u n="938" who="S0198">oh he's figured it out now he's forgot how to walk or something</u>
<u n="939" who="S0192">really need to stop smoking cigarettes</u>
<u n="940" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="941" who="S0192">it's only because we've just moved in drink a bit let's smoke a cigarette with as well</u>
<u n="942" who="S0198">cos we can't do too much else we're in limbo</u>
<u n="943" who="S0192">we are in limbo</u>
<u n="944" who="S0198">it's like being on holiday basically and when you remember you just</u>
<u n="945" who="S0192">well we're still being paid</u>
<u n="946" who="S0198">yeah <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0192">the exchange rate's good at the minute I hope it stays that</u>
<u n="948" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah that should go in Friday shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>h</trunc> it's how it's been it's been <trunc>nine</trunc> in ninety days what's today and Friday I did want</u>
<u n="950" who="S0198" trans="overlap">so do we get our severance on Friday too?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0192">no maybe it can but it probably not</u>
<u n="952" who="S0198">so yeah I remember the same old thing in our</u>
<u n="953" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it can take up to two weeks or something like that er she hasn't contacted me since</u>
<u n="954" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="955" who="S0192">she didn't replay to any of those emails I imagine she's quite busy at the moment</u>
<u n="956" who="S0198">yeah well yeah she's setting up all the new teachers isn't she?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0192">there's lots of people leaving and lots of people joining</u>
<u n="958" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0192">so I understand she's probably quite busy</u>
<u n="960" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah it must be a really busy time of the year isn't actually at that job</u>
<u n="961" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> she definitely she has to go through the rigmarole of hiring</u>
<u n="962" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="963" who="S0192">you've got a whole different round of teachers there now we're still on vacation</u>
<u n="964" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to be greeting some other people in her way</u>
<u n="965" who="S0192">yeah she ended up being a funny one didn't she?</u>
<u n="966" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="967" who="S0192">she was a strange one</u>
<u n="968" who="S0198">I wonder if she's she's she keeps talking like she's going to leave in er <trunc>ov</trunc> after Christmas but</u>
<u n="969" who="S0192">she might have been saying that for years</u>
<u n="970" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0192">she may</u>
<u n="972" who="S0198" trans="overlap">maybe she will just out of like shit I'm going to I can't <trunc>b</trunc> like just to save face almost</u>
<u n="973" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="974" who="S0198" trans="overlap">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s leaving</u>
<u n="975" who="S0192">oh he is leaving yeah</u>
<u n="976" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to have a baby</u>
<u n="977" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he said to me to yeah it's all changing <pause dur="short"/> erm her and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously get on really well</u>
<u n="978" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0192">and I do like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but at the same time she's a complete fuck up</u>
<u n="980" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0192">she's a proper alcoholic <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="982" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="983" who="S0192">but it's you know she started off so</u>
<u n="984" who="S0198" trans="overlap">she must work feeling horrible sometimes</u>
<u n="985" who="S0192">mm sun's back out</u>
<u n="986" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="987" who="S0192">I mean the sun <pause dur="short"/> it's nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's not good</u>
<u n="988" who="S0198">no the amount of wine that her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can consume and still go to work is pretty</u>
<u n="989" who="S0192">she's going to have to calm down on the front when she moves to back to America with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="990" who="S0198">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="991" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0198" trans="overlap">absolutely yeah she really is hopefully she'll just get like really active and proactive and stuff</u>
<u n="993" who="S0192">lose a bunch of weight</u>
<u n="994" who="S0198">cos yeah I can't <trunc>im</trunc> I can't picture them in</u>
<u n="995" who="S0192">she's carrying around about twenty gallons of wine</u>
<u n="996" who="S0198">in America yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="997" who="S0192">in that belly and that arse <pause dur="short"/> pretty sure she is</u>
<u n="998" who="S0198">there's a lot of wine there</u>
<u n="999" who="S0192">mm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes a bit schizo when she drinks</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0192">she clicks and she's a different person <pause dur="short"/> very very repetitive</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0192">but even before that she's a different person repetitive is her pretty drunk and then pulling faces is her extremely drunk</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0192">or she's falling asleep on random people at that point <pause dur="short"/> remember when we took her to that bar? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0192">I had to put her in a taxi</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0192">what was that called that place?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0198">where was that?</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0192">and it's where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s band kept playing</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you had to put her in a taxi?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0192">was it called Radio Star?</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0198">ah Radio Star yeah that was when it happened ah no that night like it <trunc>jus</trunc> yeah that was that was a that was a bit of an eye-opener</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0198">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean I don't think we'd ever actually gone out drinking with her in public</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0192">no and it might explain why she doesn't go out</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0198" trans="overlap">so there was no-one <pause dur="short"/> yeah there was no-one there</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0192">we were drinking quite heavily including</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah we were all drinking quite heavily just taking a lot of shots of whiskey in the park or whatever and <pause dur="short"/> I didn't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the end</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0192">she came up to me that night straight away and knew that I had a</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0198">a bottle to</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0192" trans="overlap">obviously knows that I carry it around</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0192">so I filled her up a glass</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0198">I mean she took it though so she mustn't have minded that much</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0192">no I know she didn't mind she wanted it</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0192">it was the fact that she kind of used me but then didn't really talk to me</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0198">oh right then yeah</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that group in general got a bit funny with us</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0198">yeah well they just didn't</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0192" trans="overlap">don't know what happened</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0198" trans="overlap">bother anymore did they they got bored</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no the first semester or in the second semester they were</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0192">we had a gap went on vacation came back</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0198">maybe I feel like you have to keep going to Radio Star to keep seeing those people</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> didn't really want to</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0192">so we didn't erm</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I mean that was fine and her tea party sucked</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1048" who="S0198">that was terrible <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't like you didn't wear a dress</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1050" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0192">me too</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0198">it wasn't there was nothing mad about that tea party</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well we kicked it into gear I think when we arrived</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> someone's got to step it up right</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was fairly pleased that's what's er I didn't like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they were both very <unclear/></u>
<u n="1056" who="S0198">yeah so they're going back to Korea</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0198">how do you know that?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0192">cos their status was like Seoul bound or something and I commented er underneath it like back to Korea so soon and she just liked it so I don't know if she's going with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1060" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0192">I presume she is cos they've just got married didn't they?</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0198" trans="overlap">er to teach though? they may they may be just transferring or</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0192">I know didn't sound like it</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0198">there's no I don't feel like that it would be a comeback that quickly</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0192">it sounds like it but <trunc>ne</trunc> we didn't think would</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0198">I know but we didn't come back that quickly</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0192">they may have tested the job market there and it was the wrong time for Saudi and they just turned round and <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I mean when did they leave?</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0192">and they don't have that much experience they've got no post-Celter experience <pause dur="short"/> they</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they've been basically done a few months</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they've they're like us when we left the first time they did their Celter and then were like er what job are we gonna get?</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0192">and they're like well actually I quite liked Korea <event desc="sound of children"/> I reckon they are going back I reckon they've just weighed up some things and probably had a few job interviews or tried to get into places and didn't <pause dur="short"/> that's ah it's great though Korea is too easy</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1075" who="S0192">and they'll do another couple of years there and then they'll er</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0198">they may have considered it if they've both what they consider quite good public school jobs or at Avon University positions</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0192" trans="overlap">mm yeah they might have been able to get a uni job</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0198">it's really just luck of the draw</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0192">we could have got in at <unclear/> what do you think that would have been like? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0198">I feel like <pause dur="short"/> it would be like working at where we did but that your</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0192">but just less organised</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0198">yeah that your job was was split over both programmes like you did have at <unclear/> like at <unclear/> everyone taught a bit of everything maybe</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0198">and it it was still the same yeah but like your <trunc>hol</trunc> cos do you remember they would <trunc>nev</trunc> they said you got eight weeks paid holiday but they were always dodged the question of how their eight weeks happened</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0198">and they wouldn't like they didn't want to say and I'm pretty sure it's probably the same at the end of every six weeks or semester or whatever you get a two-week break or whatever it depends what I feel like it would've been on the same <trunc>li</trunc> maybe worked you even more</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0198">we didn't have any office hours I don't know if <unclear/> did</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0192">not having any office hours is amazing why don't all jobs do that?</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0198">I know it's just do your job and make sure you do your job cos I don't know <pause dur="short"/> they don't know when they need you it depends on the type of job</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0192">I mean surely like in Saudi do you have like a boss somebody that's looking over you? or are things actually a lot more chilled than they seem to be?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0192">because like everyone seems to say oh you get like a month or two months but then everyone I've spoken to that's been out there or knows people that are out there you seem to get more vacation than that there is more vacation than that and I wonder if like they say you do eight hours and you are meant to be around for most of the day but I'm sure if you have a class and then go and sit outside for an hour or two hours or disappear or go and do whatever come back I don't know if it'll be so rigid</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0192">it depends on I guess if you've got a <unclear/> type character that's in the office the whole time</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0198">yeah I don't think <unclear/> university I don't know where you'd be going <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just it's</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0192" trans="overlap">depending when you've finished</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well if you</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it really depends on how</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0198">your compounds and <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1101" who="S0192">and if they run it like a public school and you've got like a</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0192">having three years in the public school system in Korea was a bit trippy</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1105" who="S0192">wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0198">yeah I did do three years in there</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0192">it's a lot of erm <pause dur="short"/> pandering to obligation and</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0192">getting to understand their culture <pause dur="short"/> getting out in the middle of nowhere you know like a one-street village basically living in a</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they don't let you forget very easily that you are different to them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1111" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> not at all</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0198" trans="overlap">not in a negative way they're not like horrible but maybe even the other end where they're too accommodating where you never</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0192">there's no job like we're the same you and I</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0198" trans="overlap">if you go out you you're never expected to pay for anything you're never considered Korean so</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0192">I had one guy that said to me oh you are becoming Korean</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1117" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he had that like <pause dur="short"/> did you ever meet him? I don't know if you</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0192">it's weird though it's very strange to me in the working world that we all experience different things</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0198">yeah yeah well when you go off to do a job</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> myself all four of us</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0198" trans="overlap">we've got a little bit</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0192" trans="overlap">convened at the weekend and had a good time</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0192">and like totally shared every other experience but</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0198">you're in the <trunc>jo</trunc> classroom on your own</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0192">you're in the classroom and you're in the school those teachers are the people that you know</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0192">and once you've taught there long enough like in Mokpo you start crossing over teachers and that <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1130" who="S0198" trans="overlap">we did became we we did get a <trunc>li</trunc> we got so intertwined us four that entwined? that</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0192"><trunc>in</trunc> intertwined it's</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0198">that and we ended up working at some of the same schools as each other <vocal desc="laugh"/> and we just like really kept it quite close</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0192">yeah to the point where we knew different teachers and</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and now we do some of the same and we even worked at the same</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0198" trans="overlap">school as each other let alone live I the same building</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you can talk about work easier because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know mm there was the same people that I had</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that you knew she's talking about and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s talking about the same people that you had so we can talk to them about it and still know who <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="long"/> ah it's amazing</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0198">yeah but yeah public school systems avoid that if possible</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0192">see</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0198">underneath there <vocal desc="laugh"/> deal with children too much</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0192">no I'd rather deal with adults wherever possible</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0192">definitely</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0198">children need a lot of attention and energy I don't think definitely in Korea that it was getting delivered and I'm sure in an English class or an American classroom there's too many children to one teacher</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0192">absolutely</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there's not <trunc>en</trunc></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there shouldn't be more than about twelve children to a teacher</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0192">I think</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0198">I don't like this</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0192" trans="overlap">this is you have classes up to thirty</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0198">whereas the reason the classes are <unclear/> I feel like <pause dur="short"/> you know you have no conditions up there at that point <pause dur="short"/> you know sort of self-trained in a you have to be</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0192">I really think that a school where the learners teach themselves</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you know my idea before? the learners teach themselves the teachers move about between the classrooms and you always have at least two teachers in the class at any one time but sometimes there could be three as people move in and change but you're constantly moving and making sure</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah an interacting with</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0192" trans="overlap">making sure that everything's going on and you have smaller classes</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and you get to know the students more <pause dur="short"/> even if you even just have four rooms just for listening or reading and speaking or whatever or just like different activities do you know what I mean where they come on and there's like a you can have a pre-made instruction video or something er something that they get they open they discuss as a group in English</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah and they do</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0192">and they read the instructions and they teach each other how to do it could be something as simple as board game or anything just you know what I mean? just anything that they have to figure out for themselves</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0192">and they know that their only grade is participation</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0192">that's it it's one hundred percent participation therefore they will <pause dur="long"/> they should sort themselves out they should be able to correct their correct themselves and want to grow themselves especially at the time you get to tertiary education</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0192">if it's a hundred percent you've got no other evaluation whatsoever <pause dur="short"/> you're gonna wanna play a part in that and</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0198">you don't have to</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0192">and you know that you can be evaluated all the time because there's <pause dur="short"/> you know like you know that the teachers can see through these windows you can't see through them</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0192">it's like two-way do you know what I mean? and the teachers come in and out and they just make sure that you're understanding and getting on with what you're doing <pause dur="short"/> and everyone has a different role</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it might make <pause dur="short"/> well how big would the classes be do you think?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0198">it can't be too big because there'd be too many people competing</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you don't want bigger than a team of six really</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0198" trans="overlap">for attention wouldn't there yeah yeah there'd be teams</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there's be a team of six</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0192">and they would move around I think when they came into class they would decide which room to go in do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah yeah what they wanted to practice that day</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you wouldn't tell them what it was but there were different rooms for different things and you were running different things on</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0192">and they come in and they'll be like oh I could do an hour of this and then I can do thirty minutes of that or something and provided there's always enough students in there to be getting it on with and they're doing it themselves so if they go in the room and there's not enough people in there then it's up to them to try and get other people</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0198">people in</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0192">and it's just more interactive and they would I think you'd need to ban their own language a little bit</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0192">but they need to be at a good enough level where you could ban their own language and have constant access to dictionaries and all these kind of things around so if they're trying to talk to each other and there's always teachers walking around but they're just not doing it they're just letting them get on with it</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0192">they're there to be asked questions you can stand around and they'll ask you a question</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0198">yeah yeah is this right is that right</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0192">yeah and you can point them in the right direction</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and then you can do a little bit of teaching in that to that small group</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0198">of why it is wrong and and</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah and then let them carry on</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0198">so a lot of it is self-studying and self-correction and self-management</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0192">it's being able to work</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0198">it would be nice wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0192">you'd need a crazy curriculum</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0198">yeah the planning would be</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it would be tough you'd need some good people in there</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you'd need some good teachers in there</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0192">yeah but that is a methodology</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0192">I think you could actually sell that as <vocal desc="laugh"/> if you could start up your own English school I mean really to start up your own English school you don't need much <pause dur="short"/> let's say you've just got one of these zones there's four rooms</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0192">you've got two teachers per room so you've got eight teachers you can probably get a maximum of twelve students in each class</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0192">so four classes twelve students forty-eight students how many teachers did I say?</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0198">eight</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0192">eight teachers forty-eight students and eight teachers how many eights fit into forty-eight?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1214" who="S0198">er six?</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0192">eight sixteen twenty-four</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0198">six</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0192">thirty-six</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0198">five and</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0192" trans="overlap">forty-four is it?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0198">no you said forty-eight</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0192" trans="overlap">eight sixteen twenty-four thirty-two forty</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0198">forty-eight it's six</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0192" trans="overlap">forty-eight yeah so it's six</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0192">so there's six students per teacher so if a student pays five pound per class that's thirty pounds per teacher per hour</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0192">say the teacher gets paid twenty pounds and ten pounds is left over for the running of the property and for whatever else that's a good enough business model but you need to get twelve students in each class</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0198">would the classes only be an hour long? or would you get other students come in?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no the classes <pause dur="short"/> no the classes would be continual throughout the whole day</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0198" trans="overlap">alright so they can just come and go?</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and they come in when they want really yeah</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0198">but you could you'd have to regulate it to an extent so not too many students showed up at the same time to do one particular class</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0192">erm well provided there's no more than the forty-eight provided you're not</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it would be the Tefl corridor and Toefl corridor in the university or</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0192" trans="overlap">provided no well I mean provided you're not over-capacity you can just never by over-capacity</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0198">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if everyone turned up at once you could still manage it you just can't have more children or more people than that signed up</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0198">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0192">say the capacity is forty-eight twelve students in each class and you have four classes</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but you would just would you tell them which class they went into?</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0192">no they just come in and they'd open a door and be like oh it's busy in here I don't wanna go I there or like go in so they decide for themselves</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh so they don't know what class they're going into beforehand?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0198" trans="overlap">ah I know</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they go in and there's like a roster up and they can see what's going on in this boards at what times</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0192">do you know what I mean? so like we'll be running things at certain times in certain classrooms and then they just go in and open a door and try it out and try and hey guys like a bit of talking to people</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0198" trans="overlap">what's there to prevent too many students being in one particular class?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0192">themselves and that's it</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0198">they have to stop themselves from going?</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0192">presumably <pause dur="short"/> we don't you think that people would self-regulate if you go in a class and there was like</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and it's really yeah that's not what you want yeah</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you'd probably wanna go somewhere quieter wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0192">and you could self-regulate by only have X amount of tables with the stuff set up</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0192">and I think you'd have everyone standing there wouldn't be seats</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0198">that's true and people would move in and try something else</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0198">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0192">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0192">it's all really active and task-based but completely down to their own learning and what they wanna do</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0198">mm making your own decisions</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0192">and we have different four different things running at the same time always</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0192">and you could have it in like two-hour slots so you change so effectively everyone runs the same things that day but you er you just change the rooms or you have more things going on you'd need a variety of resources to</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0198">yeah you'd need a good amount of resources</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0192">but erm it could work I think</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's why I feel like the resources and the material that you would need to make it good would be well could be what costs quite a bit initially</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0192">mm yeah and especially if if they get ruined</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0198" trans="overlap">if you need to how long would the that it would run how long would a <unclear/> semester?</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0192">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0198">run for a semester twelve weeks</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I guess so <pause dur="short"/> you could even get like them to sign something for upkeep of the materials er do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0198">yeah like take good care of them</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just like if you damage yeah just ask them to do it but like if you damage any of the materials we ask that you be honest and come up and here's the exact price list of what they are and have it very reasonably priced</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0192">if you break a little token on a board game it's ten pence or something do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you just come in and pay that</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0198">just so you're not running at a loss through wear or damage</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no through wear and tear I think that would be fair to say to them to get them to sign that</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0192">you need to get enough students and enough teachers and they all need to be like-minded it wouldn't be an easy teaching scenario but I think it would be effective</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0192">they are forced to do tasks in the language <pause dur="short"/> they have constant access with not too many students per teacher <pause dur="short"/> they can decide their learning they can decide what they're doing that day and for how long</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0192">and immediately they have to greet people when they come in cos there's different people every time you're not with the same set of people stuck</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0192" trans="overlap">sitting next to the same person doing whatever you come into a room you analyse it and you go you evaluate it and go these people look interesting and what they're doing looks interesting I'll go and do it and it can be simple stuff like you know try and build a house of cards or you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0192">tasks things that are tricky to do teach yourself to do the yo-yo</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0198" trans="overlap">t would be a really stimulated environment wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0192">likes games watch movies like do stuff that actually takes given them movies but with no subtitles and their task is to try and work out what they're saying</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0198" trans="overlap">analyse some of the movie or something yeah</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and like you know and try and make a dialogue for what they think is being said</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0192">and to discuss it all like as a team all that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0198">it could be a lot of fun</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0198">it would be a really stimulating environment very active <pause dur="short"/> it would snap you out of it and you'd have to concentrate</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0192">mm definitely</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0198" trans="overlap">too much is left to you making it too easy to just so now</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0192">you could have them have their own recommendations as well for things they wanna do and do make an effort to include some of those things in it so that if someone says you know they wanna do this instead of that then you know a week or two <trunc>l</trunc> later you do actually put it in</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0198">yeah right</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0192">like a recommendations box it would have to be reasonable I think theatre works well in an English language classroom</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0198">theatre yeah</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I do</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0198">I mean it</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0192">I thought when we did that play that was quite good</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0198">I think students need to <pause dur="short"/> you can't be shy especially in some of these like smaller classrooms being shy is not very helpful it's not gonna help you</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0192" trans="overlap">being self conscious too much</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0198">you're not gonna you will learn faster if you're just more willing to participate</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0198">so yeah doing the drama thing kind of forces everyone to do that</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0192">and they have write it so there's writing</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0192">they have to memorise it</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0192">they have to practice their intonation and their tone and their body language they're all natural things</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0192">they have to know their lines well enough so that if somebody screws up they can correct it which means they have to understand what they're saying</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0192">you definitely have to comprehend it to be able to correct it <pause dur="short"/> and they can be creative and write their own ones</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0198">mm although they struggle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1327" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there were some other ones in Korea struggled with it quite badly but some of them did</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0198">I still can't believe some like some of them would</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0192">some of them were really</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0198" trans="overlap">be quoting or acting stuff from Frozen and they never had heard of Frozen</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1332" who="S0198">or know and literally didn't know</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0192">I had some boys singing in mine</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0198">yeah it really confused me at points <pause dur="short"/> why are they singing singing about a snowman and it has nothing to do with the rest of the role play</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1336" who="S0198">it's just someone practicing singing but <pause dur="short"/> mm I love that show</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0192">yeah I really do</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hated it <pause dur="short"/> and if a seven-year-old boy doesn't like it then</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0192">there's no <unclear>hope</unclear> to it</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0198">no it might be a bit girly</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0192">the Koreans don't care about</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0192">sexuality pretty much</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I'm pretty sure erm I can't remember his name now but my first <trunc>c</trunc> co-teacher er at the middle schools what was his name? he definitely got a man-crush on Russell Crowe after watching what was that big musical? Le Mis</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0192">Les Miserables</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1347" who="S0192">a few of them did</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0198">mm <pause dur="short"/> I never watched it obviously but <pause dur="short"/> it was all to do with Russell Crowe as a Royal Marine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1349" who="S0192">man-crush you can definitely admire people of the same sex</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0198">yeah absolutely mm yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0192">and I guess be besotted with them without it being sexual</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0198">yeah that's why they call it like a man-crush or a girl-crush it's something strange people say I suppose</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0192">is crush a British thing?</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0198">no I don't think so is that?</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0192">because Koreans definitely didn't know it</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0198">oh didn't they?</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0192">no to have a crush on oh was it crush no fancy</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0198">fancy's English</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0192">that is English</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0198">yeah Americans don't say it</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0192">they say like cos you can say what do you fancy</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0192">you know what do you want all Americans say that one</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0198">maybe</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0192">but then when you say I you fancy them</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0198">I think they understand it but I don't think it's used maybe it's something that was old-fashioned</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0192">it's a little strange to have a fancy</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0192">mm what's your fancy?</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0198">I know yeah but what other word would you use instead of that? I mean you when you're like oh I really isn't want isn't the right word you don't actually want it</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0198">but you're</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you have a craving for it yeah</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you crave it yeah I fancy is a crave isn't it really?</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0192">mm oh I fancy a bit of that</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0192">or it's not necessarily a craving it can be an immediate</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0192">quite compelling want</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0198">yeah I guess it's that one word we have for that like immediate stimulation we have from something</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0192">fancy</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0198">which is why we fancy people because when we see them it's the same immediate oh</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0192">and also because fancying someone is usually quite transient l think as well</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0192">do you know that word?</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0198">transient no it was</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0192">fleeting passing not ephemeral not lasting very long</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0198">ephemeral</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0192">ephemeral ephemeral</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0192">erm transient not lasting very long <pause dur="short"/> so when you have a fancy with someone like an addiction</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0192">it's transient it's passing it's gone soon so it's kind of like a craving</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0192">you you just crave that person a little bit and then it goes away</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0192">god I had a couple of crushes on girls that were so strong</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1399" who="S0192">it's tough <pause dur="short"/> what is that feeling?</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0192">I think it's exacerbated by a culture of wants</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0192">I mean do you know what I mean? if you grew up in a culture where you've got to feel like you possess something</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0198" trans="overlap">other things if we want stuff you can you buy it or you</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I definitely</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0198">after like</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0192" trans="overlap">wanted a couple of girls not many just a couple</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0198">I guess there's a very instinctive emotion that we experience that we don't <pause dur="short"/> it's one of the first or it's the <trunc>mo</trunc> most dramatic one isn't it? that we naturally start <pause dur="short"/> fancying people</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a bit strange that</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0198">but this like this primitive inbuilt thing though</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0192" trans="overlap">boys and girls and boys and boys and girls and girls but especially boys and girls at a young age you don't have to be very old you realise very young that you're different</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0192">showing you this and I'll show you that or whatever you kind of want to have a look you know what is that down there? and then you get a little bit older</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0198">I do wonder how children I can't really remember what it's like</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and you go through a period between having a look and getting with a girl or the opposite partner or whoever you fancy and being repelled by them but jokingly</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0192">oh girls have got cooties or whatever or your kiss chase oh try and get away from them</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah kiss chase <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1419" who="S0192" trans="overlap">girl girls are horrible boys are horrible oh you know I get because in your sub-conscious I guess you know that you are meant to get together</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0192">and it's a bit strange cos you're a bit like <trunc>wh</trunc> why oh girls are horrible that can't be right <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're like having a bit of a rebellion and</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it does become more you go through a stage in late primary school I don't know you're five or something or you're six when kiss chase does go from being something that was a genuine game to being have moments of being awkward or uncomfortable</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0198">like oh that was kind of gross actually I don't want it's not so funny anymore</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1426" who="S0198">or just awkward</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0192">you grow out of it why do all little kids play kiss chase?</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0198">I don't know you get taught it at school by someone someone's</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> someone's carrying the <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1430" who="S0198">some little boy just starts chasing a girl and she then goes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1431" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0198">the girl's like no or the other way round girls like kissing</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0192">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0198">I'm always trying to kiss my nephews and they always trying to run away</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0192">yeah that's probably where kiss chase comes from</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0198">the girl but the little girls have liked it and they get like er a bit more affectionate as well</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0198">it is nice watching it's funny watching little people with other little people</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0192">yeah and they hug each other</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0198" trans="overlap">like how they treat different ages</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0192">yeah they look after each other</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0198">yeah they do</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0192">if there's one older than another one they do</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah from a really small size</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0192">just literally care for each other</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0192">they show them what they've learnt</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0192">and they pass on the knowledge it's such a very strange concept being a child</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's really weird</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0192">you know what I mean? really strange</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you are literally in your own bubble</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0192">you are</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and the adults are very much the adults</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0192" trans="overlap">an empty vessel</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0192">you are complete and full you are but you're not experienced you have no knowledge you have all the motor functions and all the instincts and all the abilities that an adult will have and you'll grow into an adult</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0198" trans="overlap">with a lot more things you learn that</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but but you yourself are shaped by all of this environment around us and now complicated by the quite deep pervasive er human society that we've created on top of the natural society</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0198">yeah that's the thing growing up before you would have had all your instincts</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0198">but it won't</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0192" trans="overlap">likes times were simpler</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0198">but you can't rely on and that's not what you need anymore it's the wrong set of skills</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0192">didn't have to learn about council tax or political correctness or</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0198">mm anything numerous things paying back loans and <unclear/> and banking</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0192">wi-fi and just</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1469" who="S0192">all these crazy concepts so many technologies that we erm we take for granted but we don't really actually know how they work</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0198">work yeah</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0192">to the point where it can almost be <unclear>matic</unclear> pretty <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="1472" who="S0198">like children not knowing that just this taking the internet as a as like a given it's just a thing</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh it's just yeah it's just information isn't it?</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's like having I don't know electricity</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0198">electricity means internet whereas it never that was it's quite a recent thing</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0192">oh it's getting dark now</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0198">yeah it is getting dark I bet some rain can pound through this window on a</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0192">yeah I bet it can</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0198">chilly my back's actually kind of cold a bit now</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0192">is it?</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0198">I might go for a wee</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0192">we can move inside</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0192">right so if we do that <pause dur="short"/> cool we're gonna cook soon aren't we?</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0198">I thought that's what we were gonna do actually yeah</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0192">shall I <unclear/> up?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0198">no I'm alright are we gonna cook?</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0192">yes I should bring us up this glass and have some water</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0198">yeah let's have some water</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0192">leave that</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0198">alright then</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0192">you can take it with you but erm <event desc="sound of tap"/></u>
<u n="1494" who="S0198">I don't know <pause dur="long"/> going for a wee</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="long"/> we'll shut this window</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="1497" who="S0192">so are we gonna cook?</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0198">yeah let's mm do some cooking</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0192">right</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0198">I'll grab some water firstly</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0192">are we making chilli con carne?</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0192">cool there must be so much of me cooking and eating and</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0198" trans="overlap">can we do this shall we do that</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0192">yeah has to be done lots of natural conversation we got plenty of kidney beans not sure how big this company is</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1507" who="S0192">Sweet Harvest</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0198">oh you have to finish this cos we need to</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0192">no no I've had enough</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0198">oh go on it's just two</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0198">go on need to get rid of them and I need to er clean this washing pan might need to get a bit of a souring pad actually and that egg seemed to be really stuck on it's a bit of a concern so there was how many have we got oh we've got a wok you might be able to cook a chilli in that that would be the best bet</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0192">the wok would be good</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0198">yeah that's the biggest one so we don't need this</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0192">do we have a chopping board?</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0198">we have a chopping board</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0192">oh here it is oh we haven't</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but we have no big knife do we?</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0192">I have a small knife</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0198">I think we have a small knife it's there</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0192" trans="overlap">probably oh it's here is it sharp enough?</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0192">oh it's got a crack in it</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0198">I don't think it was that sharp actually</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0192">sharp enough to cut some onions?</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0198">I hope so really can't get this <unclear/> off this frying pan</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0192">can you not?</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0198">I might give it a bit of a boiling water and then <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1529" who="S0192">don't worry the scourer will do it I'm sure</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0198">yeah yeah thing is by the time your dad comes Saturday it might be a bit messy because er we haven't bought cleaning products cos they're coming with them</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0192">oh that's no good</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0198">so I mean we can wash up and use like detergent and stuff and things but I can't put any we haven't bought any bleach for the toilet or anything like that have we?</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0192">mm we need I mean it's only a couple of days of living in it I'm sure it won't be that bad</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0198">I don't know things get pretty messy pretty quickly</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0192">well let's do our best to not then and do it that way</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0198">oh I like our little fruit drawer and our little vegetable drawer</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0192">you do</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and I guess we've just got to divide this with the <unclear>bathroom</unclear> or whatever</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0198" trans="overlap">rather than a lot in one go</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0192">I think so</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0198">cos once you saw a hole in there they're we're pretty done</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0198">just need you can see the I mean obviously stuff</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0192">there's some butter</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0198">got it yeah it helps that we don't have a water jug in there that's not necessary</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0192">no no that isn't necessary is it</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0192">they didn't even mention that there's no</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no drawers</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0192">drawers</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0198">can you pick out the shelves anywhere? I mean it is a very small fridge I suppose it's come out of like a bloody caravan</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0192">I mean</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0198">is that going to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1555" who="S0192">it's written down</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so no it's <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's this it's about the size of our last one</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0192">right yeah a small fridge</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1559" who="S0192">got our little bit of stuff in there it's gonna be tough when they come and stay because where's this wok?</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0198">it's in there that bottom one</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0192">okay oh it's got like a hair in it and some stuff that's typical of you</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0198">it got washed just before I came <event desc="sound of wok"/></u>
<u n="1563" who="S0192">be okay then this is going to like spray everywhere</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0198">just give it a rinse to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1565" who="S0192">give it a quick little rinse and it's alright oh bit noisy so this is our kitchen</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0198">oh no this is terrible</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0192"><unclear/> what's happened?</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0198">well it's got stuck to this</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0192">well it's leaking</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0198">yeah well that's</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0192">but I want to put some butter in there really</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0198">so chilli</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0192">but I'd normally use a bit of olive oil but we don't have any</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0198">do you need garlic?</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0192">yeah garlic onion</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's here isn't it?</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0192" trans="overlap">er a bit of red pepper</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0198">obviously there's chilli powder</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0192">you forgot the chillies</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0198">oh yeah we forgot the chillies for the chilli</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0192">but we've got red peppers and that'll replace the missing</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it'll be much sweeter now</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0192">it'll replace the missing paprika cos we don't have any paprika in there</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0198">no I don't think I did put any in there</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0192">but that's just peppers there that ought to be okay</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0198">well I mean we've got chilli powder <pause dur="short"/> hopefully the chilli powder here is quite good</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0192">yeah I hope so</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0198">I have rather higher hopes than than when we were living in Korea</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0192">oh crap I've got to open them thought but then we don't have anything to put them in</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah what are we going to put them in? I've got erm</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0192">can they just stand up for now?</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0198">yeah I've got some pegs actually</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0192">pegs would work well</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0198">just those those sort of brown pegs there</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0192">so what are we getting there? we've got cloves</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah is there any paprika?</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0192">I'll have a look lentils chilli powder we need that coriander we don't need that <pause dur="short"/> turmeric desiccated chocolate don't need any of that</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0198">we've got some er <unclear/> here oh no</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0192">cinnamon I might put a little bit in</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0198">yeah oh</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0192">cardamom we don't need</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0198">not too much cinnamon hey</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0192">cumin yes put some cumin in</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there was too much cinnamon once</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cumin yes I'll have some cumin and <event desc="sound of rustling"/> I guess we'll keep open stuff out or something will we somewhere?</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0198">yeah we ought to just some containers some jars or something</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0198">with a lid</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0192">I've got some coming up</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0198">yeah you said so hopefully that kind of stuff will come</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but some <trunc>con</trunc></u>
<u n="1612" who="S0198" trans="overlap">maybe get some up on the shelf even that like look nice</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yes yeah that would look good</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0198" trans="overlap">to have some spices around so</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so you do have pegs</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0198">I've got three pegs but you can't make too much of a hole</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0192">where's a little</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0198">there's a little pair of scissors in here no there's no these ones</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0192" trans="overlap">a pair of scissors or something of these are nail scissors</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0198">they're better aren't they? and I'm going to need a garlic although we've only got one chopping board so</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is that hole too big?</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0198" trans="overlap">this is going to be a bit of a slow process</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0192">yeah it will do won't it</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0192">do we have a little cup I can mix spices in or anything?</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0198">er we used all the cups what about a mug? there's a mug up there</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0192">did you bring that?</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0198">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1629" who="S0192">it's not just some random one</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's comes from Chessington World of Adventure</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0192">teaspoon? Chessington World of Adventure</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0198">teaspoon</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0192">why does it come from there? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1634" who="S0198">I don't know see there are two types of spoon in here which one's a legit teaspoon?</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0192">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0198">that one looks a bit too big that one</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it does look too big doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0198">is that too small?</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0192">is this a tablespoon?</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0198">no that's not a tablespoon this is a teaspoon but not</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0192">this teaspoon looks quite small though doesn't it? I'm just using the teaspoon over this side</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0198">no it's all about the flavour anyway</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0192">well</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0198">how many are you opening three?</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0192">I don't want to cook much of this over there</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that might be our three plates</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0192">think there's one there cumin's going to have to erm <pause dur="short"/> be pegged up quite well</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0192">I could make a tiny little hole</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0198">do you know how much I mean places like Aldi around probably do cumin virtually these days</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0192">yeah I don't really know yeah</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0198">I don't know if you can even buy it in there</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0192">I'm not sure if I saw it</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0198">definitely saw a hell of a lot more tortilla wraps and things in the bakery bread aisles of the supermarkets</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's gone up hasn't it?</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0198">there's loads there's taco they've definitely got getting more into</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0192">yeah my mate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was as well</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0198">yeah you see the kind of guacamole sauce</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0198">like an actual squeeze thing</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0192" trans="overlap">t's like a ketchup</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0198">of guacamole</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it was terrible I'm sure</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it tastes horrible <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1665" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's right I told her this is really good but I'm not so sure about this sauce</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> to be honest</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0192">it comes out of a bottle</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0198">cos real guacamole is pretty pretty damn good</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0192">and it's got a texture</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0198">yeah exactly it's got avocado in it like you don't want it too <trunc>s</trunc> too mushy</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0192">no absolutely not how much are we making here then? this could make I mean particularly three</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0198" trans="overlap">is it gonna be three meals then? I mean what's today? Thursday so it it could be Thursday Friday Saturday</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it just cover me for another two days really wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0198">yeah whether you have them for lunch or dinner</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0198">oh it's good to smell like spices again</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0192">yeah I mean our house always smells like an Indian's house doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0198">yeah it does yeah</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0192">that's what our friends think</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0198">need like a little</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0192">what like to make</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0198">well we're gonna get jars aren't we?</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0192">my brother's quite into his Asian cooking now I guess</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0198">yeah how</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0192">we didn't get to</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0198">did</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0192">cook Asian food because he didn't have</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0198">why not? cos</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0192">erm didn't have an tamarind</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0198">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0192">or kaffir lime leaves</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0192">my dad's bringing me up some kaffir lime leaves</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0198">yeah your dad's got all the ingredients hasn't he?</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0192">but he hasn't cut me a plant he's cut me a lemongrass plant <pause dur="short"/> he's got me a lemongrass</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0198">awesome cos I almost grabbed us a or stole some out of the cupboard but</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0192">it takes a while to heat up doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0192">at first it takes a while to heat I think it's a bit disappointing</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0198" trans="overlap">if only we had a box to put these in rather than it's not gonna lie down</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0192">well we just leave them on the side stacked up against something for now I'm sure it'll fine I need to start chopping <pause dur="short"/> onions and whatnot <pause dur="long"/> yeah it must be difficult for whoever listens to this <pause dur="short"/> when you've got rustling and bags and stuff</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah rustling must be really annoying</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cos it's quite noisy in headphones</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0198">oh no</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0192">but there's no way of we've already oh we don't even have a can opener</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0198">oh we do</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0198">that came in that sack</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0192">that's quite good beef there was well</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0198">because I just take I dunno I guess I just <unclear/> are common these days they're really not</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do we have strainer or a colander or something?</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0198" trans="overlap">erm we don't have oh no yeah we've got a colander we don't a sieve so we can't like sieve the flour</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0192">what do you call it?</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0198">colander</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0192">no the other one</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0198">a sieve</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0192">how do you say it again?</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0198">sief</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0192">sief</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0198">a sief</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0192">it's sieve</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0198">a sieve? a sieve</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0192">yeah it's sieve are these like sieve</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you do? to there's S er</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0192">sieve</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0198">a <trunc>si</trunc> sieve</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do we have a bag?</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I kind of have a picture in my head and I spell it the same <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0192">where's the bin bag?</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0198"><unclear/> to you it's here but it's looking quite full isn't it</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's this bin bag is it? it is looking quite full well wrap that one up and grab another bag we've obviously got a Lidl's bag today as well</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0198">oh we've got we've accumulated</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1734" who="S0198">oh it's not even gonna oh</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0192">you're having a bath <pause dur="short"/> do you want to turn this or different?</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0198">no no is it on? no that's the socket</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0192">that was that</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0198"><unclear>flicker</unclear></u>
<u n="1739" who="S0192">that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1740" who="S0198">no that's fine now turn on the</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it's been on it's on</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0192">nine <pause dur="short"/> no wonder it wasn't melting</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of rustling"/> a bit <event desc="sound of rustling"/></u>
<u n="1745" who="S0192">just don't normally mix the spices in with the <pause dur="short"/> hardened butter I know it's a bit <pause dur="short"/> hopefully it will cook a bit quicker</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0198">I hope they appreciate that it's not that it's just finding out which day rubbish goes out we don't actually know how to put rubbish out in this country</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0198">because there's different laws in different countries and I don't know what what the laws are here anymore</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0192">well we'll just ask the estate agent couldn't we?</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0198">well he didn't seem to he said didn't he say to ask a neighbour or something?</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0192">well we'll get him to find it out</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0192">we need to know I'm sorry</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0198">can't keep rubbish in there for too many days</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I know you yeah yeah that's doing excellently</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0198">yeah is it melting? I'll give it a stir</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0192">so it doesn't take that long to heat up</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0198">heat up no</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0192">takes a little while</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0198">those are alright for the <unclear>long term</unclear></u>
<u n="1761" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what was your mum's cooking like when you were at home?</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0198">I mean she didn't cook too much but mm she did a she did a roast dinner that was good <pause dur="short"/> on her first day</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0192">yeah where did that knife go?</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0198">and then <pause dur="short"/> I ended up</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0192" trans="overlap">sorry can we just make a new bag?</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I ended up eating out and then she was working I think and then <pause dur="short"/> I didn't eat too much of her cooking</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0192">we need the garlic</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0198">I did literally the <pause dur="short"/> the roast dinner the bangers and jacket potato and one other thing I think the rest of the time I was either out or she wasn't home cooking again so I had dad's cooking or I cooked</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0198">so actually it was a little bit of a mix I didn't do too much but it was fine I love cooking when we're home she was disappointed that she she didn't get to cook more</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0192">was she?</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0198">yeah she wanted to have she was working when she wasn't working when we had day trips somewhere <pause dur="short"/> I find my er I think my mum gets this garlic from Aldi actually is this from Spain? yeah</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0192">I don't know</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0198">it's not very hard garlic</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0192">oh it's got some pretty nasty fumes coming out of that</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0198">oh yeah that pan again</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0192">yeah where's the mince?</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0198">in the fridge still shall we open a window?</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0192">yeah I need to open it</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0192">definitely where's the mince?</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0198">in the fridge</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0192">and that was like one pound seventy-five or something wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0192">I'm pretty sure it was I'm pretty sure it was maybe it had pound ninety-nine but</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0198">yeah it was under two pounds I guess yeah</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0192">I'm sure it was a good good deal</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0198">nice looking ground <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely <vocal desc="cough"/> oh the spices straight away</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0192">it's the spices</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely oh right to the back of my throat</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0192">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0198">why does it <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1793" who="S0192"><vocal desc="cough"/> that chilli <vocal desc="cough"/> yeah the chilli</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0198">cor how does it airborne like that?</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0198">yeah it isn't good is it?</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0192">no and my immediately brand new pan sticking like a <unclear>bitch</unclear></u>
<u n="1798" who="S0198">is it cos it hasn't no</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0192">cos they haven't what?</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0198">hopefully your dad's will be better</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0192">we'll see</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0198">we shouldn't cook with them all like at once and see the <pause dur="short"/> see which ones cook better than others</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0192">I need to put a bit of water in this cos it's sticking to the bottom which it shouldn't really do</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0198">is it cos we used the fat more fat from the meat?</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0192">I don't know might be because I used butter instead of erm oil</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0198" trans="overlap">could just be the material of the pan I suppose</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0192">butter has a tendency to stick on oh can I use that?</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0198">yeah crush some garlic with the garlic crusher</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0192">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0198">if it's one that actually works I don't like the one in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1811" who="S0192"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> oh</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0198">bless you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1813" who="S0192">made me sneeze then</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0198">it's all going to the <trunc>ba</trunc>back of my throat quite badly</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0198">there's some serious er <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1817" who="S0192">the spices that seem to do it</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0198" trans="overlap">could do with some other plates and have you got any plates or plates coming out?</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0192">yeah it's</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0198" trans="overlap">or bowls you said bowls didn't you?</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0192">I think so yeah a few plates and bowls</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0192">my mum was trying to give me more of old dusty spider-webbed ridden stuff but I was like no I think you've given me too much</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0192">I think she was just trying to get rid of them really can I get rid of this garlic? it's just getting in the way can take that out</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0198">oh oh sorry</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh that was a bit noisy</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0198"><vocal desc="cough"/> there <unclear/></u>
<u n="1829" who="S0192">it's all gone down your throat</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0198"><vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear>trying not to think about it</unclear></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1831" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1833" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the quality of the beef seems okay it's seems very different from what we know in Korea that stuff we had in Korea was pretty fatty and chewy</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0192">oh no</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0198">what?</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0192">just I made a mess</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0192">never done that before <pause dur="short"/> what I've noticed though the beef here is really</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh man is it my eyes or is this coming through grey?</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0192">yeah it looks I think it's changed their colour</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0198">why would it be coming through grey?</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0192">cos it's dirty in there cos the stuff your dad gets is <unclear>bodge job</unclear></u>
<u n="1844" who="S0198">no this is from their cupboard but they they got a different one so they stopped using it but my dad didn't tell me there was anything wrong with it</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0192">well he might have been lying <pause dur="short"/> or he didn't realise</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0198">why would the <unclear>metal</unclear></u>
<u n="1847" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I think in a way you need a knife is there only one knife?</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0192">or give it a good clean <pause dur="short"/> oh this onion's punchy and <pause dur="long"/> have you got it alright?</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0198">got what alright?</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0192">the garlic crusher is it working any better?</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0198">I mean it works well it's just coming out a funny colour I'm not really sure</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0192">can you wash the garlic afterwards?</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0192">I don't think it should be coming out grey</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0192">I've never seen</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0198">it's not the inner a grey garlic</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0192">I haven't seen grey garlic before</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0198">well <pause dur="short"/> do think it will do us any harm because I need to start peeling more garlic er I need that knife</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0192">yeah I still need to do another onion <pause dur="short"/> is this the only knife we have?</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0198">it's the only sharp knife we have <pause dur="short"/> I still don't know how I'm going to crush garlic with it it's too small</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0192">is it really coming out grey? how grey are we talking?</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0198">I mean it looks grey to me it might be the light</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0192">no there's definitely bits of something in there</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0192">give that thing a wash</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0198">but I washed it I just washed it after</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0192">again then</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0198">after the first bit of grey</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0192">is it coming out any of this grey?</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0198">no I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> it's weird that</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0192">well there can't there can't be an infinite amount of grey stuff in there to</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0198">is this just is it just the material of the crusher itself?</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0198">the metal <pause dur="short"/> no?</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0192">probably not it's it's not infinite is it? you're wearing away the material <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1880" who="S0198">just don't understand see it's making the dishcloth go grey I think it's</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1882" who="S0198">I think it's the look it's the <trunc>met</trunc> it's this whatever it's covered in</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0192">yeah I think throw it</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0198">yeah that's not good a god crusher that</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0192">no can I have the can and can you wash the pepper?</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0198">I need to cut a if you can just</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the garlic can go in last but I need to do the pepper first <pause dur="short"/> unfortunate</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0198">If you're sure</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0192">yeah pepper doesn't er garlic doesn't need to cook for very long cook a onion till soft</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0198">well you'll wanna leave it on for a little while once it's finished</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0198">I'll strain these beans shall I?</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0192">yeah if you can do both cans to strain</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0198">I think the pepper</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0192">I think we need two cans if we're gonna do that</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0198">oh both of them?</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0192">yeah I think so yeah</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0198">alright then</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0192">don't you think?</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0198">yes I trust your <pause dur="short"/> judgement yeah it's <unclear/> this is do you need to rinse these as well or are they okay?</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0192">I think they're fine <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1902" who="S0198">now I've put that right near to the cloth <pause dur="long"/> it's not the easiest of stains</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0192">is it not?</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0198">the burn it's quite big</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0192">got a good amount of space at the moment</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0198">yeah yeah and it's just a better layout in general isn't it?</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0192">we didn't have the best layout for a kitchen</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0198">no <pause dur="short"/> a <unclear>lack of</unclear> surface space</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was surprised we even had a kitchen so</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1911" who="S0192">of course we're going to we're adults those kind of questions they ask are</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0192">you know like that guy I was trying to sell the bike to? the guy was telling me well then how can you have a kitchen in there that's illegal</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0192">cos I mean I'm a teacher <pause dur="short"/> I think it's okay</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0198">to say that at all though what's the point? just</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0192">he's being a dick</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0198">yeah in a manner of speaking</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0192">and then he didn't even buy the bike</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0198">no what a lot of effort to go to</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0198">I bet I bet they went and bought a new bike</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0192">why even bother? It's a fifty thousand one <pause dur="short"/> second hand bike on <unclear/> knowledge <pause dur="short"/> that was a bit of a <unclear>narrative</unclear> if you ask me</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0198">I'm sure he spent a little bit just on the bus fare or the taxi fare or whatever</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0192">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0198">or did he walk actually? was he even in</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0192">yeah it had taken him a while it was pretty hot <pause dur="long"/> there you go here's that knife you've got the <unclear>garlic</unclear> here <unclear/></u>
<u n="1928" who="S0198">right</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0192">I'll just bring this up</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0198">I need a chopping board to go with that then</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0192">we've got some scissors haven't we?</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0198" trans="overlap">snip that yeah we've got what <trunc>ki</trunc> er what do you need scissors for?</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0192">erm well we've only got plum tomatoes so they need to be put in a bowl or like chopped at least</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0198">well just put them in the blender</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0192">oh we've got our blender?</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0198">yeah put them in the blender</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0192">of course we do yeah put them in the where are they then? do they have a ring pull? no they don't</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0198">ah this is really we can do it</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0192">I can taste it</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0198" trans="overlap">hopefully the bottle opener where will</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0192">it was three cans</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0192">oh this can opener's really good</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0198">yeah it's not bad is it? I don't usually trust</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0192">no some can openers are terrible</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0198">new things <unclear/></u>
<u n="1947" who="S0192">is the blender pretty straightforward?</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0198">I mean I haven't tried it</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0192">you haven't?</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0198">no but I imagine it's okay</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0192">I'll have a look this is the main attachment is it like a Bullet</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0198">yeah the Bullet's a little er there's the other one's in <unclear/> if you wanted like the I don't know a different shaped one</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0192">where do I plug it in oh in here</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0198">yeah and maybe I should move</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0192">oh my god the <unclear>megatron</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> yeah gone in okay and this grips on top are they gonna fit two</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0198">should fit just two cans in it it's got to be a litre at least hasn't it that thing?</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0198">maybe just a litre</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0192">maybe it will just fit two cans it should fit two cans shouldn't it</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there's gonna be a bit spraying out</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0192">we'd normally have a bit of herbs in this we did have some pepper didn't we? we bought some</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah we bought some pepper</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0192">where's the pepper?</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's on the it's on the shelf with the mustard</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0192">on the shelf with the mustard I see it</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0198">do you want to just blend that tomato in with it so er blend I mean the garlic so the garlic's smaller?</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0192">yeah yeah we can do that that's a good idea so just crush a bunch</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0198">this'll probably finely dice it very well then <pause dur="short"/> peeling garlic again aren't we</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0192">yeah I know it's not as easy as it was in Korea</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0198">a longer process</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0192">that's for sure</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0198">I forgot about it <trunc>act</trunc> I hadn't even noticed</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0192">what that you're having to do it?</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0192">how do you do this thing then?</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0198">it became automatic</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0192">there's no button</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0198">yeah you just like er <pause dur="short"/> er it's a twist isn't it? yeah push down and twist</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0192">no that's how you put it on</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0198">oh right</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0192">I have absolutely no idea how that works <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1982" who="S0198">no that's gotta be something</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0192">oh hang on maybe <event desc="sound of blender"/> oh it came out</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0198">oh oh</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0192">why did it do that?</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0192">did it dribble out the side or the bottom? how did it dribble out of the bottom?</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0198">is that blended or not?</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0192">I don't think so who did could er oh</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0192">how did it do that?</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0198">that is not on at all</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0192">the bottom wasn't on</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0198">shit</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0192">quick put that in a bowl or something</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0198">er</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0192">why wasn't the bottom on?</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0198">I need a saucepan or a <trunc>bo</trunc> a cake pan</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0192">where's the saucepan?</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0198">in here</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0192"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="2002" who="S0198">no there's all holes</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0192">they're all horrible how would we</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0198">well get a plate</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0192">you get some of this</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0198">that's dripping</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0192">yeah alright we don't wanna lose any more oh my god</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's terrible</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0198">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> god</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0192">why did you do it like that?</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0198">I didn't <trunc>re</trunc> didn't think it was just going to explode like that <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0192">I've got to turn this down got to <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2014" who="S0198" trans="overlap">all those tomatoes now</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0192">you've wasted quite a bit and it doesn't need to go in yet</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0198">more to the point there's a massive mess on the floor</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0192">my sous chef what are you doing to me?</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0198">oh it's like tonight this has been disastrous</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0192">tomorrow I'm going to <unclear/> do I need to put a whole other can in?</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0198">why didn't you put the bottom on <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0192">I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't know that the bottom needed putting on you said it was ready</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0198">don't tread don't tread tomato through the carpet or whatever through there</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0192">you said it was ready <pause dur="short"/> it cannot be blamed on me you didn't even put the garlic in it</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0198">this is disastrous</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0192">oh it's a terrible mess I blame my sous chef</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0198">no <pause dur="short"/> I didn't create the mess</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0192">you did there wasn't much mess until you just opened it</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0198">you you didn't put the like you didn't put the blender on</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0192">oh it's gone on my trousers my only clean trousers</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0198">has it?</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I need to give it a wipe</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0192">it's all I've got our <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2034" who="S0198">mess this up a bit more</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0192">that won't be a good idea</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0198">we'll cover you in all tomato</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0192">well that thing sucks</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0198">no we just needed to put the lid on</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0192">as new blenders glow go I don't like it</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0198">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2041" who="S0192">might well give it away <pause dur="long"/> for good so you've strained the kidney beans that's two cans isn't it?</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0192">right and then we need to empty this</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0198">no just need to</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0192">been walking and we've been quite a bit has gone in the mechanism</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0198">yeah we need to tilt that into that bowl</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0192">yeah I'm doing that but I mean</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh tomato everywhere on the first day really?</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2050" who="S0198" trans="overlap">what a bitch <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2051" who="S0192">how do we wash this out does it need washing out?</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0198">erm er</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0192">oh no it's everywhere baby do you want to give that a washing out?</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2055" who="S0192">maybe so</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0198">you're in charge of the garlic now</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0192">okay I'm in charge of the garlic</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0198">now you said you said <unclear/> first</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0192">not very nice garlic that'll cook a while</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0198">it's basically the whole thing</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0192">it's cos we wasted a bit this cooking has been a disaster so far <pause dur="short"/> we need to get back in the rhythm</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0198">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's cos we're so unsure of things at the moment</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0192">do you think garlic's stronger here?</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0198">well my dad's one definitely is whatever he's been eating it's really strong <pause dur="short"/> but I guess you don't I mean we do eat raw garlic all the time in Korea</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0192">but with other stuff</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0192">don't just eat er yeah</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0198">I mean I eat it in like mixed in a salad thing my dad makes <pause dur="short"/> it makes my eyes water sometimes</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0192">yeah it's too much</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0198">I mean I like it but it's definitely</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2072" who="S0198">definitely strong it's good though I like it</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0192">what are we doing with this then?</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0198">with what?</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0192">the tomatoes we need you to clean it out so I can continue with my <unclear/></u>
<u n="2076" who="S0198">no but the floor's I can't let you keep treading tomato in</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0198">how am I going to clean this out?</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0192">I don't know just give it a wipe with a cloth of something</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0198">oh this is terrible</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0192">that doable? don't wanna give that cloth <unclear>scangy</unclear> cloth a wash in this tomato do you think I <trunc>n</trunc> need to add a whole another can?</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0198">what after the last one?</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0198">we need to have tomato in it I suppose</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0192">it's nice tomato anyway</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0198">yeah go on then</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0192">well I mean how much do you think we really lost?</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0198">oh it's hard to tell a little bit <pause dur="short"/> but not I doubt a can's worth</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I wish your mum was here where's the bit at the bottom?</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0198">so</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0192">oh this bit that needs a wash so basically this just wasn't screwed in?</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0198">I guess so that was the that's what it seems like</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0192">that's terrible so provided it gets screwed in properly so it just wasn't in at all oh my god that was a</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0198">well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2095" who="S0192">a <trunc>r</trunc> a <unclear>rooky</unclear> mistake</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2097" who="S0192">but we couldn't get it to turn on either there was something confusing about that</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah maybe because it knew that it wasn't it wasn't attached properly or something don't know I mean</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0192">it's all everywhere everything</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0198">tomato everywhere such a mess</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do you wanna practice this thing? yeah this needs a good clean now just this thing</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2103" who="S0192">oh <event desc="sound of blender"/> are you meant to just pull it out like that?</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0198">yeah you squeeze it and <event desc="sound of blender"/></u>
<u n="2105" who="S0192">are you sure?</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0198">and it start activates</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0192">oh that's a bit crazy</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0198">that's the same as the Bullet though the thing that looks like arrow here you just squeeze there and they you <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="2109" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and it did it</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0198">it didn't seem so crazy cos you there was a hand but this one's a little bigger</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0192">yeah so I need that garlic firstly</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0198">yeah put that in there</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0192">is that in here? I turned this off but yet it's still cooking</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0192">I turned it off a while ago</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0198">those things cool down quickly at all</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's <event desc="sound of saucepan"/> I kind of wanna take the stick that in a taco now</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0192">I mean you can do</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0198">we don't have any tacos</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0192">but I I think we should yeah we don't have any tacos do you think there's too much in here or will it just fit in here nicely? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2122" who="S0198">er did you put another can in there?</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0192">no I haven't put another can in</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0198">oh right so <event desc="sound of plates"/> from that</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0192">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's gone everywhere it's terrible</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0198">they're probably alright I mean we always boil it down anyway and <event desc="sound of blender"/> oh it's quite noisy isn't it?</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0192">mean isn't it <event desc="sound of blender"/></u>
<u n="2128" who="S0198">so before it just wasn't screwed in at all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2129" who="S0192">so is it is it done now do you think? I'd say so</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0192">pretty powerful it's good</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0198">yeah yeah it's pretty nippy isn't it</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0198">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="2135" who="S0192"><vocal desc="misc"/> I'll just put it in here</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0198">mm don't you think that looks like taco shell beef?</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0192">yeah it does</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0198">oh look how frothy that's gone</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0192">yeah it has gone frothy</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0198">different colour as well don't you think? <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2141" who="S0192">yeah it's gone a very different colour</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0198"><event desc="unintelligible"/> completely different colour</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0192">just in generally ingredients</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0198">the ones that I use</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0192">they're gonna coming out as pink</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0198">the ones the ones I used for the lasagne were like really quite sweet</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0198">but er not in a good way I don't think</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0192">right do you wanna give this a clean?</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it smells differently</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0192">sorry I made a mess</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0198">mess everywhere</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0192">there really is</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0198">where does that go?</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah this doesn't look like the right colour</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0198">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2157" who="S0192">do you have a Oxo cube?</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0198">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0192">I can make it a bit darker with a bit of beef stock</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0198">yeah it's in there</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0192">in where?</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0198">in there cupboard on the right side</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0192">oh I see</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0198">they're not permanent places here they're just somewhere there</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0192">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0198" trans="overlap">cor that one's got a chill in it hasn't it?</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0192">yeah it does have a chill <pause dur="short"/> we should have our other beer now before this</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0192">do you think?</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0192">leave it to cook?</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0198">leave it to simmer enjoy the beer and maybe settle down for the evening and watch something</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0192">yeah that sounds good to me</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0198">I need to pack a bag actually I've got to pack a suitcase to take to Dorset</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0192">yeah you have</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0198" trans="overlap">how stupid is that I haven't even unpacked here yet and I'm packing something</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0192">can't believe you're gone so quick</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0198">oh I don't wanna go <event desc="sound of clattering"/></u>
<u n="2179" who="S0192">I don't want you to go either</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0198">but</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0192">you don't know what time it is yet</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0198">no why hasn't my brov not phoned me today it was really strange</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0192">maybe they want you give them a call</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0198" trans="overlap">he's sitting at home sulking</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0192">why cos you're out there?</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0198">yeah no not cos I'm out there just cos he's home alone he's happy that I'm er he's happy that I'm in <anon type="place"/> I think</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0192">that you're around at least</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0198">yeah and he gets excited when live in different places and if it's <event desc="sound of clattering"/></u>
<u n="2189" who="S0192">yeah as long as there's</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0198" trans="overlap">somewhere else for him to drive to and something for him to actually do</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0192">do yeah <pause dur="short"/> some herbs would be good</u>
<u n="2192" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they shouldn't be too difficult to come by</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah no <pause dur="short"/> we were going to put some yoghurt in it weren't we?</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0198">oh yeah are we gonna put it in it or just have it like on the side?</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0192">yeah <event desc="sound of water"/></u>
<u n="2196" who="S0198">yeah you'll taste it more I think if you just have it at at the end</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0198">ah that's tough to open</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0192">right just got to do the kidney beans and</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0198">yeah I'll have to oh my dad's gotta call me someone's gotta call me</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0192">yeah they do</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0198">do we put we don't put garlic fridge do we?</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0192"><trunc>n</trunc> er no no garlic stays out</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0198">well well</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0192">people leave onions out as well</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0198">we were yeah <trunc>pot</trunc> well yeah potatoes are normal but I think we were in Korea though weren't we? I mean I don't have anywhere to put it so I'm just gonna put it in the fridge</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0198">that'll do for the moment</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0192">yeah we were keeping it in the fridge in</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0198">in Korea yeah</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0192">so we're going to have this with rice</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0198">have to turn off the megatron cos I think that's done yeah we'll have a see what that rice is like it's half the price of the rest <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I don't know</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0198">but erm</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0192">well I'm gonna have cheese with mine though my dad thinks that's sacrilege</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0198">what cheese on a chilli?</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2218" who="S0198">ah I mean <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="2219" who="S0192">do you think?</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0198">you know anything's sacrilege putting cheese on something like that though</u>
<u n="2221" who="S0192">it's something from Latin America I think it's</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0198" trans="overlap">if it's spicy I don't know it just like <trunc>Mex</trunc> <unclear>Texan</unclear> is isn't it</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0198">chilli</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0192">they put cheese in them <pause dur="short"/> they probably <unclear/> not to <pause dur="short"/> I mean they go so far as to have it with <trunc>noo</trunc> with noodles <pause dur="short"/> don't they?</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0198">yeah my erm my</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0192">oh gosh are you kidding me? whole black pepper corns</u>
<u n="2228" who="S0198">yeah if it's</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0192">perfect for pepper mills</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2231" who="S0192">and no pepper mill</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0198">oh you haven't got any pepper</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0192">by the time I had any Jesus</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0198">don't even have what made you pick up that one?</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0192">that was the only one there that looked like a miller</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0198">oh you've buggered that didn't you?</u>
<u n="2237" who="S0192">I need to add some more cumin and and chilli to this one but does it matter when I</u>
<u n="2238" who="S0198">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0192">somewhere <pause dur="short"/> ouch that's cinnamon</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh sorry</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0192">I don't need that one</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0198">I didn't realise your leg was there you didn't put much cinnamon in it did you?</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0192">no no I didn't I just want erm another spoon and</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0198">somewhere in this cutlery anyway</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just need to clean this mess there's a good deal of mess everywhere</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0198">so what so both times you were at your dads you were <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cooked for you did she?</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0192">no my dad cooked twice and</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0192">I cooked once</u>
<u n="2250" who="S0198">what did your dad cook you?</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0192">erm he did er</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0198">curry?</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0192">Thai curry once erm</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0198">was it good?</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and erm did chilli another time actually</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0198">oh any good?</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0192">yeah they weren't bad it was alright <pause dur="short"/> thai curry he did light coloured but when I've cooked with the chillies here</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0192">they're pretty strong</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2261" who="S0192">I only put the two in the other day pretty strong so I don't know what it's like putting twenty in</u>
<u n="2262" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0192">you know what I mean? when we used to make the Thai green curry we need to get used to their ingredients</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0198" trans="overlap">ingredients yeah I guess we'll try in the halfway point <pause dur="short"/> got to take it from there decrease and increase</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0192">maybe we'll have to</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0198">just to be clever</u>
<u n="2267" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2268" who="S0198">we're making messes already aren't we look that's already torn down there</u>
<u n="2269" who="S0192" trans="overlap">wasn't really torn</u>
<u n="2270" who="S0198">we haven't moved the oven</u>
<u n="2271" who="S0192">yeah so we need to take a picture of that</u>
<u n="2272" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2273" who="S0192">sure</u>
<u n="2274" who="S0198">and I'll roll my own rollie</u>
<u n="2275" who="S0192">well we should just make up photoshop pictures of things that we think we're gonna break</u>
<u n="2276" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think I don't know how you'd go about doing that I mean I guess there's no <event desc="sound of cutlery"/> but we are submitting that er those photos soon aren't we?</u>
<u n="2277" who="S0192">yeah soon as we've got internet <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2278" who="S0198">perhaps we can use these boxes for a side thing for now</u>
<u n="2279" who="S0192" trans="overlap">right this thing needs much more of a clean</u>
<u n="2280" who="S0198">I know it hasn't nothing's been cleaned yet</u>
<u n="2281" who="S0192">cool</u>
<u n="2282" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2283" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do I need to turn the hot water on?</u>
<u n="2284" who="S0198">no it can take too long</u>
<u n="2285" who="S0192">is this going in the rubbish?</u>
<u n="2286" who="S0198">yeah or there <pause dur="short"/> I guess I'll just wash it with cold water</u>
<u n="2287" who="S0192">that can be done</u>
<u n="2288" who="S0198">erm</u>
<u n="2289" who="S0192">or you</u>
<u n="2290" who="S0198">could boil a kettle but <pause dur="short"/> it's not really worth it is it? I think it</u>
<u n="2291" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well we do have the light on why do we have the light on?</u>
<u n="2292" who="S0198">oh sorry there was something</u>
<u n="2293" who="S0192" trans="overlap">must be</u>
<u n="2294" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I was looking at the guide the one on the <pause dur="short"/> can't leave any lights on <pause dur="short"/> especially when we've got the oven running as well I wonder if cooking is going to be really expensive</u>
<u n="2295" who="S0192">hopefully not it's electric hopefully just <pause dur="short"/> we'll just heat this through turn it off separate it what are we actually separating this into? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="2296" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2297" who="S0192">if we don't have any Tupperware or cling film have we got saucepans with lids?</u>
<u n="2298" who="S0198">yes</u>
<u n="2299" who="S0192">so are just gonna</u>
<u n="2300" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but how big are they? are they gonna fit in our fridge? I don't think so</u>
<u n="2301" who="S0192">probably it's probably about that long you could put two thirds of that in here</u>
<u n="2302" who="S0198">oh yeah you just wanna separate it out yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2303" who="S0192">we'll have today's</u>
<u n="2304" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and keep it all together can't you you don't have to separate it into days</u>
<u n="2305" who="S0192">there's quite a deep one that one</u>
<u n="2306" who="S0198">yeah there are a nice couple there that one's deep too</u>
<u n="2307" who="S0192">it's a good rice one</u>
<u n="2308" who="S0198">yeah we'll put the rice in there</u>
<u n="2309" who="S0192">oh there's a bit of Rizla in there wet Rizla lovely</u>
<u n="2310" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> wonder where that came from</u>
<u n="2311" who="S0192">no idea we gonna have another cigarette in a</u>
<u n="2312" who="S0198">and a beer</u>
<u n="2313" who="S0192">and a beer</u>
<u n="2314" who="S0198">while that cooks there</u>
<u n="2315" who="S0192">what's the time? when are you speaking to your family?</u>
<u n="2316" who="S0198">I <vocal desc="laugh"/> haven't got a set time thought they would've called by now but they didn't so I don't know why cos my I'm pretty sure my dad's been <trunc>ho</trunc> home alone all day unless he's gone out somewhere fishing or something</u>
<u n="2317" who="S0192">did you say they were doing something on Saturday or or a Thursday was it Thursday soon?</u>
<u n="2318" who="S0198">no mum was work working so I don't know what else they could be doing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2319" who="S0192">there's like a piece of garlic and like a whole piece of garlic</u>
<u n="2320" who="S0198">they look bad</u>
<u n="2321" who="S0192">yeah what's that look like to you?</u>
<u n="2322" who="S0198">yeah some garlic it's a piece of garlic it's a piece of garlic isn't it?</u>
<u n="2323" who="S0192">eat it</u>
<u n="2324" who="S0198">I'm not eating it</u>
<u n="2325" who="S0192">fine</u>
<u n="2326" who="S0198">I'm not eating it</u>
<u n="2327" who="S0192">this needs washing as well oh</u>
<u n="2328" who="S0198">de-da-de</u>
<u n="2329" who="S0192">we can get our drink if you want</u>
<u n="2330" who="S0198">cheers</u>
<u n="2331" who="S0192">nearly got through the Maltesers</u>
<u n="2332" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's good though isn't it?</u>
<u n="2333" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's looking good</u>
<u n="2334" who="S0198">yeah so it's enough for three days isn't there?</u>
<u n="2335" who="S0192">I'm pretty sure if we separate it</u>
<u n="2336" who="S0198">and then you can use it as and how you like</u>
<u n="2337" who="S0192">yeah that would be easier</u>
<u n="2338" who="S0198">portions according you can always get something you could always get like a jacket potato or something to go with it for lunchtime</u>
<u n="2339" who="S0192">yeah I could do that would be nice actually but then I've got to go out to the shop wherever that is</u>
<u n="2340" who="S0198" trans="overlap">wouldn't cost you very much would it</u>
<u n="2341" who="S0192">oh the batteries gone down a little bit on here</u>
<u n="2342" who="S0198">oh put that <unclear/></u>
<u n="2343" who="S0192">important</u>
<u n="2344" who="S0198">these are <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2345" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I think it's probably cooked enough</u>
<u n="2346" who="S0198">want to turn it off?</u>
<u n="2347" who="S0192">yeah I mean for like a few minutes we're gonna eat dinner quite early aren't we?</u>
<u n="2348" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2349" who="S0192">if we have another beer and a cigarette maybe</u>
<u n="2350" who="S0198">yeah perhaps we shouldn't leave it on anymore so you'd reheat some in a little while?</u>
<u n="2351" who="S0192">yeah I'd reheat some in a little bit</u>
<u n="2352" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2353" who="S0192">should be pretty cooked now</u>
<u n="2354" who="S0198">alright looks good actually doesn't it?</u>
<u n="2355" who="S0192">looks <unclear/></u>
<u n="2356" who="S0198">oh I didn't realise how hungry I am might be</u>
<u n="2357" who="S0192">do you wanna save the beer for after then?</u>
<u n="2358" who="S0198">no no <trunc>n</trunc> I'd rather have it now okay and then we can just chill</u>
<u n="2359" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2360" who="S0198">and we'll just have it in a little bit</u>
<u n="2361" who="S0192">cool</u>
<u n="2362" who="S0198">I think I'll be too full after dinner to drink beer</u>
<u n="2363" who="S0192">no I agree</u>
<u n="2364" who="S0198">we usually drink it earlier anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2365" who="S0192">do we have any dessert or did we eat it?</u>
<u n="2366" who="S0198">oh we've eaten it all</u>
<u n="2367" who="S0192">oh that's tragic</u>
<u n="2368" who="S0198">oh we've got fudge</u>
<u n="2369" who="S0192">there is some fudge</u>
<u n="2370" who="S0198">and</u>
<u n="2371" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2372" who="S0198">no I don't</u>
<u n="2373" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there's an easter egg</u>
<u n="2374" who="S0198">oh there's an easter egg</u>
<u n="2375" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2376" who="S0198">there you go <unclear/></u>
<u n="2377" who="S0192">have you ever been tempted to take an easter egg of that size and fill it with icing sugar like a cream egg?</u>
<u n="2378" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no it would be horrible</u>
<u n="2379" who="S0192">it would be pretty bad</u>
<u n="2380" who="S0198">it would be terrible</u>
<u n="2381" who="S0192">have actually filled it with like ice cream</u>
<u n="2382" who="S0198">yeah I haven't been <unclear/></u>
<u n="2383" who="S0192">can you imagine an egg like that</u>
<u n="2384" who="S0198">ice cream</u>
<u n="2385" who="S0192">about that big filled with ice cream</u>
<u n="2386" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2387" who="S0192">but every like few centimetres of ice cream there's another chocolate egg</u>
<u n="2388" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="2389" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so you have to keep cracking through to the ice cream</u>
<u n="2390" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that would be amazing I think isn't like the layers I think you'd want the chocolate to get quite thin</u>
<u n="2391" who="S0192">yeah yeah it would get thinner as you go along</u>
<u n="2392" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you'll want er want some chocolate</u>
<u n="2393" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it would start thicker and get thinner as you go along but can you imagine cracking that egg and eating around it and getting all the and there's another egg</u>
<u n="2394" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and there's another chocolate egg oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> sounds awful for you</u>
<u n="2395" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and more ice cream then</u>
<u n="2396" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> some days I'd find that disgusting other days it would be irresistible</u>
<u n="2397" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what are you feeling today?</u>
<u n="2398" who="S0198">just like a <pause dur="short"/> oh irresistible</u>
<u n="2399" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2400" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> for sure</u>
<u n="2401" who="S0192">oh for sure <pause dur="short"/> now the other beer should be cold now shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="2402" who="S0198">oh yeah I didn't put it in the freezer did I?</u>
<u n="2403" who="S0192">it's been in the fridge though right? I've turned this thing off though clearly</u>
<u n="2404" who="S0198">it's still bubbling</u>
<u n="2405" who="S0192">it's this electric</u>
<u n="2406" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2407" who="S0192">it</u>
<u n="2408" who="S0198">it's kind of like storage heaters but in an oven so</u>
<u n="2409" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> these hot plates take a little while to cool down <pause dur="short"/> it's not sticking too badly to this pan though</u>
<u n="2410" who="S0198">are we staying in here or going to the balcony?</u>
<u n="2411" who="S0192">erm we could just sit in the lounge couldn't we and open a window?</u>
<u n="2412" who="S0198">yeah sure</u>
<u n="2413" who="S0192">it sounds like the nursery children have gone</u>
<u n="2414" who="S0198">the children have gone home</u>
<u n="2415" who="S0192">so that's good</u>
<u n="2416" who="S0198">back home to their parents so they're there</u>
<u n="2417" who="S0192">it got a little bit cold out there for them</u>
<u n="2418" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2419" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2420" who="S0198">I really can't get over what <unclear/> good</u>
<u n="2421" who="S0192">it's not great is it</u>
<u n="2422" who="S0198">no it's not</u>
<u n="2423" who="S0192">would be nice to have a little bit of sunlight just a little <pause dur="short"/> do we need some glasses then? where's the box of then?</u>
<u n="2424" who="S0198">yeah there's two here still I had to give them a rinse</u>
<u n="2425" who="S0192">there's still two are they washed?</u>
<u n="2426" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2427" who="S0192">and where's the bottle opener?</u>
<u n="2428" who="S0198">that's still in the drawer I think</u>
<u n="2429" who="S0192">it's right here</u>
<u n="2430" who="S0198">San Miquel</u>
<u n="2431" who="S0192">San Miquel and the bottle opener</u>
<u n="2432" who="S0198">it's there <pause dur="short"/> it's in the drawer</u>
<u n="2433" who="S0192">you already told me that did you?</u>
<u n="2434" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="2435" who="S0192">I just wanted it in stages</u>
<u n="2436" who="S0198">and the glasses</u>
<u n="2437" who="S0192">yes</u>
<u n="2438" who="S0198">there you go</u>
<u n="2439" who="S0192">what percentage is the San Miquel? what do you guess?</u>
<u n="2440" who="S0198">four percent</u>
<u n="2441" who="S0192">exactly five</u>
<u n="2442" who="S0198">oh is it?</u>
<u n="2443" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2444" who="S0198">oh it's <unclear/> when it gets to five isn't it?</u>
<u n="2445" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2446" who="S0198">it's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="2447" who="S0192">yeah a lot of beers are under five nowadays aren't they?</u>
<u n="2448" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2449" who="S0192">just feel like a beer should be about five <pause dur="short"/> back in the day it was probably like eight or something</u>
<u n="2450" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2451" who="S0192">beer drinking then we're looking at five what's that girly thing you're drinking?</u>
<u n="2452" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2453" who="S0192">five? do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="2454" who="S0198">absolutely</u>
<u n="2455" who="S0192">oh I've got a perfect head on that one <pause dur="short"/> cracking</u>
<u n="2456" who="S0198">that's quite a statement</u>
<u n="2457" who="S0192">look how long this takes to cool down</u>
<u n="2458" who="S0198">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2459" who="S0192">turned it off a while ago</u>
<u n="2460" who="S0198">that's why electric's terrible terrible</u>
<u n="2461" who="S0192"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="2462" who="S0198">terrible</u>
<u n="2463" who="S0192">should be alright to leave though shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="2464" who="S0198">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="2465" who="S0192">I don't see why I wouldn't be</u>
<u n="2466" who="S0198">and I'll just keep clicking it smells good</u>
<u n="2467" who="S0192">smells okay smells like chilli</u>
<u n="2468" who="S0198">it smells like chilli</u>
<u n="2469" who="S0192">shame we haven't got any crème fraiche</u>
<u n="2470" who="S0198">we've got yoghurt it's the same thing although did you did you notice it in the supermarket just aisles of the</u>
<u n="2471" who="S0192">was it there?</u>
<u n="2472" who="S0198">crème fraiche</u>
<u n="2473" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="2474" who="S0198">next to the milk that simple</u>
<u n="2475" who="S0192">how much of it was it expensive?</u>
<u n="2476" who="S0198">I didn't see the price</u>
<u n="2477" who="S0192">that would be nice</u>
<u n="2478" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I don't think it was that expensive</u>
<u n="2479" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="2480" who="S0198">It was I don't think anything Aldi you can probably describe as expensive</u>
<u n="2481" who="S0192">no I doubt it is</u>
<u n="2482" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2483" who="S0192">are we going to go and eat this then?</u>
<u n="2484" who="S0198">drink our beer</u>
<u n="2485" who="S0192">drink our beer smoke our cigarette</u>
<u n="2486" who="S0198">and then we'll</u>
<u n="2487" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we'll eat this after</u>
<u n="2488" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2489" who="S0192">definitely</u>
<u n="2490" who="S0198">sounds good</u>
<u n="2491" who="S0192">that's quite a noisy bubbling <pause dur="short"/> okay where's the tobacco?</u>
<u n="2492" who="S0198">I think you've put it somewhere</u>
<u n="2493" who="S0192">would you like to roll it yourself or shall I?</u>
<u n="2494" who="S0198">so you haven't looked at the price of the tobacco anywhere since we've been back?</u>
<u n="2495" who="S0192">no no I haven't is it that bad now?</u>
<u n="2496" who="S0198">I don't know I I reckon a fifty gram pouch will probably be like</u>
<u n="2497" who="S0192">fifteen quid</u>
<u n="2498" who="S0198">no I think it's <trunc>prob</trunc> it was fifteen when when we left</u>
<u n="2499" who="S0192">sorry bit of an itch</u>
<u n="2500" who="S0198">so I reckon it could be</u>
<u n="2501" who="S0192">what closer to twenty?</u>
<u n="2502" who="S0198">maybe</u>
<u n="2503" who="S0192">that's insanity</u>
<u n="2504" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no maybe <trunc>seven</trunc> I don't know I bet it's closer it's just like sixteen they can only take things so high before it becomes ridiculously unreasonable</u>
<u n="2505" who="S0192">so we say but</u>
<u n="2506" who="S0198">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="2507" who="S0192">I don't think they've reached that limit yet</u>
<u n="2508" who="S0198">the sun's got purple on it definitely</u>
<u n="2509" who="S0192">yeah it has</u>
<u n="2510" who="S0198">so when do suns change colours in different continents?</u>
<u n="2511" who="S0192" trans="overlap">perhaps we're all slightly different <pause dur="short"/> are we going to have to get blinds do you think for that?</u>
<u n="2512" who="S0198">no we're gonna rig one of these it's gonna be wonderful</u>
<u n="2513" who="S0192">weren't we gonna cut one of those in half and see what we can do?</u>
<u n="2514" who="S0198">yeah but I we haven't got anything to cut this in half with</u>
<u n="2515" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="2516" who="S0198">no there's no good scissors for that</u>
<u n="2517" who="S0192">there's no knife or anything okay so we'll just have to live like hobos</u>
<u n="2518" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2519" who="S0192">for the next couple of days but we can at least put the mattress on here tonight?</u>
<u n="2520" who="S0198">yeah I don't yeah it would be nice to sleep on a mattress wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="2521" who="S0192">yeah this one's not as good as the mattress</u>
<u n="2522" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="2523" who="S0192">it's a bit of a mission carrying it <pause dur="short"/> I would say</u>
<u n="2524" who="S0198">yeah it was <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but it'll be alright <pause dur="short"/> this couch is fine <pause dur="short"/> just got to get a bit more tableidge going on</u>
<u n="2525" who="S0192">tableidge</u>
<u n="2526" who="S0198">so you're on your own Friday is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what time will <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come round? after dinner?</u>
<u n="2527" who="S0192">probably not until like eight or something</u>
<u n="2528" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2529" who="S0192">if he comes round and then it would just be for an hour or two</u>
<u n="2530" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2531" who="S0192">not entirely sure when</u>
<u n="2532" who="S0198" trans="overlap">is he still a bit <trunc>unsu</trunc> certain whether or not he will come round?</u>
<u n="2533" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah yeah he was saying</u>
<u n="2534" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you say he's not <trunc>sh</trunc> he's not certain that he's not certain</u>
<u n="2535" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no then I've got Saturday and my dad and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> aren't going to come at least you know lunchtime maybe a bit later</u>
<u n="2536" who="S0198">yeah then you can hang out and have some food</u>
<u n="2537" who="S0192">don't know maybe not it depends if parking's okay I guess</u>
<u n="2538" who="S0198">yeah parking the van</u>
<u n="2539" who="S0192">if erm it's less than a hundred pounds then I'll just</u>
<u n="2540" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2541" who="S0192">pay for the food if it's not then I'm not going to</u>
<u n="2542" who="S0198">oh right you gonna <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah okay so</u>
<u n="2543" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did miss a day at work then he should have got more <unclear>reparation</unclear> probably</u>
<u n="2544" who="S0198">yeah well they don't care but I care but</u>
<u n="2545" who="S0192">he does it for us just to</u>
<u n="2546" who="S0198">care</u>
<u n="2547" who="S0192">yeah your dad's got serious with him</u>
<u n="2548" who="S0198">he did it for my dad and my mum</u>
<u n="2549" who="S0192">did he?</u>
<u n="2550" who="S0198">yeah I dunno but that's</u>
<u n="2551" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I bet <trunc>u</trunc>?> oh I'm gonna get angry if anyone <unclear/></u>
<u n="2552" who="S0198">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2553" who="S0192">but not anymore</u>
<u n="2554" who="S0198">no he was a genuine he's just just <trunc>rai</trunc> raise the tone so he wouldn't question it again</u>
<u n="2555" who="S0192">yeah but I didn't</u>
<u n="2556" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2557" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2558" who="S0198">it works</u>
<u n="2559" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2560" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you need an ashtray don't you?</u>
<u n="2561" who="S0192">no it's cos he threatened me</u>
<u n="2562" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2563" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2564" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in a very serious tone of voice</u>
<u n="2565" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2566" who="S0198">little bit</u>
<u n="2567" who="S0192">we need to open this window as well</u>
<u n="2568" who="S0198">yeah shall we do that too?</u>
<u n="2569" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the neighbours don't seem to be too nosy or anything</u>
<u n="2570" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="2571" who="S0192">not as of yet it is a weekday I guess</u>
<u n="2572" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's hard to know who's in isn't it though?</u>
<u n="2573" who="S0192">the weekend might be a bit noisier</u>
<u n="2574" who="S0198">yeah while we've got friends here</u>
<u n="2575" who="S0192">or when they've got friends here</u>
<u n="2576" who="S0198">oh and they've got friends here</u>
<u n="2577" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2578" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2579" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="2580" who="S0198">well then</u>
<u n="2581" who="S0192">really like the windows</u>
<u n="2582" who="S0198">yeah I like how big they are definitely <unclear/></u>
<u n="2583" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the sash actually opens up <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure that's safe in your back pocket there</u>
<u n="2584" who="S0198">well it's cos I was washing up and handling dirty things I was protecting it</u>
<u n="2585" who="S0192">I'd say just wearing when it you know going out or whenever</u>
<u n="2586" who="S0198">I like wearing it I like I do I'm doesn't bother me if it gets scuffed</u>
<u n="2587" who="S0192">it's not permanent so</u>
<u n="2588" who="S0198">no it doesn't it shouldn't be it's okay</u>
<u n="2589" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but what is permanent is that I'll replace it</u>
<u n="2590" who="S0198">I don't I don't I don't need a new ring you know I mean if we can it needs to look worn everything else about me looks worn</u>
<u n="2591" who="S0192">it would be nice if it looked</u>
<u n="2592" who="S0198" trans="overlap">all those worn clothes that I get off people <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2593" who="S0192">good the first time people saw it though I guess</u>
<u n="2594" who="S0198">well most people have seen it and it still looks good <pause dur="short"/> it looks excellent there's a few people that haven't seen it I guess your family</u>
<u n="2595" who="S0192">is your mum interested or not really?</u>
<u n="2596" who="S0198">mm <trunc>sh</trunc> I mean I spoke to her and this guy at <unclear>Plenty</unclear> about it before we've come back and it's you know it's kind of <trunc>awk</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="2597" who="S0192"><trunc>di</trunc> did she ask if you knew? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2598" who="S0198">I don't remember I think so</u>
<u n="2599" who="S0192">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2600" who="S0198">I'm pretty sure she asked</u>
<u n="2601" who="S0192">I was convinced you knew</u>
<u n="2602" who="S0198">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2603" who="S0192">you feigned surprise very well</u>
<u n="2604" who="S0198" trans="overlap">quite surprised</u>
<u n="2605" who="S0192">you didn't</u>
<u n="2606" who="S0198">yeah I was pretty surprised</u>
<u n="2607" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2608" who="S0198">it's kind of surreal having your brother there too</u>
<u n="2609" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you didn't see my email?</u>
<u n="2610" who="S0198">no no</u>
<u n="2611" who="S0192">no <pause dur="short"/> fair <trunc>en</trunc></u>
<u n="2612" who="S0198">I thought it was fine well they're <unclear/></u>
<u n="2613" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="2614" who="S0198">I don't</u>
<u n="2615" who="S0192">done know innit no going back</u>
<u n="2616" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I don't really remember the temple anymore</u>
<u n="2617" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I do I've got photos of it</u>
<u n="2618" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but I think that's cos that was yeah</u>
<u n="2619" who="S0192">all the photos are on there so we've got so the printer came today they just deliver it in the little box</u>
<u n="2620" who="S0198">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2621" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the man</u>
<u n="2622" who="S0198">that's random isn't it?</u>
<u n="2623" who="S0192">think that's safe <pause dur="short"/> it was some random company it wasn't Royal Mail</u>
<u n="2624" who="S0198">no <pause dur="short"/> so I guess it depends they do try and leave it at places sometimes</u>
<u n="2625" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean there's a Royal Mail depot <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2626" who="S0198">didn't they lose your didn't they leave your suitcase in the garden <pause dur="short"/> you asked them to?</u>
<u n="2627" who="S0192">because we asked them to yes</u>
<u n="2628" who="S0198">yeah and they should if you ask</u>
<u n="2629" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that was a bit of a pain in the arse actually I couldn't get hold of my dad</u>
<u n="2630" who="S0198">so if you don't have internet and your internet goes down you can't use your printer? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2631" who="S0192">if we don't buy a cable for it you can buy a cheap printer to computer cable but they don't tend to come with them anymore</u>
<u n="2632" who="S0198">oh right</u>
<u n="2633" who="S0192">erm so this will work with wireless but yeah when if the internet were to go down then we couldn't print</u>
<u n="2634" who="S0198">yeah I'm not sure if my parents have a wireless really</u>
<u n="2635" who="S0192">yeah might not be might just look similar there are quite a few models that look pretty similar</u>
<u n="2636" who="S0198">it's very the the front of it looks looks like erm it's something well they do look identical</u>
<u n="2637" who="S0192">but you're alright with me getting that one?</u>
<u n="2638" who="S0198">that's good yeah definitely I trust your judgement</u>
<u n="2639" who="S0192">they had a lot of sales erm the other one was slightly cheaper but the ink was like seventeen pound a replacement or something I paid ten pound and got three replacements</u>
<u n="2640" who="S0198">oh have you?</u>
<u n="2641" who="S0192" trans="overlap">for each one yeah <pause dur="short"/> some other one that everyone says works</u>
<u n="2642" who="S0198">oh awesome <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely it's all about the ink cartridges really and how much they cost</u>
<u n="2643" who="S0192">definitely</u>
<u n="2644" who="S0198">that's what you're gonna continue to pay for every like month or couple of months</u>
<u n="2645" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="2646" who="S0198">around the year they were just running a printer's expensive fuck a car</u>
<u n="2647" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2648" who="S0198">or anything else</u>
<u n="2649" who="S0192">my dad said the other day oh running's a car's cheap I was like whatever I mean he doesn't even pay for it really</u>
<u n="2650" who="S0198">yeah I know he <trunc>doesn</trunc> he gets free fuel</u>
<u n="2651" who="S0192" trans="overlap">doesn't pay for his car so that was a bit of a funny thing to say <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="2652" who="S0198">you need money to buy a car to begin with although <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s car he paid three hundred pounds for it</u>
<u n="2653" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="2654" who="S0198">it's a little old car and obviously it failed its MOT but he was expecting that but he has been riding it to er from London quite a lot lately and</u>
<u n="2655" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and he's got his use out of it three hundred quid</u>
<u n="2656" who="S0198" trans="overlap">just for three hundred quid he's earned it yeah</u>
<u n="2657" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he still does he have to pay that every year?</u>
<u n="2658" who="S0198">what to re to</u>
<u n="2659" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah get get another car</u>
<u n="2660" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well people seem to anyway</u>
<u n="2661" who="S0192">yeah I know</u>
<u n="2662" who="S0198">oh what to get another car? yeah he probably will that's a <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2663" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's where you're gonna spend about five hundred quid a year just on upgrading your car and on and or maintaining it</u>
<u n="2664" who="S0198">insurance</u>
<u n="2665" who="S0192">and more people spend like <event desc="unintelligible"/> over the years</u>
<u n="2666" who="S0198" trans="overlap">just you have to pay for an MOT don't you and like everything costs</u>
<u n="2667" who="S0192">yeah road tax lessons</u>
<u n="2668" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2669" who="S0192">we are becoming the minority though of people that can't drive</u>
<u n="2670" who="S0198">no well Chris said when he had driving lessons they were ten pounds a lesson</u>
<u n="2671" who="S0192">oh it was over twenty when I did it</u>
<u n="2672" who="S0198">I know in the</u>
<u n="2673" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I reckon they're probably twenty-five</u>
<u n="2674" who="S0198">which means in er in the space of like seven years they're like seven years they've doubled in price</u>
<u n="2675" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2676" who="S0198">from when he was seventeen to when I was seventeen</u>
<u n="2677" who="S0192">well they've just like doubled in price</u>
<u n="2678" who="S0198">it's a joke ten pound a lesson is pretty reasonable isn't it? is that cos fuel doubled in price? I doubt</u>
<u n="2679" who="S0192">I guess for the driver that's pretty cheap isn't it?</u>
<u n="2680" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2681" who="S0192">you're not getting paid much an hour people paying ten pound an hour</u>
<u n="2682" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2683" who="S0192">to sit in his car and drive it around</u>
<u n="2684" who="S0198">that's true petrol is expensive as well</u>
<u n="2685" who="S0192">well just</u>
<u n="2686" who="S0198" trans="overlap">maintaining cars are expensive</u>
<u n="2687" who="S0192">mm er if you can do those crash courses for like five hundred pounds learn to drive in a week sort of thing</u>
<u n="2688" who="S0198">are they still five hundred pounds?</u>
<u n="2689" who="S0192">they were I don't know if they are anymore <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2690" who="S0198">I'd be tempted I thought they were more like a grand maybe that was just that's still a lot of money isn't it a thousand pounds</u>
<u n="2691" who="S0192">yeah it is a lot of money</u>
<u n="2692" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2693" who="S0192">well for the two of us to learn to drive</u>
<u n="2694" who="S0198">yeah well yeah <pause dur="short"/> see that's the thing I have got to the point now where I'd like to confidently get in a car and drive it regardless of like the the licence</u>
<u n="2695" who="S0192">but even if you had lessons and even if you passed the test you're not gonna do that very often so you're gonna have gaps</u>
<u n="2696" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you're always gonna be</u>
<u n="2697" who="S0192" trans="overlap">of two or three years and you're gonna be a bit</u>
<u n="2698" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you're never gonna be that comfortable in a car</u>
<u n="2699" who="S0192" trans="overlap">wary no you're gonna be wary</u>
<u n="2700" who="S0198">so long as you're confident enough though</u>
<u n="2701" who="S0192">I mean I could probably drive a car now</u>
<u n="2702" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2703" who="S0192">just not very well I don't know if I could drive a car actually or reverse like pull out of that parking space and then</u>
<u n="2704" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2705" who="S0192">I don't think I could I'm alright too many cigarettes</u>
<u n="2706" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2707" who="S0192">definitely we should probably eat soon shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="2708" who="S0198">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2709" who="S0192">just need to do another minute and it's all good</u>
<u n="2710" who="S0198" trans="overlap">those two have been sitting there as well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2711" who="S0192">yeah we don't wanna get in the habit of smoking cigarettes</u>
<u n="2712" who="S0198">yeah I'm gonna come back Sunday</u>
<u n="2713" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I think we've been smoking a load this week really</u>
<u n="2714" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and that's gonna be the first thing that I'm gonna do</u>
<u n="2715" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when you're away with your parents I don't wanna <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2716" who="S0198" trans="overlap">cos they're gonna come in and I don't want to don't want to start smelling like a smoker again</u>
<u n="2717" who="S0192">no well we've got tomorrow if we don't smoke in the morning</u>
<u n="2718" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2719" who="S0192">that should be alright <pause dur="short"/> I'm liking our Hello Kitty towel it's very cool</u>
<u n="2720" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2721" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I wonder if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got one of those with his Hello Kitty guest house</u>
<u n="2722" who="S0198">guest house statement yeah all pink <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2723" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did you hear about <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2724" who="S0198" trans="overlap">where was he where</u>
<u n="2725" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he said I was pretty feeling pretty crazy</u>
<u n="2726" who="S0198">where in northern Thailand why was there <trunc>H</trunc></u>
<u n="2727" who="S0192">he was in Pai</u>
<u n="2728" who="S0198" trans="overlap">Hello Kitty guest house?</u>
<u n="2729" who="S0192">I don't know he was in Pai Pai's obviously changed quite a bit</u>
<u n="2730" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="2731" who="S0192">they've put a lot of money into it since I've been there apparently</u>
<u n="2732" who="S0198">there are more and more eastern Asian tourists as well</u>
<u n="2733" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2734" who="S0198" trans="overlap">like the <trunc>Chine</trunc> Chinese tourists</u>
<u n="2735" who="S0192">so they're catering for themselves as their burgeoning middle class needs to travel</u>
<u n="2736" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2737" who="S0192">more and more definitely I'm glad that the speakers work</u>
<u n="2738" who="S0198"><event desc="unintelligible"/> yeah me too</u>
<u n="2739" who="S0192">that's good if I can I like to leave it go a little bit over because they round up and I guess round down and sometimes they go over</u>
<u n="2740" who="S0198">yeah and sometimes you like to</u>
<u n="2741" who="S0192">so I you know</u>
<u n="2742" who="S0198">yeah increase the chances yeah</u>
<u n="2743" who="S0192" trans="overlap">give them an extra thirty seconds or something</u>
<u n="2744" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2745" who="S0192">if I can</u>
<u n="2746" who="S0198" trans="overlap">especially if stuff you might have to edit or whatever</u>
<u n="2747" who="S0192">yeah yeah if you've got to take it down if there's any big gaps of silence or anything</u>
<u n="2748" who="S0198">yeah that makes sense</u>
<u n="2749" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> why is this rippled?</u>
<u n="2750" who="S0198">I don't know I think it's for decoration I suppose it looks like there should be a little radiator there or something like that</u>
<u n="2751" who="S0192">that's how I <unclear>kept in</unclear></u>
<u n="2752" who="S0198">it's not is it? I guess it's just decoration and it does look kind of nice but you're always gonna put you're probably gonna put something there</u>
<u n="2753" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="2754" who="S0198">I don't know this room was never designed to be a living room was it?</u>
<u n="2755" who="S0192">no wouldn't be</u>
<u n="2756" who="S0198">it must have been a bedroom or</u>
<u n="2757" who="S0192">or a dining room</u>
<u n="2758" who="S0198">yeah or something cos</u>
<u n="2759" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean they they've added this kitchen on haven't they so</u>
<u n="2760" who="S0198">yeah I guess so</u>
<u n="2761" who="S0192">where would the kitchen have been the original kitchen?</u>
<u n="2762" who="S0198">downstairs somewhere <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2763" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just downstairs yeah</u>
<u n="2764" who="S0198">I guess was is that add-on? is that it's an extension isn't it?</u>
<u n="2765" who="S0192">it's got to be</u>
<u n="2766" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="2767" who="S0192">I mean perhaps it isn't or perhaps at least the extension is quite old</u>
<u n="2768" who="S0198">but the kitchen is always on the ground floor aren't they?</u>
<u n="2769" who="S0192">yeah yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
