<text id="S3AC">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:11:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A car journey from Manchester to Cornwall (going on holiday)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Jamaica Inn, colours of the road, wizard of Oz, Sherlock Holmes, Lewis Carroll, Fairy tales, directions, languages, texts, telegrams, telegraphs, Morse code, braille, books, wind turbines, scenery, flowers, birds, fuel, houses, chocolate, beach, caravan. </topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on journey to Cornwall (summer holiday)</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0423">shall we stop for some dinner at <anon type="place"/> Inn?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0421">I don't know what <anon type="place"/> Inn is</u>
<u n="3" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>take you down to the</unclear> Caribbean <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>restaurant</unclear></u>
<u n="4" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> is it like an inn still?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0423">must be an area probably</u>
<u n="6" who="S0421">I mean I maybe there is an inn like or there was</u>
<u n="7" who="S0423">do you think they've named it after the book?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0421">no I think the book is based on the area <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0423">have you read it?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0421">no I've got it though</u>
<u n="11" who="S0423">have you?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've just told you that</u>
<u n="13" who="S0423">I always thought it was kinda some pirate story <pause dur="short"/> based in the Caribbean <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0421">no it's erm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0423">well it sounds like that <unclear>still</unclear></u>
<u n="16" who="S0421">yeah I'm not sure what that one's about <pause dur="short"/> but it's not</u>
<u n="17" who="S0423" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0421">I don't think that's a very Daphne du Maurier thing to write <pause dur="long"/> oh it's a red road again <pause dur="short"/> and then it's going grey</u>
<u n="19" who="S0423">are you like some aficionado of road surfaces then?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0421">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm just wondering why <pause dur="short"/> imagine if it did go yellow <pause dur="short"/> oh <shift new="singing"/> off to see the wizard <pause dur="short"/> the wonderful Wizard of Oz <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0423">nice clear road this is</u>
<u n="22" who="S0421">is the Wizard of Oz a book? or is it a play?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0423">I don't know</u>
<u n="24" who="S0421">cos I thought it might</u>
<u n="25" who="S0423">it was a film</u>
<u n="26" who="S0421">yeah but I thought it might be a novel but I think it's a play</u>
<u n="27" who="S0423">no I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> if I was to guess I would say it's a book</u>
<u n="28" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0423">that's <anon type="place"/> there</u>
<u n="30" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we're driving alongside <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> isn't that where the Hound of the Baskervilles <unclear>are</unclear> based?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0421">oh yeah oh we were talking about this it might be I'm not sure</u>
<u n="33" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear> oh yeah</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> or did I say it was <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0421">well one or the other <pause dur="long"/> I was reading erm The Sign of the Four</u>
<u n="35" who="S0423">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I got I kept getting really confused because</u>
<u n="37" who="S0423">I thought you'd read them all</u>
<u n="38" who="S0421">well I have <trunc>ki</trunc> no I've not read all of them I've read quite a few of them <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I always forget <pause dur="short"/> like the story because <pause dur="short"/>they're quite when I'm reading them <pause dur="short"/> they're quite difficult to like understand exactly what's going on cos I think I feel like I've lost <pause dur="short"/> when I've read them before <pause dur="short"/> I feel like I've lost a lot of the key details and not quite got the full effect <pause dur="short"/> because it well cos you've you've read them and you don't like they don't like the kind of the mystery is like this one person narrating <pause dur="short"/> like so like Sherlock Holmes and Dr Watson have gone to meet this person <pause dur="short"/> and then this one person is like saying <pause dur="short"/> like all the story <pause dur="short"/> and then there's like <trunc>s</trunc> direct speech within his speech <pause dur="short"/> and then sometimes I get confused like <pause dur="short"/> is he talking about? his father now or? is this him talking? or is he talking about someone else or did this happen <trunc>no</trunc> like? <trunc>di</trunc>did did you not find that?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh I don't remember being any confusion but I I thought it was quite er <pause dur="short"/> for like an old style <pause dur="short"/> read I thought it was fairly <pause dur="short"/> not too bad to follow along really</u>
<u n="40" who="S0421">yeah well the <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>a</trunc> the storyline I've always like <pause dur="short"/> been fine with the kind of what's happening in present day <pause dur="short"/> but when it gets to these like really long monologues I'm just like</u>
<u n="41" who="S0423">maybe I just didn't look at it too detailed like you are</u>
<u n="42" who="S0421">because like <trunc>h</trunc> I was rereading The Sign of the Four cos I've read that one before and like I was reading that and I was like right <pause dur="short"/> so this man</u>
<u n="43" who="S0423">you mean when the person who's saying right this is what happened but you're going back?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then Sherlock Holmes is like oh <pause dur="short"/> how interesting do you know what I mean? cos like Sherlock Holmes is investigating he's gone down to <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know where it is now <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but he's he's talking to this person and this person's giving him all this like <pause dur="short"/> information about erm oh yeah cos they they went to meet with this Mary <pause dur="short"/> she got a letter saying to meet <pause dur="short"/> if she can bring a friend but not the police and they then Sherlock Holmes and Watson went with her <pause dur="short"/> and then they're talking to this person <pause dur="short"/> who's talking about like <pause dur="short"/> cos her father's died and they're talking about her father and this other person in The Sign of the Four like group or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and I'm just like <pause dur="short"/> and this one person does narrating everything <pause dur="short"/> and this one person may not have even been there and they're just like narrating it to them</u>
<u n="45" who="S0423">well it's so he's <trunc>t</trunc> he's telling them what he knows about them <unclear>seems obvious really</unclear></u>
<u n="46" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but it's just confusing cos there's like direct speech within that <pause dur="short"/> and it's not <trunc>p</trunc> it's not put out it's like just put up in this like really long block</u>
<u n="47" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0421">cos I remember in erm <pause dur="short"/> cos I when I read A Study in Scarlet <pause dur="short"/> it was all good up until the point where <pause dur="short"/> it was kind of like part one and then there was like part two and then all of a sudden it was talking about this farmer and his daughter</u>
<u n="49" who="S0423">yeah I can't remember now</u>
<u n="50" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0423">I know I have read books where they just go off like that and you think what?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>what do I know</unclear> and <trunc>y</trunc> what's going on here?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0423">I don't remember <pause dur="short"/> details <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>someone who I read in it</unclear></u>
<u n="56" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah cos I yeah cos I read like quite a lot of them a while ago and I remember like enjoying them but not kind of <pause dur="short"/> like if someone was to ask me <pause dur="short"/> like afterwards oh what did you think? I wouldn't remember because <pause dur="short"/> it didn't kind of sink in enough</u>
<u n="57" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0421">cos of the way it's done cos it's kind of almost like <pause dur="short"/> they just drop all this information on you and it's like <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="59" who="S0423">well I don't think he necessarily wrote it as a novel type thing did he?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0421">no yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0423">they were really made for a magazine and they they were a series weren't they?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0423">so that probably has an effect on how it <pause dur="short"/> comes across in <pause dur="short"/> when it's all put together in a book <unclear>maybe I dunno</unclear></u>
<u n="64" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's <unclear>just from the way it's written</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> for a slightly different purpose than the probably the book he he didn't really write it with the <pause dur="short"/> idea of <pause dur="short"/> doing one story of the novel you know? although I guess the writing goes it's similar <unclear>I don't know</unclear> cos you kind of</u>
<u n="66" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0423">you just <unclear>all</unclear> go through it in chapters I suppose <pause dur="short"/> just break it down to series to be read in the magazine <pause dur="long"/> but yeah I don't remember it being a particularly difficult read <pause dur="short"/> but cos I I just <unclear>got the way through</unclear> cos certain some of them are quite short aren't they I just got a book with them all the stories in</u>
<u n="68" who="S0421">yeah that's what I did</u>
<u n="69" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0421">and I just kind of went through</u>
<u n="71" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0421">and then now <pause dur="short"/> but like <pause dur="short"/>because of the way it's written <pause dur="short"/> it's like it's not <pause dur="short"/> kind of the sort of mystery that I can engage in and kind of try and guess it's very much like wow look at Sherlock Holmes how did he do that like I didn't see that at all</u>
<u n="73" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well you know <trunc>i</trunc>it's it's just different</u>
<u n="74" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0423">to <pause dur="short"/> other kind of murder mystery things <unclear>cos it's not really like a modern murder novel</unclear></u>
<u n="76" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> then like <pause dur="short"/> so I'm like reading it now and I'm like I want to kind of try and understand like what's going on properly <pause dur="short"/>and it's quite it</u>
<u n="77" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't know whether it there is the death there is it that you want to <unclear>arrive</unclear> in that way</u>
<u n="78" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0423">well yeah I don't think it really is there no <pause dur="short"/> cos it wasn't written as that kind of a book</u>
<u n="80" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0423">it it there's clever little things in there you know?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0423">and some of them you think well <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="84" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it is well done yeah <pause dur="short"/> and like I think erm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0423" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> and that's what I like about it my some of the <pause dur="short"/> things he comes up with and <pause dur="short"/> like I I always like that that separate <unclear>that</unclear></u>
<u n="86" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I liked him like Sherlock Holmes like kind of the <trunc>w</trunc> stuff he he says</u>
<u n="87" who="S0423" trans="overlap">he he eliminates everything that's like impossible or whatever</u>
<u n="88" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0423">I quite liked when I read that sentence that stands out cos it's quite</u>
<u n="90" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0423">just cleverly put together to explain it how he <pause dur="short"/> works</u>
<u n="92" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0423">and then there's other things where <pause dur="short"/> like in the film as well where he says <unclear>oh look at that</unclear> little bit of a hair there you think well</u>
<u n="94" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0423">you know?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0421">yeah yeah it's good</u>
<u n="97" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's a bit far fetched some of it like <unclear/> you know you wouldn't be able to figure that out but it's still</u>
<u n="98" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I quite like the conversations like when <pause dur="short"/> dr Watson's like but how could you possibly know this? and Sherlock Holmes is like well <pause dur="short"/> my dear friend <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I shall explain <pause dur="short"/> and it's good I like that kinda thing</u>
<u n="99" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>good that</unclear> the explanations they make sense don't they although it's <trunc>u</trunc> still of a bit kind of <unclear>like</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> which makes him kind of special cos <pause dur="short"/> you know you know people who'd be able to figure it out from that but</u>
<u n="100" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't <unclear>obviously</unclear> the book or one of the films or series <unclear>he could somehow</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> you shaved by a window or something and he said how do you know that? and he was saying oh because of the way you've shaved you couldn't see your face right cos the light was shining on that side and</u>
<u n="102" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0423">stuff like it is good the way he figures it out isn't it?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0423">not that you could necessarily figure it out from that but</u>
<u n="106" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0423">the way he explains it you're thinking</u>
<u n="108" who="S0421">yeah it's like wow</u>
<u n="109" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah I could do that</unclear></u>
<u n="110" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you probably couldn't to be honest</u>
<u n="111" who="S0423">well no but</u>
<u n="112" who="S0421"><unclear>cos probably</unclear></u>
<u n="113" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but it would give you the idea of how determined you were</u>
<u n="114" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0423">you can put the clues together that <unclear>put a picture the same thing</unclear></u>
<u n="116" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0423">and that's kind of what he does so</u>
<u n="118" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I like in this erm Sign Of the Four one they were like oh but how did they get in? the window and the the window's locked <pause dur="short"/> and the door has not been <trunc>op</trunc> you know what I mean and it's like <pause dur="short"/>they must've come through that place in the roof <pause dur="short"/> and it's like <pause dur="short"/> it's good</u>
<u n="119" who="S0423">well I brought the Sherlock Holmes that <unclear>you've got</unclear></u>
<u n="120" who="S0421">oh did you?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0423">just in case you wanted to watch them I know you've seen them before but erm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0421" trans="overlap">the new one's out the you know that one? that one that looked quite good on the trailer?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0423">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> is it out now?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0423">yeah it might be interesting that mightn't it?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0423">he's he's like in old age isn't he?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0423">and is he a bit forgetful about <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0421">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I can't imagine Sherlock Holmes being forgetful</u>
<u n="131" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0421">cos his mind <pause dur="short"/> he says it's he's it's like erm <pause dur="short"/> an attic <pause dur="short"/> and he imagines it like an attic and he only keeps the things that he needs <pause dur="short"/> which is why when Watson's talking to him about like the solar system <pause dur="short"/> and he's like what? he doesn't know anything about it and then Watson's like how can you possibly not know? and he's like well cos I don't need to know why do I need to know that?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0423">is that the <unclear>film</unclear>?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0421">yeah I think it's in <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure which one it's in <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm any he's really shocked like</u>
<u n="135" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0421">and it's like you you have to keep only the things that he wants and like he forgets the things that he doesn't need</u>
<u n="137" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0421">and it and it's like how can you forget something? that you don't want <pause dur="short"/> in your head? but yeah that's how he that's how he can remember so much of like the things he does need</u>
<u n="139" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's quite a unique character I suppose that's why he's so <pause dur="short"/> he's so confident <unclear>ain't he</unclear>?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0423">like ahead of his time <unclear>when</unclear> it was written</u>
<u n="142" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it's it's strange that like you could think him up do you know what I mean if you weren't a similar sort of person</u>
<u n="143" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0421">it'd be quite hard to write that I think</u>
<u n="145" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0421">I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc>if Arthur Conan Doyle was that way inclined or anything</u>
<u n="147" who="S0423">I don't think he was</u>
<u n="148" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="149" who="S0423">friends with have you heard of Houdini?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0423">and he went once I think <pause dur="short"/> was he interested in spiritualism or something and he really wanted to disprove</u>
<u n="152" who="S0421" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="153" who="S0423">that it exists <pause dur="short"/> cos a lot of people pretending to be</u>
<u n="154" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0423"><trunc>e</trunc> to contact the dead then <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>back in that time</unclear></u>
<u n="156" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah there was loads of like fakes then</u>
<u n="157" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>doing</unclear> tricks and stuff yeah <pause dur="short"/> and Houdini <pause dur="short"/> cos he was a magician <pause dur="short"/> he managed to <pause dur="short"/> you know <unclear>remember</unclear> all the <trunc>way</trunc> reasons how they did this stuff</u>
<u n="158" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0423">or am I thinking of Lewis Carroll I can't remember if it's Arthur Conan if it was Arthur Conan Doyle</u>
<u n="160" who="S0421">well Lewis Carroll was erm <pause dur="short"/> like a mathematician</u>
<u n="161" who="S0423">oh was he?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he did maths at Cambridge</u>
<u n="163" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> that's very unusual isn't it?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="165" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>when you think about</unclear> the stuff he wrote</u>
<u n="166" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I've got a book that I've not had chance to <pause dur="short"/> explore properly and it's <pause dur="short"/> about Alice in Wonderland and like <pause dur="short"/> er like an analysis and about like maths in it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0421">and there are there is like some mathematical things like hidden in it</u>
<u n="169" who="S0423">oh right?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0421">but <pause dur="short"/> I dunno yeah you it's like you you you just generally don't imagine writers to be <pause dur="short"/> any in any way like mathematical or scientific it's like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0421">like I mean he wrote like <pause dur="short"/> alice in Wonderland that's so <pause dur="short"/> it's like surrealist isn't it?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0421">doesn't really seem to be any maths</u>
<u n="175" who="S0423" trans="overlap">although they say er to be <pause dur="short"/> you know if you are really good at maths you have to be quite creative</u>
<u n="176" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>and I think it's</unclear> being creative <unclear>but not</unclear> er</u>
<u n="178" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but Einstein was scientific and he was like imagination is more <pause dur="short"/> erm what is it? knowledge <pause dur="short"/> er I I used to know this quote something about knowledge but then it's got imagination encircles the world <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know what the knowledge bit was I think it's like knowledge is important <pause dur="short"/> something along those lines</u>
<u n="179" who="S0423" trans="overlap">imagination is erm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0421">yeah more so and he's like if you want your <trunc>u</trunc> children to be intelligent read read them fairy tales <pause dur="short"/> that's what he said</u>
<u n="181" who="S0423">see all those fairy tales I used to make up for you</u>
<u n="182" who="S0421">well <pause dur="short"/> could they be classed as fairy tales?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>see and I don't know how I did it</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0421">if you made them up I mean like yeah you can write your own I really like cos I did that project on fairy tales</u>
<u n="185" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0421">er <pause dur="short"/> and like <pause dur="short"/> although fairy tales are like <pause dur="short"/> were originally <pause dur="short"/> you know like?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well <unclear>cos you</unclear> know when Einstein says fairy tales he just means a really good story kind of thing doesn't he?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0421" trans="overlap">he means stories yeah <pause dur="short"/> although he he he I mean he was German so he may well have been</u>
<u n="189" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>cos er you have these</unclear> strange fairy tales</u>
<u n="190" who="S0421">referencing the Grimms there</u>
<u n="191" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think he <unclear>left</unclear> Germany <unclear>in the nineteen thirties depends how your imagination works them stories he really wanted</unclear></u>
<u n="192" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I know but that but back then back then it <trunc>w</trunc> it would've probably been mainly fairy tales that were told</u>
<u n="193" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0421">but what else would they be like to children? they would be <trunc>fair</trunc> or like folk stories</u>
<u n="195" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0421">that's what they would've been telling them <pause dur="short"/> that's what the Grimms did although I don't know how long ago was Einstein <pause dur="short"/> it might've still been Mother Goose's Household Tales or something</u>
<u n="197" who="S0423">well he was probably <trunc>bor</trunc>born in the nineteenth century and he</u>
<u n="198" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0423">his work was kind of like early twentieth century wasn't it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0423">that it became <unclear>this</unclear> well known for relativity and so on <pause dur="short"/> theory of relativity</u>
<u n="202" who="S0421">it might not have been <pause dur="short"/> it might've been Grimms by then</u>
<u n="203" who="S0423">why who's the other one?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0421">Hans Christian Andersen <pause dur="short"/> no but I was just saying like the time</u>
<u n="205" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what was they were before Grimms?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0421">no they were about the same time</u>
<u n="207" who="S0423">well he was Danish wasn't he?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0421">yeah no but <pause dur="short"/> he <pause dur="short"/> I mean like <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> cos I was saying the book the book of Grimms' Fairy Tales it might've been still the tale of mother goose</u>
<u n="209" who="S0423">well Grimms did they make them up <unclear>like Hansel</unclear> or they <trunc>th</trunc>they're historical tales that they just wrote down?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no they <pause dur="short"/> erm well they they collected them but they edited them themselves <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0423">well yeah so <pause dur="short"/> they they didn't make them they're kinda folk stories aren't they?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0421">yeah they well they are they are folk stories but <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0423">but it's I always imagined they're original works by them that they'd written</u>
<u n="214" who="S0421">well <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> they although they did go around Germany and get the stories from people <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>sto</trunc></u>
<u n="215" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they added to them and <unclear>stuff</unclear></u>
<u n="216" who="S0421">they have been changed <pause dur="short"/> a lot like through the years <pause dur="short"/> I don't know like the first edition might have been more <pause dur="short"/> the first the very first edition might have been more true to the originals <pause dur="short"/> but I do imagine that like they would've changed them anyway themselves</u>
<u n="217" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they they've not come up with any original story though</u>
<u n="218" who="S0421">er no <pause dur="short"/> but so then the</u>
<u n="219" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Hans Christian Andersen was his original? like The Ugly Duckling and stuff like that? I think it was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think it was yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0423" trans="overlap">he he was a storyteller <pause dur="short"/> his his stories rather than <pause dur="short"/> reworking fairy tales</u>
<u n="222" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but but the erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know but I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I think a lot of them now like the ones we know now <pause dur="short"/> erm they are changed a lot the Grimms changed them quite a lot cos they used to <pause dur="short"/> add in like different things that they wanted to <pause dur="short"/> and then the publishers insisted on different things in later editions as well <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> whether they can be considered <pause dur="short"/> like you know like fairy tales <pause dur="short"/> any more</u>
<u n="223" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0421">like they are kind of very much a product of Grimm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0421">but yeah no I think <trunc>Christia</trunc> Hans Christian Andersen wrote them</u>
<u n="227" who="S0423">yeah I think he is original tales aren't they? stories</u>
<u n="228" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but like the Grimms in terms of like <pause dur="short"/> they're probably older <pause dur="short"/> because they're like</u>
<u n="229" who="S0423">I've not been looking where we're going I don't think we would've passed it yet would we?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0421">no hopefully not</u>
<u n="231" who="S0423">Poison?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0421">Poison? imagine where are you from? oh I'm from Poison <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>fair enough <pause dur="short"/> we're there next</unclear></u>
<u n="236" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0423"><unclear><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></unclear> <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0421">I think erm <pause dur="short"/> cos there was a French <pause dur="short"/> person <pause dur="short"/> er I think he was a <trunc>wri</trunc> no like a writer I don't know if he collected the stories but I think he wrote them himself <pause dur="short"/> he's called Charles Perrault or Perrolt I don't know <trunc>Per</trunc> probably Perrault but if not Perrolt</u>
<u n="239" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear></u>
<u n="240" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="241" who="S0423" trans="overlap">did you see the <anon type="place"/> language there?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0423">said something in another language it must be <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0421">oh no he wrote like Little Red Riding Hood and <pause dur="short"/> that's like the first <pause dur="short"/> instance of it <pause dur="short"/> in print</u>
<u n="245" who="S0423">yeah but he didn't write that did he?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but he might've done I don't know</u>
<u n="247" who="S0423">I thought that's a folk tale again</u>
<u n="248" who="S0421">maybe <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if he wrote it or if</u>
<u n="249" who="S0423" trans="overlap">to make children <pause dur="short"/> beware of wolves</u>
<u n="250" who="S0421">but we don't know if we he <pause dur="short"/> he wrote it <pause dur="short"/> or <pause dur="short"/> erm he just <pause dur="short"/> wrote it down <pause dur="short"/> he probably just wrote it down</u>
<u n="251" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>alright</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> and he's French?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's the first <pause dur="short"/> recorded instance it was <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="253" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what time was that?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0421">erm <pause dur="short"/> just before Grimm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0423">when were they?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0421">dunno like <pause dur="short"/> sixteen hundreds or something</u>
<u n="257" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0421">seventeen hundreds maybe <pause dur="short"/> I think Perrault might've been sixteen <trunc>fi</trunc> or sixteen</u>
<u n="259" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah it is kinda the time I imagined or seventeenth</u>
<u n="260" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0423">whatever it was <pause dur="short"/> I didn't think it was <pause dur="short"/> too recent</u>
<u n="262" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> and I think he did Cinderella as well <pause dur="short"/> oh what do you know? <trunc>Cinderell</trunc> no cos <pause dur="short"/> cinderella I'm sure that's French</u>
<u n="263" who="S0423">er it does sound yeah it does seem like <unclear>it could be</unclear> French <pause dur="short"/> <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear></u>
<u n="264" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah Cinderella I think he did Cinderella first and then but Grimms have got Cinderella as well</u>
<u n="265" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> do we not go off at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0421">doesn't say anything about <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> is on the coast probably around there</u>
<u n="268" who="S0421">we might've <pause dur="short"/> passed this <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0421">although no that was <anon type="place"/> and we need to change at the that's gonna be <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0423">oh is it we're there <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0421" trans="overlap">although <pause dur="short"/> what <anon type="place"/> no isn't here but I saw it just there like a turn off</u>
<u n="273" who="S0423">oh why didn't you tell me <unclear>gotta</unclear> look out for the <anon type="place"/>? is that the next turn off?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0421">no it's <anon type="place"/> we need to branch left</u>
<u n="275" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0421">and then at the roundabout we need to take the third exit onto the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0423">well there hasn't been any branch left yet?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> don't think so <pause dur="short"/> oh what's this? coming up</u>
<u n="279" who="S0423">er this is a turn rather than a branch</u>
<u n="280" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0423">did you say that?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="283" who="S0423">it's a funny <pause dur="short"/> place name isn't it?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0421">I know does anyone still <trunc>s</trunc>? no one speaks <anon type="place"/> any more do they?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no the last woman died er so many years ago <unclear>it's familiar</unclear></u>
<u n="286" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no she died</u>
<u n="287" who="S0423">must be still <pause dur="short"/> must be written down or something</u>
<u n="288" who="S0421">yeah if they've still got yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0423" trans="overlap">must be still in existence but nobody's I suppose a linguist could</u>
<u n="290" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh it's a dead language like Latin</u>
<u n="291" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>probably teach you</unclear></u>
<u n="292" who="S0421">do you think Ancient Greek is any different to normal Greek?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0423">yeah it's a completely different language isn't it?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0421">is it like Latin and English?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0423">yeah I mean Latin</u>
<u n="296" who="S0421">is it the same alphabet?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well Latin <pause dur="short"/> was <pause dur="short"/> latin was what the what the Romans spoke wasn't it so</u>
<u n="298" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0423"><unclear>you'd have to</unclear> you'd have to say do you think the Italians are there's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="301" who="S0423"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear></u>
<u n="302" who="S0421">it's just cos it's got the same name like Greek and Ancient Greek</u>
<u n="303" who="S0423">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> the Italians don't speak</u>
<u n="304" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0423">it's not like Latin is it?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="307" who="S0423">but I know Latin <unclear/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0423">see that <anon type="place"/>? shouldn't I be going there?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know cos it says take the third exit after the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0423">maybe it's <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> I don't think we'll've done fifty miles yet will we?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it doesn't have <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> there's the is that a <trunc>le</trunc> oh no that's a <unclear>join</unclear></u>
<u n="313" who="S0423">do you want to have a look at my satnav again just stroll down <unclear/> see where it says turn off? on the satnav? maybe I can put my satnav in there <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>cos I don't trust that one</unclear></u>
<u n="314" who="S0421">oh you've got a text do you want me to look at it?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0423">no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> but <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0421">where's that postcode gone?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0423">will it not be in there somehow?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0421">no you've got your history turned off <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0423"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> Quarry <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> that's just <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0421">can't search <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0423">do you wanna try my satnav?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0421">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="323" who="S0423">I'm sure you know it's just to make as we get closer it might be <unclear/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh hang on <pause dur="short"/> it might <pause dur="short"/> no results <pause dur="short"/> why? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0423">might need to get some fuel</u>
<u n="326" who="S0421">go <pause dur="short"/> oh it's going</u>
<u n="327" who="S0423">what's going?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0421">it's start navigation <pause dur="short"/> oh it says stay on the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> says we'll be there in forty minutes</u>
<u n="329" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>so</unclear></u>
<u n="330" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><unclear>do you want?</unclear></u>
<u n="331" who="S0423">any idea where we turn off?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0421">erm we're going to <trunc>tur</trunc> oh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> we're gonna be on the <anon type="place"/> for a while</u>
<u n="333" who="S0423">are we?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> <unclear>or</unclear>?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0421">wow how long are we gonna be on this for? <pause dur="long"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> it's just one long road it I thought we were always on the <anon type="place"/> there but <pause dur="short"/> <unclear><trunc>presu</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="337" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we are on the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0421">no on this map <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> oh this is taking us a different <pause dur="short"/> this is taking us a different way</u>
<u n="339" who="S0423">why have we missed the turn off</u>
<u n="340" who="S0421">we must've done</u>
<u n="341" who="S0423">can't believe we've driven fifty miles <pause dur="short"/> can't've done it's only half an hour since you last looked</u>
<u n="342" who="S0421">maybe not then but this is taking us a different way</u>
<u n="343" who="S0423">well how could it change its mind so quick?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0421">this satnav</u>
<u n="345" who="S0423">yeah but you used that before didn't you?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0421">no but that wasn't I that didn't say anything like I didn't look at the directions on that</u>
<u n="347" who="S0423">on what?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0421">on the satnav I didn't look at the directions before I just looked at the time <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well why but why do you think it's taken us a different way?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><trunc>d</trunc> a different way to that thing that paper</u>
<u n="351" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> does it not mention that turn off?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> cos we're gonna it on according to this one it's gonna be first exit somewhere not a third <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0423">would've been handy I should've stopped and looked at that one maybe</u>
<u n="354" who="S0421">what?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0423">should've stopped and looked at the map <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I might have done</unclear></u>
<u n="356" who="S0421">do you want me to stop this satnav?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0423">no <trunc>du</trunc> do you not have written instructions on there?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="359" who="S0423">oh right well how did you see the <trunc>t</trunc> the the times does it say arrival time?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I've just got <pause dur="short"/> it just says thirty-eight minutes</u>
<u n="361" who="S0423">for what?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0421">then we'll arrive</u>
<u n="363" who="S0423">what till we get there?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0423">in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0423">on I thought you meant till we turn off</u>
<u n="368" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="369" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="370" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0423">well how do you know it's taken us a different way? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0421">because I've just looked through the directions</u>
<u n="375" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0421">and what it's gonna tell us to do <pause dur="short"/> right so it's gonna say stay on the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0421">and then</u>
<u n="379" who="S0423">to the end?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0421">and then we're gonna go onto the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> according to this</u>
<u n="381" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="382" who="S0421">and then we're gonna go take the first exit at the roundabout <pause dur="short"/> then we're gonna go into the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> then we're gonna go to the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> like I don't know if you wanna follow this one</u>
<u n="383" who="S0423">well it might be worth just going down <trunc>s</trunc> so we don't have to keep looking at the thing <unclear>I don't think the other one's usable what's <anon type="place"/>?</unclear></u>
<u n="384" who="S0421">do you want me to get your other satnav out?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0423">yeah put that in and see what that says keep that one on as well</u>
<u n="386" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> watch we'll see the <anon type="place"/> thing in a minute <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0423">so we should be turning left here next left <pause dur="short"/> well put it in the the <unclear>turn left turn left</unclear></u>
<u n="388" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I'm going I'm going</u>
<u n="389" who="S0423">maybe we'll maybe we should follow that this turn off and then</u>
<u n="390" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0423">what's the name of that place again?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0423"><unclear>where we're going <pause dur="short"/> is that it?</unclear></u>
<u n="394" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>n</trunc> <anon type="place"/> Hill <pause dur="short"/> this one isn't it this postcode?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of clicking"/>
<u n="397" who="S0421">no search results</u>
<u n="398" who="S0423">is there an address on it?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0421">do I need to put a space?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0423">probably</u>
<u n="401" who="S0421">oh there we go <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="402" who="S0423">that was quick</u>
<u n="403" who="S0421">shall I take this one off?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0423">leave it on for a moment <pause dur="short"/> what's this has it given any info on <pause dur="short"/> on the other satnav <unclear>that</unclear>?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0421">oh street not digitised</u>
<u n="406" who="S0423">that doesn't matter it's maybe the main road</u>
<u n="407" who="S0421">it's just spinning</u>
<u n="408" who="S0423">oh right is it? well that's not a good sign then is it?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0421">it doesn't have a clue</u>
<u n="410" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh it's at <anon type="place"/></unclear></u>
<u n="411" who="S0421">it says we'll be there in thirty-four minutes <pause dur="short"/> like this one</u>
<u n="412" who="S0423">our satnav?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they both say thirty-four minutes</u>
<u n="414" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh so it's</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> is it saying how far away till we turn?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0421">no cos it doesn't know where we are</u>
<u n="416" who="S0423">well how can it know how long till we get there?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it doesn't it doesn't know what road we're on <pause dur="short"/> so it doesn't know where we're gonna turn cos it it thinks we're in the middle of that field over there</u>
<u n="418" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but <trunc>h</trunc>how can it know how long we're gonna arrive <unclear>then</unclear>?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0421">cos it knows where we are but it doesn't think we're on the road <pause dur="short"/> it thinks we're in that field over there</u>
<u n="420" who="S0423"><unclear>that doesn't</unclear></u>
<u n="421" who="S0421">according to this map that's where it's got the arrow over there in that field</u>
<u n="422" who="S0423">that doesn't make any sense though</u>
<u n="423" who="S0421">that's where it is</u>
<u n="424" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="425" who="S0421">sheep <pause dur="short"/> yeah look</u>
<u n="426" who="S0423">eh?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0421">thinks we're in that field look</u>
<u n="428" who="S0423">oh well it's rubbish then isn't it? no point in us depending on that satnav</u>
<u n="429" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0423">queue ahead?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0421">doesn't seem to be queue</u>
<u n="432" who="S0423">no maybe there is <pause dur="short"/> rush hour or something <pause dur="short"/> what what am I looking for the <anon type="place"/> is it?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/> Hill branch left</u>
<u n="434" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0421">then at <anon type="place"/> roundabout take the third exit <pause dur="short"/> onto the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0423"><unclear>so it is yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="437" who="S0421">yeah so you're gonna branch left before you go to the roundabout</u>
<u n="438" who="S0423">that <pause dur="short"/> thing on my phone's not saying to go left</u>
<u n="439" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="440" who="S0423">oh look at all these queues <pause dur="short"/> but why we have to go forty mile an hour along here? it's silly</u>
<u n="441" who="S0421">that's probably why there's queues oh there's <vocal desc="laugh"/> no queues</u>
<u n="442" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="443" who="S0421">wow look at that lake</u>
<u n="444" who="S0423">I thought it was some massive thing</u>
<u n="445" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0423">not very big is it?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> quite big <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0423">so has anything happened on mine?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0421">no <pause dur="long"/> oh we're on the road</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="450" who="S0423">are we on the road now?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0423">how long does it take?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0421">thirty-three minutes</u>
<u n="454" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> shall we just follow this?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0421">yeah shall I turn this one on?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0421">it'll be using your thing</u>
<u n="458" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know how to get it off?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just close all windows <pause dur="short"/> do you want me to look at this message?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0423">no <unclear>phones are</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to check messages instantly <pause dur="short"/> you know I I <pause dur="short"/> I'm not</u>
<u n="461" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0423">eager for a <pause dur="short"/> a <trunc>go</trunc> I I'm not a surgeon that needs to attend a major operation I'm on holiday</u>
<u n="463" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0423">probably from the phone company telling me something</u>
<u n="465" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0423">not looking cos it's stupid <pause dur="short"/> if it was something urgent somebody'd ring me <pause dur="short"/> do you respond to messages immediately?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0421">if I see it then yeah but if not then no <pause dur="short"/> you might have an SOS message</u>
<u n="468" who="S0423">off who?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0421">dunno anyone <pause dur="short"/> sOS</u>
<u n="470" who="S0423">who's it from? did anyone say?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0421">I didn't look <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> now you're thinking is it an SOS message? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I've never had an SOS message so I'm not likely to get one</u>
<u n="473" who="S0421">neither have I but you never know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> might be SOS <pause dur="short"/> stop <pause dur="short"/> please help <pause dur="short"/> stop <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0423">could be <pause dur="short"/> why are you not at work? think you're supposed to be on holiday? <vocal desc="laugh"/> get get back here</u>
<u n="475" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's how they used to on the telegrams isn't it? <trunc>s</trunc> they always put stop</u>
<u n="476" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they wrote it kinda shorthand <unclear>so it wasn't too</unclear></u>
<u n="477" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos you had to pay per word didn't you?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0423">well per letter probably possibly character or</u>
<u n="479" who="S0421" trans="overlap">per letter <pause dur="short"/> and they they they wouldn't use like function words? they they just like <pause dur="short"/> put like <pause dur="short"/> I shop <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow do you know what I mean instead of I am going to the shop tomorrow?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0423">well yeah that's why</u>
<u n="481" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0423">at the end of a sentence you'd have to <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>only few</unclear></u>
<u n="483" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well <trunc>y</trunc> there wasn't any punctuation</u>
<u n="484" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah sentences yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0421">that's why they put <pause dur="short"/> but stop <pause dur="short"/> that's four letters is that really <trunc>nec</trunc></u>
<u n="486" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no they they'd put a <pause dur="short"/> they don't mean like a full stop</u>
<u n="487" who="S0421">no they would write stop</u>
<u n="488" who="S0423">how <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>d</trunc> how do you know that?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0421">cos I I I know stuff about telegrams</u>
<u n="490" who="S0423">no they wouldn't write stop</u>
<u n="491" who="S0421">they would</u>
<u n="492" who="S0423">well you mustn't be charged for that word</u>
<u n="493" who="S0421">well maybe <pause dur="short"/> that's what they'd do cos there was no punctuation</u>
<u n="494" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="495" who="S0421">it would literally so stop so you'd know where the sentence stops</u>
<u n="496" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0421">because you would have to type it out on like a Morse thing wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0423">well <pause dur="short"/> before telephones yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0423">and then they they they would have a they just only used to have telegramming but they had telephones and they wouldn't use that</u>
<u n="501" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="502" who="S0423">they'd they'd still type a message out and have deliver it <pause dur="short"/> which'd be a telegram <pause dur="short"/> so the original telegrams yeah you'd be doing it by telegraph</u>
<u n="503" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I'm on about</u>
<u n="504" who="S0423">yeah so well you'd still have the same thing in existence even when telephones existed</u>
<u n="505" who="S0421">so how did they do it on telephone?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0423">well you <pause dur="short"/> ring them up say I want to send er a <trunc>tele</trunc>telegraph</u>
<u n="507" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh and you'd tell them and they'd write it down?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0423">yeah so they hand deliver it</u>
<u n="509" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="510" who="S0423">erm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0421">I don't know about that</u>
<u n="512" who="S0423">to the person <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="513" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I only know about the Morse one <pause dur="short"/> and I know that you used to have to write stop</u>
<u n="514" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="515" who="S0421">cos you can't cos obviously you can't put full stops that means something in Morse <pause dur="short"/> cos it's dash dot</u>
<u n="516" who="S0423">oh I see what you're saying yeah with the original er</u>
<u n="517" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so you have to put stop</u>
<u n="518" who="S0423">telegrams yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh for the telegraph that's a telegraph <trunc>mess</trunc>message isn't it like that</u>
<u n="519" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> so you'd you'd have <pause dur="short"/> you'd er also a service telegram <pause dur="short"/> you heard of a telegram?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0423">so you could ring up and give your message <pause dur="short"/> and then they would hand deliver it</u>
<u n="523" who="S0421">oh <pause dur="short"/> like a singing telegram?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0423" trans="overlap">er you know if something urgent if <trunc>i</trunc> if <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="525" who="S0421">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0423">not necessarily that but yeah that was kind of <unclear>stuff like</unclear> that came from it <pause dur="short"/> but if you had an important message that <pause dur="short"/> needed to be <pause dur="short"/> you know it's usually for emergencies or if there <trunc>of</trunc> quite often bad news so if somebody said you've got a telegram <unclear>you'd be like <pause dur="short"/> oh</unclear></u>
<u n="527" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0423">what's happening has somebody died or something?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0421">yeah I did say I said telegraph but then you started talking about telegrams</u>
<u n="530" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="531" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so then I thought oh it must be called a telegram <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos I always get those two mixed up yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no the telegrams yeah that that was before telephone wasn't it? it was er before <pause dur="short"/> telephones were invented a way of communicating <pause dur="short"/> yeah they'd use like Morse code for that</u>
<u n="533" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0423"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0421">but that'd take ages wouldn't it because it's like <pause dur="short"/> three dots or like three <trunc>da</trunc> you know what I mean it's quite a lot for one letter</u>
<u n="536" who="S0423"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="537" who="S0421">isn't SOS dot dot dot dash dash dash dot dot dot?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well you you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="539" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think SOS is the only one I've ever learned and I think that's what it is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah I <unclear>did know</unclear> I knew what it was but I don't know what it is now <pause dur="short"/> well yeah the person who's doing it would be really quick and quite skilled wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> we we were taught <pause dur="short"/> they taught us the er Brownies <pause dur="short"/> and we all had to stand in the room and send messages with our torches</u>
<u n="542" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="543" who="S0421">and they taught us SOS and told us to remember that one <pause dur="short"/> because if we're ever stranded on a hill we can get our torch <pause dur="short"/> and call for help <pause dur="short"/> that's what they told us that <trunc>en</trunc> like ever since I was like oh <pause dur="short"/> better remember that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but now mobile phones are invented you don't</u>
<u n="545" who="S0421">yeah no but you might not get erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0423" trans="overlap">signal</u>
<u n="547" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I <trunc>m</trunc> I mean I'm sure there was mobile phones <vocal desc="laugh"/> when I was at Brownies</u>
<u n="548" who="S0423">yeah you're on a hill and you'll be flashing your light <unclear>somebody</unclear> in the distance saying <pause dur="short"/> oh what's that light?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0421">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0423" trans="overlap">shut the window <unclear>so that guy doesn't come here</unclear> shut the <unclear>window</unclear></u>
<u n="551" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no one's gonna know that <unclear>you didn't <trunc>e</trunc></unclear> like <trunc>w</trunc> probably wouldn't even see it unless you've got a really powerful torch</u>
<u n="552" who="S0423">it's good on <pause dur="short"/> to be doing stuff like that</u>
<u n="553" who="S0421">yeah but</u>
<u n="554" who="S0423"><unclear>get a bit of</unclear> extra knowledge on that kinda thing <pause dur="short"/> I hope we come to a garage soon <pause dur="short"/> sOS</u>
<u n="555" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0423">do you think there's a thing there dot dot dot that you can?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh can you imagine if that's what the breakdown phones are like? you have to send it in Morse <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> well this is slowing us down quite a lot</u>
<u n="559" who="S0421">but didn't you see them? didn't they at one point have when a telegraph was coming through it like the machine would punch <pause dur="short"/> holes in a piece of paper or something?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0423">no that's a <pause dur="short"/> teletype or something</u>
<u n="561" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="562" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's a different thing cos had <unclear/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> I think I saw it on a film</u>
<u n="564" who="S0423">not sure <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="565" who="S0421">is that so the person wouldn't have to listen? so carefully?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0423">I've no idea I don't know what <pause dur="short"/> that's gonna be I don't know how could somebody interpret it?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0421">cos it would be a dot or a dash</u>
<u n="568" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="569" who="S0421">I don't know</u>
<u n="570" who="S0423">like Braille?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0421">maybe <pause dur="short"/> oh it's so cool and like <pause dur="short"/> it'd be so cool to read Braille cos like I always <pause dur="short"/> on like boxes of like medicines or like creams or whatever <pause dur="short"/> not always but on most of them <pause dur="short"/> has it in Braille <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like oh like touching it like oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0423">well</u>
<u n="573" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0423">it's better that you can actually read it rather than touching it</u>
<u n="575" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and erm on the I I've I realised that <pause dur="short"/> you know the erm stop button on buses they have Braille on that I always wondered what the little</u>
<u n="576" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="577" who="S0421">and I I <trunc>alway</trunc> I was like <pause dur="short"/> I it never kind of clicked and then one day I pressed the button and I was like oh it says it in Braille</u>
<u n="578" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I never really noticed that but now you mention it <unclear/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and also <pause dur="short"/> you know like before you're about to cross the road and they have all those like knobbly tiles with the dots and they're not nice to stand on that's so</u>
<u n="580" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0421">blind people know that the road's coming up</u>
<u n="582" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0421">I was <trunc>wond</trunc> I was like why do they have these?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0421">that's probably why it is</u>
<u n="586" who="S0423">suppose unless we need to know we don't really pay much attention</u>
<u n="587" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0423">oh look hills in the distance</u>
<u n="589" who="S0421">where?</u>
<u n="590" who="S0423">they've gone behind</u>
<u n="591" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0423">trees <unclear>that's where</unclear></u>
<u n="593" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they've gone <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> they ran away <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0423">yeah that turn off's still not come up has it? strange</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/> <pause dur="long"/>
<u n="595" who="S0421">basically just carry on and don't bear left</u>
<u n="596" who="S0423"><unclear>yeah</unclear> just keep going straight</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="597" who="S0421">thanks for that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0423">what road are we on? are we on the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> wind turbines <pause dur="long"/> hey you know that book? erm The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night Time</u>
<u n="600" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0421">that title <pause dur="short"/> has come from Sherlock Holmes Hound of the Baskervilles</u>
<u n="602" who="S0423">oh really?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because erm <pause dur="short"/> it's something like I can't remember the exact exact quote <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> it was something like oh it was a curious incident and Watson was like what was so curious about it? and then Sherlock Holmes was like nothing happened <pause dur="short"/> or something like that</u>
<u n="604" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0421">it comes from there <pause dur="short"/> and cos I cos I was reading that book and there's like all these like Sherlock Holmes references in it as well</u>
<u n="606" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's been made into a play that won won loads of awards</u>
<u n="607" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but like it <pause dur="short"/> is it? it didn't click like the title didn't really click until I was like <pause dur="short"/> oh there's Sherlock Holmes in this and then like <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise I didn't make the connection <pause dur="short"/> yeah I didn't really enjoy the book very much</u>
<u n="608" who="S0423">did you not?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0421">no have you read it?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is it? no it's not a <unclear/> is it?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0423">oh we're only nineteen miles now</u>
<u n="613" who="S0421">I thought it was quite interesting <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> like his perspective was quite interesting but</u>
<u n="614" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's quite famous isn't it?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0421">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0423">yeah I should make the effort to try and start reading some <unclear>more</unclear> books some kind of books that are <pause dur="short"/> have interest for me cos <pause dur="short"/> I tend to see a <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna read a book I'll just go for something that's cheap</u>
<u n="617" who="S0421">yeah then they're just rubbish</u>
<u n="618" who="S0423">yeah well they're readable</u>
<u n="619" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0423"><unclear>not <pause dur="short"/> really</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> they're not page turners</u>
<u n="621" who="S0421">but if you go for erm <pause dur="short"/> some classics <pause dur="short"/> if there's some classics that are interesting you <pause dur="short"/> they're usually you can get them so cheap</u>
<u n="622" who="S0423">from where?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0421">Amazon</u>
<u n="624" who="S0423">oh really?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0421">yeah like</u>
<u n="626" who="S0423">okay</u>
<u n="627" who="S0421">some of them like what have I got? I got erm <pause dur="short"/> like if you get like the the paperbacks <pause dur="short"/> some of like the really plain looking ones they're quite cheap</u>
<u n="628" who="S0423">actually you know classics are <pause dur="short"/> there are quite a few that I think but you know I've read some as well like</u>
<u n="629" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0423">classic you know I've really loved <pause dur="short"/> you know famous stories and some of them <pause dur="short"/> just they can be quite</u>
<u n="631" who="S0421">slow</u>
<u n="632" who="S0423">well <trunc>la</trunc> you have really have to labour don't you? you don't <pause dur="short"/> you don't always get</u>
<u n="633" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0423">the satisfaction out of it that you <pause dur="short"/> cos you kind of</u>
<u n="635" who="S0421">like a page turner?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0423">yeah depends what you're reading for doesn't it? <pause dur="short"/> you know I've been interested in loads of it it's good read them but <pause dur="short"/> like I've got Moby Dick and <unclear>that's very sad part of it</unclear></u>
<u n="637" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> even yeah but other</u>
<u n="638" who="S0423"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="639" who="S0421">even among classic readers <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> moby Dick <pause dur="short"/> is</u>
<u n="640" who="S0423">I think I've read a a certain amount of pages but</u>
<u n="641" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like <trunc>peo</trunc>people just er don't go for that one</u>
<u n="642" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the thing is the book the prose is really thick and <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> the words <unclear>didn't</unclear></u>
<u n="643" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's basically a guy that has to hunt whales <pause dur="short"/> basically</u>
<u n="644" who="S0423">yeah but I could find it</u>
<u n="645" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0423">you know I could see why that might have its interest but <pause dur="short"/> again <pause dur="short"/> it probably is <pause dur="short"/> worth labouring through it</u>
<u n="647" who="S0421">do you think?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0423">but the words are the book I've bought for really cheaply</u>
<u n="649" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really small <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0423">and the the words are tiny <pause dur="short"/> so I really struggled to kind of even read it so I need to <pause dur="short"/> yeah it it probably would be best maybe intersperse some classics with some good books you know?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0421">if you enjoyed <pause dur="short"/> sherlock Holmes you may may like The Moonstone by Wilkie Collins</u>
<u n="652" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="653" who="S0421">it's like one of the first kind of proper like detective novels I think</u>
<u n="654" who="S0423">what is it an old one?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="657" who="S0421">it was like <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure that yeah it was like a <pause dur="short"/> it's about erm <pause dur="short"/> I think it's like I know it's about a moonstone in like I think it's from India or something</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="658" who="S0423">it's about what?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0421">it's about a <trunc>moon</trunc></u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="660" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what what did it say? turn now?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0421">take the <trunc>roundab</trunc> take the fourth <trunc>e</trunc>exit at the roundabout but there isn't one</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="662" who="S0423">maybe I should've turned left there and it didn't tell me</u>
<u n="663" who="S0421">er oh</u>
<u n="664" who="S0423">this <pause dur="short"/> satnav why did I trust it?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0423">so <unclear>you've put</unclear> my phone on we're only twenty miles away <pause dur="short"/> unless <pause dur="short"/> what's it doing now? look it's lost us</u>
<u n="667" who="S0421">I know <pause dur="short"/> it thinks we're in the field <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my phone <unclear>up</unclear> put it on <pause dur="short"/> travelling by car <pause dur="short"/> it should have a voice thing on shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0423">oh it's back on now is it? fourteen miles maybe I should just follow the signs</u>
<u n="671" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0423">tell me where to turn off then go back to that</u>
<u n="673" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0423">when we get close to it</u>
<u n="675" who="S0421">no it's back here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="676" who="S0423">look there's a left turn here <pause dur="short"/> what's it saying there? I bet I had to turn left back there didn't I?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0421" trans="overlap">probably yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0423">but it didn't say turn left did it? maybe this is quite a new <pause dur="short"/> no it's not new it was a new road <pause dur="short"/> recognise it <unclear>but</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> maybe sections of it've changed <pause dur="short"/> what's that B road I thought it said to go up that? I've not seen that thing on that sheet at the end of the road</u>
<u n="679" who="S0421">what?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0423">that where we have to turn off left</u>
<u n="681" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/> Hill</u>
<u n="682" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's the B road you go on to?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0421">er that's right at the bottom that's</u>
<u n="684" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>there</unclear></u>
<u n="685" who="S0421">at roundabout take second exit onto <anon type="place"/> Way</u>
<u n="686" who="S0423"><unclear>and</unclear> that's further down</u>
<u n="687" who="S0421">but that's after you've <pause dur="short"/> turned on to</u>
<u n="688" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0421">that's quite a while</u>
<u n="690" who="S0423">look more wind <unclear>look at</unclear> those</u>
<u n="691" who="S0421">oh <pause dur="short"/> wind turbines</u>
<u n="692" who="S0423">there's the <anon type="place"/> services as well</u>
<u n="693" who="S0421">oh yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> services</u>
<u n="695" who="S0421">I always call them windmills cos you call them windmills</u>
<u n="696" who="S0423" trans="overlap">why <trunc>d</trunc> why didn't I go in there for some fuel? no you said wind turbine before</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="697" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0423">what?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah because I'm consciously like deciding to call them turbines because I called them windmills in my French</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="700" who="S0421">I called them windmills in my French lesson <pause dur="short"/> when we were doing <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> global warming and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and people were like windmills? what do you mean? because I looked up I looked up windmills in the dictionary and got the French word</u>
<u n="701" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos I think</u>
<u n="702" who="S0421">and it's a turbine it's not a mill <pause dur="short"/> it's not a mill <pause dur="short"/> it's not a windmill it's a wind turbine but it's a <trunc>d</trunc> completely different word in French so it was really obviously</u>
<u n="703" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="704" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and people were like why are you going on about windmills? and I was like cos windmills they're like no it's wind turbine and I was like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> and I got that from you</u>
<u n="705" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>what did they say?</unclear> er did you?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0421">yeah you <trunc>call</trunc> you always call them windmills</u>
<u n="707" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="708" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so I <trunc>d</trunc> I like call them wind turbines now because</u>
<u n="709" who="S0423">yeah a windmill it it it the old flour and so on and stuff <unclear>they don't do it</unclear></u>
<u n="710" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's a mill yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's essentially the same thing though I mean</u>
<u n="711" who="S0423">well the operation the wind turns the sails doesn't it? I think <unclear>now</unclear> try my phone <unclear>that's gone further</unclear> that satnav <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know where we're up to on that sheet there so <pause dur="short"/> and as we get into <anon type="place"/> I need to <pause dur="short"/> know where <unclear>the market</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> we're coming a different way from that <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>think we're gonna be now</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I can get a bit lost</u>
<u n="712" who="S0421">right <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> shall I turn this other satnav off?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0423">you may as well it doesn't seem to working right does it?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> right <pause dur="short"/> we're off <pause dur="short"/> we should be there in seventeen minutes</u>
<u n="715" who="S0423">really? is it on voice thing now?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0421">yeah well it said I clicked on the settings then it said mute so I'm guessing it's on loud</u>
<u n="717" who="S0423">alright yeah <unclear>it won't say</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>turn left it's this one I think</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>no <pause dur="short"/> it says turn left here</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if my <pause dur="short"/> volume is up <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>this phone it's near the silver button <pause dur="short"/> below it on the right erm</unclear></u>
<u n="718" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's up loud <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0423">just about had enough fuel to get here <pause dur="short"/> be about ten pounds worth left in it</u>
<u n="720" who="S0421"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/> they look like volcanoes over there</u>
<u n="721" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah look at those hills they look really weird</u>
<u n="722" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0423">like kind of pointed aren't they?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and they've got like a bit of white on them <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="725" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0421">ash or something going down the side <pause dur="short"/> why don't we have any volcanoes in this country?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0423">I don't know</u>
<u n="728" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0423">it's to do with where you are in the <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> in the world isn't it they have the the faults <pause dur="short"/> seismic faults running through</u>
<u n="730" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0423">and you have to be on that line I guess don't you?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah we don't really have any do we? but it's funny because</u>
<u n="733" who="S0423">I think <trunc>volca</trunc> I know earthquakes are affected by that I don't know if volcanoes are the same kinda thing <pause dur="short"/> affected by <pause dur="short"/> not sure</u>
<u n="734" who="S0421">yeah because isn't it like?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0423">they're only in a certain part of the world</u>
<u n="736" who="S0421">yeah because I think like hills are formed something like where it's been pushed together isn't it like the land? so</u>
<u n="737" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or it's been by the river</u>
<u n="738" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="739" who="S0423">over billions of years the river</u>
<u n="740" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0423" trans="overlap">creates a valley <pause dur="short"/> but I I don't know if something like the Himalayas was that created was that kind of like pushed up wasn't it?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="743" who="S0423">can we turn left here?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0421">duh duh duh duh duh <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="745" who="S0423" trans="overlap">gotta figure out what the sign means left for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0421">I think so</u>
<u n="747" who="S0423">looks like it</u>
<u n="748" who="S0421">er <pause dur="short"/> right there we go <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="749" who="S0423">is this it yeah? is this that turn off we were supposed to be looking for? yeah <pause dur="short"/> look how long it's took to get here it said it like it was right away</u>
<u n="750" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> Hill <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> shall I turn this off cos we can just use the paper again?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0423">no leave it on cos we're not far</u>
<u n="752" who="S0421" trans="overlap">use the left lane to take the <anon type="place"/> ramp</u>
<u n="753" who="S0423">the <anon type="place"/> ramp? ramp?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="755" who="S0423">is it American that voice?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0421">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so</u>
<u n="757" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like where where is he now third?</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="758" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="759" who="S0423">signed anyway <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0421">one <pause dur="short"/> two <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> three me and mummy always count the exits</u>
<u n="761" who="S0423">why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="762" who="S0421">to make sure we get the right one</u>
<u n="763" who="S0423">I can't believe it it it started like <pause dur="short"/> we had to <pause dur="short"/> straight after <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="764" who="S0421">yeah it was like boom</u>
<u n="765" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>like</unclear> wait <pause dur="short"/> I should've asked you how many miles between <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>but I don't know that I did</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> well we're only nine miles away</u>
<u n="766" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh buh <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0423">I'm getting <pause dur="short"/> quite low on <pause dur="short"/> fuel like</u>
<u n="768" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0423">we'll have enough to get there I think</u>
<u n="770" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we'll have to call your pick ups out</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="771" who="S0421">your</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="772" who="S0423">what did he say do now?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> in point three miles</u>
<u n="774" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we're coming up to something <pause dur="short"/> take the fourth exit no first exit <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0421">oh is it?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0423">that's what the sign says what's the sign gonna say?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0421">it should say it again</u>
<u n="778" who="S0423">it should tell you there now <pause dur="short"/> is it straight on?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0421">it it's showing you there don't know what that is</u>
<u n="780" who="S0423">that's not <unclear>a first exit quite possibly</unclear></u>
<u n="781" who="S0421">is it the third?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0423">well that says <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0421">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah we <unclear>needed</unclear> to take the third</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="784" who="S0421">oh well it'll redirect you <pause dur="short"/> rerouting</u>
<u n="785" who="S0423"><unclear>look at that</unclear> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="786" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0423">this seems like this seems like it should be the way we should've gone</u>
<u n="788" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0423">well it might take us a <trunc>d</trunc>different way you know for the camp?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="791" who="S0423">is it saying any different time or anything?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> fourteen minutes</u>
<u n="793" who="S0423"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> is it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0421">yeah me and mummy always count the roundabout stops to make sure we get the right one</u>
<u n="795" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0421">cos sometimes it's not clear <pause dur="short"/> do you not count them?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0423">I kind of in my head just look at them</u>
<u n="798" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0423">I don't go one two three and all that <pause dur="short"/> just do it in my head can't I?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0423">but you yeah you just pay attention which <pause dur="short"/> what you're going past and what you're coming up to</u>
<u n="802" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is that a? these bends are a bit sharp aren't they you can't even see what's coming round the corner</u>
<u n="803" who="S0423">mm?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0421">all the cyclists <pause dur="short"/> that could be you</u>
<u n="805" who="S0423"><unclear>watch out for them and be polite haven't I?</unclear></u>
<u n="806" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that must be so scary <pause dur="long"/> to all of a sudden hear like a car vroom vroom that <vocal desc="gasp"/> is he gonna knock me over?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>exciting though</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> you know he's not cos he's he can see you <pause dur="short"/> the driver's not blind is he? got an open road there so <pause dur="short"/> you have to ride with confidence if you're nervous then <pause dur="short"/> that's it you've had it <pause dur="short"/> you you're more likely to</u>
<u n="808" who="S0421">oh I like those bushes</u>
<u n="809" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>it looks quite nice don't it?</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0421">are they hydrangeas? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="811" who="S0423">don't know</u>
<u n="812" who="S0421">they're like erm <pause dur="short"/> on my game Animal Crossing they have big bushes like that and you get them in blue and pinky like blue purple and pinky <pause dur="short"/> and er they're called hydrangeas</u>
<u n="813" who="S0423">same thing then</u>
<u n="814" who="S0421">although <pause dur="short"/> the flower looked a bit different <pause dur="short"/> we have some hydrangeas</u>
<u n="815" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well no they <trunc>d</trunc> they're not hydrangeas</u>
<u n="817" who="S0423" trans="overlap">were they not chrysanthemums?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="819" who="S0423">do they look I dunno <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no I think they're a bit different</u>
<u n="821" who="S0423">oh okay</u>
<u n="822" who="S0421">do you not know much about flowers?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0423">I know what a rose looks like</u>
<u n="824" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0423">oh it's on empty now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="826" who="S0421">I don't know that much about flowers</u>
<u n="827" who="S0423">yeah but you probably know more than me</u>
<u n="828" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know a bit but</u>
<u n="829" who="S0423">I could recognise a daffodil a tulip a daisy a rose <pause dur="short"/> an orchid <pause dur="short"/> it's not bad is it?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> a lily</u>
<u n="831" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> know them</u>
<u n="832" who="S0421">water lily <pause dur="short"/> foxglove <pause dur="short"/> bluebell</u>
<u n="833" who="S0423">showing off now aren't you?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0421">I like foxgloves</u>
<u n="835" who="S0423">they're poisonous</u>
<u n="836" who="S0421">not if you don't eat them</u>
<u n="837" who="S0423">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they're poisonous to look at</u>
<u n="838" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>look in a scary way</unclear></u>
<u n="840" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> they look nice though like</u>
<u n="841" who="S0423">what's that? see it?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0421">ooh wow it's an eagle</u>
<u n="843" who="S0423">is that an eagle? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0421"><unclear>can't you see there and</unclear> a buzzard?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0423">probably a seagull <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0421">no it was an eagle it was grey</u>
<u n="847" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it was a bird of prey</u>
<u n="848" who="S0421">yeah it was grey and it had a sharp beak</u>
<u n="849" who="S0423">probably a buzzard</u>
<u n="850" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's some form of eagle</u>
<u n="851" who="S0423">not an eagle we don't have</u>
<u n="852" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="853" who="S0423">eagles here</u>
<u n="854" who="S0421">yeah I like foxgloves cos I can understand why they're called foxgloves cos they look like little gloves for foxes</u>
<u n="855" who="S0423">eh? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0421">they're like little bells but they look like they could be gloves for foxes like they could wear them <unclear>as a</unclear></u>
<u n="859" who="S0423" trans="overlap">why do they not call them bells then?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0421">cos they've <trunc>o</trunc> got loads of bells already <pause dur="short"/> might as well call them foxgloves cos they're like little gloves for foxes <pause dur="short"/> I wish we had albatrosses over here <pause dur="short"/> I'd really like to see an albatross</u>
<u n="861" who="S0423">where are they from?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0421">er I think they like <pause dur="short"/> cos they fly for like miles and miles and miles and miles <pause dur="short"/> but I think you get them around <trunc>Me</trunc> er in America <pause dur="short"/> er but I'm not sure where they fly to from there <pause dur="short"/> we don't get them really in Europe I don't think</u>
<u n="863" who="S0423">no they fly fly practically half around the world but</u>
<u n="864" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they they don't even have to like flap they just glide like</u>
<u n="865" who="S0421" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0421">and then they they like live on cliffs <pause dur="short"/> they look really nice like flying over the sea</u>
<u n="867" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they've got a very big wingspan haven't they?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fly over the sea they're like they're just basically massive seagulls aren't they? <pause dur="long"/> be there in ten minutes</u>
<u n="869" who="S0423">oh that's good it's just as well <pause dur="short"/> my light saying I'm low on fuel has come on</u>
<u n="870" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos you you were always like oh <trunc>i</trunc> I'd be so embarrassed to call for help if I run out of fuel</u>
<u n="871" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I would yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0421">and like you <trunc>d</trunc> I don't understand how people do it like <pause dur="short"/> how do they not miss?</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="873" who="S0423">what's that?</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="874" who="S0423"><unclear>thank you</unclear></u>
<u n="875" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0423"><unclear>we're obviously right there</unclear></u>
<u n="877" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in <pause dur="short"/> a thousand feet</u>
<u n="878" who="S0423">take the third exit did it say?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0423">maybe you should correspond it with that thing there <pause dur="short"/> or that might be different anyway cos of the</u>
<u n="881" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0423">might've come a different way or it's <anon type="place"/> where we are? <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/>? so it must be just outside of the town <pause dur="long"/> it's probably signposted soon the camp I would've thought <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we can be too far from it</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="883" who="S0423">it's handy we had thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="885" who="S0423" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="886" who="S0423">be nice to stop driving and have a break <pause dur="long"/> has it said anything? straight on isn't it?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0421">er</u>
<u n="888" who="S0423">what's going on up here? there's a flashing light there</u>
<u n="889" who="S0421">they're building houses <pause dur="long"/> they're building houses in <anon type="place"/> estate where my house is</u>
<u n="890" who="S0423">are they?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="892" who="S0423">I wouldn't've thought there'd be anywhere to build <unclear>er</unclear></u>
<u n="893" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> through my bedroom window you could see <unclear>like</unclear> this spot of land and they're building there <pause dur="short"/> it's they're building like loads there so it's not very nice really</u>
<u n="894" who="S0423">mm oh is that chocolate alright <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0421">probably not</u>
<u n="896" who="S0423">let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0421">probably is <pause dur="short"/> is it alright?</u>
<u n="898" who="S0423">oh no it is quite soft <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0421">look at the state you've <pause dur="short"/> you've just ripped it</u>
<u n="900" who="S0423">ripped what?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0421">the chocolate <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> they're really nice those jelly beans aren't they in it? it's like oh</u>
<u n="902" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's what I chose in <anon type="place"/> for my mixture with chocolate</u>
<u n="903" who="S0421">oh yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0423">jelly bean what you get? popcorn?</u>
<u n="905" who="S0421" trans="overlap">chocolate popcorn and you were like er and I was like of course chocolate</u>
<u n="906" who="S0423">didn't they do something with popcorn in it as well once?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think so yeah <pause dur="long"/> Jelly Babies</u>
<u n="908" who="S0423">oh I I put Jelly Babies not jelly beans in it didn't I?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> same thing</u>
<u n="910" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/> are your feet? are your legs hurting?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna stretch them in seven minutes</u>
<u n="912" who="S0423">well <pause dur="short"/> don't know what's going on here</u>
<u n="913" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="914" who="S0423">oh there we are <pause dur="short"/> must be lights <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0421">oh <pause dur="short"/> they're pretty houses</u>
<u n="916" who="S0423">are they?</u>
<u n="917" who="S0421">like pretty little neat houses they look like doll houses</u>
<u n="918" who="S0423">is this the roundabout it was on about?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="920" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear>? didn't it say third exit?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0421">here</u>
<u n="922" who="S0423">there was no third exit <pause dur="short"/> can only go straight on</u>
<u n="923" who="S0421">well</u>
<u n="924" who="S0423"><unclear>lot of real trouble</unclear> these satnavs <unclear>aren't</unclear> they? oh here we are look what's this is it <anon type="place"/> resort</u>
<u n="925" who="S0421">is it? welcome to</u>
<u n="926" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> view</u>
<u n="927" who="S0421">coast of dreams <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="928" who="S0423">oh there's a fuel station down here</u>
<u n="929" who="S0421">ohh <pause dur="short"/> is it Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="930" who="S0423">no unfortunately it's gonna be quite dear here I think <pause dur="short"/> bP</u>
<u n="931" who="S0421"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0423">I don't think you'll get any cheap</u>
<u n="933" who="S0421">the Co-op</u>
<u n="934" who="S0423">er the could be <pause dur="short"/> possibly a</u>
<u n="935" who="S0421">but you</u>
<u n="936" who="S0423">supermarket in <anon type="place"/> couldn't there with cheap fuel?</u>
<u n="937" who="S0421">but supposedly <trunc>s</trunc> erm <pause dur="short"/> the fuel stations <pause dur="short"/> although they're more expensive they're supposed to provide you a better quality fuel than a supermarket</u>
<u n="938" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="939" who="S0421">cos the supermarkets they tend to be cheaper but</u>
<u n="940" who="S0423">I think I'll leave it for now we could get some tomorrow cos we're nearly there aren't we?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="942" who="S0423"><unclear>dunno what</unclear> this is</u>
<u n="943" who="S0421">is that dear?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0423">yeah it's a bit dearer but I don't think it's gonna be much cheaper than that anywhere</u>
<u n="945" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="946" who="S0423">can't really afford to be driving around tomorrow cos of what I've got left so <pause dur="short"/> I'll either come here or might have a quick look in the town see if we see anything but I can't imagine it's much cheaper than that anyway <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0421"><unclear>nets</unclear></u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="948" who="S0423">six hundred feet? thought you usually hear it in <unclear>few</unclear> metres</u>
<u n="949" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I know it's weird isn't it? <unclear>a hundred</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> feet?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> Beach <pause dur="short"/> <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> <pause dur="short"/> that sounds like is it? is it this one we turn right yeah? yeah that looks like <unclear>beach</unclear></u>
<u n="951" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> tourist park isn't it?</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="953" who="S0423">oh there's the sea</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="954" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="955" who="S0423">look at the house on the cliff there</u>
<u n="956" who="S0421">mm <unclear>ah lovely</unclear></u>
<u n="957" who="S0423">well we're not far from the Co-op fuel station <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="958" who="S0421">oh people on the beach at this hour</u>
<u n="959" who="S0423">it's only seven o'clock</u>
<u n="960" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="961" who="S0423">it feels really late</u>
<u n="962" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="963" who="S0423">do you think that's our bungalow on the hill?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0421">I don't think so <unclear>I think</unclear> our bungalow isn't here but <pause dur="short"/> we're in <unclear>the</unclear> caravan now</u>
<u n="965" who="S0423">oh look bowling <pause dur="short"/> ten pin bowling there</u>
<u n="966" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="967" who="S0423">oh we're in a caravan yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="968" who="S0421">I'll go for the bungalow later <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/> Inn</u>
<u n="969" who="S0423">that sounds good doesn't it?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="place"/> Beach</u>
<u n="971" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> Beach I thought you said <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> thought that <trunc>w</trunc> look at those waves wow</u>
<u n="972" who="S0421">where? I can't see</u>
<u n="973" who="S0423">crashing against the cliff</u>
<u n="974" who="S0421">oh wow</u>
<u n="975" who="S0423"><unclear>like Pacific ones</unclear></u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="976" who="S0423">oh <pause dur="short"/> where now?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0421">I think it means just keep going</u>
<u n="978" who="S0423" trans="overlap">will we miss it?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0421">no I think it just means keep going round the mountain</u>
<u n="980" who="S0423">no it said turn right</u>
<u n="981" who="S0421">yeah we did didn't we? oh no it's coming up</u>
<u n="982" who="S0423">is it? oh right here yeah there's a sign there isn't there?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0423">turn right onto <anon type="place"/> Road <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> that's it</u>
<u n="985" who="S0421">ohh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0423"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear><anon type="place"/> Hotel</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0421">why stay in a hotel when you can have a caravan?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0423">yes exactly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="989" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit more convenient though isn't it like? you get the kitchen</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
<u n="990" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="991" who="S0423">what's that?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0421">that's the sign that's our reaching our destination noise <pause dur="short"/> in ahead <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0423" trans="overlap">where's my phone?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0421">here</u>
<u n="995" who="S0423"><unclear>why have you got it</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="996" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think that's what it means <pause dur="short"/> it's coming up our destination</u>
<u n="997" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav talking"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
