<text id="S3AV">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:31</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0208</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>France</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Sport, uni, work, bands, translation, scientific methods</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting about general stuff</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0208">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0208">does it make sense to say eight percent dispersion of product X and product Y?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0202">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>wha</trunc>what is the context?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0208">erm it's in it's like science</u>
<u n="4" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0208">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s asked me to translate it for her so in French what she wants to say is basically like eight percent dispersion erm of a total mass in a solution so like liquid and solid it's like putting powder into liquid and then it turns like the mass</u>
<u n="6" who="S0202">dispersion yeah I think erm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0208">cos it sounds good to me like that's how I would've translated it it's like eight percent dispersion of product X in product Y</u>
<u n="8" who="S0202">dispersion yeah cos that dispersion means erm to move or mix doesn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0202">I'm just going to just google the definition and then I might be able to</u>
<u n="11" who="S0208">she's erm going to <anon type="place"/> for two weeks to do her trials so she's just translating all her documents</u>
<u n="12" who="S0202">the action and process of <trunc>distr</trunc>distributing things or people over a wide area erm state of being dispersed <trunc>phys</trunc> is she doing physics or statistics?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0208">physics</u>
<u n="14" who="S0202">the separation of white light into colours or of any radiation according to wavelength</u>
<u n="15" who="S0208">yeah so like the separation of things into something else? yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0202">yeah that sounds right yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0208" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah <foreign lang="fre">elle a dit</foreign> I love my brother but I'm not confident when it's about English <unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> eh his his strong subject is not English</u>
<u n="19" who="S0208">I'm just reading this really funny article that completely relates to me so it's erm twelve secrets skinny fat people have think of a twig rolled in gak but cute</u>
<u n="20" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0208">so basically skinny fat is a woefully under-representeted eh under-represented body type it describes a body that appears relatively slender but that is not toned and is in fact quite squishy and those of us that have this body type harvest several secrets number one we're totally aware that <trunc>when</trunc> that we look like a steamrolled <unclear>sharpe</unclear> the minute our clothes come off</u>
<u n="22" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0208" trans="overlap">let the rolls roll free so you don't have to tell us number two yes we're going to eat that and you don't have to ask us where we store it because we both know the answer everywhere</u>
<u n="24" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0208">three not all <trunc>rim</trunc> not all real women have curves some have a sort of amalgamation of angles and squishy bits four yes some of us are perfectly healthy because having a lot of chub doesn't necessarily mean a person is in poor health or doesn't get enough exercise some people build muscle mass easily some don't</u>
<u n="26" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0208">number five then again some of us aren't because ultimately being thin doesn't necessarily mean being mean someone is healthy number six some skinny people have double chins as well as a <vocal desc="nonsense"/> arms and melty buns isn't the human body a wondrous thing?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0208">seven and sometimes there's no avoiding a muffin top they're the new cronut</u>
<u n="30" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0208">eight good posture can do a lot it's like stretching out a roll of cookie dough <vocal desc="laugh"/> nine but hey not every thin person has a flat belly pot bellies are sexy <vocal desc="laugh"/> number ten we know very well which fabrics skim but don't cling eleven do not poke us we will deflate and then attack twelve sure you might say Olive Oyl is a bit of a skinny fat icon so shake the tops of your legs and embrace it <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos we don't have bums</u>
<u n="32" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0208">look at the photo</u>
<u n="34" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0202">look it's moving</u>
<u n="36" who="S0208">aw</u>
<u n="37" who="S0202">just don't think it can fly</u>
<u n="38" who="S0208">little thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0202">fly little one fly</u>
<u n="40" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I saw this video last night and it made me laugh so much <pause dur="short"/> when you feel a song</u>
<u n="41" who="S0202">oh I were watching this it were funny <vocal desc="laugh"/> he looks like a monkey doesn't he?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's the funniest thing ever <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0202">I think with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or whatever he however you pronounce it has worn off but I just don't think it has worn off properly yet</u>
<u n="44" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0202">maybe that's what it is</u>
<u n="46" who="S0208">aw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent me a message last night but I was already in bed saying hey is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> okay?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0202">aw I wish she'd stop calling me fucking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's doing my head in she refuses to call me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though cos she's got someone who's already called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in like as a friend it's like yeah but that doesn't mean you have to call me by by my Christian name she's like well I like it</u>
<u n="48" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I replied anyway</u>
<u n="49" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0208">oh <foreign lang="fre">delicieux</foreign> <unclear/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0202">you jealous of my T-shirt?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0208">I have a Paramore T-shirt</u>
<u n="53" who="S0202">did you get it from a concert though?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0208">nope <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got it for me cos I couldn't go to the concert with him</u>
<u n="55" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0208">cos erm what use what we use to do is like a dynamic duo</u>
<u n="57" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0208">erm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0202"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0208">yeah <trunc>be</trunc>before wait was it before or after before he moved out when I was still in like my emo phase</u>
<u n="61" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0208">erm I used to always get flights over to <anon type="place"/> like to go to concerts and stuff stay with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then he'd pick me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up and take us as our sort of chaperone sort of thing</u>
<u n="63" who="S0202" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0208">to the concerts and we went to Bullet for My Valentine</u>
<u n="65" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0208">that was awful because there was like no age restriction so like there were really really young kids there and that's how we were able to go cos we were still like obviously</u>
<u n="67" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0208">like thirteen and erm <vocal desc="cough"/> there was a massive mosh pit but like all of death it's called and I found it on Youtube from the exact concert that we were at and you can literally see the whole of the room part and there's just me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just standing there like run away</u>
<u n="69" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0208">he was like when the beat drops next time I want you all to crash into each other and everyone was like yeah so we were just standing on the edges watching everyone run and mosh into each other we were like I don't like this</u>
<u n="71" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0208">I want to go home</u>
<u n="73" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0208">and he took us to Linkin Park and Jay Z and Fall Out Boy and then he got me a ticket to go to Paramore but I couldn't go</u>
<u n="75" who="S0202">why couldn't you go?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0208">I think cos it was during my school period I had exams or something</u>
<u n="77" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0208">so my mam said no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0202">bitch</u>
<u n="80" who="S0208">so he gave his ticket to someone else</u>
<u n="81" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0208">and he fucking met Paramore there as well</u>
<u n="83" who="S0202">he met them?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0208">yeah at the time he was doing photography and stuff and he was like I think shadowing another photographer</u>
<u n="85" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0208">who was there so like they all got to go backstage and meet them and say hello</u>
<u n="87" who="S0202">oh my god</u>
<u n="88" who="S0208">I know I've never forgiven my mam for that was like one exam for that <unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0202">oh come on butterfly fly away see it moved its wings then I think it's broken that leg or something cos it's just dragging it</u>
<u n="90" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah it does seem to be dragging it's going to fall seems to like you though he's ah I'm happy here now</u>
<u n="91" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0208">aw he must be terrified he's probably like humans that saved me don't leave me</u>
<u n="93" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I picked him up off the floor this morning like I said</u>
<u n="94" who="S0208">aw</u>
<u n="95" who="S0202">I want to look at his wing it's really damaged but I don't know if it were like that before cos <trunc>spi</trunc> cos I don't think spider got hold of it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0208">well that wing there at the bottom's ripped and it's not on the other side</u>
<u n="97" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0208">and that's one's a bit ripped as well but like sometimes butterflies can be fine with a ripped wing</u>
<u n="99" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0208">like I've seen other ones with ripped wings flying around and stuff but maybe it touched a nerve or something</u>
<u n="101" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0208">I just don't understand the anatomy of butterflies</u>
<u n="103" who="S0202">they're so tiny aren't they? like can you imagine having like <trunc>th</trunc> <vocal desc="cough"/> like can you imagine how small the lungs are?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0202">so weird aren't they?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0208">mm are you going to give give <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a ring later?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0202">yeah I'm going to Facetime her later yeah <pause dur="short"/> like tonight or something <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0208">ah she said thanks for getting back to me anyway hun just let me know if she needs anything I'm glad you're with her</u>
<u n="109" who="S0202">ah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0208">and of course she's going to ring you later <pause dur="short"/> I can't get over how funny that video is though <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0208">I'm going to like make my own version oh I just put my hand back in a bogey I just wiped on a chair</u>
<u n="113" who="S0202">ah you're so attractive</u>
<u n="114" who="S0208">look <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0202" trans="overlap">er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> no vomit <pause dur="short"/> I think that she purged herself though <unclear/> the vomit</u>
<u n="117" who="S0202">yeah she probably felt sick that's probably why she did it long time for a wash</u>
<u n="118" who="S0208">I always thought that but it's because it's that kind of washing machine I don't know like it's she always does it on that one I've asked her about before but she always puts it on that cycle</u>
<u n="119" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I put them <pause dur="short"/> cos I always put mine on for an hour and then a spin cycle for ten minutes and that always washes mine cos my clothes never get dirty they just need freshening up</u>
<u n="120" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0202">bloody flies go away do you want a cigarette <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="122" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of humming"/>
<u n="123" who="S0202">have those flies actually got teeth then or what?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0208">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="125" who="S0202">how do they bite you?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0208">I don't know maybe with pincers</u>
<u n="127" who="S0202">oh yeah never thought of that</u>
<u n="128" who="S0208" trans="overlap">never looked into that</u>
<u n="129" who="S0202">Google solves all of life's questions</u>
<u n="130" who="S0208">mm I've got to google about the Union Jack as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> they bloody started at half five this morning them roosters</u>
<u n="132" who="S0208">yeah they do sometimes they start earlier so help you if you're awake <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> right it says it doesn't explain where the Jack came from though it says it's so cool because it combines the crosses of three countries under one sovereign the kingdoms of England Wales and Scotland and of Ireland but it doesn't say why it's called Jack</u>
<u n="133" who="S0202"><vocal desc="cough"/> don't know</u>
<u n="134" who="S0208"><unclear/> a look deeper research</u>
<u n="135" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh er the term Union Jack derives from the Jack flag</u>
<u n="136" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0202">but I don't really know what a Jack flag is <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's all together something</u>
<u n="138" who="S0208">mm it is commonly referred to as the Union Jack but Union Flag is actually the correct form as it only becomes a Jack when flown from the ship's Jack mast</u>
<u n="139" who="S0202">oh right well there you go then mystery solved</u>
<u n="140" who="S0208"><unclear/> Union Jack <unclear/> mystery solved</u>
<u n="141" who="S0202">thank you Google</u>
<u n="142" who="S0208">right what was the other mystery?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0202">I don't remember <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0208">no why you do this?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0202">what on earth are you doing? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0208"><event desc="sound of humming"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0202">so we're going to go into <anon type="place"/> get some shopping</u>
<u n="148" who="S0208">mm hm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0202">get some sunglasses</u>
<u n="150" who="S0208">mm hm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0202">and then what? come back and chill by the pool? do the <unclear/> in <anon type="place"/> tomorrow</u>
<u n="152" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm hm yeah dad said we didn't have to do it today</u>
<u n="153" who="S0202">cos if we do that tomorrow morning like get up at a similar time do it tomorrow morning and then we've got the rest of the day</u>
<u n="154" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0202">and your dad's still happy cos we done what he wanted us to do</u>
<u n="156" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0208">erm <unclear/> to the big supermarket in <anon type="place"/> first cos if I can get a pair of cheap sunglasses in there saves trekking into town cos I can get dry shampoo there</u>
<u n="158" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0208">so I'd rather just stay in one place if possible</u>
<u n="160" who="S0202">yeah er why don't you invest in a pair of Ray-Bans?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0208">I would but I'm perfectly happy like with some cheap stuff</u>
<u n="162" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0208">cos then at least I'll know that I don't have to worry about losing them or breaking or damaging them</u>
<u n="164" who="S0202" trans="overlap">worry about them mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0208">cos I don't really like having very expensive nice things cos I'm always scared I'm going to ruin them and then I end up not using them because I don't want to ruin them and that defeats the point of getting them</u>
<u n="166" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah well I've lost mine already or thought I'd lost them</u>
<u n="167" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0202">it's like I had <trunc>ca</trunc> when I went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0208">case in point <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0202">yeah when I had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>s when I went to <anon type="place"/> he dropped me off at the airport and he were like if you lose these or break these or damage them in any way you are going to replace them and the whole four days I was terrified of them like I would wear them cos they all they was all that I had but I was terrified of losing them or breaking them but as soon as I bought my own like that just went out the window just like ah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0202">they're mine you know? I was still gutted when I thought I'd lost them but then I thought well they're a pair of sunglasses like</u>
<u n="173" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0202">yeah I've spent a lot of money of them but it doesn't matter they're a pair of sunglasses you know it's not like it's a sentimental</u>
<u n="175" who="S0208">but that's what's I mean for me it's like there's no point in me investing so much because they are just a pair of sunglasses</u>
<u n="176" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0208">and I only use them in the summer</u>
<u n="178" who="S0202">mm I love my Ray-Bans though cos I don't often spend a lot of money on myself like clothes and stuff like that I'll go to Primark or New Look or somewhere cheap</u>
<u n="179" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0202">I never go to like Top Shop except for my jeans but I only buy a pair of jeans every six months so like I <trunc>don</trunc> I didn't mind spending and I'd spent so long saving that money to go to <anon type="place"/> with so I just thought well do you know what?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0202">fuck it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0208">fair enough that was part of your holiday money part of your treat</u>
<u n="184" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0208">cos at the moment I've managed to save up quite a bit this summer I don't know how some miracle erm but every penny of it now is I might go out for another meal or another few drinks when I say goodbye to my friends and stuff but I I don't want to spend any more than fifty euros now</u>
<u n="186" who="S0202">you might have to</u>
<u n="187" who="S0208">because that's going to be money I'm going to be living off once I pay my rent</u>
<u n="188" who="S0202">well I've got an idea obviously you've got your savings off your grandad which you don't want to dip into except for driving lessons and stuff like that</u>
<u n="189" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0202">erm obviously next summer you'll be doing internships won't you? so it might be worth using that money next summer because you'll not be able to work</u>
<u n="191" who="S0208" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0202">and I don't know if interns pay you</u>
<u n="193" who="S0208">I was thinking of using that money I'm going to look into that three-week <anon type="place"/> internship</u>
<u n="194" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0208">erm obviously if I can do that then I'm going to put my grandad's savings towards it</u>
<u n="196" who="S0202">mm hm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0208">because they say that like it's unpaid but it's three weeks so I just need three weeks' worth of living costs but they said that they put you up</u>
<u n="198" who="S0202">oh so you get your accommodation?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0208">yeah so it's just living fees like obviously food travel paying for flights there and back</u>
<u n="200" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0208">but obviously I mean if I do get onto the internship like now I can book the flights so far in advance that there won't be a problem</u>
<u n="202" who="S0202">yeah it depends on what date you go though <unclear/> cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> booked our flights in September for erm June and the day after if we'd have booked them the day after they'd added three hundred pound on to each flight so it it doesn't even matter how far in advance you book them really? it saves you a few hundred quid but it doesn't save you a lot cos it's</u>
<u n="203" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah well I'll have a look and then I was speaking to my dad and I asked him as a joke completely at first I was like when are you going to hook me up with an internship in your company? cos we were talking about I don't know if you were yeah I think you were there actually I don't know</u>
<u n="204" who="S0202">yeah I were there yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0208">just like just like the rich lifestyle and all that like I don't agree with any of the ethics of working there as an internship</u>
<u n="206" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no but you can work there for a few years make a lot of money and then leave</u>
<u n="207" who="S0208">exactly and then I can actually have money to go into the stuff that I want like if it's voluntary work obviously it's unpaid</u>
<u n="208" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0208">and as a complete joke he was <trunc>li</trunc> he was like oh do you mean in <anon type="place"/>? and I was like oh I was thinking <anon type="place"/> but <anon type="place"/> works and he was like okay I'll just give my friend a call</u>
<u n="210" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0208">and he literally said it like so matter of factly</u>
<u n="212" who="S0202">he said something about the UN as well</u>
<u n="213" who="S0208">and I was just like why why the fuck did you not tell me about this sooner? cos like I would have been there in a heartbeat</u>
<u n="214" who="S0202">I don't know if I could live in <anon type="place"/> I don't know maybe it was cos I were a tourist if I lived there it would probably be different</u>
<u n="215" who="S0208">I would love to live there</u>
<u n="216" who="S0202">but it were just so busy so so busy all the time every hour of the day</u>
<u n="217" who="S0208">I love that though I've always loved it every time I've been but I'd like to go back now that I'm that little bit older</u>
<u n="218" who="S0202">but I were living out of a suitcase and I were out from eight o'clock in the morning till eleven o'clock twelve o'clock at night so maybe that's why I didn't enjoy it as much as what I should have</u>
<u n="219" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0202">because we were doing we had four <trunc>d</trunc> five <trunc>da</trunc> we had five days to do everything so we were out from the crack of dawn till late at night and we were jet-lagged</u>
<u n="221" who="S0208">yeah that's what we were like when we were there</u>
<u n="222" who="S0202">so like I'm just thinking like maybe that's why I didn't enjoy it whereas if I had my own flat there or something like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah I think that's a thing as well cos you were staying in hotels weren't you?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0208">we were staying with our friends like in a flat like we got to see the actual like not the tourist part of it if you know what I mean? like we did tourist things obviously</u>
<u n="226" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0208">but yeah even if it was another three weeks that would be a six week thing over the summer and I would already have so much experience just from six weeks then if I did a three-month paid internship in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0208">cos to be honest I'd rather go somewhere else than <anon type="place"/> if possible or somewhere else than <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0202">yeah you definitely need to do an internship though or or and or a placement year</u>
<u n="231" who="S0208">a a well I'm hoping that I can do a placement in three months rather than a year</u>
<u n="232" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0208">erm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0202">you still going to think about that study abroad thing?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0208">erm I would like to but I didn't get the the grades that I needed in first year</u>
<u n="236" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like seriously enquire about that because I didn't get the grades</u>
<u n="237" who="S0208">well I'm going I'm going to in September I'm going to talk to them and just I'm going to ask what they recommend</u>
<u n="238" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0208">like whether I do a three-year <trunc>placemen</trunc> eh a three-month placement in industry like getting work experience whether that would be more beneficial for me than doing a year abroad studying</u>
<u n="240" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0208">because I don't particularly want to go away for a whole year</u>
<u n="242" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0208">and I think I'd benefit more from the situation if I was working rather than just studying</u>
<u n="244" who="S0202" trans="overlap">well an internship the placement year you do get paid for that</u>
<u n="245" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0202">yeah if you do a placement year you get paid for it</u>
<u n="247" who="S0208">well I'd much rather do that then</u>
<u n="248" who="S0202">so what you do is you do your first and your second year then you do a placement year then you come back and finish your final year in <trunc>se</trunc> in seventy percent of people who do an <trunc>in</trunc> seventy percent of people who've done an internship get a job after uni straight away like as soon as they leave</u>
<u n="249" who="S0208" trans="overlap">cos eh I was when that guy was staying in <anon type="place"/> erm the professor at <anon type="place"/> he was telling me all of the things that are available and he like when I said I was interested in NGOs and like voluntary work and stuff he said that <anon type="place"/> is like the booming economy for NGO work</u>
<u n="250" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0208">and it's like right on my doorstep</u>
<u n="252" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0208">and because I already have a little bit of Spanish but I also have the French and fluent in English he said that I would probably be right at the top of the list</u>
<u n="254" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0208">and I'm studying international relations I've sort of got everything going for me</u>
<u n="256" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0208">so I was thinking I'm going to apply for <anon type="place"/> I'm going to talk to my dad about <anon type="place"/> and then I'm going to talk to people at uni on whether or not I could do a three-month placement as part of my degree but in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0208">cos if I can do that as part of my course then I won't have to go to <anon type="place"/> in the summer</u>
<u n="260" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0208">but if it comes to it I can just do another placement during the summer cos we've got three months' worth of summer</u>
<u n="262" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah we've got more than that cos our exams finish my last exam was June second that was latest exam so you've got June July August September and then you come back to uni on the first of October</u>
<u n="263" who="S0208">yeah I mean my last exam was earlier than that as well</u>
<u n="264" who="S0202" trans="overlap">so you got like four months exactly</u>
<u n="265" who="S0208">it was the end of may</u>
<u n="266" who="S0202">so if you finished at the end of May you've got five months</u>
<u n="267" who="S0208">so the <anon type="place"/> one is three weeks in July</u>
<u n="268" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0208">I could do from I probably go in June to <anon type="place"/> if possible</u>
<u n="270" who="S0202">yeah go a bit earlier so it's cheaper</u>
<u n="271" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and then I could I could always do August in <anon type="place"/> if that's not an option on my course or something</u>
<u n="272" who="S0202">yeah oh did I tell you? Disney's booked</u>
<u n="273" who="S0208">yeah you told me</u>
<u n="274" who="S0202"><vocal desc="misc"/> going in the middle of the fucking summer holidays though cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mam is obviously a teacher well</u>
<u n="275" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's going to be a fucking nightmare</u>
<u n="276" who="S0202">I know but we're there for fourteen days <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="277" who="S0208">that's really good</u>
<u n="278" who="S0202">like we've got a <trunc>pa</trunc> Disney passes for the full fourteen days so we don't have to go to Disney every single day but like we've got fourteen days to do what we want basically so we can spend like a week in Disney then a week as a holiday or whatever</u>
<u n="279" who="S0208">yeah cos to be honest you'll probably get around everything it's going to be in the middle of summer holidays you probably won't but <pause dur="short"/> ah I remember my trip to Disneyland it was so special it's like one of my fondest memories</u>
<u n="280" who="S0202">yeah what in America you went?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0208">no <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0202"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0208">we erm it was my eighth birthday we were driving down cos like we did every year we always went down for two weeks like drove down from <anon type="place"/> to we'd usually stay in like the <anon type="place"/> area in the north of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0208">and this is the year that we decided to go to <anon type="place"/> so we actually drove through <anon type="place"/> for once and I was asleep and then I woke up and my sister was really trying to <unclear/> do you know where we are? I was sort of looking around and I was like no</u>
<u n="286" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0208">and my parents were like really? do you do you want to look out that that window so I looked out and I just saw the castle and I was like are we really here? is it real? is it real? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you've not just stuck a piece of paper out of the window have you?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0208" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <unclear/> like oh my god</u>
<u n="290" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0208">that's one of my fondest memories of my sister cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> never used to come on holiday with us and then when she found out we went to Disney <anon type="place"/> she was like <vocal desc="misc"/> typical teenager</u>
<u n="292" who="S0202">I have to meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did everything with me it was so sweet like she was so much older than me</u>
<u n="294" who="S0202">yeah but she it was because like she didn't have a relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0202">like because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s such a bitch basically</u>
<u n="297" who="S0208">but it was just it was so amazing and I remember I don't remember everything cos I was quite young but I remember what it looked like where we were staying I remember always listening to Avril Lavigne Let It Go eh Let Go</u>
<u n="298" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0208">that album like on my little Walkman I got for my birthday</u>
<u n="300" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0208">I was like oh my god this is amazing so me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would be sitting in bed listening to it like learning all the lyrics</u>
<u n="302" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0208">like yeah oh yes</u>
<u n="304" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0208">and I remember having a pizza in the shape of Mickey Mouse and thinking it was the best thing in the world I was like nothing will ever top this pizza</u>
<u n="306" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0208">then I found Domino's</u>
<u n="308" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0208">and I remember we went into a restaurant once and my mam and dad had arranged for Goofy and Minnie Mouse to come and sing Happy Birthday</u>
<u n="310" who="S0202">oh</u>
<u n="311" who="S0208">I still have a picture of me and my sister with Minnie Mouse somewhere</u>
<u n="312" who="S0202">oh so cute</u>
<u n="313" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so sweet</u>
<u n="314" who="S0202">I'm a bit gutted though cos like obviously this has happened with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and mam wanted to take us to Disney my mam wanted to be the one that took us so like she's got this with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then like</u>
<u n="315" who="S0208">well would there be any way? would it be at all possible for you to maybe arrange everyone pool some money together and your mam and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come with you</u>
<u n="316" who="S0202">I don't even know if he'll be alive when I go next year <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it sounds awful but I don't know</u>
<u n="317" who="S0208">or in any case your mam let her be a part of it</u>
<u n="318" who="S0202">I might have to talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s parents cos obviously it's their family holiday that they've invited me on</u>
<u n="319" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0202">but like <unclear/> circumstances like I'm sure</u>
<u n="321" who="S0208">that might be a nice thing to do</u>
<u n="322" who="S0202">but I might even just like I <trunc>so</trunc> er it sounds awful saying this but if and when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> dies I'm going to take her on holiday anyway as soon as all the funeral stuff is over I'm taking her on holiday like we're going to go on holiday somewhere just me and her</u>
<u n="323" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah that'll be really nice</u>
<u n="324" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like even if it means like we're going to fucking I don't know <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> for a week like just in a shitty apartment I just want to get her away you know?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0208" trans="overlap">well always welcome to be here even if I'm not here my parents will put you up and that's already rent that you don't have to worry about</u>
<u n="326" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah thank you yeah thank you I really appreciate that you my mam and your parents would get on like a house on fire</u>
<u n="327" who="S0208">they really would</u>
<u n="328" who="S0202" trans="overlap">they really would</u>
<u n="329" who="S0208">but to be honest that might be a really nice option to do</u>
<u n="330" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0208">cos <trunc>e</trunc> like even if I am still here like even if I'm still at uni and you're taking a week off or whatever my parents would still be more than happy to have you here</u>
<u n="332" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0208">and then if it's nice weather then you get all the stuff of the pool you're an hour away from mountains if it's the winter or even just to go sightseeing like it's so beautiful in the summer</u>
<u n="334" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0208">and an hour away from the seaside</u>
<u n="336" who="S0202">yeah cos I could rent a car or something? or borrow one of your mam's and dad's</u>
<u n="337" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah exactly and there's so much stuff you can do here like we're like forty-five minutes away from a canoeing and kayaking place you can do white-water rafting</u>
<u n="338" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0208">there's a place actually in <anon type="place"/> when you can like jump through the trees and there's a big lake with like a fake beach</u>
<u n="340" who="S0202">wow</u>
<u n="341" who="S0208">it's so sweet and there's a massive zip wire that goes across the lake and if you're big enough I've never been able to reach it but if you're tall enough you can slide backwards and put your hands through the water</u>
<u n="342" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0208">yeah I remember there was a bald guy that always used to be our instructor when we went cos like someone always comes up with you</u>
<u n="344" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0208">and erm he would he he's so tall that he would always go backwards and put his bald head through the water when he was zip wiring</u>
<u n="346" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0208">but it's so amazing there's loads of different things you can do like a blue one a green one a red one and then a black one it's like a black one is like a pass that gets you everywhere</u>
<u n="348" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0208">but there's like it's a bit harder</u>
<u n="350" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="351" who="S0208">but I always do everything when I'm there and your there for like a good maybe three hours but it's just so much fun</u>
<u n="352" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0208">we should actually go if you're up for before before we leave cos it's it just takes an afternoon</u>
<u n="354" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah I'll go yeah well I'm I'm still here I'm here for like a week I don't leave till next Wednesday</u>
<u n="355" who="S0208">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says that he's up for so we could go and take my parents as well</u>
<u n="356" who="S0202">yeah that'd be good</u>
<u n="357" who="S0208">well take my parents my mam I don't know cos she gets back on the twenty-first I think</u>
<u n="358" who="S0202">yeah <trunc>yo</trunc>you won't be able to go with your mam I won't be here</u>
<u n="359" who="S0208">well we could go with dad if he's happy to take an afternoon off we could suggest it to him or if not then we could just go as us</u>
<u n="360" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah us three go yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0208">although I could always ask if other people want to come take a few cars there some of my friends and then we can all go together and then go to the lake cos it's right next to it afterwards</u>
<u n="362" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0208">and then just spend the afternoon swimming there</u>
<u n="364" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0208">cos you can take little pedalos out as well</u>
<u n="366" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0208">yeah it's so sweet I can't believe it hadn't thought of it sooner</u>
<u n="368" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0208">oh really? <unclear/> says there's good inflatable stuff on the water they've branched out a bit</u>
<u n="370" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0208">I haven't been for years I think the last time I went was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think a few years ago</u>
<u n="372" who="S0202">erm what do you macall it? erm but yeah like I'm going to give them some money like to go on holiday together like if they want to go on holiday together I'm going to give them some money erm but like when it happens and like the funeral is over and done with I'm taking her on holidays I don't even care where it is I take her but I need to get her away do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0208" trans="overlap">that would be absolutely amazing yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0202">well</u>
<u n="375" who="S0208">you could look into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0202"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0208">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are going to start looking into it for next year cos we wanted to go this year but we've sort of left it too late</u>
<u n="378" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0208">but Thomas Cook do package deals I think it's three hundred and something pounds per person all inclusive</u>
<u n="380" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0208">so for a week and you get well all inclusive so you get your flights you get the hotel and you get two meals a day</u>
<u n="382" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0208">like breakfast and dinner</u>
<u n="384" who="S0202">that's not bad well erm obviously I don't know when it's going to happen hopefully not for a long time yet but erm I'm probably just going to get a late deal or if I if it's okay for me and my mam to come and stay here then we'll come here</u>
<u n="385" who="S0208" trans="overlap">obviously we'll we'll talk to my dad about it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0208">cos I mean it's still really early early days but I mean like I said they'll be more than happy and they'll get on so well with your mam</u>
<u n="388" who="S0202">yeah and your mam will have someone smaller than her so</u>
<u n="389" who="S0208">oh exactly she'll love it</u>
<u n="390" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0202">or the same size at least but yeah thank you for that it means a lot</u>
<u n="392" who="S0208" trans="overlap">obviously</u>
<u n="393" who="S0202">you going to stroke the cat? you're obsessed with those cats</u>
<u n="394" who="S0208">I know they're so cute</u>
<u n="395" who="S0202">you don't need it you'll want to cuddle it</u>
<u n="396" who="S0208"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0202">will you just translate to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that on that website that he's using the United Kingdom isn't an option like so UK is not an option so he needs to use like a different website or something that has that option or is it for his university? <unclear/> shower?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0208">yeah I will do <pause dur="short"/> aw my poor little cat <unclear/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
