<text id="S3CK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:34:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-06-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0416 S0417 S0418</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home Cork</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>To do list, arrangements during the week, birthday party arrangements, gymnastics show, anime and TV, geology and faults, learning Japanese online, making dinner, avocadoes, movies, kids at school being mean, plans for visiting London &amp; UK, @Bristol science centre, Ravioli,</topics>
		<activity>Discussion with ANON about what to do in the week while making dinner.</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0416">
				<exactage>12</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bristol, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0417">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>not currently working, caring for toddler</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>some French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0418">
				<exactage>2</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Cork, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig></lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English/Irish (only just talking)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>toddler</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0417">so you going to do up your list again for what you're what you're supposed to do every day? or just just have some kind of structure to your day? rather than nothing</u>
<u n="2" who="S0416">mm yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0417">what you going to start with?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0416">get dressed <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0417">have you brushed your teeth this morning?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0416">I have</u>
<u n="7" who="S0417">did you brush your teeth last night right before you went to bed?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0416">I did <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0417">oh okay <pause dur="long"/> so erm at some point you can go swimming maybe next week or something?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="11" who="S0417">or the week after <pause dur="short"/> I better check actually check how much that is</u>
<u n="12" who="S0416">also erm I'm going to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="13" who="S0417">stop banging the cupboards</u>
<u n="14" who="S0416">sorry I'm going to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum's phone number and then you can call eh at around eight and then you can talk about the party soon</u>
<u n="15" who="S0417">erm can I just send a text? cos I'm <unclear/> about when it is</u>
<u n="16" who="S0416">I guess you're going to be today</u>
<u n="17" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0416">tomorrow?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0417">no can well why do I need to chat?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0416">I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just said erm you can discuss things with my mum and then we can have it all sorted out</u>
<u n="21" who="S0417">okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0416">unless you don't want to</u>
<u n="23" who="S0417">well it's just we just need to tell people the times and see see their come</u>
<u n="24" who="S0416">okay <unclear/> can just say can my mum just text her?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0417">well if it's a <trunc>mo</trunc> she's got a mobile phone?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0417">yeah I'll just text her then <pause dur="short"/> you know you can't do it on a <unclear/> you can't do it on a Saturday the thirteenth because you're doing your performance thing your show with gymnastics?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0416">it's Friday I'm doing my performance</u>
<u n="29" who="S0417">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="30" who="S0416">it is</u>
<u n="31" who="S0417">no there's like different days let me have a look no yours is Saturday the thirteenth of June at three forty-five</u>
<u n="32" who="S0416">oh <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0417">well they've given me a ticket for display two on the Saturday</u>
<u n="34" who="S0416">okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0417">better double check that so I'm not turning up at some other person's thing</u>
<u n="36" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="37" who="S0417">so what have you been up to today?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0416">I've just been watching some <unclear>Naruto</unclear> really</u>
<u n="39" who="S0417">watching what?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0416"><unclear>Naruto</unclear></u>
<u n="41" who="S0417"><unclear>Naruto</unclear>?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0416"><unclear>Naruto</unclear></u>
<u n="43" who="S0417"><unclear>Naruto</unclear> what's Naruto?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0416">Naruto it's a Japanese anime an anime is like a carton in <trunc>jap</trunc> in Japanese style so they don't do as much of like real-life acting they do it in cartoons but it's not like a kids' cartoon it's like what I guess it's not like it's not like that thing where you're like running off a cliff and then you're still like running and then you only realise it and then you fall down do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0417">right hold on I've just got to get a form hold on <pause dur="long"/> I don't really get that worried <unclear/> running it off a cliff anyway</u>
<u n="46" who="S0416">because you know in cartoons?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0416">you know how they just make everything really silly usually?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0416">like in erm erm what's that one with the ostrich and it's just running and then there's like the wolf thing that tries to eat it?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0417">oh yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0416">yeah and then eventually a lot of the times he'll chase it and then he'll be in the edge of like in the air on a cliff and still be running and then only when he looks down he falls</u>
<u n="53" who="S0417">oh oh I see</u>
<u n="54" who="S0416">silly cartoon bit</u>
<u n="55" who="S0417">yeah but the yeah I think they're supposed to be quite good some of them but some of them aren't supposed to be pretty graphic and a little bit violent aren't they? the ones that I heard although some of them are good</u>
<u n="56" who="S0416" trans="overlap">it's possible that's like that's like just saying some TV shows are like that cos anime is anime is everything basically</u>
<u n="57" who="S0417">right I'm just checking that the ones you're watching aren't are they?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="59" who="S0417">yeah okay do you like kiwis?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0416">mm not really</u>
<u n="61" who="S0417">anyway what's it called? Naruto I'll look it up Naruto how do you <trunc>pr</trunc> say?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0416">N A R U T O</u>
<u n="63" who="S0417">U T O okay cool erm I mean do you think you're? some of cos I'll have to do a different date for your birthday party do you think you're? what about weekdays? or would it be harder for people to get there on weekdays?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0416">probably I'd say Sunday</u>
<u n="65" who="S0417">yeah no yeah Sunday's fine <pause dur="short"/> okay let's say Sunday then Sunday the fourteenth at two o'clock?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0417">and do you want to go and like you're going to see the San Andreas faults San Andreas yeah?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0416" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0417">I was telling you about that wasn't I? when we were talk we were doing revision in homework?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0416">oh yeah cool</u>
<u n="71" who="S0417" trans="overlap">do you remember? and I said does that? there's an actual fault</u>
<u n="72" who="S0416">mm mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0417">it's running through the city and then suddenly there's a film about it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0416" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0417">so what do you know of? what is a fault? tell me what you think it is</u>
<u n="76" who="S0416">erm a place where there's two two plates like that then they can collide they can collide or separate which would create a volcano a mountain <unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0417">do you know what makes them do that?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0416">plates? tectonic plates?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0417">yeah I mean well it's very hard to predict</u>
<u n="80" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> molten lava molten lava</u>
<u n="81" who="S0417">or you might see it in the film that why would they not predict that? why would it be commotion? cos cos around San San Francisco around there they're cos obviously it's very important for them to know when it's going to come <unclear/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0416" trans="overlap">because it's because they're <trunc>al</trunc> they always put strain on each other if they're goinna make an earthquake and eventually they snap but you never know when it is going to snap <pause dur="short"/> that's <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0417">yeah I can't really remember enough of the</u>
<u n="84" who="S0416" trans="overlap">mum do I have to learn Japanese at six PM? why can't I just do it different like at whatever time of the day?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0417">yeah you can I was just so as you don't forget but you've got to do everything by that time <pause dur="short"/> you could <unclear/> do something different another day so you could do learn Japanese Sundays and do something different the other days if you want? it's completely up to you</u>
<u n="86" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I just I wouldn't really learn much Japanese then</u>
<u n="87" who="S0417">well I mean what are you using to learn it?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0416">well I was using a really good program called Busuu</u>
<u n="89" who="S0417">mm mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0416">it's like you can learn languages but erm you need to upgrade to premium you need to upgrade to premium to go any further cos I've I've already done all the exercises <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> you need to upgrade to premium to continue</u>
<u n="91" who="S0417">mm how much is premium?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0416">it's like four euro a month <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0417">do you have to do it for like twelve months?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0416">mm?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0417">do you have to do it for twelve months?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0416">well <pause dur="short"/> there's a thing it's kind of like you can either just get it for one month and then it's like five euro something or if you do it for twelve months you have to get like you have to basically pay sixty-six euro something but that goes down to four euro a month</u>
<u n="97" who="S0417">yeah that's too much sixty-six I'm sure there's another way YouTube is usually very good do you want me to help? and find like a good thing on YouTube?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0416">no that's okay I can do it myself <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0417">maybe I'll just look it up about learning Japanese <pause dur="short"/> cos there's usually</u>
<u n="100" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I'm not going to move on to anything else yet cos I I barely know the basics</u>
<u n="101" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0416">I only know <unclear/> and that's just what's in here? and erm there's <unclear/> which is where are you from? and then you say <unclear/> I'm from whatever</u>
<u n="103" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0416">and I'm pretty sure there's still some more and yeah <unclear/> which is good morning and <unclear/> good evening</u>
<u n="105" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign> that's the only word I know</u>
<u n="106" who="S0416">that sounds a little bit more <trunc>jap</trunc> Chinese Japanese is a bit quicker</u>
<u n="107" who="S0417"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="108" who="S0416">yeah kind of <foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="109" who="S0417"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="110" who="S0416"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="111" who="S0417"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="112" who="S0416"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="113" who="S0417"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="114" who="S0416">and then there's some <unclear/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> is goodbye see you soon</u>
<u n="117" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0416"><unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0417" trans="overlap">is that <trunc>ri</trunc> is that goodbye?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0416">and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0416">which <trunc>me</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc>you don't say it you don't say it like <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0416">you say it more like <unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0416">no that's goodbye see you soon</u>
<u n="129" who="S0417">oh</u>
<u n="130" who="S0416">you've got to say goodbye see you soon there's a pause in it</u>
<u n="131" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> like <unclear/> kind of</u>
<u n="133" who="S0417"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="134" who="S0416"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="135" who="S0417"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign> is it <foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign>?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0416"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="137" who="S0417"><foreign lang="jpn">konichiwa</foreign></u>
<u n="138" who="S0416">and and <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0417">mm mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0416">what's your name? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0417">I'm doing some rice for you okay?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0416">okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0417">so what made you learn Japanese again? what's <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0416">erm I just really like Japanese culture I'd like to go to Japan Japan is very into games very into games</u>
<u n="145" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0416">they made some of my favourite games</u>
<u n="147" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0416">like they made</u>
<u n="149" who="S0417" trans="overlap">ah that's a shame</u>
<u n="150" who="S0416">what?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0417">it's like you buy an avocado and it's gone <unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0416">I can eat that</u>
<u n="153" who="S0417">that's from M and S as well</u>
<u n="154" who="S0416">I could have eaten that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0417">oh no you can't it's the same waste of money <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0416">surely you could go to M and S about that and you could just say</u>
<u n="157" who="S0417">when did we go? it was only oh Tuesday we should have just ate them Tuesday <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stop clicking that pen can you just write?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0416">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0417">so okay we'll do your thing on Sunday your birthday thing</u>
<u n="160" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="161" who="S0417">erm did you want to go and see erm <pause dur="short"/> er Spy?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0416">Spy?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0417">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0416">erm I don't know I'd have to look at the movies that are out really</u>
<u n="165" who="S0417">cos we could do that when we go on Friday after we go to <anon type="place"/> it's on at six thirty on Friday</u>
<u n="166" who="S0416">so we could go <trunc>to</trunc></u>
<u n="167" who="S0417" trans="overlap">it might be quite busy cos it's the first time out</u>
<u n="168" who="S0416">Spy</u>
<u n="169" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0416"><unclear/> do like it then yeah I'd love to go</u>
<u n="171" who="S0417">mm look it up then</u>
<u n="172" who="S0416">so is this for my birthday? or just for exams finishing?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0417">erm whichever you want really I don't know whether some of your friends would have seen it by the time you go I don't know maybe it's the one you want to see</u>
<u n="174" who="S0416">I don't know I'll have a look if it's a really</u>
<u n="175" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're just not writing</u>
<u n="176" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I am</u>
<u n="177" who="S0417">okay well I'm going to use this for a minute and I'll give it back to you</u>
<u n="178" who="S0416">I was just talking to you</u>
<u n="179" who="S0417">okay go on <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0416">well I've finished talking now</u>
<u n="181" who="S0417">you were talking about whether you should go to the cinema</u>
<u n="182" who="S0416" trans="overlap">oh well <trunc>i</trunc>if it if that's really good and there's nothing else that I really want to watch then I think I'll save that till my birthday cos wait are you saying that I can watch two movies? one after <anon type="place"/> and one at my birthday?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0417">erm yeah you could <pause dur="short"/> if there's enough so you better look at what's on look at the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> you can look that up can't you?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0416">yeah they probably would have seen it by the time of my birthday cos that's a week and two days</u>
<u n="185" who="S0417" trans="overlap">do you still need an Ipad charger?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0416">erm well I have an I have an Ipod charger that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gave me and it it works for the time being but I've had a couple of those leads before and they've all broken</u>
<u n="187" who="S0417">oh so it's working for the minute?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0416">yeah that's what I wanna get I want one of those stretchy flexible ones that are made up like nylon and they're actually quite cheap on Amazon</u>
<u n="189" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0416">they're like three or four euro</u>
<u n="191" who="S0417">yeah but there's postage so</u>
<u n="192" who="S0416" trans="overlap">they don't they don't</u>
<u n="193" who="S0417">no there's postage as well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we haven't got the money <unclear/> we can get them at the maybe the pound shop or something</u>
<u n="194" who="S0416">they won't have they won't have a good one at the pound shop</u>
<u n="195" who="S0417">maybe wait till your dad's</u>
<u n="196" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0416">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0417">so what else are you going to do today? it's Thursday you're not supposed to be around games you at all</u>
<u n="199" who="S0416" trans="overlap">yeah I haven't been on games <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0417">so you're just watching Japanese anime things then?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0416">yeah Naruto <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0417">oh Naruto <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0416" trans="overlap">Naruto</u>
<u n="204" who="S0417">okay <pause dur="short"/> you going to play with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a bit today as well? <pause dur="short"/> stop doing that with your</u>
<u n="205" who="S0416">sorry I didn't mean to</u>
<u n="206" who="S0417">just going to have to</u>
<u n="207" who="S0416">do what?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0417">electric shock your way out of that</u>
<u n="209" who="S0416">and that will do a lot more damage than those</u>
<u n="210" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I am joking</u>
<u n="211" who="S0416">okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0417"><unclear/> play with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0416">I will yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0417" trans="overlap">later when do you think you'll do that then? cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s doing football I think so he's not back till half seven so I've got him all day <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0416">play with him <pause dur="long"/> for how long?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0417">mm?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0416">for how long?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0417">for one hour maybe</u>
<u n="219" who="S0416">mm mm mm <pause dur="long"/> maybe</u>
<u n="220" who="S0417">there's a pen</u>
<u n="221" who="S0416">at six and if not six then then I guess six is the latest <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> unless you want me to do it later</u>
<u n="222" who="S0417">okay</u>
<u n="223" who="S0416">because</u>
<u n="224" who="S0417">six</u>
<u n="225" who="S0416">but <trunc>i</trunc>if I if I'm getting bored of Naruto <unclear/> kind of bored then I'll then I'll just kind of do it then</u>
<u n="226" who="S0417">okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0416"><unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0417" trans="overlap">but sometimes with these like internet TV things he might not want to just <unclear/> so you might have to come back again like when it's finished</u>
<u n="229" who="S0416">oh okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0417">I was going to cook some erm bacon bacon and rice</u>
<u n="231" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="232" who="S0417">I was going to have it with avocados shame <pause dur="short"/> or peas <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0416">oh well</u>
<u n="234" who="S0417">does that? would you eat that anyway if I'd?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0416">eh I would have have probably</u>
<u n="236" who="S0417">well I'll put the peas through the rice and then you can have the bacon next to it</u>
<u n="237" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0417">or or rashers as they say here</u>
<u n="239" who="S0416">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0417">do people erm talk about how you speak here? <unclear>things you say</unclear> or would you say that?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0416">yeah they mock me</u>
<u n="242" who="S0417">what do they mock?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0416">old news like around my accent</u>
<u n="244" who="S0417">what? a lot?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0416">pretty much yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0417">really?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0417">that's bad</u>
<u n="249" who="S0416">mm mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0417">what? like every day?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0416">most days</u>
<u n="252" who="S0417">who mocks you? not your friends surely</u>
<u n="253" who="S0416">no not really occasionally but that's just kind of like a funny kid just like just kidding but other people I just hate them but it's old news <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0417">well it's really not I mean don't your teachers <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0416" trans="overlap">they did it for my three years of primary school as well</u>
<u n="256" who="S0417">well I didn't think they did it much whenever anyone else asked you about it it was like well it wasn't much just every now and again</u>
<u n="257" who="S0416">the first year and a half they did a lot of the first half year this year they did it a lot just because they're new people</u>
<u n="258" who="S0417">mm <pause dur="short"/> they're not in lessons and things surely with all the teachers around?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0416">no not really just in yards just if they see me they'll just go alright in just like a really bad English accent <pause dur="short"/> and like with their friends and they just laugh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0417">have you told the teacher that? cos they shouldn't be doing that in the yard either</u>
<u n="262" who="S0416"><unclear/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0417">you okay? you bump your head? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0416">mm mm?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0417">have you told any of your teachers about that?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0416">mm no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0417">cos you know if somebody has like an Irish accent?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0418"><event desc="sound of screaming"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0417">hey <pause dur="short"/> you want more to eat <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0418"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0418"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0417">cos it's like racism really</u>
<u n="276" who="S0418"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0416"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah I'm not affected by it anymore doesn't matter just yeah doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0417">well I can still say something if you want me to</u>
<u n="279" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/> that'll probably make it worse to be honest it's not like I'm heavily affected by it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0417">mm it still shouldn't happen <unclear/> and it's the teachers' responsibility to have a place where that kind of thing doesn't go on <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0416">mm mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0416">it didn't happen as much in <anon type="place"/> for the last year and a half or like two and a half years or whatever because they did enforce a lot of no bullying like they always came in to talk about no bullying</u>
<u n="284" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0416">they don't really anymore <pause dur="short"/> well as much</u>
<u n="286" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah there's a bit more of a like ah kids get on with it attitude in secondary but I don't I don't know if it's always good cos I think you've still got to keep an eye on things and <unclear/> people go there to learn <pause dur="short"/> and if you're getting stick just for being a for learning then on something that you can't control then I do think <unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0416">mm mm <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0417">right so have you got everything down?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0417"><unclear/> mm yeah you just take me through it</u>
<u n="292" who="S0416">get dressed latest in bed twelve AM brush teeth open curtains eat my breakfast tidy my room</u>
<u n="293" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0416">and then after that game time five hours learn Japanese thirty minutes twenty minutes guitar one hour maths on a Monday snack and drink <unclear/> brush teeth and change into pyjamas at nine thirty PM read book for last thirty minutes at ten PM and then close the curtains and go to sleep <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0417">yeah <pause dur="long"/> erm there was something else I was going to talk to you about <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> so you know we're going to Scotland do you?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0416">kind of</u>
<u n="297" who="S0417">we're going to go to Scotland in summer <unclear/> spend about a week in <anon type="place"/> with granny</u>
<u n="298" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="299" who="S0417">bit of a shame really</u>
<u n="300" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="301" who="S0417">erm but we'll try and pack a lot in maybe do something nice with granny as well I'm going to take you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <anon type="place"/> for a day</u>
<u n="302" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="303" who="S0417">you've got to come visit a couple of my friends as well and my my maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="304" who="S0416">in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0416">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0417">mm?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0416">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0417">yeah and maybe and also definitely erm my cousin <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's had twin girls they're about one year's old now <unclear/> I haven't seen them yet so we're gonna go to see them</u>
<u n="310" who="S0416">how old are they?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0417">pardon?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0416">how old are they?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0417">sorry?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0416">how old are they?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0417">well about one I said</u>
<u n="316" who="S0416">one? oh okay</u>
<u n="317" who="S0417">they're quite sweet erm and they're <pause dur="short"/> but we can we can do something nice in between it it won't be like <unclear/> everything maybe we could go down and look at the battleship again HMS</u>
<u n="318" who="S0416" trans="overlap">can we go to the aquarium?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0417">er</u>
<u n="320" who="S0416">that was so cool</u>
<u n="321" who="S0417">maybe it's quite expensive the aquarium but</u>
<u n="322" who="S0416" trans="overlap">that's the coolest ever that part where you walked over the glass and the sharks were underneath that was pretty scary</u>
<u n="323" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0416">it was awesome as well</u>
<u n="325" who="S0417" trans="overlap">that's true</u>
<u n="326" who="S0416">and there was <unclear/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> cos it might be just this as like nice to just walk around all the shops or something look around</u>
<u n="328" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0417" trans="overlap">the science museum do you think you'd like that?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0416">I don't remember the science museum</u>
<u n="331" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> remember?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0416">no can you? what was in it?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0417">erm <pause dur="short"/> don't don't erm I'm not sure it was like a <trunc>spaces</trunc> there was a spaceship that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0416">oh that one and didn't one of your friends come?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0417">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her two boys</u>
<u n="336" who="S0416">yeah I remember getting ice cream there</u>
<u n="337" who="S0417">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0416">I don't really remember anything else though oh I do I do remember a bit yeah that was okay <unclear>that was okay</unclear></u>
<u n="339" who="S0417">yeah see that's free you see</u>
<u n="340" who="S0416" trans="overlap">somehow I don't think it was good as at <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="341" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0416">I think at at <anon type="place"/>'s more interactive I think you could press buttons in that that like</u>
<u n="343" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0416">things like at <anon type="place"/> you have to actually like go go in one of those hamster wheels there and it would power a whole little mechanism where there's water and it's carried out and it goes into a tube and then other people can like open like <trunc>li</trunc> mini lock gates and they can learn how locks work and all that stuff and you can do all kinds of stuff and you can see your body as a skeleton and you can move it around and you can like do like hypnotic tests where you get different images and things and there's a</u>
<u n="345" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it is good <unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0416">and there's a face that's like going in but it looks like it's going out</u>
<u n="347" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0416">which is cool</u>
<u n="349" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0416">and also there's there's a there's like these really cool things where you have like tennis racket things and you'd just like but they're made out of like soft stuff and you put them over these holes and it goes like do do do do do</u>
<u n="351" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0416">and there's you can build like cool houses out of life-size Lego bricks that are really big and</u>
<u n="353" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0416" trans="overlap">you can do TV like there's the TV thing</u>
<u n="355" who="S0417">mm mm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0416">I'm sure you know this but</u>
<u n="357" who="S0417">I haven't been there for ages</u>
<u n="358" who="S0416">and then it's like there's a green screen and you go up there and the green screen and you can get like one of those cameras and you can use that as a hand and there's like a big control panel where you can change what's on the green screen like you can have a massive spider or you can have a roller coaster so it looks like you're in a roller coaster and then you can like move the cameras around and you can do like news reports and you can do special effects so it can be like <vocal desc="misc"/> and then like have like a storm effect when it says there's a storm coming or something like that</u>
<u n="359" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0416">and also there's <trunc>pla</trunc></u>
<u n="361" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's quite good</u>
<u n="362" who="S0416">and there's a planetarium which is my favourite part</u>
<u n="363" who="S0417">what?  do you go in there?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0416">eh I've been in there a lot of times with my dad <pause dur="short"/> we don't go as much now because they literally have the show</u>
<u n="365" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/> hello</u>
<u n="366" who="S0417">yellow</u>
<u n="367" who="S0416">cos they literally have the same show every time I'm pretty sure</u>
<u n="368" who="S0418" trans="overlap">yell</u>
<u n="369" who="S0417">yell</u>
<u n="370" who="S0416">they basically just quiz you on a lot of things and then you've got to shout it out</u>
<u n="371" who="S0417">oh right</u>
<u n="372" who="S0416">I'm going to show you the different stuff</u>
<u n="373" who="S0417" trans="overlap">we've never been to the planetarium here have we? in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0416" trans="overlap">huh? there's a planetarium?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0416">ah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0417">I think so</u>
<u n="378" who="S0416">it's weird how I've been to the planetarium in <anon type="place"/> like five times even though they show the same thing</u>
<u n="379" who="S0417">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0416">you forget it every time <unclear/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0417" trans="overlap">so your dad is quite into astrology <trunc>as</trunc>astronomy for a while isn't he? it's kind of a mutual thing</u>
<u n="382" who="S0416">I think he's always been interested</u>
<u n="383" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0416">well</u>
<u n="385" who="S0417">do you go to the like <unclear/> bit of it?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh you mean the place where it's really <unclear>humid</unclear>?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0416">erm no we don't really go to that</u>
<u n="389" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0416">there's an aquarium in <anon type="place"/> that we still haven't been to I'd like to go there</u>
<u n="391" who="S0417">aquarium in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0417">where?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0416">it's quite new actually</u>
<u n="395" who="S0417">mm yeah I've never heard of it</u>
<u n="396" who="S0416">it's actually very very close to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0417">mm?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0416">no yeah it is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0417">mm mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0416">it's just like the other side of my dad's <unclear>boat</unclear></u>
<u n="401" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0417">mm mm it's good all that stuff because that there used to be nothing there just cinema and now they've really made all that whole area really good</u>
<u n="403" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0417">so I thought with the bacon</u>
<u n="405" who="S0416">well my dad's</u>
<u n="406" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> chop it up or you can have it with cheese if you want? <unclear/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0416" trans="overlap">oh I I don't want to chop it up sorry</u>
<u n="408" who="S0417">you don't want your bacon chopped up?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="410" who="S0417">okay</u>
<u n="411" who="S0416">cos it has like erm the word</u>
<u n="412" who="S0417">what? the fat bit?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0416">no it's like erm there's like a dish <unclear/> like <unclear/> or something</u>
<u n="414" who="S0417">sorry?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0416">or it's like it's called like <trunc>ravi</trunc> <trunc>ravi</trunc> yes</u>
<u n="416" who="S0417" trans="overlap">ravioli</u>
<u n="417" who="S0416">yeah something like that and it looks and tastes and smells disgusting in my opinion</u>
<u n="418" who="S0417">why is it like that? it's not anything like ravioli chopped up bacon</u>
<u n="419" who="S0416">but chopped up bacon peas and rice all in ravioli and then it's got a weird sauce <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0417">it's only just got <trunc>ba</trunc> Bolognese is supposed to be in ravioli</u>
<u n="421" who="S0416">I don't like it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0417" trans="overlap">what? you might have had a different kind of <trunc>ra</trunc>ravioli</u>
<u n="423" who="S0416">you <trunc>ga</trunc> you gave me some and it looked</u>
<u n="424" who="S0417">oh they're not they're not quite ravioli it's a</u>
<u n="425" who="S0416">you you you gave me</u>
<u n="426" who="S0417">they're tortellinis I think</u>
<u n="427" who="S0416">I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0417">which is a bit different</u>
<u n="429" who="S0416">and then it had like it had like bacon in it and then like it looked delicious but it tasted disgusting and I ate the whole thing and then afterwards I could like smell it on my own breath</u>
<u n="430" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's just a horrible story why did you eat it then?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I'm sorry because</u>
<u n="432" who="S0417">come on</u>
<u n="433" who="S0416">at the time it looked good and I thought it was good and I thought it's just weird that I'm not liking it I'll like it in a bit but I didn't <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0417">but you just ate it?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0417">I see <unclear/> I'm going to have <unclear/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0416">okay</u>
<u n="438" who="S0417">what are you going to have?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0416">mayonnaise</u>
<u n="440" who="S0417">okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0416">thank you very much <unclear/> there's only four people going to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s party actually</u>
<u n="442" who="S0417">there's only four people</u>
<u n="443" who="S0416">yeah cos a lot of the other people <unclear/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0417">I know and there might be not a lot of people going to yours either</u>
<u n="445" who="S0416">eh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0417">maybe you'd like have to ask for a contribution and then</u>
<u n="447" who="S0416">well yeah they're all paying for their own stuff</u>
<u n="448" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0416">if they're going to the party</u>
<u n="450" who="S0417">what's he doing in there? <pause dur="short"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
