<text id="S3GS">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:46</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0631 S0632 S0635</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living Room in a shared House in Finchley London; all speakers’ home.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Vegetarianism, synthetic/cultured meat/shmeat, vitamin tablets, animal cruelty, oppression, the environment, the cooking, hunting vs abattoirs, Curb Your Enthusiasm. </topics>
		<activity>Best friends and Housemates talking while eating dinner</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0631">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hereford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Pharmacy Dispenser</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0632">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kings Lynn, Norfolk, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Carer/ Freelance Illustrator and writer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0635">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Perth</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Non- regional - slight influence of American mother, lived in Cambridgeshire most of my life</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Illustrator and careworker</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0631">I'm very like well why why aren't we living in like communes and why aren't we just fending for ourselves? because we're all buggering up the world</u>
<u n="2" who="S0632">it does seem that way</u>
<u n="3" who="S0631" trans="overlap">it's too complex</u>
<u n="4" who="S0632">I mean for all the benefits of erm of erm <pause dur="short"/> the benefits of I guess medical science and society and living in cities and the kind of way that we've made our world suit us for all those benefits there are huge disadvantages and people feeling isolated and stressed out in their jobs and</u>
<u n="5" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0632">losing perspective of what life is really meant to be about</u>
<u n="7" who="S0631">and you know what you know like there's always the erm like they use in like science like animals and things and like making medicines and things my honest I don't I don't think there's an immediate need for all of those medicines if we were all not living in the lifestyles that we do</u>
<u n="8" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0631">like they're creating all these medicines for things that actually probably would be be prevented if it is wasn't for the world that we live in anyway</u>
<u n="10" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0631">erm <pause dur="short"/> for instance blood pressure medication</u>
<u n="13" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0635">there's various names for it cultured meat synthetic meat and shmeat</u>
<u n="15" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0631">I like shmeat</u>
<u n="17" who="S0632">schmeat</u>
<u n="18" who="S0635">schmeat</u>
<u n="19" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0635">and they've already made a burger by a Dutch team at the moment it's more expensive to make than conventionally produced meat but hopefully that will rebalance</u>
<u n="21" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0631">but then would the processes of making that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0635">apparently it's cultured never attached to a live animal</u>
<u n="24" who="S0631">okay but would there be someone who is kind of marginalising the processes like if they were gonna make that cheaper would then somebody a person</u>
<u n="25" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0631">be given unfair deal deals?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0635">erm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0632">as on not on the Wikipedia page <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0631">oh yeah yeah and are they gospel?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0635">but you take muscle cells and apply a protein that promotes tissue growth</u>
<u n="31" who="S0631">okay you could do that from injured animals to be fair</u>
<u n="32" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0635">erm it would be theoretically possible to or to continue producing meat indefinitely without introducing new cells from a living organism</u>
<u n="35" who="S0631">but if you think about it you know the human body if you hurt yourself your skin will reform over it and you can attach skin to skin and like</u>
<u n="36" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0631">you know you can move</u>
<u n="38" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0631">fat tissue around your body and stuff</u>
<u n="40" who="S0635">yeah a bit like a sour dough just rising constantly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0632">a bit like a yeast culture constantly growing</u>
<u n="43" who="S0631">what if it got out of hand? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0632">shit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was meant to be <unclear/> this weekend and it's just come out the door so</u>
<u n="46" who="S0631">it's like hacking a bit off and fry it hacking a bit off and fry it come on</u>
<u n="47" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0632">have a barbecue for discount price</u>
<u n="49" who="S0631" trans="overlap">everyone everywhere have a barbecue you can't stop it growing what if that happened?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0632">and then there's a meat monster and it becomes sentient and we can't kill it because it's sentient now</u>
<u n="51" who="S0631">but what if it suffocated you like you just you were in the building and it got it covered the doorway and it got so big and then you got?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0632">that would be awful</u>
<u n="53" who="S0631">see someone is always gonna be injured and someone is always gonna be</u>
<u n="54" who="S0632">basically we can't win</u>
<u n="55" who="S0635">but it's</u>
<u n="56" who="S0631">no</u>
<u n="57" who="S0635">true in anything we do like you just</u>
<u n="58" who="S0631" trans="overlap">you could get <unclear>someone</unclear></u>
<u n="59" who="S0635">you can hope to make things better but I don't think there'd ever be a way that we can all live without hurting each other or succeed without making someone else's</u>
<u n="60" who="S0631" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="61" who="S0635">life difficult</u>
<u n="62" who="S0631">wow</u>
<u n="63" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I think that's very hard and we should always work towards it</u>
<u n="64" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/> them <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> you'd never <unclear>consider like that it</unclear></u>
<u n="65" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I'm going to be like <trunc>d</trunc>devil's I always really wanna say avocado because that's what my mum says</u>
<u n="66" who="S0631">advocaat</u>
<u n="67" who="S0632">advocaat devil's advocaat to say oh you know no progress is made without marginalising or hurting something or someone but I know what you mean and we should always strive to not do that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I'm not saying it's good and we should strive not to do it but mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0631">oh yeah it's like every argument I have to have at uni is it always boils down to equality or something and I'm like yes</u>
<u n="71" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0631">but it doesn't mean that just because it's not achievable you shouldn't strive to it or do that</u>
<u n="73" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm yeah you should get as close as you can</u>
<u n="74" who="S0631" trans="overlap">you should get</u>
<u n="75" who="S0635">I feel like people give up and just do whatever</u>
<u n="76" who="S0631">yeah like like</u>
<u n="77" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's like oh we'll never get there so let's not try</u>
<u n="78" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0631">definitely</u>
<u n="81" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0631">and you should always attempt to understand more about what you're</u>
<u n="83" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="84" who="S0631">caring about and that's important</u>
<u n="85" who="S0632">that's true I do live in ignorance of a lot of things because to be honest the news stresses me out and I I go into a tailspin</u>
<u n="86" who="S0631">oh yeah the news is horrible</u>
<u n="87" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0631">erm but with like erm talking about schools and things is always the <trunc>e</trunc>equality opportunity</u>
<u n="89" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0631">debate and like that you can't cos you've got a classroom of thirty children say how do you give an actual equal education to those children? do you give them equal time? time how much time are you giving them?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0631">or do you go these are the the less erm able children and I'll give more time to them but then the children that are more able why are they not getting that?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0631">why are they not being excelled as much? you know and</u>
<u n="95" who="S0632" trans="overlap">aha</u>
<u n="96" who="S0631">it <trunc>co</trunc> it comes in swings and roundabouts kind of like you can never win so you have to just do what the best you can do is erm and that's</u>
<u n="97" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0631">just I've lost my thread of thought but like but by like erm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0632">there isn't a simple answer</u>
<u n="100" who="S0631" trans="overlap">but by thinking about it and conjuring up those ideas and you understand that situation more <pause dur="short"/> and that's how you can sort of strive</u>
<u n="101" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0631">to do the best by getting it by understanding it</u>
<u n="103" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0631">and that is how I feel about lots of things</u>
<u n="105" who="S0632">that makes sense</u>
<u n="106" who="S0635">is it kosher in vitro meat shmeat?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0632">shmeat</u>
<u n="108" who="S0635">and that's a good question</u>
<u n="109" who="S0631">how would it not be?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0632">or how could it be?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0635">some Muslim scholars have stated that in in vitro meat would be allowed by Islamic law if the original cells and growth media were halal</u>
<u n="112" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0635">fascinating</u>
<u n="114" who="S0632"><unclear>okay perhaps I'm thinking</unclear></u>
<u n="115" who="S0631" trans="overlap">then you get all of these people though that are like</u>
<u n="116" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh no all the all the</u>
<u n="117" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I'm not touching it cos it's halal</u>
<u n="118" who="S0632" trans="overlap">all the in vitro meat is halal <vocal desc="laugh"/> because it's made in the lab</u>
<u n="119" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but the best</u>
<u n="120" who="S0631" trans="overlap">because because like before er and no animal was killed it has to be alive</u>
<u n="121" who="S0635">that's</u>
<u n="122" who="S0632" trans="overlap">they kill them when they're alive</u>
<u n="123" who="S0635" trans="overlap">there was the best quote someone said on</u>
<u n="124" who="S0631" trans="overlap">was it Russell Brand?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0635">said it on Radio Four yeah or was it Russell Brand said it?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and he says the and he says</u>
<u n="127" who="S0632" trans="overlap">he did say that</u>
<u n="128" who="S0631" trans="overlap">he has a similar</u>
<u n="129" who="S0632">and it was quoted it was quoted from a newspaper that was like</u>
<u n="130" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0632">they they kill the animal they they like slit their</u>
<u n="132" who="S0631" trans="overlap">what do you want us to do give it <trunc>c</trunc>cuddle it to death <unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0635" trans="overlap">the animal is alive while it's killed yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah and it was something like they slit their throats while they're completely alive and it's like well yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0631">well yes you're <unclear/> to understand the concept of life and death here</u>
<u n="136" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0635">you can like stun them</u>
<u n="139" who="S0632" trans="overlap">if <unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0635">first but I think the stunning is as stressful as the killing thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah there's no evidence to say that stunning does anything</u>
<u n="142" who="S0631" trans="overlap">they're still alive and they will always come back around while they are bleeding to death</u>
<u n="143" who="S0632">I don't think being stunned is a nice experience to be honest</u>
<u n="144" who="S0631">no of course it's not and <trunc>h</trunc>how do you know that that doesn't actually still cause them pain? it just means they're more confused surely</u>
<u n="145" who="S0632">oh you electrocuted me in the head thanks thanks for that</u>
<u n="146" who="S0631">insult to injury yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0632">so someone was like I'm gonna kill you now do you wanna be electrocuted first or do you just want me to kill you?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0631">I'd just wanna be killed well it wouldn't make any difference</u>
<u n="149" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0631">cos if I was gonna get slaughtered and therefore essentially bleed to death I wouldn't want to come back around during it I I'd you might as well just do it and let's get get it done and I think hunted animals are killed straightaway aren't they generally?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0632">if you hunt</u>
<u n="152" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0632">something really well as in not with dogs to tear it apart</u>
<u n="154" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0632">you should shoot it in the head or the heart</u>
<u n="156" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah exactly so why are they not just doing that?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0635">it doesn't always work out though</u>
<u n="158" who="S0632">it doesn't always work out you sometimes shoot them in the wrong place but you aim</u>
<u n="159" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and then you have to spend days chasing after them to try and finish them off</u>
<u n="161" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that's horrible yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0635">before they went around with like an arrow in their back or something</u>
<u n="163" who="S0631"><unclear/> them then cos I I wouldn't be up to it I wouldn't do it right</u>
<u n="164" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0631">I'd be like <unclear>oh why get the</unclear></u>
<u n="166" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that's why I haven't shot anything</u>
<u n="167" who="S0631">no I wouldn't do it right</u>
<u n="168" who="S0632">cos that happened to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he shot a squirrel but he didn't do it right <pause dur="short"/> so they had to wait by the tree for hours my dad made him</u>
<u n="169" who="S0631">mm mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0632">he was like you have to finish that squirrel off he's like you gotta wait for it to come back out the tree so you can finish it</u>
<u n="171" who="S0631">mm mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0632">it's just horrible</u>
<u n="173" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I remember my dad erm when he used to fit phone lines and things and like he'd have to do a lot of outside like work to put the phone lines in through the ground and everything he accidentally dug through erm <pause dur="short"/> some rabbit a rabbit's nest</u>
<u n="174" who="S0635">oh</u>
<u n="175" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0631">and he had to end up finishing them all off like he brought home this bucket of rabbits to my mum going these er haven't got a mum any more you're their mum <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she was just like <pause dur="short"/> they're all gonna die if they haven't got a mum <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so but there there was one I think I think it was actually the mum I think he like really badly injured it it would you know?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0631">he had to literally just grab a spade for it like just to finish it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0631">I think it was that that had happened anyway he had to just do it <event desc="sound of hands slapping"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0632">horrid</u>
<u n="182" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0632">really horrid</u>
<u n="185" who="S0631">I don't like that kinda thing <pause dur="short"/> like erm I think I had to do it before me it was either me or I think it was in the garden I made dad do it you know when you find a bee and it's really hurt or something and it's just on the floor</u>
<u n="186" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0631">it's just not it's just dying?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0631">I've made <unclear>I've said to</unclear> dad just go and help me finish that <unclear>you know</unclear> just do it</u>
<u n="190" who="S0632">I didn't get that as much when I was little because I used to find birds that had flown into a window and like try and cuddle them back to life</u>
<u n="191" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh they never yeah we never done that they cos they're</u>
<u n="192" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0631">always just in shock they die of shock</u>
<u n="194" who="S0632">they don't shock and their little hearts are like</u>
<u n="195" who="S0631" trans="overlap">they're not in pain</u>
<u n="196" who="S0632">yeah and I've done that a couple of times and like I had like my so the cats are bought in</u>
<u n="197" who="S0631" trans="overlap">you always think that you can do it but you can't they will always die every bird</u>
<u n="198" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I was only little erm and <trunc>u</trunc> the cats used to bring in so much wildlife that I'd always</u>
<u n="199" who="S0631">yes</u>
<u n="200" who="S0632">try and make it better one time erm I there were the mouse was alive</u>
<u n="201" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0632">and then I just assumed it'd gone to sleep so I was keeping in my room under my play pram and I think I covered it in a little cloth until my parents noticed the smell</u>
<u n="203" who="S0631">oh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0632">and they came and they they discovered it and they were like what the hell is this?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear>it just stinks</unclear></u>
<u n="206" who="S0632">and I was like oh my mouse he's sleeping but he's gonna wake up at some point like I'm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0632">I'm looking after him and</u>
<u n="209" who="S0631"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0632">they were like this mouse has been dead for days you need to flush it down the loo <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I was like oh my god</u>
<u n="211" who="S0631" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="212" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0631"><unclear>dead stink's</unclear> so horrible isn't it?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like my first experience of something dying I didn't get that it had died at all <trunc>did</trunc>didn't even have the concept in my head that it had died</u>
<u n="215" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0632">I was like well it's asleep for some reason it won't wake up and I didn't notice the smell</u>
<u n="217" who="S0632" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0635" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0632">I know it's gross but little kids you know?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I I did I think I went back to find my goldfish</u>
<u n="222" who="S0632">my <trunc>m</trunc> I think my mum used to dig things back up in their garden</u>
<u n="223" who="S0635" trans="overlap">after they died <pause dur="short"/> <unclear><vocal desc="laugh"/></unclear></u>
<u n="224" who="S0632">the <trunc>n</trunc> the things got buried</u>
<u n="225" who="S0635">what? on purpose? or just <trunc>t</trunc>?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm to have a look</u>
<u n="227" who="S0635" trans="overlap">why? yeah I did that yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0632">see how it's getting on</u>
<u n="229" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0635">just for the fish though</u>
<u n="232" who="S0632">trying to think I'm sure it was my mum who said that and it would've been old guinea pigs and hamsters and things</u>
<u n="233" who="S0635">mm mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0632">or rabbits maybe</u>
<u n="235" who="S0635">ugh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0632">they didn't have pet rabbits they only ate rabbits so it could've been <pause dur="short"/> I dunno if they'd've just thrown the bones in the bin I'll ask nan tomorrow when she calls <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> do you like the wine? I do</u>
<u n="237" who="S0635">yes <pause dur="short"/> it is very good <unclear>I like this</unclear></u>
<u n="238" who="S0632"><unclear>numbing</unclear></u>
<u n="239" who="S0635">mm mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0632">and I really like the way you cooked the steaks that was like blackened on the outside but still pink in the middle</u>
<u n="241" who="S0635">mm well you need to make it very hot first and then you cook it <pause dur="short"/> on both sides but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0632">both sides oh</u>
<u n="243" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="244" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's where I've been going wrong</u>
<u n="245" who="S0635">and then you check it</u>
<u n="246" who="S0632">you check it?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0635">mm mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0632">how do you check it?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0635">with a slicey knife</u>
<u n="250" who="S0632">a slicey knife <pause dur="short"/> beautiful</u>
<u n="251" who="S0635">mm mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0632">so you're quite excited about the er prospect of lab meat aren't you?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0635">yes</u>
<u n="254" who="S0632">I can tell <pause dur="short"/> and you'd <trunc>d</trunc> you'd definitely eat it you'd be like there's no problem with this I'm not freaked out by it at all</u>
<u n="255" who="S0635">well yeah from what I was just reading it sounds</u>
<u n="256" who="S0632">it's no worse than my multivitamin</u>
<u n="257" who="S0635" trans="overlap">fine yeah they were saying someone was saying there was ethical concerns cos they had to use some sort of foetal fluid in producing the culture</u>
<u n="258" who="S0632">foetal fluid from what animal?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0635">a cow</u>
<u n="260" who="S0632">a cow?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0632">so they had to do something to</u>
<u n="263" who="S0635">er yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0632">a pregnant cow?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0635">they need like proteins and stuff I don't know</u>
<u n="266" who="S0632">foetal fluid?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0631" whoConfidence="low">what's this?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I mean I think the early stages of <pause dur="short"/> creating cultured meat will probably have to hurt some animals but it will be for eternal good</u>
<u n="270" who="S0631">it might be done from things that they've already harmed <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="271" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0631">they could do it from things they've already produced</u>
<u n="273" who="S0635">yeah you could probably get everything you need from that <pause dur="short"/> scrap there</u>
<u n="274" who="S0632" trans="overlap">apart from the foetal fluids that you just said</u>
<u n="275" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0631">fluids?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0632">foetal fluids apparently there's some concerns about ethics because</u>
<u n="278" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0632">of foetal fluid <vocal desc="laugh"/> basically</u>
<u n="280" who="S0631">in what respect? what way?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that that they need to use the foetal fluid of a cow in order to help create the cultures that you need</u>
<u n="282" who="S0631" trans="overlap">the foetal fluid?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0631">are you on about just like when it gives birth and all the?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like amniotic fluid?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0635" trans="overlap">no no no well I don't know if it if it it I I don't know</u>
<u n="287" who="S0631">cos if it's amniotic you can just wait for a cow to give birth and then just use it</u>
<u n="288" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like scoop it up</u>
<u n="289" who="S0631">just be there with a bucket</u>
<u n="290" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0635" trans="overlap">erm reactions of vegetarians vary some feel in vitro meat presented to the public was not vegetarian as foetal calf serum was used in the growth medium</u>
<u n="292" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0635">but it's very early days like I think we'll I think we'll get better</u>
<u n="294" who="S0631">will we get there though? or will someone else in a different generation get there?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0635">I don't know there's a company that wants to be selling it erm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0632" trans="overlap">will the <unclear><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s</unclear> eat lab meat and live on Mars</u>
<u n="297" who="S0635">within the next five years</u>
<u n="298" who="S0631">it's the word lab that makes me think there's something there's something funny there</u>
<u n="299" who="S0635">yeah we'd have to cast aside</u>
<u n="300" who="S0632">have they actually made any yet?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0635">yes</u>
<u n="302" who="S0631">are they running their machines with little mice on turntables?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0631">cos something goes</u>
<u n="306" who="S0632" trans="overlap">cos you're against it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah is yeah is there <trunc>some</trunc> you know there's gonna be something weird about it <pause dur="short"/> are they exploiting mice?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's always the mice they get terrible end of the deal</u>
<u n="309" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but like your carrots are probably exploited in some way</u>
<u n="310" who="S0631">who are they testing it on? who they who they're testing it on might be considered very unethical</u>
<u n="311" who="S0635">er what like who eats them?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0631">yeah who <trunc>d</trunc> cos they wouldn't be able to sell it without having like?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0632" trans="overlap">have you ever considered doing medical trials?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0632">I see the adverts on the tube sometimes and I'm like</u>
<u n="316" who="S0631">I wanna do Flucamp</u>
<u n="317" who="S0632">Flucamp yeah <unclear>I used to want</unclear> Flucamp</u>
<u n="318" who="S0631" trans="overlap">Flucamp you get four grand</u>
<u n="319" who="S0632">it's like yeah I'll I'll do Flucamp I'm I'm strong and young</u>
<u n="320" who="S0631" trans="overlap">all you have to do is being isolated for two <trunc>y</trunc> two weeks</u>
<u n="321" who="S0632" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0631">and not have had a flu jab and I haven't had one I got offered I get offered</u>
<u n="323" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no I've never had one</u>
<u n="324" who="S0631">I get offered them all the time I can get one for free and I'm just like no I can't be bothered</u>
<u n="325" who="S0632" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying he thought he might get a flu jab</u>
<u n="326" who="S0631">it's like a tenner</u>
<u n="327" who="S0632">and I was like yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0635">so do young people have a flu jab?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0632">well I was like it wasn't that</u>
<u n="330" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I could have one because I can get one for free</u>
<u n="331" who="S0632">just cos you can</u>
<u n="332" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0632">cos I associate it with like my grandparents who like</u>
<u n="334" who="S0631" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="335" who="S0632">are like yes get a flu jab because if you get the flu</u>
<u n="336" who="S0631" trans="overlap">if you've got certain criteria like being elderly or having certain medical conditions being pregnant like that kind of thing yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0632">get one definitely</u>
<u n="339" who="S0631">but I cos I've been offered one</u>
<u n="340" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0631">quite a lot but you know I'm being offered one because it's a target</u>
<u n="342" who="S0632">uhu</u>
<u n="343" who="S0631"><unclear>one extra</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear>one extra</unclear> <unclear/> was a target and I'm a bit like I've never had flu <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that makes you more susceptible to getting it again <unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no I don't know if I have</u>
<u n="347" who="S0635">how do you know if you have flu?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0631">because if a <trunc>f</trunc> er my mum describes it if you <trunc>ha</trunc> a fifty pound note was about to fly out your window you wouldn't stop it you wouldn't get out of the bed and stop it</u>
<u n="349" who="S0632" trans="overlap">a lot of people say I've had flu but they've had a cold</u>
<u n="350" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><unclear>don't think I've ever had that</unclear></u>
<u n="351" who="S0631">oh yeah they promote a cold is not flu</u>
<u n="352" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0635">oh okay mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0632">cos this is</u>
<u n="355" who="S0631" trans="overlap">a flu is you're like you're aching in your <trunc>bo</trunc> like you're just hurting you can't really move that well</u>
<u n="356" who="S0632">this is why I was saying earlier cos you were like I'm sick of feeling run down basically</u>
<u n="357" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I feel like people use the word flu er just like cos they feel like they have a cold</u>
<u n="358" who="S0631">yeah yeah people come into work all the time <trunc>sa</trunc></u>
<u n="359" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0631">I say what are your symptoms? and they say flu and I'm like you've not got flu cos you're out of bed</u>
<u n="361" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0632">like I know <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="364" who="S0631" trans="overlap">you've got yourself dressed and you've come to <unclear/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I don't think I have ever had flu I think I've had <trunc>foo</trunc>food poisoning once I was really really sick and it might've not been food poisoning but I was <trunc>c</trunc> almost delirious I didn't know where I was I was so hot and</u>
<u n="367" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah flu is just you're horrible in bed and you're just you're not <unclear/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I couldn't <pause dur="short"/> do anything yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah you're just completely kind of paralysed by it or</u>
<u n="370" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I my <trunc>paren</trunc> my mum was driving me cos we were at a friend's house and I got really I was fine in the morning and then all of a sudden I was freezing cold even though it was the middle of summer I got into bed</u>
<u n="371" who="S0631">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and just covered myself up mum came and found me and I was just like <trunc>sha</trunc> shivering and I had like a sweat</u>
<u n="373" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0632">so she was just like right I'm driving you to grandparents cos that's the nearest place</u>
<u n="375" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0632">that's like <trunc>n</trunc> like home and she was driving me and we went round a roundabout I was sick er I was like gonna be sick got the window about halfway down</u>
<u n="377" who="S0631" trans="overlap">how old were you?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0632">eleven</u>
<u n="379" who="S0631">okay</u>
<u n="380" who="S0632">er and I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> just sick out of the <trunc>w</trunc> car window all down the side of the car you know in the groove where the window comes out?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0631">oh were you on the inside?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0631">oh the outside would've been brilliant</u>
<u n="384" who="S0632">well it was erm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0631"><unclear/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was a bit of both to be honest</u>
<u n="387" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear>on a</unclear> catherine wheel</u>
<u n="388" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0632">and my mum always makes a joke about like oh that motorcyclist wasn't very happy</u>
<u n="390" who="S0631" trans="overlap">of sick</u>
<u n="391" who="S0632">and I was like was there a motorcyclist <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I know there wasn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> but erm I was half and half I like got it like half down I was kinda sick over the window</u>
<u n="392" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0632">so er it was some on the outside there was some on the inside there was some in the actual groove of the window</u>
<u n="394" who="S0631" trans="overlap">ah but if you need to be sick you need to be sick you can't always choose your places <unclear/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that's the only party of the journey I remember and it was like a like an hour and a half journey and I don't remember anything else I was just</u>
<u n="396" who="S0631">too knocked out <unclear/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I was completely so that might've been flu cos I never went to the doctor about it and my <trunc>m</trunc>my mum got sick like a day or two after but we were already at nan and grandad's so they looked after us</u>
<u n="398" who="S0631">mm could've been <pause dur="short"/> anything <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="399" who="S0632">could've been anything yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0631">could've just been <unclear>repeatedly</unclear> taken cos I've been a bit like that when I've had sort of like tonsillitis and I've been like very very very <trunc>dr</trunc> not being sick but very very drowsy and just not myself and like literally just sit</u>
<u n="401" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0631">just like that</u>
<u n="403" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0631">not being able and just <pause dur="short"/> zoning out all the time</u>
<u n="405" who="S0632">yeah I've had that tonsillitis as an adult and it wasn't pleasant but it wasn't it wasn't as horrible as I thought it was but I was told that I had a very minor case of tonsillitis like about as minor as you can get</u>
<u n="406" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0632">and still have tonsillitis</u>
<u n="408" who="S0631">I er I've had it and it's not it won't've been the worst tonsillitis <unclear>I just couldn't get it either</unclear> but I've had it and it just feels like you're swallowing like a golf ball or something</u>
<u n="409" who="S0632">yeah I remember it being horrible to swallow things and just being the <trunc>s</trunc> it was just like a particularly bad sore throat it was like</u>
<u n="410" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0632">it's a sore throat but it's worse than usual and I feel more unwell than usual like I feel really woozy and hot and</u>
<u n="412" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0632">just like rubbish and I went back to work and I couldn't really concentrate on anything and all the telephones ringing were like</u>
<u n="414" who="S0631" whoConfidence="low">ah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0632">in my head</u>
<u n="416" who="S0631">mm yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0632">so that was that was <trunc>h</trunc> like really really unpleasant but <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> not not unbearable <pause dur="short"/> not the worst <pause dur="long"/> you haven't had tonsillitis have you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0635">mm maybe</u>
<u n="419" who="S0632">maybe?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0635">dunno</u>
<u n="421" who="S0632">might've? but have you <trunc>a</trunc> had flu do you think?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0635">er probably not</u>
<u n="423" who="S0631">I haven't had it definitely <unclear>anyway</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> that's the only way I could get mum to describe it to me <unclear>once she says</unclear> you feel it's a wad of cash or something about to fly out of your window you wouldn't bother getting it you wouldn't bother stopping it if it goes out of the window you'd just let it go</u>
<u n="424" who="S0632" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0631">apparently</u>
<u n="426" who="S0632">I think my dad had flu when he was in London and he was living in that bedsit and he said that heater saved his life that little</u>
<u n="427" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0632"><trunc>con</trunc>convection heater <pause dur="short"/> I think that was flu</u>
<u n="429" who="S0631">do you remember when <trunc>Tami</trunc> like erm bird flu came out and everyone suddenly thought they had it?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and it's one it was one flu yeah bird flu</u>
<u n="432" who="S0632">bird flu yeah cos there was swine flu as well wasn't there? but</u>
<u n="433" who="S0631">no might've been I'm I'm trying to think of the actual specific cos er no might've been <trunc>swi</trunc> no it was swine flu actually that one when that one was out <pause dur="short"/> so obviously everyone goes a bit frantic and they all think they've got it for some reason don't they? a lot of them think they</u>
<u n="434" who="S0632" trans="overlap">some reason everyone's got it yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0631">think they've got swine flu erm and so obviously when I was in working in <anon type="place"/> so you have to put like a proper sign on your door saying if you've got if you think you've got the symptoms of swine flu don't come in <pause dur="short"/> erm ring like call the NHS Direct <unclear>or the</unclear></u>
<u n="436" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah I remember seeing those around</u>
<u n="437" who="S0631">but erm my nan walked past it and she felt discriminated against she didn't bloody have it</u>
<u n="438" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0631">she said I've been discriminated by Boots against <unclear>that</unclear> <unclear/> cos of my swine flu what?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0631" trans="overlap">my my nan loves an ailment</u>
<u n="442" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0631">she loves it she <trunc>real</trunc> she's attention seeking</u>
<u n="444" who="S0632" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0631">she's not a nice woman <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's that's the store I work in and she feels discriminated against because we've said</u>
<u n="446" who="S0632"><trunc>i</trunc> don't come in and infect everyone please</u>
<u n="447" who="S0631">yeah but bizarrely we had <trunc>p</trunc> we had to stock Tamiflu how are they gonna come and get it? <trunc>fr</trunc>from a distance?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0631">I mean</u>
<u n="450" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> bring it to you on my break</u>
<u n="451" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0632"><vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah that's weird</u>
<u n="453" who="S0631">I <unclear>want to do it now permanently now</unclear> it doesn't hurt any more well it's just a little bit achy but not like you know when it felt bruised?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0631">now it just feels like it's just healing now</u>
<u n="456" who="S0632">yeah I'm getting more a</u>
<u n="457" who="S0631">it's gone more normal</u>
<u n="458" who="S0632">I feel like a get more kinda scabby bits than I used to</u>
<u n="459" who="S0631">that's just the <unclear/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0632">but it doesn't hurt as much</u>
<u n="461" who="S0631">I'm always doing this trying to fiddle round the inside of the <pause dur="short"/> piercing <unclear><trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="462" who="S0632" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>what is it there?</unclear></u>
<u n="463" who="S0631"><unclear/> don't wanna look looks like I'm really like <trunc>do</trunc> being gross but I'm just not</u>
<u n="464" who="S0632">yeah I know and <trunc>a</trunc> it's worse with my nose when I'm like is it straight? is it straight?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0631"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0632">I'm sticking my fingers up there</u>
<u n="467" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I'm gonna get this bit ear done on this ear I've gone like you now I'm gonna get wanna get</u>
<u n="468" who="S0632" trans="overlap">he he</u>
<u n="469" who="S0631">get collection right I'm gonna get er so there there and there</u>
<u n="470" who="S0632">nice little triangle</u>
<u n="471" who="S0631">and then cos but this is what I'm confused about cos I wanna get a forward helix but would I get one there and one there? <pause dur="short"/> will that look too much? I think that'll look too much</u>
<u n="472" who="S0632">you could get away with it but yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0631">but then I thought maybe I'll stick it on the other ear but then does that make it look lopsided?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0632">no no <pause dur="short"/> doesn't make it look lopsided</u>
<u n="475" who="S0631">I suppose if this one had a ring anyway</u>
<u n="476" who="S0632">and you can very rarely see both ears at the same time</u>
<u n="477" who="S0631">that's true</u>
<u n="478" who="S0632" trans="overlap">you even like face on you can't really</u>
<u n="479" who="S0631">yeah that is true</u>
<u n="480" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like I can't see my <unclear>days</unclear> at all <pause dur="short"/> face on I have to go like that</u>
<u n="481" who="S0631">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose if this one had a ring though and this one had a <trunc>s</trunc> like a bar or something</u>
<u n="482" who="S0632">it'd look different and <trunc>i</trunc> I like it I like er multiple ear piercings <pause dur="short"/> a lot</u>
<u n="483" who="S0631">me too</u>
<u n="484" who="S0632">and I'm looking forward to changing the jewellery <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure if I'll do it before Seychelles in November I might do it for like Christmas but get like</u>
<u n="485" who="S0631"><unclear>both both</unclear> change of jewellery <vocal desc="laugh"/> I might do that for Christmas</u>
<u n="486" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll change it change that before Seychelles god I wanna change that before the summer especially this this can go in a couple of weeks erm conch and rook</u>
<u n="487" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>now</unclear></u>
<u n="488" who="S0632">on this side</u>
<u n="489" who="S0631">oh no get em done whenever you want <unclear/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I know it does still hurt a little bit to <trunc>slee</trunc> I sometimes sleep on this side</u>
<u n="491" who="S0631">oh I didn't even have the problem from day one</u>
<u n="492" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and it aches a little bit and I have to change</u>
<u n="493" who="S0631" trans="overlap">just slept with it straight away</u>
<u n="494" who="S0632">so I don't know if they'll do it <trunc>m</trunc> for me in cold steel if I'm like I've only these piercings are only this old if they'll even do it for me do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0631">yeah they will</u>
<u n="496" who="S0632">do you think they will?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0631">yeah course they will</u>
<u n="498" who="S0632">cos they'll be like but we know that you've only just had those done</u>
<u n="499" who="S0631">so? they know you said <unclear/> if you have you'll just be lying on your back for a bit they just did they just stopped you having it done for your own convenience really if you're feel like that is happy to lie on you're happy to lie on it</u>
<u n="500" who="S0632">once I'm happy to lie on this side then I'll go and get the other ones done but I want to be able to change the jewellery before the wedding in the summer or before Seychelles so either get it pierced after the wedding in the summer erm at the point where I could change the jewellery before Seychelles does that make sense?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0632">so that's I could have?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0631" trans="overlap">when's your wedding in the summer?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0632">July</u>
<u n="505" who="S0631">so you're gonna get those done <pause dur="short"/> ah <trunc>J</trunc> like from July just after really</u>
<u n="506" who="S0632">I could I could get it done like when it we get back</u>
<u n="507" who="S0631">or can you get it done now <pause dur="short"/> and then change it before you go?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0632">I could maybe get</u>
<u n="509" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah do it now get it done now</u>
<u n="510" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I could maybe get it done in a month</u>
<u n="511" who="S0631">yeah do it now I'll go with you I'll get some stuff done I'll get one the other one here</u>
<u n="512" who="S0632">and that'll be like but it's on either side</u>
<u n="513" who="S0631">no I'll be dangerous cos I don't really care</u>
<u n="514" who="S0632"><unclear>you don't think</unclear></u>
<u n="515" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I'll sleep on a rubber ring <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0632">sleep on a rubber ring around your ear</u>
<u n="517" who="S0631"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0631">a little doughnut under <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0631">mm that'd be quite <trunc>c</trunc> that'd be nice wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0632">that would be I've kind of ended up doing</u>
<u n="523" who="S0631" trans="overlap">let's invent now</u>
<u n="524" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I've done that a bit actually I've slept like that</u>
<u n="525" who="S0631" trans="overlap">the doughnut the the piercing doughnut</u>
<u n="526" who="S0632" trans="overlap">the piercing doughnut doughnut</u>
<u n="527" who="S0631">then you could like</u>
<u n="528" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's out there</u>
<u n="529" who="S0631">put put it on your tummy so if you wanna lie on your tummy if you've got a belly button piercing or</u>
<u n="530" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0631" trans="overlap">or whatever anything you know</u>
<u n="532" who="S0632">any any kind of piercing <pause dur="long"/> do you wanna top up of wine?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0635">yes thank you</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
