<text id="S3JF">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:58:45</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0190 S0192 S0227</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In Dad andANON's kitchen, Rushden</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Family, health, phone calls, cooking, flights, weather, hospital, freelancing, taxes, recording, phonology, dialect, friends, extended family, grandchildren, moving house, laptops, children, board game, forms, memory, South Korea, renting an apartment, navigating, family and friends visiting, traffic, university, losing weight, TV, accent, work, Aaron, telepathy &amp; sign language, utilities, winter, plants, whisky</topics>
		<activity>Dinner with Dad &amp; Ann</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, inviting, anecdote telling, making arrangements, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0190">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>St Neots. Cambs.</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>55</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Activity co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0227">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crayford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>customer services agent</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Spanish -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0227">sorry</u>
<u n="2" who="S0190">keep that quiet</u>
<u n="3" who="S0227">alright</u>
<u n="4" who="S0190">hence I didn't say anything about any else either</u>
<u n="5" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0190">and that so I thought oh she's eighty now it was her eightieth birthday?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0227">er no she's older than that she's born the same she was born in thirty-two so</u>
<u n="8" who="S0190">well she told me she was eighty so I wasn't going to turn and say no you're not Mike says you're not</u>
<u n="9" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no she's not she's lying about she's lying about her age</u>
<u n="10" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0227">she the same age as my dad so she's probably be eighty-two</u>
<u n="12" who="S0190">well she said she was eighty</u>
<u n="13" who="S0227">she <trunc>wa</trunc> she was born in thirty-two I'm sure she was</u>
<u n="14" who="S0192">thirty-two</u>
<u n="15" who="S0190">no <unclear/> with that stuff please?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0192">it sounds a while ago now doesn't it? nineteen thirty-two</u>
<u n="18" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it does yeah thirty-two it does</u>
<u n="19" who="S0192">phenomenal</u>
<u n="20" who="S0190">remember last night he had to like this <trunc>we</trunc> mince is <trunc>ve</trunc> it's got its own fat in it you don't really need it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0227" trans="overlap">has it got its own fat on? alright okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0190">so last time I had to scoop it all off cos it was so oily</u>
<u n="23" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've pressed the button on this do you mind if I turn that down a tiny bit</u>
<u n="24" who="S0190">oh sorry no turn it off</u>
<u n="25" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no I'll do it I'll do it is that alright I'll just turn it down a little bit</u>
<u n="26" who="S0190"><unclear/> is it oh god</u>
<u n="27" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0190">doesn't matter</u>
<u n="29" who="S0227">oh does it not work very well on that one</u>
<u n="30" who="S0190">no you have to keep to just keep it <unclear>secure</unclear></u>
<u n="31" who="S0227">oh there you go</u>
<u n="32" who="S0190">yeah you have to keep going keep pressing it</u>
<u n="33" who="S0192">pile of rubbish <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0227">I'm getting there</u>
<u n="35" who="S0190">just turn it off if you don't want it on</u>
<u n="36" who="S0192">no no no I'll keep it on I just wanted to turn it down a little bit for the recording so that's Neighbours isn't it? from a long time ago</u>
<u n="37" who="S0190">I don't know cos I was talking to your dad and I went off</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192">there you go that's a bit better so how have you been feeling? <unclear/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0190">erm pretty good thanks I've had a couple of ups and downs sometimes my eyes don't feel as if they're</u>
<u n="40" who="S0227">ooh that's fine</u>
<u n="41" who="S0190">lining up and that sounds really silly but they're as if they don't work together</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="43" who="S0190">so and it makes me lose my balance a little bit</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">okay I understand</u>
<u n="45" who="S0190">apart from that it <trunc>g</trunc>good</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192">that's good</u>
<u n="47" who="S0190">it is good</u>
<u n="48" who="S0192">you're looking really good yeah I'm so pleased</u>
<u n="49" who="S0190">I'm not looking all that good I absolutely hate <unclear/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah you are I'm liking the shock of white hair</u>
<u n="51" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0227">when I read it when she had it it said that erm radiation on the head I mean you see it in films when they've been bombarded with radiation there's two things you <trunc>s</trunc> you that <trunc>phy</trunc> that physically they present one is they're sick</u>
<u n="53" who="S0190">that's what your dad said</u>
<u n="54" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0227">and then they go <unclear>for a graft</unclear> <unclear/> hair and a load of hair comes out</u>
<u n="56" who="S0190">I wasn't sick one once from the radiation</u>
<u n="57" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no but I'm saying I'm saying like radiation poison poisoning so</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192" trans="overlap">were you not?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0227">radiation to your head is going to affect your hair</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0227">so erm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192">but it's all coming back it's just changed colour</u>
<u n="63" who="S0227">yes but it said yeah it lasted but it said that um there's a possibility that if you have it on your head your hair won't come back rather than if you <unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no no of course do you still wear a wig from time to time?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0190">I I do occasionally but the only trouble is</u>
<u n="66" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0190">it's been too hot for starters</u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0190">and it really makes it like as if you've got an wooly hat on</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0190">and my hairdresser said that if because it you sort of like this because it's it's hot erm it will rub the hair cos you'll <trunc>be</trunc></u>
<u n="72" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0190">because you've got so much hair now there's not really room for hair plus you know I know they wear them in in theatre you have the bonnets don't you? they pull on really tight and then you put your wig over the top but because it's rubbing my hair she said it's gonna you'll lose it faster than it grows</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">yeah yeah I know</u>
<u n="75" who="S0190">so I I just tend to</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192">it looks good to me just changed colour</u>
<u n="77" who="S0227">the thing</u>
<u n="78" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0227">the hormones she's on femara also a side effect of it is thinning hair so you know of</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0190">I'm fighting against everything</u>
<u n="82" who="S0227">you're kind of fighting that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0190">we'll get there</u>
<u n="84" who="S0227">now what's this called?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0192">did you say your printer doesn't work at all?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0227">yeah the printer works</u>
<u n="87" who="S0192">if I could print a bank statement out I'll bring it to the bank and</u>
<u n="88" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah the printer works it's just the scanner's not working any more the scan we we'll scan it's the it's a software problem not a hardware problem</u>
<u n="89" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah cool</u>
<u n="90" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0192">I just need to print off one thing or with the student loans now dad I've given them my Brighton address so hopefully they'll stop hassling you after that</u>
<u n="92" who="S0227">so yeah well it's never really been a hassle</u>
<u n="93" who="S0192">yeah I've wondered if you've got random phone calls about me</u>
<u n="94" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="95" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="96" who="S0192">random calls cos you haven't? that's amazing because the amount of time I've put your number down cos so many things require a number and I the only number I have in the UK I've given yours but I've worried that maybe you've had random phone calls from people or</u>
<u n="97" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no no no no only erm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0190">they never once asked for you</u>
<u n="99" who="S0227">here's a pen</u>
<u n="100" who="S0192">oh I know I'm popular</u>
<u n="101" who="S0227">did you er you couldn't remember your mum's obviously when you were <unclear/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0192">good god it's yellow</u>
<u n="103" who="S0227">yes this is the elephant <unclear/> elephant <unclear/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0192">really?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0227">you put you put it might be your mum's cos er address ours is the same number eight</u>
<u n="106" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0227">but it was you couldn't remember</u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">no no no oh what for the</u>
<u n="109" who="S0227"><unclear/> the time you were travelling</u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">no yeah I remember yours well but I don't remember I I remember mum's but I couldn't be a hundred percent certain of it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192">and that's where my bag's going and I was just like I defiantly know dad's off my heart and I know the telephone number off by heart</u>
<u n="113" who="S0227">yeah and actually you've been travelling for quite some time you're quite tired you're thinking</u>
<u n="114" who="S0192">I was knackered</u>
<u n="115" who="S0227">I'll default with what I know <trunc>ray</trunc><trunc>what</trunc>rather than what I think I know</u>
<u n="116" who="S0192">terrible they so many of our bags went missing so many of us so I had a connection in Moscow from Seoul so I flew nine hours to Moscow by the time I landed in Moscow it was already like midnight my time so I was already kind of tired and then we had to run like mad cos they only gave us a one hour transfer</u>
<u n="117" who="S0227">that's tight</u>
<u n="118" who="S0192">which is tight yeah and Moscow Sheremetyevo or something airport is notoriously busy and notoriously not good just in general and we left late so we actually arrive <trunc>wh</trunc>when we arrived it was boarding my flight it had just started boarding so we ran like mad through the airport and then got to for some reason even though we weren't checking in we were just transferring they still asked for our passports and they still security checked us which added even</u>
<u n="119" who="S0227">did they scan?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0192">no no we just passed through we kinda had to queue jump so we ran l like mad and it was horrible and obviously <trunc>a</trunc> none of our bags made it so anyone who did that connection with us which was about eight people nobody got their bags and then I bumped into some other people that had a had a similar connection they'd flown from China not from Korea to Moscow connected with a one hour connection and none of their bags arrived either so there was about thirty of us forty of us that just didn't have our bags it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="121" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0227">I was slightly concerned you about your flight path only slightly because of the Ukraine</u>
<u n="123" who="S0192">what's been going with Russia</u>
<u n="124" who="S0227">plane that got shot down over the Ukraine</u>
<u n="125" who="S0192">yeah it concerned me as well a little a little obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was still a little she doesn't take flying too well</u>
<u n="126" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="127" who="S0192">really she makes me nervous</u>
<u n="128" who="S0227">you could have <unclear/> in your time</u>
<u n="129" who="S0192">I think that's the problem I think you start thinking law of averages something's going to happen at some point if we keep flying you've got my mobile number now though?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0227">yes that's all keyed in</u>
<u n="131" who="S0192">yay I have a phone</u>
<u n="132" who="S0227">and I put it on to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s I'll get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s as well <trunc>d</trunc>cos I mean</u>
<u n="133" who="S0192">yeah I'll take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> definitely if you've got your number</u>
<u n="134" who="S0227">there's yeah a possibility that <trunc>you</trunc> erm you might not be able to get hold of me but erm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0192">that would be a great save</u>
<u n="136" who="S0227">if you</u>
<u n="137" who="S0190">you won't at the weekend because you switch it off</u>
<u n="138" who="S0227">cos yeah as I said</u>
<u n="139" who="S0192">do you both switch them off at the weekend?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="141" who="S0190">no I do</u>
<u n="142" who="S0227">no she doesn't</u>
<u n="143" who="S0190">I have my normal phone</u>
<u n="144" who="S0192">yeah cos I can't get hold of dad</u>
<u n="145" who="S0227" trans="overlap">this is what I'm saying</u>
<u n="146" who="S0190">no you won't he'll switch his off</u>
<u n="147" who="S0227">if</u>
<u n="148" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0227">you know if if it's a weekend use <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s rather than mine</u>
<u n="150" who="S0192">yeah cos they were telling me originally that it was going to be delivered on the Sunday and I was kind of panicking a little bit cos I couldn't get hold of you at all on the Sunday</u>
<u n="151" who="S0227">no what I was at a barbecue</u>
<u n="152" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0192">I rang you quite a few times</u>
<u n="154" who="S0227">I was I was negotiating the van</u>
<u n="155" who="S0192">is that your number?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0190">that's my number</u>
<u n="157" who="S0192">okay well one second and I just need to write one more number</u>
<u n="158" who="S0190" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0192">zero erm I'm still getting used to this thing</u>
<u n="160" who="S0227">yes you're not really a friend with phones are you?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0192">no I don't really like phones <event desc="sound of phone"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0227">you get that off of me</u>
<u n="163" who="S0192">four two three two erm save to people this is a touch one as well thinking that so it's a little bit confusing shall I give you mine?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> er I think your mum used to get us off <unclear/> or something so it's like a hand me down</u>
<u n="165" who="S0190">if you just ring that number it'll tell me yours</u>
<u n="166" who="S0192">okay sorry dad?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0227">I think your mum used to get hers off of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or something her like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hand me down or unless she splashed out and got one herself</u>
<u n="168" who="S0192">I think that's probably what it is yeah it's a hand me down</u>
<u n="169" who="S0227">it's a family air loom</u>
<u n="170" who="S0192">did you get it?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0227">it's a lot more sophisticated than mine though</u>
<u n="172" who="S0192">It does the job I didn't have to pay for it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0227">once money exactly all I need a phone for is free I an do my texts I don't want a <trunc>co</trunc> to go on to the internet with it or</u>
<u n="174" who="S0192">no this one does that but I don't</u>
<u n="175" who="S0227">take photographs and stuff</u>
<u n="176" who="S0192">no I just want and I don't even want to ring people I want people to ring me</u>
<u n="177" who="S0190">have you got it one pay as you go?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0192">yes yeah so it came with I couldn't believe it it came with ten pound credit I made a two minute call to you do you remember that first call we did?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0192">three minutes that cost me a pound sixty</u>
<u n="181" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0192">this thing's forty pence a minute</u>
<u n="183" who="S0190">stupid it well you want to <unclear/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0192">forty pence a minute it's gone up quite badly I mean last time I had a mobile phone it was about five pence a minute or something why it's forty pence a minute</u>
<u n="185" who="S0190">because you like you're doing pay as you go</u>
<u n="186" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0190">if you have a contract I don't pay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0192">no one's on that yeah contracts you get like loads of stuff but you're tied in for a year</u>
<u n="189" who="S0190">I pay <trunc>f</trunc> I pay five pounds</u>
<u n="190" who="S0192">or two years or something</u>
<u n="191" who="S0190">we</u>
<u n="192" who="S0192">five pounds</u>
<u n="193" who="S0190">a month yeah and that's all the landline is erm free a hundred minutes for erm to</u>
<u n="194" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s quite good and getting you good deals isn't he?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0192" trans="overlap">amazing</u>
<u n="196" who="S0190">to any other to ordinary phones and all my texts are free</u>
<u n="197" who="S0192">I just can't don't want to commit to a year or sometimes even two year contract</u>
<u n="198" who="S0227">well you could commit to a year cos you're going to be here for a year aren't you?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0192">yeah but don't you normally pay something at the start? you like pay for the phone or something and then you pay like five pound a month six pound a</u>
<u n="200" who="S0227">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s pretty good at coming up with these erm little little deals for the phones and that for him mum</u>
<u n="201" who="S0190">yeah he's gotta look after his mum</u>
<u n="202" who="S0227">I mean I said I we or we automatically default to David <event desc="sound of blender"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0192">sorry that <unclear/> was a bit noisy for the</u>
<u n="204" who="S0227">I just got up to speed with them</u>
<u n="205" who="S0192">no I'm not either</u>
<u n="206" who="S0227">I just see the phone normally cos its work phone is the bringer of bad news <trunc>some</trunc>someone wants something</u>
<u n="207" who="S0192">someone wants something from me again</u>
<u n="208" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0192">how's this summer been?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0227">well it's unfortunately the seasons changed early this year</u>
<u n="211" who="S0190" trans="overlap">July was quite good</u>
<u n="212" who="S0227">is this is end of summer now then?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0190">yes I think so they talk they suggest that August will be below average temperatures</u>
<u n="214" who="S0227">I think sometimes there's a little bit of flexibility with the season it it flexes one or the other it flexed the wrong way this this year</u>
<u n="215" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0227">this time last year it was hot</u>
<u n="217" who="S0192">it would have been nice I mean sometimes September's nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0227">yes it can be warm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0190">I mean it has been if if the sun comes out it's actually quite warm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it can be warm but not hot</u>
<u n="221" who="S0190">but it's not <trunc>e</trunc> it's not as to as it has been</u>
<u n="222" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="223" who="S0190">I mean it was quite so that you really couldn't do an awful lot</u>
<u n="224" who="S0192">and the buildings aren't designed for it here they're not really</u>
<u n="225" who="S0190">well and these are we're alright in here</u>
<u n="226" who="S0192">yeah this is nice and high</u>
<u n="227" who="S0190">it goes really tall and it's cool throughout the house cos there's the brick work and that</u>
<u n="228" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0190">but then you see it's cold in the winter</u>
<u n="230" who="S0192">yeah difficult</u>
<u n="231" who="S0190">so you don't yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0227">my twelve <trunc>we</trunc>weeks off the last year was erm it was really nice weather but it was not good for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she couldn't breathe</u>
<u n="233" who="S0192">no no too stuffy</u>
<u n="234" who="S0227">and with this fungus in her lungs <trunc>d</trunc> at her worst this is how fast you could work</u>
<u n="235" who="S0192">wow</u>
<u n="236" who="S0227">about that fast and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's the <trunc>w</trunc> I don't know if you've met yeah I think you met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said you could not beat <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> over a hundred metres and she's like eighty-two eighty-three with a bad heart or her heart was plumbed the wrong way round</u>
<u n="237" who="S0192">it's phenomenal how much better you've gotten I mean how bad you were</u>
<u n="238" who="S0190">oh yeah I'm really lucky I really am lucky yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0227">you she turned a corner</u>
<u n="240" who="S0190">this time last year</u>
<u n="241" who="S0227">she turned a corner I did worry very much when erm erm she wasn't holding down the anti-sickness tablet</u>
<u n="242" who="S0192">no we were all worried</u>
<u n="243" who="S0227">that is that's when we really started to think you know if you can't hold those down you're not going to get you can't eat anything cos these things things</u>
<u n="244" who="S0192">you can't get any treatment</u>
<u n="245" who="S0227">they will really hold a lot if you have like the strong erm anti erm erm anti emetics the anti-sickness that are like erm ondansetron erm you could probably eat something off the floor and you wouldn't</u>
<u n="246" who="S0192">yeah no worries</u>
<u n="247" who="S0227">you wouldn't be sick it's that strong but she was being sick</u>
<u n="248" who="S0192">that was bad</u>
<u n="249" who="S0227">so yes it was a lot of <unclear/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0192">brilliant turn around</u>
<u n="251" who="S0227">I mean it's hard to believe that that the time has gone by and it's almost been a year since <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been in hospital she's been to hospital a few times since</u>
<u n="252" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0227">but this is for check-ups and stuff</u>
<u n="254" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0227">she's not actually been <trunc>c</trunc> admitted</u>
<u n="256" who="S0192">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="257" who="S0227">which has been good <pause dur="long"/> christ how many times we went to the hospital or how many times I went to the hospital cos obviously I went more cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there I was going backwards and forwards and backwards</u>
<u n="258" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0227">it was a lot</u>
<u n="260" who="S0192">so I still can't believe it's been two years since I've seen both of you in in the flesh</u>
<u n="261" who="S0190">well time just goes so quickly</u>
<u n="262" who="S0192">yes it does</u>
<u n="263" who="S0190">it really does</u>
<u n="264" who="S0227">yes it's it's it is it does go very fast</u>
<u n="265" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are getting on for thirty now</u>
<u n="266" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0192">not too far off</u>
<u n="268" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="269" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="270" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0192">he he's the same age as me isn't he? twenty-eight</u>
<u n="272" who="S0190">he's a little bit erm older than you</u>
<u n="273" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0190">about three months</u>
<u n="275" who="S0192">about three months older</u>
<u n="276" who="S0227">well he was born in April wasn't he?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0192">I'm May</u>
<u n="278" who="S0227">yeah and he's May one month</u>
<u n="279" who="S0190">yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0192">is he the beginning of April though and I'm the end of May?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0190">no twenty-seventh of April</u>
<u n="282" who="S0192">twenty-ninth of May so there's not a big difference</u>
<u n="283" who="S0227">well one month one month</u>
<u n="284" who="S0190" trans="overlap">just a month</u>
<u n="285" who="S0192">exactly</u>
<u n="286" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0192">so he'll turn thirty before I do</u>
<u n="288" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0192">thirty I'm not scared about forty a little bit just cos I think it's only a year and a half until I'm thirty and then it's only another ten years till I'm forty and the last ten years have gone really quickly from eighteen to twenty-eight so</u>
<u n="290" who="S0227">yes it's yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0192">if it does that again when I'm forty it's completely terrible</u>
<u n="292" who="S0190">big four oh</u>
<u n="293" who="S0227">it really does fly</u>
<u n="294" who="S0192">I will be sixty-five</u>
<u n="295" who="S0190">that's true</u>
<u n="296" who="S0227">it's almost enough to put you into tears or is it these onions god</u>
<u n="297" who="S0192">yeah but I didn't see an elephant</u>
<u n="298" who="S0227">elephant <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="300" who="S0227">yes we got it last year eh sorry this year I've got to cut some off erm in in two months' time I'll plant garlic again for to harvest next year <pause dur="short"/> right erm place to start</u>
<u n="301" who="S0192">er I've got to sign a contract it's a <trunc>lit</trunc> a little annoying I'm a freelancer I have to do my own taxes now just cos of this</u>
<u n="302" who="S0227">yeah but you're not going to earn enough to pay tax</u>
<u n="303" who="S0192">no no</u>
<u n="304" who="S0227">well I pay tax</u>
<u n="305" who="S0192">I mean I've I've worked out if I can well the <trunc>ta</trunc> you have to earn less than ten thousand pounds isn't it?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0227">well I said I I can hear <trunc>eel</trunc> eleven thousand four hundred pounds after I have to start paying tax</u>
<u n="307" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0227">so</u>
<u n="309" who="S0192">but basically I I'm hoping that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I can earn I mean a maximum a hundred pounds a week each</u>
<u n="310" who="S0227">yes this will not take you this will not trip</u>
<u n="311" who="S0192">but the problem is it may a little bit because for their ease they've put <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I on one contract this is elected to the both of us but this is a contract just for me</u>
<u n="312" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0192">so all the money is coming to me</u>
<u n="314" who="S0227">what whatever tax you pay will get back</u>
<u n="315" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0227">you you're going to be under your</u>
<u n="317" who="S0192">well I'm not paying they're not taxing me</u>
<u n="318" who="S0227">no oh we</u>
<u n="319" who="S0192">I'm having to file my own taxes at the end of the year</u>
<u n="320" who="S0227">yes well you're going to be under the threshold</u>
<u n="321" who="S0192">yeah erm eighteen pound an hour they pay every one hour of recording yeah I have to put in an extra half an hour per recording to listen through it and cut bits and edit bits and erm write I have to fill out some forms for every single thing that I send in general it's another I reckon another half an hour per for every hour that I record</u>
<u n="322" who="S0190">it's not bad though is it?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0192">it's a pretty good job yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0227">expect another expect an <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't have to go for job interviews I don't have to worry about teaching or meeting new students or wearing a suit or doing anything</u>
<u n="326" who="S0227">and it's also better than having <trunc>t</trunc>to be in bar or say would you like french fries with that?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0192">oh yeah no absolutely</u>
<u n="328" who="S0227">it's the sort of thing you would have</u>
<u n="329" who="S0192">and it's in my field yeah I can put down that I was a researcher for Cambridge University Press</u>
<u n="330" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="331" who="S0192">for their corpus linguistics</u>
<u n="332" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0192">and what's better I couldn't believe when they first told me but I was saying okay firstly can I be in the recording is that okay? yeah you can be in the recording can I how how many times can I record the same people? unlimited amount of times okay and</u>
<u n="334" who="S0227">well every conversation's different isn't it?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0192">well how many how many recordings can I send you? as many as you can until next June so I've got and I get paid eighteen pounds an hour so if I can just do five hours of recording a week that's a hundred pounds a week</u>
<u n="336" who="S0190">so what does it record on to?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0192">MP3</u>
<u n="338" who="S0190">oh right</u>
<u n="339" who="S0192">so I'm recording onto an MP3 they've given me a Dropbox link so I upload my <trunc>f</trunc> recording files the speaker consent forms and also the the forms for everyone every month at the beginning of the month I upload them with my invoice and then at the end of the month they pay me</u>
<u n="340" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0192">and I've got until June next year which is basically until I finish my degree so</u>
<u n="342" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0192">it's perfect</u>
<u n="344" who="S0227">it will help</u>
<u n="345" who="S0190">yeah it's a good thing</u>
<u n="346" who="S0192">I contacted them today about transcribing cos somebody after somebody's going to listen to this afterwards and then turn it into a different alphabet I don't know if you know IPA? but if you look in a dictionary sometimes there'll be how you pronounce the word and you <trunc>lo</trunc></u>
<u n="347" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0192">it's it's in a different alphabet</u>
<u n="349" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0192">I can read and write that and I use it to teach like pronunciation because English orthography on English spelling doesn't line up with pronunciation</u>
<u n="351" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="352" who="S0192">you have a G and an H and it makes an F sound</u>
<u n="353" who="S0190">right</u>
<u n="354" who="S0192">so I teach with this different alphabet and they're going to be paying other freelancers to listen to these and type them up in this phonetic alphabet so I contacted her today and said look maybe I'm not quite qualified yet but maybe you know once I'm further headlong into my course maybe if I I have quite an interest in phonology can I get involved with with transcribing?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0190">oh right</u>
<u n="356" who="S0192">I wonder if they how much they pay for that if they pay an hour just to transcribe cos transcribing it would be difficult I think sitting down for each hour</u>
<u n="357" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0192">so you'll be you will all be cemented in history</u>
<u n="359" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="360" who="S0192">the cambridge british national corpus two thousand and fourteen if historians ever want to wonder what we sounded like in the year two thousand and fourteen they'll hear us</u>
<u n="361" who="S0227">if I if I remembered I was being recorded I'd have used bigger words</u>
<u n="362" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there is some sociolinguistic variables that they're looking into they do ask your education your age what you perceive your accent to be how long you've lived in your location these kind of things so I guess they're going to look at what colloquialisms do you use</u>
<u n="363" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="364" who="S0192">what your accent is what these kind of things but <trunc>the</trunc> but regarding the content they're not using that at all it's just how you sound the words that you use</u>
<u n="365" who="S0227">you need to get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on this cos she's got a bit some of those <anon type="place"/> words that she uses erm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0190">ain't can't shalln't and not gonna</u>
<u n="367" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0192">what are these words?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0190">ain't can't shalln't and not gonna that's where they say like instead of I can't it's I can't</u>
<u n="370" who="S0192">can't?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0190">I can't</u>
<u n="372" who="S0192">and that's predominantly in <anon type="place"/> not around any other areas?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0227">Its like <trunc>colloqu</trunc><trunc>colloqu</trunc>colloquial dialect</u>
<u n="374" who="S0192">because I will have to do my thesis and chances are it'll be on some kind of sociolinguistic variation and if I can find that this area hasn't been properly marked as an accent or a dialect but but does have enough grammar or syntactical differences to make it its own dialect then I can potentially do my thesis on that <pause dur="short"/> interesting I might have to ask you a bit more about that or record this lady <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you think you and dad have the same accent?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0190">sorry?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0192">do you think you and dad have the same accent?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0190">no <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> because I've been here a lot longer I've been here thirty-five odd years now</u>
<u n="378" who="S0227" trans="overlap">this is gonna have to be green er yellow</u>
<u n="379" who="S0192">thirty-five years in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0190">yeah erm so I think I pick it up and use probably some of the <anon type="place"/> slang as I call it</u>
<u n="381" who="S0192">vernacular yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0190">yeah whereas your dad doesn't</u>
<u n="383" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="384" who="S0190">no doesn't I don't think I've never heard him say can't I know I say it</u>
<u n="385" who="S0192">no you say it sometimes yeah it slips</u>
<u n="386" who="S0190">yeah erm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0192">so you think you say it more than he does purely because you've lived here longer?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0190">probably</u>
<u n="389" who="S0192">yeah?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0192">I mean what <anon type="place"/> words are there? I mean I know we drop our Ts terribly computer</u>
<u n="392" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0192">bottles what?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0227">this person doesn't</u>
<u n="395" who="S0190">no this person has adds his Americanisms in we're going in the garage</u>
<u n="396" who="S0192">oh dad does?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0192">he says garage</u>
<u n="399" who="S0190">terrible oh and we found a vase</u>
<u n="400" who="S0192">does he say advertisement</u>
<u n="401" who="S0227">no I just use garage</u>
<u n="402" who="S0192">advertisements</u>
<u n="403" who="S0227">tomato zucchini erm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0192">yeah why do you use the Americanisms</u>
<u n="405" who="S0190">oregano</u>
<u n="406" who="S0227">I don't know</u>
<u n="407" who="S0190">he just does he just starts it's so annoying</u>
<u n="408" who="S0192">oregano and basil</u>
<u n="409" who="S0190">yeah or</u>
<u n="410" who="S0192">why?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0227">oregano I say</u>
<u n="412" who="S0192">you watch too much American TV</u>
<u n="413" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0227">well I was there for a while you know three weeks and I it kind of stuck</u>
<u n="415" who="S0192">oh you're going to pick up the accent yeah three weeks</u>
<u n="416" who="S0227">well yeah I know I didn't pick up the accent I I I utilised the <unclear/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0192">I mean I lived in India for five months do I sound like an Indian?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0227">I utilised the lingo</u>
<u n="419" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0227">some of the words I thought I can't I prefer those I'd rather them</u>
<u n="421" who="S0190">no they're horrible well don't come back here and</u>
<u n="422" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so do you say do you say aluminium?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0227">yes cos I can't say the other word</u>
<u n="424" who="S0192">you just physically can't?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0227">yes I have difficulty with alluminuminium</u>
<u n="426" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0227">so I say alluvium cos it's easier</u>
<u n="428" who="S0192">you didn't even say it correctly that time</u>
<u n="429" who="S0227">to say I say</u>
<u n="430" who="S0192">you did some kind of mix of the two</u>
<u n="431" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's easier to say right I'm going to</u>
<u n="432" who="S0192">I used to have have be adverse to Americanisms I couldn't stand them when I was younger I really didn't like the sound of them now I'm very used to them there are certain words that really sounds nice like candy to me that's the most American word in existence candy do you want some candy?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0190">I don't think I've really had much to do with American language to be fair</u>
<u n="434" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="435" who="S0190">er</u>
<u n="436" who="S0192">I've had quite a lot recently</u>
<u n="437" who="S0190">you've got friends in America haven't you?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0192">yeah a lot of friends in America</u>
<u n="439" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0192">most people that teach out in Korea are American</u>
<u n="441" who="S0227">and what's happened to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is he back here?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0192">oh god I haven't heard from him really he's erm I think he takes our friendship for granted a little bit so he doesn't feel like he has to contact me but I erm I could do with an email from him from time to time</u>
<u n="443" who="S0227">yes well it can't be a one way street can it?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0192">no but I've given up whatever he'll contact me when he he contacted me a couple of weeks back <event desc="sound of oven"/> <trunc>how</trunc> I ask I can't send him longer than a sentence cos he just won't reply to it so I sent him a sentence just like give me your telephone number and he didn't so</u>
<u n="445" who="S0227">are are you erm is that still going?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0192">yeah as long as you're not going to be longer than how long do you think</u>
<u n="447" who="S0227">about thirty seconds</u>
<u n="448" who="S0192">thirty seconds hang on a minute if we could be silent now</u>
<u n="449" who="S0227">keep talking</u>
<u n="450" who="S0192">okay I asked whether I could do that I wasn't sure whether I could pause it mid stream but she said provided the same people are around and the same kind of discourse is going on afterwards so it should be alright</u>
<u n="451" who="S0227">yeah I was going to say it's just a a a crude noise</u>
<u n="452" who="S0192">you're quite good people to record actually mum's there's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> running around shouting and</u>
<u n="453" who="S0190">oh right</u>
<u n="454" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0227">have you put erm have you done your mum?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0192">yeah a little bit I mean so far I've got seven hours recorded</u>
<u n="457" who="S0227">of not of your mum good god</u>
<u n="458" who="S0192">mum <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0227">does this break</u>
<u n="460" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah just about</u>
<u n="461" who="S0227">cor blimey governor apples and pears</u>
<u n="462" who="S0192">bit of cockney rhyming slang I got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for a couple of hours last night</u>
<u n="463" who="S0227">oh yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0192">about an hour and hour and a half last night I had to edit it down a bit but</u>
<u n="465" who="S0227">how is he?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0192">he's good it's good to see him he sounds so local it's unreal the way he talks his erm relative pronouns so which where when you know I said that's the man who gives me bread or that's the house in which my father lives</u>
<u n="467" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0192">these connectors they're relative pronouns he replaces them all with what that's the man what my father knows that's the house what my friend lives in he replaces them all with what every single one of them</u>
<u n="469" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0192">he says a a lot of things erm he uses erm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0227">he could be your erm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0192">personal pronouns incorrectly as well</u>
<u n="473" who="S0227">he could be your <trunc>prof</trunc> erm Eliza Doolittle to your Professor Higgins</u>
<u n="474" who="S0192">somebody I could study yeah I'll tell you what I've been looking in recently to doing I could deviate now and do a different masters and with one more year I could be a speech therapist and that's kind of interesting <pause dur="short"/> I've got enough <trunc>ph</trunc>phonological background now to go with one more year I could be a speech therapist</u>
<u n="475" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0227">I think what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s undertaking is a bit of a a <unclear/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0192">computer science</u>
<u n="478" who="S0227">yes I mean computers or science in in isolation is quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0192">he's good at it though</u>
<u n="480" who="S0227">but to combine well fortunately he is I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has given him high praise and and the fact that erm erm in order to replace him they couldn't replace him with one man they had to replace him with two people</u>
<u n="481" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="482" who="S0227">to do his job they couldn't get one bloke couldn't do it</u>
<u n="483" who="S0192">that's interesting</u>
<u n="484" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that he reminds him very much of of himself that he's a problem solver</u>
<u n="485" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0227">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to solve problems I've <trunc>got</trunc> I said I I'm having a beer with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in October beginning of which is too late for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know I had said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if you want any work and he said well yeah I I'm I'm sure we would be able to but I can't like set up a meeting to twist his arm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="488" who="S0227">to so that he does this <unclear/> at the end of the day all I did when I'm with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was I I facilitated the interview <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sold the job himself</u>
<u n="489" who="S0192">he got the job</u>
<u n="490" who="S0227">I didn't say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know give him the job cos he's my son erm I just made the connection he turned up to the interview and the rest is history</u>
<u n="491" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and he got it if he erm pursues a career and is successful in a career in in his area he'll end up being the most successful of the all the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0227">probably that won't be too hard</u>
<u n="493" who="S0192">no none of us have set the bar too high have we? do you see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> much?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0227">I haven't seen him for some time I spoke to <unclear/> on the phone</u>
<u n="495" who="S0192">he keeps saying something on Facebook like really vague messages that sound like he's having a bit of a bad time but I haven't <unclear/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0227">he's been having a bit of a bad time with his missus I don't know if they're together or apart he says they're together but I'm erm the meat mince is it oh it's in</u>
<u n="497" who="S0190">I don't know</u>
<u n="498" who="S0227">in</u>
<u n="499" who="S0190">yeah you kept it's by the sink</u>
<u n="500" who="S0227">oh right I'm looking in the fridge and in the microwave</u>
<u n="501" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this this is</u>
<u n="502" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0192">he's getting worse is he?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0227">I don't always believe he's my half-brother but I don't always believe what he says I take it with a pinch of salt so I</u>
<u n="505" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="506" who="S0227">although er erm you know so everything he says I don't take it seriously but erm <pause dur="short"/> like I said the point that he is he does he does share the family surname so er</u>
<u n="507" who="S0192">yeah there aren't many of us and if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or I never have children well it's soon to die out</u>
<u n="508" who="S0227">well no erm going back to my <trunc>s</trunc> half-sister I believe has a child so from my dad the baton will have been on on from his dad definitely cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s had so many children and so many grandchildren</u>
<u n="509" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0227">she's got loads so er yes I could genetically hit the buffers after you two if you don't have children</u>
<u n="511" who="S0192">I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will have children</u>
<u n="512" who="S0227">I don't think erm you know at the end of the day grandchildren are nice I'm sure I'm going to get grandchildren from some quarter you know anyway but erm if you two don't erm deliver erm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0227">it just er I'm sure your mum will be <trunc>depr</trunc> that's why she had plan C just in case plan A or plan B didn't work out</u>
<u n="515" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah weren't panning out</u>
<u n="516" who="S0227"><trunc>un</trunc>unfortunately she'll be too old if she's alive to know much about her plan C's grandchildren unless he does a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and pops them off <unclear/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0192">yeah I can't believe he's had children no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have been quite seriously discussing children lately and</u>
<u n="518" who="S0227">oh you what</u>
<u n="519" who="S0192">maybe at the age of forty</u>
<u n="520" who="S0227">your biological clock isn't ticking hers is</u>
<u n="521" who="S0192">hers is we just said we'll probably adopt if we end up having children</u>
<u n="522" who="S0227">wow</u>
<u n="523" who="S0192">just when we're forty or something and then at least we can choose and we were thinking if <trunc>we</trunc>I think the best time to adopt a child would be just before they go to university</u>
<u n="524" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0192">so if I pay for them to go to uni and then we've got an agreement going on and then they just pay they sort us out when we're old</u>
<u n="526" who="S0227">when you're old yeah that's what they say be nice to your parent erm to your children cos there's the ones that chose what old people's home you're going to go in</u>
<u n="527" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think I left my glass of water somewhere</u>
<u n="528" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0190">erm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0227">you left it upstairs</u>
<u n="531" who="S0190">upstairs yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0192">shall I grab it?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0190">it's up to you</u>
<u n="534" who="S0192">I'll leave this on so continue</u>
<u n="535" who="S0190">alright thank you <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0227">yes did you your mum wouldn't have come today I I I tried I rang about between twelve and one she must have been in the garden or out or something</u>
<u n="537" who="S0190">well I was just coming in the front door and the erm and I heard the phone and by the time I'd walked from the front door to the phone it had stopped</u>
<u n="538" who="S0227">I did ring from work</u>
<u n="539" who="S0190">you didn't phone back</u>
<u n="540" who="S0227">I <unclear/> sorry?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0190">you didn't</u>
<u n="542" who="S0227">no cos I thought er well I think something cropped up</u>
<u n="543" who="S0190">I was going to say cos if anything had happened you'd <trunc>no</trunc> <unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0190"><unclear/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0227">I just assumed you were with your mum it was that you'd seen her the day before erm something cropped up and I I I didn't give it another thought</u>
<u n="547" who="S0190">I just walked into town</u>
<u n="548" who="S0227">oh right you Fitzwilliam or do you go the long way now?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0190">no Fitzwilliam</u>
<u n="550" who="S0227">just up the hill?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0190">yeah I wanted to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday card and erm things <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0192">these orchids are lovely</u>
<u n="553" who="S0227">did you think that erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had erm changed?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0192">erm I've seen him on Skype so not lots</u>
<u n="555" who="S0227">I think that erm he will have more of a relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s there erm it's it's probably awkward for you not for him but for you because mum mum will subconsciously be trying to <trunc>bl</trunc>blend you two</u>
<u n="556" who="S0192">yeah it's not that subconscious it's quite overt <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="557" who="S0227">and erm for you he will a brother's the person that you were punching in the back of the car</u>
<u n="558" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0227">and erm making them eat erm chili peppers and trying to tell them that they were something else and things like that you know through experience</u>
<u n="560" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0227">this is this is what erm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0190">you must have missed him out on here</u>
<u n="563" who="S0227">this is what erm galvanises</u>
<u n="564" who="S0190">and the only reason I've got it on for was because I thought the erm jackpot was fifteen and a half thousand pounds and I just wanted to see it's not very often it gets up that high but it must be something else</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">sorry you want to turn it up? I can stop this</u>
<u n="566" who="S0190">no no it's finished now</u>
<u n="567" who="S0192">are you sure?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0192">sorry if you missed it</u>
<u n="570" who="S0190">no it's alright I just wanted I don't listen to it intently it's thank you it's just habit but it's they don't very often win very much like this time they've just won a thousand pounds</u>
<u n="571" who="S0192">fifteen grand</u>
<u n="572" who="S0190">and it got to fifteen and a half and I just thought oh but it must have been somebody else unless we've missed the one did we have it on yesterday? I can't remember</u>
<u n="573" who="S0227">er no we missed it erm just came to the end erm yes I think it's it's experiences like that that galvanise erm I treat <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> more <trunc>th</trunc> as a brother than my own <trunc>bro</trunc> half-brother</u>
<u n="574" who="S0192">because you went through more with him</u>
<u n="575" who="S0227">because I grew up with him so and I've always kind of continued to see him you know there hasn't there's probably not been hardly erm there's probably only been about three three years in the last since sixty-nine</u>
<u n="576" who="S0190">is that alright?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0227">that I haven't seen them</u>
<u n="578" who="S0190">the onions are</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">yeah the onions are going into my eyes as well</u>
<u n="580" who="S0190">yeah they make mine sore</u>
<u n="581" who="S0227">erm so yeah so I don't think your mum does it consciously it's probably but like you said things have to be natural if they you you can't make round pegs go into square holes there's you know but I think erm there will be more of a relationship between him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because they have lived sometime together there was like with my own half-brother it is my blood but we don't have a common erm upbringing we can talk about the same father but that's about it really you know but I accept him and there is that bond because if someone walks in the room and they're looking for Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> me and him will turn our heads when if that was the situation in say ten years' time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will not turn his head</u>
<u n="582" who="S0192">no I'm I'm not gonna know him obviously erm I can't see myself living close enough even if I did live in England I still wouldn't see him very much</u>
<u n="583" who="S0227">no I just don't see you living in England to be fair</u>
<u n="584" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="585" who="S0227">this is a stage this is a staging post</u>
<u n="586" who="S0192">maybe</u>
<u n="587" who="S0190">is that sun in your eyes do you want the blind down?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0227">somewhere else</u>
<u n="589" who="S0192">no it's okay as long as I don't there you go perfect are you sure?</u>
<u n="590" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0190">I don't know if it's the right one</u>
<u n="592" who="S0192">no it's the other one I think</u>
<u n="593" who="S0227">that's the plant that you sent <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> behind you</u>
<u n="594" who="S0192">oh that one</u>
<u n="595" who="S0227">year</u>
<u n="596" who="S0192">oh it's looking healthy</u>
<u n="597" who="S0190">it is not we've tried everything</u>
<u n="598" who="S0192">will it flower again?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0190">hopefully um I've tried everything I've done I tried putting it in the lounge I tried changing it in different positions in the window I just nearly lost it and then your dad said well I'll take it and <unclear/> and he reported it and it was because it was shot no end of new shoots out but as fast as it shot the new shoots all the old ones the leaves were just falling off any time you got anywhere near it</u>
<u n="600" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0190">but now he's he's put it in to erm I bought plant food and everything but it seems to have a hold now</u>
<u n="602" who="S0192">well it's climbing up there nicely</u>
<u n="603" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0192">do you have to encourage it to do that or does it just start climbing?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0190">oh no it just goes those trails like mad</u>
<u n="606" who="S0227">bit of training</u>
<u n="607" who="S0192">you've got a few orchids your kaffir lime tree looks in amazing</u>
<u n="608" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="609" who="S0192">really good</u>
<u n="610" who="S0190">window I spoiled</u>
<u n="611" who="S0227">it has erm</u>
<u n="612" who="S0192">how many can I take?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0227">well I'll cut you off some erm leaves I have to make sure that there was something eating away and I I as you can see here hoping I've got it but they're not I don't pick a leaf off when I cut it I cut a branch cos that sends a message to replace branch leaves don't send messages to replace leaves</u>
<u n="614" who="S0192">no well if you cut them off a couple of branches that would be great</u>
<u n="615" who="S0227">yeah well I'll I'll <trunc>be</trunc> when I when I come down cos erm we need to get from this end we need to get everything that we're supposed to be getting you're on about the table I think it's <unclear/> about the table is that the one that's at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0190">I've no idea</u>
<u n="617" who="S0227">where is</u>
<u n="618" who="S0190">you know I ever since you sent that message I came in the same morning that you sent it I went through everything with your dad and mine and then he said to me some time about it ooh so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent the list back and erm he's put our names by the side of it so I said alright so will you print that off so we know what to get ready I have been asking that for ages so I left it up to your dad I'm afraid until he sorts it out I I haven't a clue <unclear/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0192">well what what I've got a copy on my computer so we can print it tonight and erm sit down and go through what there is I've organised everything with mum's and</u>
<u n="620" who="S0190">but this this person doesn't organise</u>
<u n="621" who="S0192">no?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0190">no I can just see where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets it from now you're like your mum</u>
<u n="623" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like dad</u>
<u n="624" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="625" who="S0192">sounds about right I think that is more right I'm more</u>
<u n="626" who="S0190">I like to be organised I like to know where things are as soon as it came through and I went through it yes so that we've got this that and the other I said right I won't remember so when it was all sorted and you put our names by it I said right you need to run that off now so I can look at it and then we can begin to pick it all up</u>
<u n="627" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0190">and that's as far as it's got</u>
<u n="629" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I like to be organised too</u>
<u n="630" who="S0227">well print it tonight so we can get on the case erm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0190">that you can get on the case</u>
<u n="632" who="S0192">there was erm there was a table mentioned what kind of sized table is it?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0190">it's erm you know the one you had in at your erm house at <anon type="place"/> road the two with the two collapsible chairs that used to sit in front of the window?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0192">two collapsible chairs?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0190">yeah the chairs are fold up ones</u>
<u n="636" who="S0192">no I don't remember that</u>
<u n="637" who="S0190">yeah it used to be underneath the window in the kitchen directly behind the as you came in the back door it was just underneath there</u>
<u n="638" who="S0227">yes yeah by the window</u>
<u n="639" who="S0192">yeah I think I do remember</u>
<u n="640" who="S0190">it's an oval one</u>
<u n="641" who="S0192">it's big enough to get four people round it would you say or?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0227">oh yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0190">yeah you could it I mean it's not probably overly comfortable but yes you can</u>
<u n="644" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0190">it's about as wide as that and about as long</u>
<u n="646" who="S0192">the table itself doesn't fold down does it? With like a divider in the middle</u>
<u n="647" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no well it does yes yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0192">it does?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0190">it does cos it's in bits own</u>
<u n="650" who="S0192">I think I do remember that yeah that's brilliant I can't remember what else was on the list</u>
<u n="651" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="652" who="S0192">I think I can have a look actually I've got it with me this is my new laptop</u>
<u n="653" who="S0190">way nice</u>
<u n="654" who="S0192">mm remember I've been using that tiny little one for years yeah I upgraded so I could study</u>
<u n="655" who="S0227">in style</u>
<u n="656" who="S0192">yeah I mean not really in style it's not like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s eight hundred pound whatever but I paid three hundred and fifty pounds</u>
<u n="657" who="S0190">are you using that <unclear/> any more?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bought a laptop?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no no I don't need that any more no no no he's not he's run out of cash</u>
<u n="660" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I was gonna say he told me he told me he wasn't going to</u>
<u n="661" who="S0192">he's run out of cash</u>
<u n="662" who="S0227">he's over budgeted been <unclear/> too many <unclear>massages</unclear> I fear</u>
<u n="663" who="S0192">yeah you heard those stories then?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0227">indeed</u>
<u n="665" who="S0192">jesus I'm glad he came out to visit me though I am</u>
<u n="666" who="S0227">yes well I I was glad that he didn't bottle it</u>
<u n="667" who="S0192">no yeah me too</u>
<u n="668" who="S0227">he did go</u>
<u n="669" who="S0192">so I'm looking for the list daily list to buy okay I've got you down for one frying pan or a or a wok or something what it was you said</u>
<u n="670" who="S0190">frying pan</u>
<u n="671" who="S0192">erm you said you had two medium sauce pans</u>
<u n="672" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0192">if you don't have any of this stuff that's okay but this is just what what you've written down you said</u>
<u n="674" who="S0227">are you writing this down?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0192">one large and one small knife</u>
<u n="676" who="S0190">one large</u>
<u n="677" who="S0192">and one small knife</u>
<u n="678" who="S0190">one small knife</u>
<u n="679" who="S0192">again if you don't have it don't worry a cheese grater</u>
<u n="680" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0192">a whisk</u>
<u n="682" who="S0190">hand whisk?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0192">yeah I don't know just it says whisk any kind of whisk you've got</u>
<u n="684" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0192">one that you do that or one that you crank a handle that'd be great</u>
<u n="686" who="S0190">the one where you crank the handle</u>
<u n="687" who="S0192">oh that'd be great that would be really good</u>
<u n="688" who="S0227">give you some exercise</u>
<u n="689" who="S0192">yeah erm what else do we have you</u>
<u n="690" who="S0227">is this a keeper or a thrower?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0192">you said you had a double duvet</u>
<u n="692" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0192">and two pillows</u>
<u n="694" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0192">you didn't have any baking trays or pans or anything did you?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0190">no I use them</u>
<u n="697" who="S0227">we'll probably getting you some from Wickes</u>
<u n="698" who="S0190">you said you have some curtains</u>
<u n="699" who="S0227">that must have yes I think I have I'll just double check will they fit the windows I don't know</u>
<u n="700" who="S0192">anything will do I've noticed on the street the house that we're on we're the only place with a street lamp and its right outside of my bedroom basically</u>
<u n="701" who="S0190">oh so it's bright</u>
<u n="702" who="S0192">yeah big kind of heavy curtains would be great</u>
<u n="703" who="S0190">I'll have a look</u>
<u n="704" who="S0192">did you say anything else?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0227">that was too bad about the TV because erm the <unclear/> of me making that explanation</u>
<u n="706" who="S0192">yeah they got back to you</u>
<u n="707" who="S0227">they then got back to us so I thought oh crap</u>
<u n="708" who="S0190">it was even <trunc>work</trunc> well yeah but you couldn't listen to it properly it was worse it was far worse than this is sounds as if the speakers have gone</u>
<u n="709" who="S0192">was it even quieter?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0190">no it wasn't a case of being quieter it was just</u>
<u n="711" who="S0227">it was tinny</u>
<u n="712" who="S0192">it was just broken</u>
<u n="713" who="S0190">it was so tiny it was awful absolutely terrible and this is bad enough <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sort of cringes when he comes in so you couldn't really watch anything on it</u>
<u n="714" who="S0192">is the onion gone enough do you think? is it still?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0192">just saying about the the thing</u>
<u n="717" who="S0227">there we are I can put in down</u>
<u n="718" who="S0192">but is it still getting into your eyes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0190">no it's alright now I can open the window</u>
<u n="720" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s more sensitive than I am with er onions</u>
<u n="721" who="S0190">just recently onions have been really strong</u>
<u n="722" who="S0192">leave it on if it hasn't gone enough or</u>
<u n="723" who="S0190">no no I'll open the door</u>
<u n="724" who="S0192">or open a window or something</u>
<u n="725" who="S0190">no you can't open the window with the the key's gone and there's alarms on it</u>
<u n="726" who="S0192">you lost the keys where did we get up to? er a table</u>
<u n="727" who="S0227">a cuddly toy</u>
<u n="728" who="S0190">table table</u>
<u n="729" who="S0192">there was a table as well</u>
<u n="730" who="S0190">table</u>
<u n="731" who="S0192">there were two chairs</u>
<u n="732" who="S0190">and two chairs yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0192">er and that was everything</u>
<u n="734" who="S0190">brilliant</u>
<u n="735" who="S0190">okay right is there any furniture in the house at all?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0192">er there won't be anything no but er mum's</u>
<u n="737" who="S0227">what have you got for a cooker?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0192">there's a not very good electric cooker there the whole house is electric it's all erm electric cooker they didn't provide a washing machine so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad's got that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad's also got a sofa bed he bought then and has got a van to drive down</u>
<u n="739" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right okay ah taking charge</u>
<u n="740" who="S0192">mum's got us erm like a canvas wardrobe and some chest of drawers and a bed frame the mattress is more important than the bed but they'll all at least make things more comfortable</u>
<u n="741" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0192">so we've pretty much got most things we need really</u>
<u n="743" who="S0190">well the cooker's in there from <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="744" who="S0192">you have a cooker</u>
<u n="745" who="S0190">we've got cooker you can take it if you want it?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0192">ah maybe</u>
<u n="747" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is taking it around I'm not sure whether the back is fixed or not cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had it up in his <trunc>hou</trunc> first house that he rented</u>
<u n="748" who="S0192">and it's electric?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="750" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0190">and it's it's an it's a <trunc>m</trunc> it's a good cooker it's got single erm over a <trunc>do</trunc> an ordinary oven and it's halogen top</u>
<u n="752" who="S0192">what would I do with the other cooker though that's the question?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0190">is there any outbuildings?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0192">no I tell you what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm being ripped off seven hundred and fifty pound a month it costs for a one bedroom apartment it's just one bedroom one living room and a kitchen</u>
<u n="755" who="S0227" trans="overlap">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has been paying six hundred and fifty pounds for her</u>
<u n="757" who="S0192">on her own</u>
<u n="758" who="S0190">one bedroom and she's just got one little the literally the kitchen and the living room is all one room and you just got one bit where the bathroom goes off</u>
<u n="759" who="S0192">it's ridiculous isn't it?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0190">that's it</u>
<u n="761" who="S0192">so expensive</u>
<u n="762" who="S0190">yeah and students</u>
<u n="763" who="S0192">my friend in London is paying seven fifty each and they got like a fifteen hundred pound apartment nothing plush just two bedrooms in London</u>
<u n="764" who="S0190">it's horrendous prices</u>
<u n="765" who="S0192">yeah I couldn't believe how much it was and then we paid about three hundred pounds in fees</u>
<u n="766" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0192">not best pleased but never mind I've already paid that money so that's money gone</u>
<u n="768" who="S0190" trans="overlap">mm but well yeah that fortunate <unclear/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0192">I paid the tuition and I paid my rent and just get it out of the way try not to worry about it</u>
<u n="770" who="S0190">Right I do want to sort that out now</u>
<u n="771" who="S0192">yeah thank you for providing that and then dad said he's going to get a van erm off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="773" who="S0192">yeah that's brilliant</u>
<u n="774" who="S0190">I think my brother said you can borrow it the only thing you have to do is you have to fill it up with diesel</u>
<u n="775" who="S0192">yeah of ours</u>
<u n="776" who="S0190">and erm</u>
<u n="777" who="S0192">I'll get that in how much do you think it will cost for a return tank?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0190">well I don't know I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> must have got this wrong but erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s eldest daughter's erm boyfriend was down in erm in Brighton erm doing a erm he's on the stage down there for a I think he was there for a month and she went down to visit him now she's only got a little car and she went down there and back and she said she spent a hundred and ninety pound on fuel I can't believe that ninety pound it must have been so I think you're talking</u>
<u n="779" who="S0192">god I hope I'm not paying a hundred and <trunc>n</trunc> a hundred and ninety pound in fuel for the damn thing</u>
<u n="780" who="S0190">fuel so I don't think that can be right</u>
<u n="781" who="S0227">what's that?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she went to visit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it cost them a hundred and ninety pound in fuel down there</u>
<u n="783" who="S0192">to get to Brighton and back</u>
<u n="784" who="S0190">that can't be right can it?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0227">no I mean my car filling it up will be seventy quid and that gives me almost seven hundred miles</u>
<u n="786" who="S0190">yes and don't forget hers is a little tiny weeny <trunc>n</trunc>Nissan Micra so they sort of</u>
<u n="787" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah how much do you think it's going to cost me for the</u>
<u n="788" who="S0190">so they sort</u>
<u n="789" who="S0227">well it's probably going to do about thirty thirty odd to the gallon I think</u>
<u n="790" who="S0190">it's gonna cost you nearly a hundred's quid's worth in fuel</u>
<u n="791" who="S0227">well well we'll see what it is fuel's not cheap that that's what when I was thinking</u>
<u n="792" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><unclear/> vans don't do the</u>
<u n="793" who="S0227"><anon type="place"/> as well it was going to be extra and extra</u>
<u n="794" who="S0192">or</u>
<u n="795" who="S0227">kidney beans have we got any of those?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0192">there's no other way of getting my stuff up is the problem</u>
<u n="797" who="S0227">no kidney beans we have</u>
<u n="798" who="S0192">I didn't think fuel was that much unbelievable</u>
<u n="799" who="S0227">we'll see how we'll see what it it it it is for</u>
<u n="800" who="S0190">but it's about isn't it?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0192">it is what it is yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0190">cars cars are erm I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got one that's twice the size his van he's got to pay I think my brother's <trunc>man</trunc> my <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> managed to get the because my brother's aren't big enough you see you can't put they've got the sides have all got things in them they're all cut boarded out a lot of things</u>
<u n="803" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0190">so there isn't the size and then not the height either</u>
<u n="805" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="806" who="S0190">and they've got a fridge freeze to bring back so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has had to erm pay for one erm I think he's paying thirty-five pounds for a day and then obviously all the fuel on top of it</u>
<u n="807" who="S0192">mm all the fuel</u>
<u n="808" who="S0190">well they're down in <anon type="place"/> so he's got to go from <anon type="place"/> up up to <anon type="place"/> from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> and then all the way back again so god knows how much they're going to</u>
<u n="809" who="S0192">no so he's moving to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0190">no no no my <trunc>bro</trunc> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="811" who="S0192">oh okay</u>
<u n="812" who="S0190">and because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s going to he's got some of the stuff down in his <trunc>gas</trunc> erm garage</u>
<u n="813" who="S0192">they've got to pick it up</u>
<u n="814" who="S0190">he's then got to pick it up so it's easier for Rob to have it there than have to go backwards and forwards</u>
<u n="815" who="S0192">and where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going to be living?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="817" who="S0192">so he's staying local but just</u>
<u n="818" who="S0190">yeah he's not going far</u>
<u n="819" who="S0192">yeah no</u>
<u n="820" who="S0227">yeah he's not going far</u>
<u n="821" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="822" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="823" who="S0192">what's his place like that he's moving into?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0190">it's nice it's erm it's like a modern middle terrace</u>
<u n="825" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="826" who="S0190">so erm yeah and its three bedrooms bathroom</u>
<u n="827" who="S0192">oh nice</u>
<u n="828" who="S0190">two double rooms</u>
<u n="829" who="S0192">and he's living with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still are they still together?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0190">yep yeah yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0192">they've been together for a long time now</u>
<u n="832" who="S0190">they have now yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0192">do you see children on the horizon?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0190">not that side no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yes but not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="835" who="S0192">why do you think not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0190">well eventually but not the near future no they were I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got an awful lot with work at the moment</u>
<u n="837" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just focused on other things</u>
<u n="838" who="S0190">he's uh changing direction with work and everything so</u>
<u n="839" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0190">what with all that and then on top of that erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s job is sort of she likes it but it's not really what she wants to do so I think no and also she's quite um what can I say you know it sounds horrible it doesn't mean I don't mean it horribly in any way she younger</u>
<u n="841" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="842" who="S0190">she's still quite happy to enjoy going out with her friends and doing all this so I don't see and I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is ready for children at all</u>
<u n="843" who="S0192">no that's fair</u>
<u n="844" who="S0190">so</u>
<u n="845" who="S0192">that was very diplomatically put she's younger</u>
<u n="846" who="S0190">no but she is isn't she?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0227">she's <trunc>chon</trunc>chronologically eh and emotionally younger</u>
<u n="848" who="S0192">than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="849" who="S0227">she's not young young but she's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s probably more savvy more a <trunc>bi</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> head's head is older than his shoulders</u>
<u n="850" who="S0192">yeah but</u>
<u n="851" who="S0227">where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is probably about right or slightly younger but <trunc>she</trunc> I mean she's not immature she's just the the focus is different</u>
<u n="852" who="S0192">I understand</u>
<u n="853" who="S0227">the focus is different</u>
<u n="854" who="S0190">what's that purple Oxo?</u>
<u n="855" who="S0227">that's beef er or is it lamb beef lamb</u>
<u n="856" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no it's not</u>
<u n="857" who="S0192" trans="overlap">beef or lamb</u>
<u n="858" who="S0227">it's lamb</u>
<u n="859" who="S0192">are the cubes lamb?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0192">like er sorry are the cubes purple when you open it?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="863" who="S0192">cos I asked for mum to send me out some lamb and she sent me out green ones it didn't come in a box it was just green wrappers and I thought that green was vegetable</u>
<u n="864" who="S0190">it is</u>
<u n="865" who="S0227">yes it would be</u>
<u n="866" who="S0190">but it's there's the vegetable ones in there</u>
<u n="867" who="S0192">so I've been cooking and it hasn't even been lamb this whole time it's been vegetables</u>
<u n="868" who="S0227">you can smell the you can smell the lamb it's it's lamb stock</u>
<u n="869" who="S0192">but I'd never had lamb stock before so I just it was kinda like a it didn't look like vegetable stock either it was like a light brown colour and I was just like a light brown colour and I was just like</u>
<u n="870" who="S0227">brown yeah it's</u>
<u n="871" who="S0192">something weird</u>
<u n="872" who="S0227">yeah it it's</u>
<u n="873" who="S0190">no cos we had to get</u>
<u n="874" who="S0192">cos sometimes you have lamb with mint don't you? so I thought maybe they made it green</u>
<u n="875" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><trunc>sm</trunc> yeah smell that open that open that and smell that</u>
<u n="876" who="S0190">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="877" who="S0227">because that's going in here that I put lamb and beef in</u>
<u n="878" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="879" who="S0227">can you smell the lamb?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0192">good</u>
<u n="881" who="S0227">can you smell the lamb?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0192">yeah I love lamb</u>
<u n="883" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0192">do you have your password to your Wi-Fi?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0227">er yeah but it's a huge one it's cos it's it's a</u>
<u n="886" who="S0192">is it on the on the router?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0227">it's not even a <trunc>we</trunc> erm it</u>
<u n="888" who="S0192">what do you call that box?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0227">erm it's a router</u>
<u n="890" who="S0192">yeah so you don't use the American for everything</u>
<u n="891" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="892" who="S0192">the router</u>
<u n="893" who="S0227">no only the words that suit me</u>
<u n="894" who="S0192">yeah you just pick and choose</u>
<u n="895" who="S0227">yeah I've got it but we'd have to get it erm</u>
<u n="896" who="S0190">can't remember it off the top of his head</u>
<u n="897" who="S0192">well after dinner</u>
<u n="898" who="S0227">no it's a huge it's it's our names and birthdays er for you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0192">oh wow</u>
<u n="900" who="S0227">it's a tough tune to so it it'll be a case of cut and pasting it eh and them erm</u>
<u n="901" who="S0192">well if I could grab that after dinner that'd be great</u>
<u n="902" who="S0190">are we having dinner before midnight tonight?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0192">yeah I'm hungry what's taking him so long?</u>
<u n="905" who="S0190">yeah it's taken ages</u>
<u n="906" who="S0192">he could have asked for my help but he didn't want it</u>
<u n="907" who="S0190">oh no</u>
<u n="908" who="S0227">no it's you're a guest</u>
<u n="909" who="S0190">he doesn't like help</u>
<u n="910" who="S0192">yeah but I offered I offered</u>
<u n="911" who="S0227"><unclear/> on</u>
<u n="912" who="S0190">he likes to do it himself</u>
<u n="913" who="S0227">you're a guest not a</u>
<u n="914" who="S0192">I can get you filling out forms in the meantime if you'd like to where be my bag actually?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0227">your bag's in you in the bedroom</u>
<u n="916" who="S0190" trans="overlap">in your bedroom it's across from your bed</u>
<u n="917" who="S0192">okay I'll be back in a mo can't bring this so</u>
<u n="918" who="S0227">right this'll be ready in about erm fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="919" who="S0190">sorry</u>
<u n="920" who="S0227">fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="921" who="S0190">before tea?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0227">yeah I my mistake I put the erm I put the kidney beans in late I should've put them in earlier and they're very hard</u>
<u n="923" who="S0190">oh yes please I'd rather wait that bit longer and have them</u>
<u n="924" who="S0227">yes that's what I I was thinking it's got erm apparently they've got a game it it's you like games it's probably not a the topic you won't like but it's supposed to be a puzzle solving thing erm that erm he's going to bring over tomorrow and we'll play it'll take a couple of hours it's the says it's battlestar galactica but it's actually you've got a you're working out who the cylon is so basically it's like a a mystery you've got to work out who the person is so you like things like that so forget about the the</u>
<u n="925" who="S0190">topic</u>
<u n="926" who="S0227">the topic I was just saying about that game that you were going to bring over tomorrow</u>
<u n="927" who="S0192">oh yeah if you're happy to play it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0190">yeah I</u>
<u n="929" who="S0192">it'd be great it's a sci-fi series that we'd all watched but it it's it's just a board game really and</u>
<u n="930" who="S0190">that's fine</u>
<u n="931" who="S0227">it's trying to find out who the cylon is or something</u>
<u n="932" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's quite fun yeah yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0227">so it's a mystery kind of a working out the</u>
<u n="934" who="S0192">there's there's the first round one person is given you're each given a loyalty card and there's only one cylon in the whole game of four people and you get the loyalty cards twice in a game so potentially at the beginning nobody's a cylon but you don't know</u>
<u n="935" who="S0190">what is a cylon?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0192">a <trunc>cy</trunc> is a bad guy just a baddy</u>
<u n="937" who="S0190">oh right</u>
<u n="938" who="S0192">like the robot bad guy so</u>
<u n="939" who="S0227">but they look human</u>
<u n="940" who="S0192">but it follows the series cos in the TV series they look human so you can't tell that they're cylons and sometimes they don't even know they're cylons the yet switched on later</u>
<u n="941" who="S0190">I'm not going to need to know this am I?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0192">no no</u>
<u n="943" who="S0190">I'm not at a disadvantage</u>
<u n="944" who="S0192">you don't need the back story</u>
<u n="945" who="S0190">alright then</u>
<u n="946" who="S0192">would you fill one of these out? would that be okay? dad will need to as well once I get these</u>
<u n="947" who="S0227">I'll let you fill mine out cos er <trunc>ta</trunc> and I'll sign it</u>
<u n="948" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="949" who="S0227">yeah I'll take it <unclear/> ready</u>
<u n="950" who="S0192">erm one once you've signed this once I don't have to do it again it's just the first time you use you need to sign it</u>
<u n="951" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0192">so today's date is the</u>
<u n="953" who="S0227">twentieth</u>
<u n="954" who="S0192">twentieth of August I might move up here with you</u>
<u n="955" who="S0227">er right what do I need erm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0192">twentieth August what happened</u>
<u n="957" who="S0190">I if I ever just catch it when open my glasses and pinch</u>
<u n="958" who="S0192">oh your skin oh not nice</u>
<u n="959" who="S0190">do you write the month in words? so what do we say?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0192">yeah they're a little particular</u>
<u n="961" who="S0190">so what do we say it was the twentieth</u>
<u n="962" who="S0192">twentieth of August yeah two thousand and fourteen full name family name you're a <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> then dad? you're going as a <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="964" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="965" who="S0190">this is going to look good isn't it?</u>
<u n="966" who="S0192">not at all how old are you then pa?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0227">er almost fifty-five now</u>
<u n="968" who="S0192">so you're fifty-four</u>
<u n="969" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="970" who="S0192">fifty-four anything special for this year cos obviously I'm around</u>
<u n="971" who="S0227">sorry erm</u>
<u n="972" who="S0192">if you're doing anything I can come back up to <anon type="place"/> or</u>
<u n="973" who="S0227">yeah erm probably I don't think I'm going to do anything actually do be fair</u>
<u n="974" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="975" who="S0192">well I'd like to take you out for a meal or something</u>
<u n="976" who="S0227">I'm thinking about going to get <unclear/> I I haven't even looked into that yet <unclear/> and that but I let's go out for a meal that might be nice</u>
<u n="977" who="S0192">yeah well either I'll come back up here or you guys could come up to <anon type="place"/> or else go up there or whatever</u>
<u n="978" who="S0227"><anon type="place"/> we'll probably wait come up to you before Christmas not after Christmas</u>
<u n="979" who="S0190" trans="overlap">mother tongue English British</u>
<u n="980" who="S0192">sorry?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0190">sorry he was speaking that's my fault mother tongue English British</u>
<u n="982" who="S0192">what do what do you think? just write down whatever you think so what would you say</u>
<u n="983" who="S0227" trans="overlap">mother tongue</u>
<u n="984" who="S0192">if somebody asked you what your mother tongue is</u>
<u n="985" who="S0190">English</u>
<u n="986" who="S0192">English then write English</u>
<u n="987" who="S0227">she speaks it like a native</u>
<u n="988" who="S0192">dad you male or female</u>
<u n="989" who="S0227">erm one hundred percent a hundred and ten percent male</u>
<u n="990" who="S0192">hermaphrodite birth place</u>
<u n="991" who="S0227">erm <anon type="place"/> erm <trunc>pen</trunc> erm erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="992" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that's a county</u>
<u n="993" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="994" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/> mother tongue English</u>
<u n="996" who="S0227"><foreign lang="spa">Inglaterra</foreign></u>
<u n="997" who="S0192">which country has most influenced your language or the way you speak? I mean you were saying earlier a bit of American</u>
<u n="998" who="S0227">America American yeah</u>
<u n="999" who="S0192">so would you say you're kind of <trunc>affe</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0192">by American dialect</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0192">so I'm going to say English American dialect</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0190">accent</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0192">what would you consider your accent?</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0190">I don't think I particularly have an accent</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0192">well you told me earlier that you have a bit of a <anon type="place"/> twang</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0227">well she uses some of the <anon type="place"/> words possibly</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0190">well but then it's not really an accent is it?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0192">again this is your perception</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0190">right</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0192">they might even be interested in what do you think your own accent is over what it actually is so what's your</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0227">I wouldn't say I wouldn't say I have an accent</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0192">so if I asked you dad what's your accent or your dialect?</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0227">I don't have one I don't think er</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0192">okay interesting I don't have one</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0227">I don't really have one I night have one but I wouldn't know it</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0190">I had to think about that</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0192">linguistically you absolutely have one everyone has an accent but because you believe that you have Received Pronunciation which is the the elite form that that's having no accent or dialect</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0192">everyone has an accent everyone has a dialect</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0190">so how many months or years have you lived there as in the town or the country</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0192">it's a very debatable question that everyone's been getting confused by that I got people to draw a little arrow and did the one for the country and then did an arrow for the town if it was different</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0190">right okay so</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0192">I guess if you've lived in the same place your whole life you could just write one but if you've lived in England longer than you've lived in <anon type="place"/> then maybe write two</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0190">right</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0192">with a little arrow</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0190">England fifty-five years</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0227">you've been in <anon type="place"/> quite some time now haven't you?</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0190">and in <anon type="place"/> erm well they're not going to check are they so I'll just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1031" who="S0192">yeah just roughly</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0190">I think it's about thirty-five years</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0192">how long have you lived in <anon type="place"/> for dad?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0227">er about almost nine years</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0192">nine years do you speak any other languages what do you think he'll say?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0190">Spanish French</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0192">French and Spanish if yes give further details how how well does he think he speaks it?</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0190">education secondary school college sixth form college</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0192">how well do you think dad will er say he speaks French and Spanish?</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0190">what would you say are you beginner intermediate advanced</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0192">er</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0190">beginner</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0227">I wouldn't say advanced I wouldn't say beginner either I can hold a conversation</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0192">intermediate? lower intermediate? upper intermediate</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0227">intermediate</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0192">just intermediate</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0227">in French I can have a conversation in set pieces that I would know</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0192">that would probably be lower intermediate</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0227">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0192">I would say I'm lower intermediate in Spanish</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0192">education you went to secondary school?</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0192">did you go to sixth form or college?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0227">I went to <trunc>u</trunc> er college at work but er not at with school I did that further education when I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0192">yeah that's fine that counts as college</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0227">yeah that's <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> college in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1060" who="S0192">what's your job title</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0227">erm I'm now a customer services agent</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0192">customer</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0192">services agent</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0227">yeah I'm the only one</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0192">topic of subject <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> here I think because we covered so many things just write various</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0190">oh right okay</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0192">right you need to do this bit dad</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0227">what's that sign?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0192">sign name in block capitals date and your contact details so either a postal address or an email address cool and then I don't have to bother you with that again given your email address?</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0192">so obviously if they contact you at some point which I don't think they will but they may just send you out an email or a letter just saying can you confirm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0192">that you did were a part of it then just say you were</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0227">can you read that is that legible</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0192">er more or less yeah more or than less</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0227">my handwriting is not brilliant</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> follows in your footsteps on that one as well</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0192">my handwriting's the same as mum's I guess cos</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I <trunc>do</trunc> I guess I'm not calligrapher calligraphy guy</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I guess cos she taught me to write everyone says I have really girly handwriting so</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0227">well girl's handwriting's actually better than boys'in my view</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0192">I mean I'm being extremely legible here I'm not</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0227">alright well I've done all mine in black capitals cos they're all <unclear/> forms</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0192">yeah that's the west best way to do it</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0227">okay signed dated</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0192">perfect</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0227">and address</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0192">thank you very much a done deal you went to secondary school as well so I'm just going to tick that off</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0190">oh sorry</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0227">actually she she had a private education it was private</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0192">oh so does that not count? in secondary school</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0227"><unclear/> private you were privately educated weren't you? you were at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0227">which is a private school</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0190">well what difference does that make it's still secondary isn't it?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0192">it's still <unclear/></u>
<u n="1099" who="S0227">well it's not well I well yeah I suppose so but it's not it's</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0192">it's just a better one</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0227">yeah it's a better one</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0190">no I went</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0192">was it all girls when you were?</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0192">yeah cool thank you very much <foreign lang="spa">muchos gracias</foreign> so I need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0227">have you continued Spanish at all?</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">is me continua Espaol</foreign></u>
<u n="1108" who="S0227">erm or <foreign lang="spa">como no</foreign></u>
<u n="1109" who="S0192">huh?</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0227"><foreign lang="spa">como no</foreign></u>
<u n="1111" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">como no</foreign></u>
<u n="1112" who="S0227"><foreign lang="spa">como no</foreign></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa"/></u>
<u n="1114" who="S0227">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0192">but not so much recently I've been reading a lot of books</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0192">linguistic books erm I haven't had so much time for Spanish</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0227">well you you can forget it I don't think you'll ever go back to Korea to work will you?</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0192">no I'll forget my Korean that needs to fall out of my head</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0227">yes I still obviously remember I you probably get your linguistics from me rather than your mum</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0227">and I remember you know <unclear/> even though I'm these words just stick in my skull</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0227"><foreign lang="kor"/> and erm erm <foreign lang="kor"/> and things like that</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0192">they they've changed a little bit over the years but</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0227">I just I just stay in my head</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0192">it's definitely a useful talent</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0227">well it I just remember words to be fair it's just yeah just remember them</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0192">is it just the three of us tonight?</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0192">just the three of us might pop to the toilet would you mind if I keep recording while we're eating</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0227">that's fine with me I'll try to chew quietly right</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0192">it's actually better for me like now if I can just get a long recording for like an hour or two hours and then I don't have to keep filling out the forms of everyone I talk to with mum I get like ten minutes and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will come in all crazy or something happens</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0227">he's got a little drum kit</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0192">yeah and he started playing it when I was recording</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I said erm <trunc>d</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had asked for a drum kit and we said no he's got a it's cute it's a little it's a proper drum kit it's but it's like a small one but it's still going to make a lot of noise</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0190">do you want water?</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0227">please</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0190">oh</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0227"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1143" who="S0190">and sit <unclear/></u>
<u n="1144" who="S0227">yes I know</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0190">talking instead of working can't do both</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0192">smells good didn't put any mushrooms in it</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0227">no I don't put mushrooms in it</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0192">good yeah I mean you did put mushrooms</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0192">you did put mushrooms</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0227">ah yes I was one oh it's the magic ingredient I'd forgotten</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0192">I put I put in loads of kidney beans when I do it now you were saying you don't do them from erm</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0227">I've forgotten the magic ingredient</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0192">chocolate</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0227">yeah I've forgotten</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0192">you said you don't do them from dried beans</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0227">er no they they're from the tin they're</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0192">they are poisonous but I mean I I do use them dry</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0227">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0192">I have to soak them for a night</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0192">and then I have to boil them for quite a while</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0192">but they're erm</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0227">you're doing it the old fashioned way</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0192">well they were so expensive in Korea to get a can a beans</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0192">whereas I could get a bag of dried beans</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0192">it was much easier same with garbanzo beans chickpeas</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0227">you're you're going to obviously be able to erm get source things much cheaper than er</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0192">yeah I've been really pleased I went to Lidls the other day and was like ah food is a lot more <unclear/> than I've been used to</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0192">sometimes we it was so seasonal that we could buy a kilo of potatoes for fifty P or a kilo of potatoes for four or five pounds it was like</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0192">really changed</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0227">I I once picked up a carrot one I mean it was a big carrot but it was like three pounds for one carrot</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0192">what in in</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0227">in Korea</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0192">if it's out of season it just like shoots but the problem is it can spike from week to week it just like really jumps on us one week you go in and celery's a pound for a bunch the next week it's three or four pound for a bunch</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0227">yeah so there's no <trunc>con</trunc></u>
<u n="1184" who="S0190">do they grow anything like this in the actual country? or is it all imported?</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0192">they that's the thing the the prices my</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0227">they grow everything</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0192">they grow a lot they grow a lot of what they can but there's no way that they're growing as much as they say they're growing the amount of the amount that they eat I don't see where all these farmers are coming from they eat so much pork and I've never seen a pig in the entire country so they must import that from China but they do have farms everywhere they have a lot smaller farms it's not like one person farms everything it's like wherever there's a free spot of land the local people are farming something but it's it's kind of the same crops they do a lot of pumpkin a lot of courgette a lot of chillies and green onion all that kind of stuff but they don't vary on the local farming they don't really vary on what they cook it's just kind of there for their food</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0190">right</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0192">so things like broccoli and cauliflower they are farmed there but not as commonly so they're more expensive and they're more <unclear/></u>
<u n="1190" who="S0227">the seasons</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0192"><foreign lang="kor">subak</foreign> watermelon you can buy humongous I'm not even joking are about that big they're about two pound two pound fifty in the height of the summer but then off season it'll be about twenty pounds for like one thing</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0190">what?</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0192">oh no joke it goes up to like forty thousand yuan like twenty pounds</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0227">god</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0190">did you buy in bulk from school</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0192">yes yeah I have to so I buy celery when it's cheap and then I get home and I freeze the leaves so I use the leaves for like soup and stuff and then I blend with a bit of water the rest of the celery</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0192">and freeze it so then I can use it later I have to do that with coriander as well cos it's really hard to come back</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0227">yes cilantro</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0192">so when I get it buy a lot of it freeze it use it</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0227">yeah it is expensive I tried to grow <trunc>cori</trunc> I mean that little jar will be about in eighty-nine coriander</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0192">coriander</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0227">yeah and that jar of kaffir lime leaves</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0192">mustardy almost</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0227">will will be at the same price all curry leaves</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0192">yeah yeah these are really expensive</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0227">hence that's why</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0192">why I might steal some</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0227">I crop them</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0192">you go in Sainsbury's there's about four leaves in for about ten pound</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0190" trans="overlap">of right yeah</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0227">yeah I mean I've got some dried I you <trunc>co</trunc> I don't actually use dry I like to have it freeze and thing but I you can have all it should be okay cos this is hot and they were dried they should be</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0192">yeah I'll have those for sure if I can have some fresh ones too</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0227">yes I'll give you fresh but you can have all those as well</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah well that's what I've been using I've been using dried ones</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0227">so you'll have fresh and freeze them straight away</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0192">the only lemongrass I've had was dried as well</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0227">yeah freeze it straight away</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0192">freeze the <trunc>dry</trunc> the fresh ones</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0227">the ones that I bring down with me on that day froze freeze that</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0192">but you don't have any tamarind?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0227">no I got</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0192">galangal?</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0227">no I I have used galangal but galangal's like ginger that's palm trees</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0192">yeah it is the same as ginger</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0192">I told that to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he said he wasn't cooking these recipes because</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't like stuff that's too sweet so I don't use <trunc>t</trunc> I haven't used tamarind myself but obviously if you made dish she would she would she would eat it</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0192">the curry that I want to cook is erm probably my favourite curry ever</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0227">is it massaman?</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0192">in no no it's an Indonesian curry called a rendang and you take I get like a kilo of beef steak I really tenderise it and then cook it really high erm take that off and then the sauce is really easy to make but it's the same as any kind of other green curry you've got your onions red chillies in this one erm ginger or galangal kaffir lime leaves lemon grass tamarind it does have so it's a bit sweeter but the spices that go into it is it has a lot of cinnamon in it has a lot of cardamom in it which gives it a real lemon kick</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0192">and it has quite a bit of clove in it as well</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0192">erm but you normally for me clove is really really strong</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0227">no nuts</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0192">no it doesn't have any nuts</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0227">no cos I was going to say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't like nuts in <unclear/> you don't like nut do ya?</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0192">massaman no not the rendang</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0190">I like nuts but don't like I don't like the the peanut curries</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0192">no and then you just add a lot of coconut cream cook it really really low for about four hours so all of the sauce goes away until there's just a thick dark browny red paste that's on it and right at the end you turn it up really high and caramelise the the beef in its own fat and it's so good</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0227">sounds nice</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0192">it's so flavoursome it's like way more flavoursome than almost every other curry I've ever had but it is sweet the cinnamon and the tamarind does make it kind of sweet</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0227">have you got two room</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0192">it's countered by the clove though</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0227">two bedrooms in your house</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0192">no one seven hundred and fifty pound a month one room</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0192">it's quite spacious though everywhere we were looking</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0190">the rooms look quite big on the pictures you sent</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0192">oh did you see the photos yeah?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0192">it won't be amazing but it was really problematic trying to find a flat from out there and I'm glad we did it in advance</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0227" trans="overlap">from from the other side of the from the other side of the world yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0192">yeah nobody trusted us local landlords would lead us along and they'd be like no I want someone local and I'm like telling them I've got the money I can give you the money right now</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0227">and and and we're teachers you know did you go to school</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0192">they basically just ignored us and just were like you're foreign I don't trust you effectively and then same through the letting agency they didn't really trust us either so we had to have so much paperwork behind us and like it was a real stress getting everything sent over and</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0192">I had to get my bosses involved in Korea and you know they tell you they want erm your bill statements to prove that I'd been living in this residence in Korea and I'm telling them I don't pay for bills it's all included in my thing</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0227">it's all yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0192">okay well we want bank statements from your bank I don't get bank statements in Korea we don't have them</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0192">so having to go into the bank and ask for special forms and</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0227">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0192">like scanning and all this</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0192">it went on and on and on and then they failed us so we sent them all this information I sent them the details of how much savings I had which was easily enough for the whole year</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0192">and they failed us but they didn't tell us they failed us and then what really annoyed me is this third party company this this agency that reference checked us was not allowed to tell us the result they could only tell the agency and the agency were like on holiday so they wouldn't tell me what the result were and I'm thinking I paid you I gave you a lot of my personal and sensitive information</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0192">and and you're telling me that you can't you're not at liberty to give my information so if the reason they do it is because the letting agency can just tell you what they want to tell you so even if this company passes me they can still request that I get guarantors and all these kind of things</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0192">so they can still fail me so they do that system so it's at their discretion to</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0190">I suppose though it's like everything isn't it? all these like erm health and safety and all that it's all done because people have messed people around</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0190">and they've got to find a way to cover it</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0192">I think it's done as well to make more jobs we we need more there's more and more people we need more and more jobs so you get inspectors inspecting inspectors doing something else cos you need to make the jobs so it keeps being more and more third middle men</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0192">cos you need to put somebody in the middle to make another job</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0190">yeah somebody you can blame</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0192">so</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0227">another middle man <unclear/> middle men everywhere they make them you'll sit here?</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0192">yeah I'll sit there</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0192">so I found out why they erm failed me and my savings hadn't been in my bank account for long enough on the the thing is I sent them savings from like months ago and I had the money in my account then but the most recent one I had nothing in my account really and then the money appeared in my account only a few days before now if they told me this before failing me I'd have rectified the problem I'd have been like yeah I'll send you you know I'll tell you why but actually I'd just come back from Cambodia and in Cambodia I don't keep all my savings in the bank account I'm using because that would be dangerous if somebody takes my bank card empties my account</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0227">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0192">so I move it to my own digital account</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0192">and then when I got home I move it back in again</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0192">so I explained that to them and I sent them copies of the digital account I moved it into so we got passed in the end</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0192">it was just a lot of effort it went on for about two weeks of solidly calling them and you know</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0227">bit of a palaver yeah</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0192">it was a real palaver I thought it would be easy I thought if I come home with enough money to pay for my rent twice out you'd think you'd think they'd just be like</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah you think money talks you think money talks</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you're a student</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah go for it but no they just went no so we managed to get around I didn't want dad to have to go through the hassle of a guarantor so we ended up paying I've paid them eight months in advance</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0227">yeah although <trunc>that</trunc><trunc>the</trunc>that was an available with this so yeah I did say I'd do that</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0192">it was just and for us I didn't want another week of stress thinking is dad going to be passed is this going to go through</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0190">yeah is your dad going to be passed yeah dodgy</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0192">I didn't want him to go through the same rigmarole that we just had to go through so</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0227">neither do I</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0192">well like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents were really happy to do it but we were genuinely concerned that they might fail <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad is retired and never had earned very much</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0192">so his pension wasn't particularly high and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum works part time</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0192">so</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0190">and the oven's hot don't touch the plates alright</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0192">I was not convinced that I wasn't convinced <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents were gonna pass and then if we fail our own reference and they fail a reference we're definitely not going to get it</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I was gonna say you don't get no</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0227"><unclear/> right</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0192">well thankfully that's in the past <pause dur="short"/> are we having it with rice?</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0227">yes yes</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0192">looking forward to it hungry</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0227">yeah sorry for the delay guys it was I put the beans in too late</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0192">no don't be silly</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0227">I'd already put them in simmering in the process if I can like go just here by myself just hand's like normally what happens when I cook and the weather's okay and I'll be doing something in the garden so I I I go for a methodical way of doing things</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0227">If I start talking the <trunc>meth</trunc> the methodology gets a bit erm it will all go in I don't hence the chocolate I forgot the chocolate</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0190" trans="overlap">busy talking and you forget the</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0227">but I remember it in time it's just that not in the sequence that I would have done it</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0192">yeah last few times he's picked me up we've gone a bit wrong on the journey</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0227">on the sat nav yeah</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0192">overshot that one overshot this one</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0227">yes I mean hopefully you're unfamiliar</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1329" who="S0192" trans="overlap">fun to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1330" who="S0227">unfamiliar road talking and the sat nav's screaming at you as well it's too much information coming in</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0192">well nowadays it seems with the sat navs that people cannot pay as much attention to you get caught talking whereas I think before the sat navs probably at the time dad've been like I need to do this bit now I need to concentrate here we can't talk now</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0190" trans="overlap">concentrate yeah</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0192">but instead we're like oh the sat nav'll tell us and we'll just go on cos mum did exactly the same thing with erm</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0227">did she pick you up or?</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0192">yeah she <trunc>pi</trunc> she picked me up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and erm</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0227">oh right okay</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was navigating with the sat nav and we were talking and they went wrong and sat nav <trunc>s</trunc>sent her down some wrong road and we had to go back up the junction a few miles and then come back again</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0190">mm <unclear/> we did that when we were going to erm <anon type="place"/> with my sister</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0190">and we were in convoy the two cars and we just it's such a bad turn off to the airport</u>
<u n="1341" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0190">when you get there that erm and we missed it and we had to go ten miles out of our way to come back</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0192">oh god</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0227"><unclear/> didn't we laugh?</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0192">so it's another twenty miles <unclear/></u>
<u n="1346" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0227">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1348" who="S0190">no we didn't laugh dear</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0227">at the time that's what I meant I was being er I was being sarcastic</u>
<u n="1350" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1351" who="S0227">at the end of the day it was just a simple mistake and you go okay fine better go down turn round but oh christ it's almost ten miles to the next junction and then we've gotta come back up again so you're thinking okay we left a reasonable time for the plane you know</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0227">but you don't want to be pushing it right to the wire</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0192">that's where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would come unstuck he was still last minute dot com travelling</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0192">he really was</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0192">he nearly missed his flight twice twice he was so close</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0192">the first time he came to meet me and I told him before don't take the <trunc>b</trunc> night bus up the day of that you fly like get to Bangkok a day early and spend the night in Bangkok recuperate and fly the next morning he didn't do that</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1362" who="S0192">so his bus arrived you know like he only had about twenty minutes to get to the airport to like sort it out and then on the way home when he was going back to Thailand</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0192">I said to him book your flight in advance</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0192">you know make sure you can get it cheaper and get it all sorted</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0192">of course he didn't do that the night before the flight ten o'clock at night</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0192">still hasn't booked his flight</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0192">and now the the Wi-Fi's not working properly</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0227">yes yeah he</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0192">he gets a bit stressed out about that</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0227">he he he does erm</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0192">and then he barely made that flight either because he again he decided to take an eight hour bus journey</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0192">on the same day as his flight</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0192">so I was telling him you're you're what if you get stuck in traffic or you</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0192">you're one hour late or two hours late you're not gonna make it</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0227">mm mm</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0192">and he again had to rush and like made it with like</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0192">five minutes to go</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0227">well it's just er you're putting yourself under a lot of stress</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0192">it's gonna end up costing you more money</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0192">cos it's gonna things are gonna go wrong</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0227">yeah I'm glad that he</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0192">guaranteed</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0227">he was talking about going to Spain to see this girl and I said cos I was a bit concerned that he might get derailed from the mission but <unclear/></u>
<u n="1394" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I was thinking that too</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0192">just starts travelling and not really</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0227">yes but he the the mission was you know he gave up work because he er had the goal and the er and the the the the means to achieve that goal the vehicle to achieve that goal was going to university to <trunc>d</trunc> get a degree</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0227">you know? but if he got side-tracked with either the the Spanish <foreign lang="spa">conchita</foreign> or someone at university was gonna divert him from that mission he had to remain focused yes have some fun and especially like the first week when you have <trunc>re</trunc> fresher and stuff like that but the mission wasn't to meet you weren't going to university to meet girls</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1401" who="S0227">you were going to go there to get a degree you can get the</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's an ancillary mission</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0227">yeah you can get the girls afterwards you know there'll be always girls available</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0227">so get your erm but he was concerned initially about he delaying it and I was saying look delay it because you're not gonna be an old student not by any stretch and but you're gonna be older than a few of you <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>p</trunc>peers and so the these young ladies'll all look up to you anyway as a bit of a man of the world</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0192"><unclear>yeah yeah definitely</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0227">cos you will be a bit of a man of the world compared to them</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0227">but erm obviously once <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got it into his head I said well as long as you've you've mapped it out and you can afford to do it I've I've given him a I'm giving him a customary cursory erm some money in September</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0192">yeah he told me <unclear/></u>
<u n="1411" who="S0227">because I couldn't do nothing for him when I I didn't give you money but I gave you something else I gave you the the house and and I would pay the bills and I thought erm I can't just <trunc>d</trunc>do nothing</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0192">there was a bit of a catch twenty-two though with that house</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0192">because the only reason I was staying in the house was to save money to go to university had I had the</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0192">money to go to university I wouldn't have needed to stay</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0192">in the house</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0192">I mean I'd have just gone I would've gone to uni it was a bit of a catch twenty-two</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it was it was the <trunc>on</trunc> I know it was the only way er that I could actually do something</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0227">you know</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0192">I realize that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1425" who="S0227">by holding onto the place and continuing to to pay the bills</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0192">I'm definitely glad you did I don't know where I would've gone</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0192">I think had you sold that place and moved to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1429" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0192">I wouldn't have lived with mum I wouldn't have lived with you I don't think I'd have made it to uni I'd have probably just</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0227">though your life <trunc>pr</trunc>probably erm erm your</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0192"><unclear/> become an alcoholic on the local banker's draft or whatever</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0227">well they obviously the the breakdown of your er er your mum's and I's marriage forged you to be the kind of person you are now you would've been different er like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is different <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> before this <trunc>w</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was very extrovert</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0227">you were not you were you were but he was much better er he was a much better</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0190">is that alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0192">yeah that's brilliant thank you very much</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0227">erm you were more <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was er was your warm up act and you were the main deal</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1440" who="S0227">so you were like on holiday and you can see it in like erm erm Gran Canaria that he er er gets to know the people you get the know the people through him and then you come into your own element</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0192">mm at least at that age things might've been different</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0227">it it it knocked him he he <trunc>n</trunc> it <trunc>hi</trunc> it knocked his confidence it it's forged you both in different ways you you both would not be the same person you are now erm you would be different you probably wouldn't have travelled you probably wouldn't you know have done what <trunc>y</trunc> what you've done so</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0192">I hope I would've travelled</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0227">erm you've no no I'm on about as extensively</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0227">as you have you've travelled massively for your age erm so bon apptit</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0192">thank you very much</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0227">erm so erm</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0192">do you have any cheese? I really like cheese on my chilli</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0227">er <trunc>y</trunc>yes we have er I I've</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0192">don't worry if you don't but if you did it would be great</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0227">I'll get the grater</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0192">do you hang on is this the thing that you keep in the drying cupboard or something?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0227">erm no underneath the boiler</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0192">oh it's in there? do you mind me having cheese?</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0227">no it's like it's sacrilege it's like pouring tomato ketchup on it</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0192">cheese cheese on your chilli?</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0227">no I don't erm</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0192">not at all</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0227">I do have crme frache on it every now and again</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0192">yeah it's good with something some kind of erm something creamy sort of</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0227" trans="overlap">or salsa yeah</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0192">it's nice to have proper cheese again</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0227"><unclear>so</unclear> you you you yeah there there is a possibility you'd have just got a job in in <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> or something and not never ventured you know you would on a Spanish holiday or something like that but</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0227">didn't do what you'd done</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0192">who knows?</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0227">I mean if I would've said fifteen years ago to the pair of you whilst we were paddling er in the rock pools in <anon type="place"/> more just to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> than you because he was younger that in fifteen years time you'll be doing this your brother on er on some beach in Cambodia</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0227">he'd have said what part of <anon type="place"/>'s that?</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> where where's Cambodia? no it was good to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out there it was good to erm get close to him again I think he seems more like a man now</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0227">well he is a man isn't he?</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0190">do you think you'll get to see him much erm when you're actually both at uni?</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0192">I hope so cos</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0190">not that far</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/>'s not too far from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1478" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0192">erm <pause dur="short"/> although saying that I think it's about an hour's drive it's still two hours and forty minutes on the train for some reason it's some ridiculously slow train</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0192">that still costs thirty pounds return or something so but I'll see him as much as I can</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0192">and erm I guess it'll be easier for everyone else to come and visit as well cos we won't be too far away</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0190">well</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0192">from each other so</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0190">well</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0192">you might be able to come <unclear/></u>
<u n="1488" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and <anon type="place"/>'s a nice it's not a bad place to go erm we'll we'll go down there you haven't got a room so unfortunately unless we stayed the night in <anon type="place"/> it's a bit</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0192"><unclear/> I mean you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could have our bedroom and we sleep on the sofa bed the</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0190">we can go to a Holiday Inn or something like that they're only thirty pounds a night</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0192">yeah you could do either but</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0190">can't we? <unclear/> out of your bed</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0192">but failing that</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0192"><trunc>f</trunc> I mean whenever our friends come and stay they're gonna sleep in our bed and we're gonna move into the sofa bed we have American friends that are coming to to stay with us for three weeks</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0227">when are they here?</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0192">in November</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0227">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0192">erm just before they're gonna go back just before Thanksgiving so they're gonna be taking our room up for three weeks</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0192">so we're gonna be used to people doing that</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0192">you know? that won't be a problem erm and then the living room's connected to the kitchenette and everything</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0192">so it's completely private in the bedroom so should you want to I understand if you don't want to</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0190">no no thank you</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0192">but should you want to you can</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0227">see well you're you're you're used to this anyway but erm the traffic in <anon type="place"/> we were going when I was travelling down er erm on the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1509" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1510" who="S0227">front oh my god you know to try and get to the hotel I was er er getting the sat nav</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0192">terrible</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0227">I actually erm recognised one of erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mates the other day we'd walked er out for so he spun round and got me into the hotel I was virtually there but I went oh and I went</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1514" who="S0227">you know cos it was hot the windows were open and er I I called he saw me I saw him and he spun round and er cos it was er we stayed at er in halls you know erm erm for erm we managed to get a deal</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0227">erm so we stayed er there <pause dur="short"/> but nice town but lots of nightlife but obviously that's not gonna probably er appeal to you too much but</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0227">obviously there's er there's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're gonna take them out and you know there there is plenty to do</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0227">er in in in the evenings</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we've already booked a few gigs and we're looking forward to seeing some live music</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0192">we've got a nice jazz band to go to on Saturday evening</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0227">it was quite a nice atmosphere erm being there even you know because it had been a hot summer you know it was like the <trunc>th</trunc>thirty-first of August we went or first of September and it was it was hot you know</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0227">it was still nice when erm two of us laying on the beach the next day</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0192">the beach can be quite busy can't it? no I'm glad you liked it <unclear/></u>
<u n="1528" who="S0227">which was full of stones it's a stoned beach</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0192">yeah it's a pebbly beach mm I'm glad you liked it we <trunc>w</trunc>would rather live somewhere a little touristy I guess it's generally a bit safer</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0227">yeah yes</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0192">a bit nicer but you pay for it</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0192">it's more expensive but it's a good uni we're going to so</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0227">when I took erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to erm <anon type="place"/> er the the complex was erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="1535" who="S0192">he really didn't like it the complex</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0227">I think it the erm I think what he didn't like was the fact that he felt it was too elite</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0192">he did too clinical too elite</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0227">yes too elite</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0192">I don't blame him</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0192">you wanna at least be studying with like-minded people not</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0227">mm I said to him at the end of the day I said you've got to make your decision based on what's best for you not like what's best for me or what's best for er</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0227">cos I think mum was plumping for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1545" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0227">and I could've given a case for <anon type="place"/> because it was a better university but I did think also it <anon type="place"/> will be a lot easier for me to actually get to cos networking to get the network is very bad from here to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1547" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0227">not good erm I got it that I I thought to myself if er you know it's not an easy <trunc>s</trunc>subject you're going to be it's a lovely er you know what sold it was the the facilities were were breathtaking you know? it's like it was amazing er facilities they've got in that university</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0192">I went there quite a bit</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0227">and it's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1551" who="S0192">I used to go swimming there</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0227">yes and it's in <anon type="place"/> it's lovely but getting there and then erm convincing him you know I said erm don't let <trunc>y</trunc>you being at er for uni er er <trunc>u</trunc>uni for just a year convince you to <trunc>d</trunc>do that don't er do what for whatever reasons are best for you to to go to erm to whatever and he chose <anon type="place"/> I said fine wherever it was I er I don't have a problem but I didn't want to er unduly influence him because of er I said to him that either way er it's not me or your mum going to university to do this course because we couldn't</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0192">it's you</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0227">so it's you and you've gotta do whatever it is that er cos I was looking and I'm thinking I'm glad I'm not doing this I'm thinking you know you you get er</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0192">it's interesting that we chose those two universities actually there are have you heard of plate glass universities?</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0192">they were made the sixties and there's only about eight of them</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0192">and they were designed to be the most you know newest revolutionary universities</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/> my one was the first one that was made <anon type="place"/> was the second one that was made and there's like five or six others that were made at this time in the sixties and they're all doing pretty well</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> are like fairly neck and neck</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0192">they're like twenty twentieth in the country</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0192">for some I'm at a really international one about <trunc>ha</trunc> a third of the population is international</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0192">that study there which is pretty high</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0227">which'll suit you cos you're you're kind of geared up for erm</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0192" trans="overlap">one one in three people it pushes their international ranking <trunc>se</trunc> er <anon type="place"/> seems to beat <anon type="place"/> in the national rankings</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0192">but in the international ranking a new one came out yesterday</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/> were <anon type="place"/> was eighteenth in the country and a <trunc>h</trunc> a hundred and sixtieth in the world or something</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0192"><trunc>s</trunc><trunc>s</trunc> <anon type="place"/> wasn't even on it</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0192">so it's not on the list at all</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0192">and like <anon type="place"/> that scores in the top ten in England all the time on the national rankings</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0192">was like four hundredth in the world on the world rankings</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0192">so they must rank them differently I don't really understand how the systems work</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0227">I can only imagine that <anon type="place"/> er er <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> come quite high in the in in er national and international <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1587" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it seems it seems very fixed to me</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0192">when you look at these rankings and like the top twenty in the world are always American and British</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0192">you literally don't see any other country coming into the top twenty ever</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0192">and then top hundred there'll probably be five countries in total</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0227">cos it</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0192">and it's mainly</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0227">it <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="1597" who="S0192">eighty-five per cent American and British</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0227">it will change because nothing stays the same</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0227">is that alright? is that alright?</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0190">yes thank you</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0192">have you been to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0190">not that I I think I have but I can't remember it at all</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0192">it's meant to be nice there I think</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0227">I'm sure I've probably driven through it but I I don't recall</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0192">it's very close to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s family</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0227">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1609" who="S0190">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> coming up to join you at all or?</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0192">yeah I hope so at some point <pause dur="short"/> train's not very cheap between here and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1611" who="S0190">I remember you saying that before</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0192">it's about forty pound and that's a day return <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1613" who="S0227">did your erm did you get a reference from your your school with it?</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0192">my last job?</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0192">yeah they still owe me quite a bit of money <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1617" who="S0227">cos you had to forfeit your erm erm <trunc>w</trunc>with your first time you were out there you got erm flights back and everything didn't you?</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0192">yeah I had to forfeit I lost about five thousand pounds taking that job</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0192">quite a bit of money</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1622" who="S0192">seeing as I was only on about sixteen thousand pounds</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1625" who="S0227">but erm</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0192">it was a better job</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0227">it's a better job and its <trunc>g</trunc> on your CV it will</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0227">be better won't it? sometimes you have to take erm a <trunc>l</trunc> a strategic erm retreat or sideways</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's a top it's a top five hundred in the world uni so</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0192">it's not bad</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0192">seeing as Korea has three hundred unis</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0227">which one did you enjoy the most there?</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0192">oh the uni</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0227">yeah you prefer <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>o</trunc>older students?</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0192">I prefer working with adults</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0192">firstly they have more of a desire to learn and they know what their focus is</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0227">that's why they're doing it they're not there because they have to be</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0192">erm some of the students I teach are</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0192">they're in Korea university's almost mandatory about ninety-five per cent of everyone goes to university it's ridiculously high</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0190">god</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0227">I saw a erm documentary it was it was a there's an American university in North Korea that's funded by them and it's got a few teachers there</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0192" trans="overlap">doesn't surprise me</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0227">erm I think they're what they're trying to do is erm trying to erm put a seed in the upper echelons because all these people at this university were upper echelons' children</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0227">and it was remarkable because this guy was allowed to come in and to the class and ask some questions but obviously he's been he's been vetted what he can say what he can't you know and he said has anyone heard of Michael Jackson? and they were going is he your president? they didn't <trunc>hea</trunc> they hadn't heard of him then but erm even more remarkable one have any of you flown in a plane out of Korea? not one of them and you think if you said that even in a sink erm hole school here replete with council chavs half of them in that <trunc>s</trunc> class would put their hands up and say yeah we've been to Spain or something like that these are the top people's in the country's children</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0192">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1654" who="S0227">they haven't been anywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1655" who="S0192">you only have to take erm South Korea only about twenty years ago there the people were the same</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0192">they hadn't been anywhere even in the eighties they weren't allowed to go abroad unless it was for business</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0192">they couldn't just go abroad for pleasure it's only within the last twenty years</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0227">do you want another spoonful of chilli?</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0192">this is enough for me thanks</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0192">that's fine thank you</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0227">I just need another little spoonful for me</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0227">that's why your waistline looks like yours and mine looks like mine</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0192">I had a big enough plate of food though</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0190">your dad doesn't know when to say no</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0227">I don't have much more I'm quite good now <unclear/></u>
<u n="1670" who="S0190">quite good oh</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0227">I was worse come on I was worse</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1673" who="S0190">I've given up</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0192">has he not improved? no?</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0190"><unclear/> not at all</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0192">he doesn't look as big as I was expecting</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0190">cos he's got a baggy shirt on</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0192">is that what it is?</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0190">shorts don't do up properly trousers don't do up</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1683" who="S0192">use your old postman shorts</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0227">no they're done they're done up er they're done up I did</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0190">and that's I'm not</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0227">I was in a bit of a shock I put some clothes on and they just didn't fit at all before we went on holiday er I've gotta try and get some weight down erm but surprisingly and almost in a pleasing way I'd put weight on my legs and my backside normally</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1688" who="S0227">when I lost weight those were the places it always went even if you didn't want to you know if you wanted to lose weight you were rather <trunc>th</trunc>thinking on your on your on your chest moobs and on your side no they would stay the weight would drop off your backside and off your legs where you didn't want it to</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0227">to come off of or your face but I'd actually put weight on everywhere I <vocal desc="laugh"/> had weight on my legs my arse <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0192">you're going to be a fat old man in another ten years</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0190">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1695" who="S0227">er <trunc>w</trunc> I don't know about that what is difficult I tried to diet but</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1697" who="S0227">the</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0190">see food and eat food believe you me</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> how hard did he try <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0227">well the medication I'm on the the the number one side effect is increased appetite so that er</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0190">that that is the key</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0227">so you're</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0192">you wrote that on there</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1706" who="S0227">so you're actually you're actually you know number one is is</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0192">voracious appetite</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0190">first of all we started with well erm I'll only eat at the weekends</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0190">erm and I won't have any extras don't offer me anything well that's got to a stage where we'll eat the main course and we'll eat two <trunc>p</trunc> lots of pudding in the week as well</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1712" who="S0227">and then we'll have like a cup of coffee and then we'll eat half a packet of biscuits and what have you I've I've gone soft again I had hardened up I wasn't eating anything</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0192" trans="overlap">gone soft indeed</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0227">I wasn't I wasn't I had hardened up but <trunc>y</trunc>you sometimes you just have lapses</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0190">yeah one big lapse</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0192">you sound like you're having more lapse than more of the discipline</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0190" trans="overlap">obviously I'm not yeah <unclear/> I've just let him get on with it now I used to sort of say look watch this and not not offer him er that and everything it doesn't work so we just eat</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0227">well I get smaller portions</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0190">huh</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0227">oh come on I would've I would've had double</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0192">I mean that was quite a small portion you had there wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0190">excuse me</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0227">I would've had double</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0190">yeah he had two bowls last night two bowls of <trunc>f</trunc> of food and then he had a pudding after that</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1727" who="S0190">and then he had biscuits and coffee after it in the evening but I but I can't</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0227">like I said I'm cutting down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1729" who="S0192">well who does the shopping?</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0190">I do</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0227">we do</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0192">buy less</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0190"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1734" who="S0192"><trunc>d</trunc>don't let him have these biscuits and things around just never never buy them</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0227">they're so cheap they're er for the Bourbons they're only about thirty P <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1737" who="S0192">oh Bourbons are good</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0227">they're not the top rate Bourbons</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1740" who="S0227">but they're thirty P</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0190">yeah I know but the thing is you can say don't buy them but then why should I <trunc>f</trunc>forgo it when I eat in moderation?</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0192">no you should</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0190">so</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0192">you need a locked cupboard <unclear/></u>
<u n="1746" who="S0190">no I just hide all the chocolates and things like that don't I? mm</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0227" trans="overlap">she hides the chocolate but actually I've been quite good on chocolate I eat</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0192" trans="overlap">let me know where you let me know where you hide them <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1749" who="S0227">you well</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0192">I need to put on weight don't I?</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0227">you must agree er on the chocolate front I've been quite good I mean like that chocolate in there I haven't been eating it er I know that you've got</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0190">so what about the Kit Kats that we take er and er the big Kit Kats the Chunky Kit Kats and the Bourbons that's not chocolate is it?</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0227">well it is but it's not made of chocolate is it?</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0190">well there you go then</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0227">but I'm on about chocolate like chocolate you know er the Kit Kats once they're er I knew they were gone I didn't bother to try and find your your stash</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0192">he's like an alcoholic isn't he? beer doesn't count beer and wine</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0192">it's only whisky that's bad</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0190">yeah that's right yeah no</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0227">no those I don't do much</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0192">alcoholic that was really good thank you very much</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0227">I got film you can watch if you like if we're going to play a game tomorrow</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0227">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s seen it once before but erm erm she won't watch Game of Thrones</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0192">no?</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1768" who="S0190">I absolutely think that is absolutely</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0227">unless she's been</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1771" who="S0190">urge</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0227">stunned and rendered unconscious <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1773" who="S0190">I'm having a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bedroom when he moves out I'm having all my own television and</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1775" who="S0190">that room up there is going to be a woman cave we've had a man cave and a woman coat so Idol not have to sit through all these programmes er</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0192">I don't blame you</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0190">I don't think we're all I mean as a on a whole there's quite a few programmes that we like erm</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0192">together</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0190">you know together to watch and that but there's so many of the ones that he just is either sitting through a history lesson or they are blood and guts all the time like that Dracula and erm er no</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1781" who="S0227">Breaking Bad series five I haven't seen yet I've got it erm it's all still wrapped in the Blu-ray but I haven't opened it yet I will get round to it</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0192">get that on</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0190">so if I have a room upstairs I can do my ironing I can <trunc>l</trunc>lay my cards and that out and</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0192">the woman cave</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0227">she watched Game of Thrones until erm erm Sean Bean died and he was beheaded and then sudden suddenly it was</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0192">I'm not interested any more</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0227">too much nudism there's too much nudism</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0190">it's not the nudism it's the <trunc>mu</trunc></u>
<u n="1790" who="S0227">it's the swearing</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0190">it like it it's the swearing</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0227">there is a lot of profanity in it</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0190">there is and it's so well you watch it don't you? you know what I'm saying so I just I just won't watch in any more it's just there's no need for it there is absolutely no need we know it goes on we know it did it we don't have to do it every other word and so I'm a bit it's for pleasure I'm not sitting listening to it it's terrible</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0227">sometimes you won't get a swear word in the whole episode but whenever <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes in there to do it ironing somebody will be there there's swearing everywhere it's like they've saved it up for that episode</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0192">just as you walk in</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0192">I can't say I've noticed the swearing in it but I'm quite desensitized to it so I haven't noticed it at all but therefore perhaps I'm at the point where I don't notice it so it doesn't have any effect swear words are disempowered erm then you should be using more accurate adjectives to describe rather than just</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0190">you don't need to there's other words to</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0192">general words</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0227">normally people swear because they have a poor command of the language they just don't know the right adjective to use to describe whatever it is so they use these link words which can mean anything like you said about what</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0227">it can mean anything it doesn't you know they just use that as</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0192">fills a lexical function</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0227">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0192">I think they found though that with swearing it is stored in a slightly different part of the brain</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0192">and you do revert to it in times of intense shock or pain or whatever it just kind of comes out there words are stored in different parts</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0227">yeah like I swore I must have told you this before I'd only it was a first Christmas at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s obviously I'm minding my Ps and Qs and erm I swore at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I I couldn't believe it in front of his her parents I went you bastard but it was a compliment but I couldn't believe I was shocked because I was reading the cards and he didn't have the count hand that I thought he had and he he did have this brilliant hand and I didn't see it and so it was it was a compliment like but I just said you bastard and realised what what I'd said</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0190">my <trunc>he</trunc> my mum and dad do not swear ever</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1812" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they're not released now they don't swear at all</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0190">I don't think my dad has had a couple of choice words in his time but they just don't</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0192">did he take you aside and say I'm not sure if this one's the one you need to get another one</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0227">fortunately I haven't I've managed to repair the <trunc>fill</trunc> the break-mouth filter in that department and I've never ever sworn in their <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1818" who="S0192">presence</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0227">presence again</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0190">we just to go through now everything jesus <trunc>chri</trunc> oh jesus christ so I said we we see my aunty if he does actually happen to be quite religious if you could please refrain from that this time <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1821" who="S0227">I didn't say jesus christ erm</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0190">so we're getting a hold just takes a while</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0227">in poor company I swear quite a lot</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0190">well you <trunc>d</trunc> yeah yeah I I do I I kind of am a bit comedian like I whatever I'm my surroundings are I tend to do <trunc>go</trunc> be driven downward or or upwards depending on</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0192">it has a term it's called accommodation you can either converge or diverge with people</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0192">and you often it's subconscious people don't realise it do they</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you try to to fit you're trying to fit in yeah</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0192">they'll probably be listening to this to see if I'll make my accent sound more like somebody around me to fit in or if I'll diverge from them because I don't want to be seen to be similar to them</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0192">sometimes you'll make you sound more posh because you don't want to sound like that rough guy so you kind of speak</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0227">mm when I'm speaking to the operatives I'm I'm using profound words</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0227">because I'm trying to communicate with them I'm not trying to <trunc>proud</trunc>produce a stand offish erm them and us approach</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0192">you'd rather sound like a savant than an idiot savant</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0227">yeah yeah so I erm I mean I in the office now I I I'm I do tend to in the district manager he calls me brains cos he goes brains look come over here have a look at this and I go what is it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I'll wash up</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0190">no I'll do it</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0227">and he's no it's alright and he's like the district manager he'll default to me on on oh various things I mean him</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0192">Brains from the Thunderbirds? Brains from Piggy and the Brain or?</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0227">we had erm er sometimes the tail tries to wag the dog and one of these guys had made accusations it wasn't at me it was at one of my colleagues and er really what he was <trunc>as</trunc> about five per cent of what he actually put in this cos he loves to grandstand he gives global emails and he's giving it to all the upper echelons and you're thinking that was for upper echelons so why are you bothering me with this rubbish but he likes to they give him oxygen of publicity so he continues to do it but with his erm with his erm accusations is this guy <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm five percent of it was valid the rest of it he was talking it was a complete load of nonsense and I I just said in the mean time I said you know it's not you know <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said well I didn't know I said it afterwards not in his in his presence I said <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was a principle officer in the old school country er my pay grade is scale five which has five scales then you've got scale six which has five scales then you've got SO one which is three scales then you've got SO2 which is three scales and then you have PO one he he's a technician but he's still under protected salary he's in PO1 he was a big cheese at one time er in the authority but now he's just a he's a technician but it's massively it's a bit like erm erm Mr White in Breaking Bad but the other way round he's <trunc>o</trunc> he's extremely overpaid for what he does rather than underpaid</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0227">but he's a clever guy I said to erm I said erm you can an idiot can drive a car it deals with two dimensions you go that way or you go that way he's got a pilot's license I said they don't give pilots licenses to imbeciles you've got to be clever to have a <trunc>pil</trunc> he's got his own plane he's got his own motorbike he's got his own car er you're dealing with you're dealing with three <trunc>dime</trunc> it's it's it's only a small plane but it's a plane he flies it you're dealing with three dimensions and they don't give pilot's licenses to idiots they can I've seen some real dumb driving cars but you don't get stupid people who can fly it's too much going on</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0227">so yes I said yeah and the bloke was talking a load of rubbish he was ninety-five percent of it is accusations worth completely wrong</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0192">unfounded</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0227">he was talking about saying he should have more training the man had been in the job thirty-five years he was a principle officer he doesn't need training at all</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0227">this bloke had only been in the has only been in the line of work for about five years and you're thinking no erm you're the one who's you know I I I just said it a eaten I said why are we giving this guy oxygen and publicity I'd ignore him you know just just ignore him so he's what he's doing he's his his erm is erm reach is exceeding his grasp he's doing things that is not his brief what he's supposed to be doing you know I'm saying that that was annoying me but I was thinking yeah just do what you're supposed to be doing don't start getting involved in other things that you don't you know</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0192">what's happened since?</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0227">er well nothing</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0192">as a result</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0227">nothing does happen really to be fair we we just like erm a report would go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's the top man and that would be about it really but you know you this bloke just gets to sound off and I think to myself no this stick you know er he he's supposed to do a certain job and that's it he's he's trying to <trunc>bra</trunc>branch into yeah he's empire building basically so I think to myself no just ignore him that's what I do</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0192">yeah I mean ignore him then I guess you need to ignore him</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0227">mm mm</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0192">are these plums form the garden?</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0227">indeed</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0192">are these Victoria plums</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0227">they are yeah they are from originally from <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0192">is it the same plum tree?</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0192">same plum tree?</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0227">there was one that was pulled out the front garden</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0192">the cutting yeah</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0227">no I pulled the tree out</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1867" who="S0227">out out the front garden</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0227">put it on here it was the last thing to go on</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0192">I think that one might be a bit mouldy</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0227">yes I think that can be thrown erm it was the last thing to go on the erm removal erm lorry</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0192">yeah sure</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0227">we had a lorry</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0227">we had so much stuff er we had stuff at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s we had stuff at <anon type="place"/> road we had stuff at er I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents' and we had at ours</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0192">was <anon type="place"/> road where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to live in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1877" who="S0227">no <anon type="place"/> road is is another erm erm they got a <trunc>prop</trunc> the company has got a property at <anon type="place"/> which is on the industrial estate but they've also got another property in <anon type="place"/> which they now disuse as storage and that's in <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0227">so just <anon type="place"/> is where um um um they just store stuff erm they don't have to <trunc>rid</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did they ever trade out of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0190">sorry?</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0227">did they did your dad ever trade out of you know do the business from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1882" who="S0190">he <trunc>wo</trunc> he worked but er no it's not doing that now</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0190">it's for storage</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0192">he did</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0227">cos they were based on Bedford do you know <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0227">well there was a place called <anon type="place"/> on <anon type="place"/> road by <anon type="place"/> street erm um um he was close he was next door to that and the he moved to <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/> road is not the nicest part of <anon type="place"/> really</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0227">no but I'm going back thirty years when it you you</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0192">it was probably a bit better</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0227">it wasn't er what it is today</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0192">so rough around the edges</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0227">now and then they moved to <anon type="place"/> erm road in <anon type="place"/> er down by <anon type="place"/> er if you come if you're coming you you've you're driving in towards through <anon type="place"/> you've just gone past <anon type="place"/> on your right hand side</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0227">you come to a set of lights if you turn right that's down <anon type="place"/> road you carry on the first <trunc>r</trunc> the next right where there's a bicycle shop on the corner</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0192">yeah I know exactly where it is</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0227">that's <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0227">so they they had a company down there but then they moved out to <anon type="place"/> and on on to an industrial complex and traded form there</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0192">cool yeah moving all this stiff must've been a bit of a pain in the arse</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0227">well it we it <trunc>was</trunc> the logistics of selling two houses at the same time with erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s being ahead of mind in in in in the curve meant that we had to get all her stuff try and put it into our house</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0192">store it somewhere</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0227">but with two in one of them wasn't going to go so that meant we had to get it into storage which meant then when erm the house sold we then had to move again and get the pull all the stuff</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0227">from different places so selling a house is supposed to be <trunc>sass</trunc> stressful try selling two at the same time and then moving into one knowing that all that hassle forming within six weeks you're going to be doing it again cos normally you think oh god thank god for that won't be doing that for a few more years</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0192">it's meant to be one of the most stressful things isn't it I think moving <trunc>hou</trunc> well moving</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0227">one well one of the most yeah</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0192">moving city I think is more stressful than moving house</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0227">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0192">nah I move I move country every year</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0227">well yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> moved to <anon type="place"/> and moved back here again so that would imagine it won't be long before you start making plans for what happens after the masters to get back on the</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0192">no I'll be applying for jobs after Christmas</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0227">yes good man to that's why that fear with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sees your holidaying but I said you've got to have a job and you know you like it if it I think he saw reason about going to Spain I said if you can't afford it I I romantically I get it but practically you can't cos he was like trying to be a bit evasive about paying mum rent I said you can't really you need to take seize manage that you go to her and say this is money and you sure as hell don't go on holiday again</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0227">and you're not giving her a <unclear/> rent rent while you're there so er eventually she collared him</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0192">I just think it's a bad idea he <trunc>do</trunc> he doesn't want to be going to uni tied up in a long distant relationship</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0192">with some girl that he barely knows</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0227">no no cos I know he's like when he's over here the phone's going ping ping ping</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0192">yeah he's talking to her a lot</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0227">ping ping ping its</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0192">and I suppose in this day and age you can get to know someone pretty well</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0227">without actually ever meeting them</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0192">without actually meeting them but biologically you don't know if your bodies connect I don't think if you know if you actually get along or whatever</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0227">there's a lot of exactly there's when I meet you as the opposite sex there's a lot of things being transmitted between us that we we're not detecting</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0192">no your body's assessing the other person's body</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0227">yes exactly erm pheromones and hormones and all sorts of things that's to coming over on Skype</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0192">no not at all</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0227">yes you don't realise you're you're assessing each other's compatibility even without saying a word</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0192">yeah smell transmits a lot doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0192">I've wondered if</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0227">that's why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> keeps telling me cor your breath stinks</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1937" who="S0192">I've wondered if you know a form of telepathy could be possible if you could hyper you know exacerbate those kind of <trunc>cha</trunc> imagine a creature that was so sensitive to its smells and could exude so many different smells like a cuttlefish sees in different colours and like changing its body its colour if we released different smells for different things and it was able to communicate enough information it would effectively look like telepathy</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0192">it would look like I'm just standing here and I'm able to read things</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0192">that are going off in your body but I'm picking it up through other <trunc>club</trunc> cues</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0227">yeah yeah and you can say that that aside <unclear/> you're talking but</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0227">that stuff</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0192">I didn't realise how complex sign language was until I looked at doing some linguistics research it is grammatically syntactically morphologically as complex as a <trunc>re</trunc><trunc>re</trunc> spoken language it has as much grammar</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0192">it has as much derivation inflation everything it's got it has everything</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0192">it's insane <pause dur="short"/>  it shows you that again they're saying in these book that erm yeah we shouldn't have been homo sapien we should have been homo loctous and it was like one of our most defining features is our ability to communicate</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0192">and as clearly proven it's not just spoken communication either cos if you remove someone's ability to hear then they learn sign language</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0192">they just have to communicate</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0192">there as part of main</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0227">the hardest way to communicate in a in a in a second language is on the phone</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0227">because you're not looking at the person you're not you can use gestures and eye movement and that to help try and describe</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0192">even a bit of lip reading</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0227">to describe what it is you're trying to to convey where on the phone you don't see them it's just the you're dealing with at voice and that's it there's no other communication going on in the background</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0192">it's definitely harder  definitely harder</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0227">the old alarm started pinging again I've got to change those</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0192">fire alarm?</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0227">no the erm burglar alarm I got a</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0192">cos you were broken into weren't you?</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0227">yes hence we got the alarm there's a sensor on that door window there's a bit and there's one on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s on the woman cave door and then we've got two motion sensors one's in the hall one's in the lounge one of these four is battery's gone and it the every night it <trunc>s</trunc> it starts this time isn't it it starts talking</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0190">yeah just for some reason it just</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0227">it starts talking saying</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0192">are you sure I can't help in any way</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0227">yeah no it's fine without the diagnostic it would be good to try and find out the diagnostics of what unit it is</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0192">which one it is yeah</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0227">erm I'll go through replacing all the batteries but the batteries in these ones are round little celery celery job jobbies</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0192">there was a theft in mum's little close the other day</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0227">was there?</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0192">the old lady on on the opposite here</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0227">oh right? the one she sometimes looks after stuff like the cat</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0192">yeah maybe yeah she's some old <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or something they know her</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0192">she had her door kicked down and her handbag stolen or something so there were police round there when I was there the other day</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0227">I <unclear/> I was this <unclear/> cos we had a lamp <trunc>co</trunc> there was quite a few similarities</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0192">are you going to talk about the penis on the lamp <unclear/> again</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0227">yes is that still there?</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0192">I think you've said that every time I've</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0227">why don't they paint that over I paint I'd just go and paint that over for god's sake I'd just say we're not having that we had a lamp column here and we paid probably the most rates in the street cos we're a band E</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0192">yeah I looked at your council tax and saw it was band E because I was looking at different council taxes of different areas I was like what's dad's the biggest one the road</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1987" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah and they took and they took away our <unclear/> outside our house and we've been burgled so you think well it's going back to the dark ages we came out the dark ages erm into the light now it's like oh now we're evolving we're going to get back into the dark you know you think no we're that's what Edison and Teller and that were doing striving to get us out of darkness</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0192">yeah right do you just drink tap water</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0227">I remember one of my colleagues at work he did smile cos I just I didn't give the correct <unclear/> not by a long short but the answer was quite flippant and he started to laugh cos it was quite a good story I said erm do you know what happened in the dark ages I said yes it was dark and it lasted for ages</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0190">excuse me come on</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0227">and he laughed <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1994" who="S0190">you don't need to have that</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0192">yeah I know he's earning me money in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1996" who="S0227">yes I was going to say what's May's my cut</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0192">what's your cut? my presence</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> at least you'll have plenty of material</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0192">yes yeah definitely if I can just do ten more minutes than we've done two hours and I can call it</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0227">right okay must be one of the most loquacious people you know</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0192">oh absolutely your vocabulary is very impressive ah there's still quite a bit left</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0227">yes we'll freeze that</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2004" who="S0227">of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s erm I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday that I was cooking it if you erm you'd like some for</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0192">yeah where is he tonight</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah normally we <trunc>fre</trunc> er pass where where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2007" who="S0190">football</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0227">footy</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0192">he he's still playing or reffing?</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0227">both</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0190">he does reffing coaching and plays</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0192">oh good stuff</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0190">he's got his own team</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0192">his own team is wow</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0190">yeah and he also is at the academy</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0190">and he teaches the coaches there</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0192">so he's really enjoying still?</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0190">he's does <unclear/></u>
<u n="2020" who="S0227">keep him busy</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0192">I imagine he's pretty fit</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0190">he needs to be done he he got his bike line coming up</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0192">yeah yeah in Tanzania</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0192">brilliant is he nervous about that at all</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0190">no it doesn't seem to be</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0227">I think he's up for it he's not nervous but er</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0192">is it raining is that what I can hear</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0192">have you had much rain this year there was a lot of flooding last year wasn't there?</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0227">yes so we had a lot of flooding in the winter</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0190">it was it's been quite good</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0227">it's very erm not for us er because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s illness erm she was cold all the time so I I had the heating on all the time</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0227">you know not twenty-four hours a day but</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0192">a lot</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0227">long periods where we only had two frosts no snow just two frosts light frosts that was it</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0192">oh wow</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0227">it was a very mild winter erm but she was cold all the time so my heating bills erm didn't reflect where normally because I have a erm a spreadsheet erm macro driven it erm I every month at the end of the month I take the gas reading and the electricity reading bit sad but I know how much I'm spending and I can see over the year what the temperature was like so I can tell you was it warmer last June than it was this June cos I'll go and have a look at the gas and I'll have a look at the electricity but the winter</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0192">or are you more sensitive to it</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0227">yeah the winter will give me more of a a a false reading cos like I said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was erm cold all the time</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0227">so you erm I had the heating on from September er onwards you know it it was kicking in all the time keep it warm</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0192">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have basically going to try not using any utilities at all we're not going to have any heating</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0227">that that's going to be a challenge</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0192">well I mean heating wise we survived in Korea with no heating in winters that were much colder than here consistently minus ten</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0227">dry or <trunc>co</trunc> or damp cold?</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0192">erm it was dry cold</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0227">huge difference</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0192">there is a big difference but two degrees three degrees is a big different to minus ten</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0227">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0192">and when I got to erm</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0227">but you were being heated by in a you were in a unit weren't you like <trunc>f</trunc> and the heat was coming <trunc>f</trunc> probably from below you</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0192">trust me I could see my breath in my apartment</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0227">oh god lord</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0192">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I just had duvets wrapped around us the whole time it was horrible in the morning taking shower provided we have hot water for a shower we're okay</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0192">but we're still young we can do that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0227">you didn't have to pay for this stuff though did you?</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0192">no I did in the year prior only the last year</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0192">actually the last year was ridiculous the winter was too hot for me I quite like look forward to being cooler in winter so I can you know have a duvet snuggle up get a leg out that kind of stuff but they kept the heating on throughout the whole winter</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0192">and <trunc>w</trunc> I couldn't control it</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0192">so I was sleeping with a fan the entirety of winter I was still in basically a sheet and a fan</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0227">trying to cool down</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0192">yeah it was terrible as I said I quite like it now I'm back and I can sleep in a duvet and like</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0227">yes yeah</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0192">I like being cool at night not hot</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0227">I always have a leg out erm erm I it has to be really cold for me to bring my feet in</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0192">yeah I mean I've been in consistently I've been in thirty degrees or above for the last four months five months</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0227">yeah so you must notice the temperature drop here</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0192">it's quite cool yeah</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0227">yes it so cool</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0192">it's nice though the skies are really pretty you get these really big skies here with big white fluffy clouds that just change every three minutes</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0227">yes and you're used to boring old blue</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0192">it just every time I come home now I realise how northern England is it feels northern it feels that bit closer to the the the pole</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0227">well we are <trunc>re</trunc> we here we're only fifty-two degrees off not like thirty-four where you were</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0192">I don't know why England isn't part of Scandinavia I really don't</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0227">I mean thank god for the erm Gulf stream cos we'd be really cold if we didn't have that</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0227">cos there's polar there's polar bears at our level in Canada</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0227">so yeah</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0192">I like that sound as well rain on glass it's nice to be somewhere warm and indoor what plants are these <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are you growing something specific?</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0227">that's a lily a lily</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0192">they're lilies</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0190">the other one I'm not sure it's sort of like a daisy isn't it?</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0192">so this one is a lily pretty lily</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0227">did you see the kaffir lime before you left or what was it two years ago or not?</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0192">erm it was here I'm pretty sure oh it was definitely here it wasn't that big though</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0227">now oh like <unclear/> it it it it was <unclear/> it was probably only about that big when I first got it</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0192">how big?</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0227">up to about there</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0192">yea it was quite short wasn't it?</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0192">yeah this rain is probably interfering with this quite badly</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0192">even when I just sit in the car it's</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0227">that's something that <unclear/> if you've got a cheap <unclear/> erm <unclear/> roof so rather than having glass you wouldn't hear that that it was acoustically dampened</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0192">yeah it would I think I scanned in that book last time I was home</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0227">one weekend baking yes</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0192">yeah I've got a copy of that</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0227">yes you did you did I think it was</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0192">I scanned in a few cook books yeah I think I've looked a couple of things out of it I make a good cheese cake rum and raisin</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0227">you do erm you do sweet things as well as savoury?</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0192">yeah occasionally birthdays it was Zach's birthday so I cooked him a run and raisin cheesecake</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0192">I didn't think I liked cheesecake but</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0227">cheesecake's nice</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0192">it's very tasty</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0227">rum and raisin sounded very nice I hope there's loads of rum in</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0192">it was good it wasn't too bad I mean I don't think you could put too much rum in it it wouldn't it would just go all</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0192">you know too it'd be too moist wouldn't it? I think it only had like a hundred mils of rum or something</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0227">just to give it the eh the taste</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0192">how is your whisky collection these days?</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0227">erm oh I haven't added to it to be fair er</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0192">have you taken from it?</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0227">er there's er oh dear I think this is you gave me this one this one here I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0192">me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were what?</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0227">you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had this and you brought it over</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0192">me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had what drank it or?</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0227">yeah black label</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0192">oh it's still a little bit left</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0192">is that for me?</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0192">I might have one later you've got a few DVDs</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0227">Jack Daniels I got that from my mate for doing some babysitting ah ah</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0192">oh don't fall</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0227">no <trunc>norma</trunc> access isn't normally a problem</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2135" who="S0227">I like I like I thought I thought this is quite a nice little er</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0192">yeah it is a nice place</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2138" who="S0192">oh you've still got a good <unclear/> that is a terrible ironing board</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0227">I don't use it</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0192">looks horrible does that not like mess with your eyes a bit</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0227">no she covers it I can see I can see what you're looking at it's a bit hypnotic</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0192">it's so it's horrible</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0227">I must iron I must obey or something</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0192">yeah must iron</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0227">didn't I get erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> an ironing board</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0192">you did we just sold it</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0227">didn't you use it as a surf board or something?</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0227">used it to put plants on or something</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0192">no we used it to iron she irons</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0227">cos it was like when you did on your knees or something you kind of was</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0192">yeah that's how they are in Korea they're all really low everything's low</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0192">so these are lilies as well are they</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0227">they're lilies yeah they're hibiscus over there that's I never took that out this year</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0192">that's doing good it's an interesting smell in this room</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0227">yes it's called damp well no it shouldn't be damp now because I</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0192">there you go there's your <unclear/></u>
<u n="2159" who="S0227">took the I took the what's it called there was a a what's it called tree I've still got more bottles in this but yeah</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0192">what's that one? old rod shoe</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0192">never even heard of it I've heard of quite a few oh I've never even tried Glenridge I'd quite like to it's always too expensive Muscatel that's not even wine</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0227">no god knows what it is</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">gran vino dulce</foreign></u>
<u n="2165" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0192">sweet red wine</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0227">so I just don't yeah I don't <trunc>ti</trunc> I don't drink them</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0192">Portuguese something or other Paddy Oldham what?</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0227">I got a there's an ox upstairs</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0192">oh it is whisky it's very clear isn't it?</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0227">yes yeah Irish whiskey</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0192">Irish whiskies do tend to be like that</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0192">I really like Bushmills and that's quite clear</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0227">mm the erm <event desc="sound of breaking glass"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0190">what fell?</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0227">what happened there?</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0192">I'm really sorry I have no idea I barely touched anything</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
