<text id="S3KY">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:45:56</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house, Cambs</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Talking about how much someone likes their job and career professional development ideas.  Young people today. Talking about a colleague at work. </topics>
		<activity>A couple talking about their jobs and other people's jobs</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0261">well I at the time I would have been talking about erm particular well not talking about I would have been talking of particular characters that I was working with yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0262">were they likeable characters?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0261">not really</u>
<u n="4" who="S0262">no they didn't sound very likeable <pause dur="long"/> so you're saying it's more complicated than that</u>
<u n="5" who="S0261">well I <trunc>d</trunc> I I think more the point was that it was erm simply er if you're dissatisfied in your job and you're not getting the opportunities that you're looking for either there's a problem on your side or there's a problem on the other side yeah? and the fact is is that the two of you don't meet somewhere in a zone where you can work together and part of that will be poor management that I had an awareness of what I think modern management is and the people that I was working with didn't operate under modern management they <trunc>o</trunc>operated what I would have thought was cold hard old boy style old-school management styles you know</u>
<u n="6" who="S0262">I know but I love the fact that also you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to go down to the pub every single fucking <event desc="recording skips"/> with a rebellious you know spirit which was I'll fucking turn into work when I want if I don't fucking go into work who cares I'm a fucking contractor I'll go when I want to go there's something that changed in you and you got different you went different about things you got more serious about things and it was around the time you met me</u>
<u n="7" who="S0261">erm well <trunc>wha</trunc>what changed was that I went from being a contractor to being erm a a one of the people on the books with the company and part of the reason for it was that I could see as a contractor people wouldn't choose to take you seriously and allow you to grow in the sense that you needed to</u>
<u n="8" who="S0262">but but contractor suited you in your early <trunc>twenti</trunc> I mean sorry your late twenties because you were your own man you had your own company you know that woman was doing the accounting for you I'm not quite sure who it was or if that <unclear/> you were still actually running your own show you were in control</u>
<u n="9" who="S0261">to be to be fair yeah I suppose you were</u>
<u n="10" who="S0262">you fucking totally were</u>
<u n="11" who="S0261">mm mm yeah you could choose where you wanted to work and all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="12" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you were running through the books yourself you were doing you know you were doing what you want</u>
<u n="13" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0262">and you just went and bought nice expensive cameras you had lovely holidays you did what you wanted to do that was the point</u>
<u n="15" who="S0261">yes exactly</u>
<u n="16" who="S0262">you never</u>
<u n="17" who="S0261">yeah it's a very valid it's an interesting valid point</u>
<u n="18" who="S0262" trans="overlap">really interested in the work really <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come on be honest with yourself you weren't all that interested really the times when you were hanging out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you weren't that interested in your work</u>
<u n="19" who="S0261">if you put that aside look the the fact is is quite a lot of the time when I turned up to work I would do a good job cos I was still at work</u>
<u n="20" who="S0262">I'm not saying you didn't</u>
<u n="21" who="S0261">alright?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0262">when did I say that you didn't do a good job?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and for the majority of the time while I was doing that I I enjoyed the job because I was working with people that I liked yeah? and</u>
<u n="24" who="S0262">that's very true about you</u>
<u n="25" who="S0261">er and and so there were there was a sense of partnership and we got along alright and then of course things changed the management changed and roles changes and so on and so on and so on and you come across different people and different characters and so on you know and and part of the role is trying to mix and match and fit in between the reality is that when you come home that's when you let the steam out when you're at work you act professional when you need to and and otherwise erm you're probably relaxed and getting along with people</u>
<u n="26" who="S0262">yeah but why did that bloke <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the working for PB in <anon type="place"/> why did he rise up the ranks so fucking quickly? why the fuck did he have it all?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0261" trans="overlap">ah because he was a he was a chatter</u>
<u n="28" who="S0262">and and you and others didn't get that fucking chance why did he get it then?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0261">well I mean that happens in all companies you know they they</u>
<u n="30" who="S0262" trans="overlap">is he really that much better than you?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0261" trans="overlap">there are young young people</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262">young people he wasn't that much younger than you</u>
<u n="33" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well no erm five years or something like that okay?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262">well fuck you mean he was that switched on that he needed to to to butter it all up?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0261">look the simple the simple point of it and and you made it before was that erm he was one of these people who could erm talk himself up that he had the ability to market himself in front of everybody and er and that all started fairly straight forwardly and and these things people notice one day he was working as a courier and he knocked on the front door to deliver a parcel and he noticed that it was a company that was an engineering company he said I've got a degree in <trunc>aeroen</trunc>aeronautical engineering and no jobs going on that that's why I'm doing this have you guys got any jobs going and they said well pop round and we'll have a chat and that's how it started yeah? so he obviously</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262">aeronautical engineering?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0261">and he yeah and he has now become a chartered civil engineer and er has his own patch within the company you know and he's a specialist in some particular things and that's because he chose a certain line to go down and from his point of view he might find that he gets rather bored with that but what he's selling is a product that for a company is saleable around the world</u>
<u n="38" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0261">erm he has expertise in it and until the the the the environment changes so that product is no longer focused or our money isn't spent on it by government and so on and it's all about public transport then he will still have a job in it he might not enjoy doing it day in and day out but he gets on and he does it cos from my point of view if you do something forever for a long time it gets a bit boring erm if it's something I'm passionate about it won't because I will just continue to learn more and if he's interested in something called <trunc>but</trunc>bus rapid transit and that rocks his boat and he wants to spend his career doing that then fine but you wouldn't find me doing it more than five years I would go I'll give it a shot and then I would have had to find something else to do and and part of it comes off the back of probably something a lecturer said when I was at uni which was don't do job for more than five years</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262">why did you not pursue the land surveying?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0261">well when I came from New Zealand to erm to to England it wasn't the same job the same job didn't exist erm we had a very project management based role when we were working in New Zealand and then when we got to England the reality of it was in in England they use the work surveyor for a variety of different things you could be a plumber and be a surveyor you could be a building surveyor you could be a land surveyor you could be erm you you could be electrical surveyor you know you could be an insurance surveyor all of these kind of things and he uses it in its true sense but the thing is is in New Zealand surveyor and in Australia surveyors were important because they were the people who set out the land they were the people who did a lot of exploration and adventure up front</u>
<u n="42" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0261">so erm a lot of what we have been trained in didn't apply in the same context in the UK</u>
<u n="44" who="S0262">so do you feel actually that was a right bugger in a way you know what I mean? because you weren't using your expertise that you had started in Hamilton as a job you'd got quite good at it yeah from what I can tell you you still have your surveyor mates today</u>
<u n="45" who="S0261">well I became a chartered surveyor</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">right so and you know and people you know I know they're friends but they're also professionals still working in their field are still land surveyor and chartered surveyors so you kind of know what the picture is in New Zealand from having that kind of you you know you're not right in there with them but you've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so do you feel like sometimes a bit fucking like oh you know I could have gone this way and stayed in New Zealand had you not go to the UK and I I could've just actually got really fucking good at something that I think I think I loved at the time or did you never love land surveying so where you felt that you were much kind of like hard done by that you know you kinda went oh you know actually well yeah no</u>
<u n="47" who="S0261">er I think there was a bigger thing erm I I I gave it a crack and em there would be a lot more that I would've learned along the way and that would have involved me needing to to do a different job et cetera et cetera and the time I left was the time to leave</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">was it? was it not going too well?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">well it wasn't that wasn't the point the point was is erm I I always had this kind of goal which was I've been through uni and er education all of this time and then I've gone straight out of that into work there was no break it was leave uni straight to work kind of thing and then I did that for three years and in that time I got my chartered thing yeah? so you know in England they have a gap year and lots of people make use of it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262" trans="overlap">after you fuck around for ages like I did yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261">yeah mm but a lot of people use it for for a good reason and that is to have break from the system</u>
<u n="52" who="S0262">well I did use it for some good reason you know I got my degree and I went off</u>
<u n="53" who="S0261">no not just you but a lot of people</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262">no no no you're right but <trunc>y</trunc> I'm actually a product of what you're talking about but I got a as you know I got a first class degree in business?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">what did I do? I went and became an au pair for a fucking year so people do make their own decisions right about what they're going to fucking do rightly or wrongly but you didn't you went and did the sensible thing which was go and get a job get your chartership and you could have actually just stayed there</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261">yes I could have but my interest was in exploring the world</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262" trans="overlap">some people did yeah some people stayed didn't they? some of your mates stayed</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">yeah but also some some some of them explored the world too and then they went back to what it was about</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262" trans="overlap">for a year or two and they came back</u>
<u n="61" who="S0261">mm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was away for five or six years</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">yeah but some of the others</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">as an example</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">some of the others just you know dipped their toe in the water and came back</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261">erm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">no nobody was <trunc>no</trunc> away as long as you were or has been</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261">no I don't think well there is some that are still away that's not true</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262">er who's that? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">like erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s still in Ireland I think</u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">well okay then there's one</u>
<u n="71" who="S0261">as an example</u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">but yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261">as an example you know that's one example so erm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0262">but you're one you're one of the few who actually have not returned to New Zealand</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261">maybe that's the case I don't know there were a crowd of them I don't know where everybody is but a lot of them are in New Zealand yes your point's taken alright okay?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0262">are they doing the thing that they did when they left?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0261">yes they started off with something they went back to it</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262" trans="overlap">thank you thank you thank you</u>
<u n="79" who="S0261">the point is that they</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262">they like it</u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">are doing the same thing that they started out with and yeah but I get the <trunc>con</trunc> sense that you know for some of them it's no longer as enjoyable as it was it's it's it's business it's graft it's making money</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">do you know what it is it's a traditional point of view</u>
<u n="83" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">I did my studies as a bachelor degree which is what I was told to do I fucking became a chartered land surveyor which is what I was fucking told to do I've grafted my fucking graft and now I'm trying to make my way in the world okay? until I'm a pensioner why shouldn't society my contribution is this why shouldn't society give me a fucking good crack at it you know pursuing one career and getting very very good at what I do why should I not be a given an an an opportunity to have a life long career in the thing that I've worked hard at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> other people</u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">yeah but that's the way we're all brought up we're brought up that it's going to last for life</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">right okay</u>
<u n="87" who="S0261">and that's what we want for life</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262">do you want that from life?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">well no not from my point of view cos I've always kind of thought well well part part of it is if I was doing my own thing my own business like I've said erm it was about the location thing I always liked the idea of moving around because that kind of reinvigorates you it's new stuff you learn new stuff it forces you to look at thing differently you try different stuff just because you're doing that when you're based in one place sure you get to know the community you become better known in the community you know more people there but you're there and that's it you know? erm you don't necessarily get the freedom to go and have a look around and look at other stuff and</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262">so who's a a not a role model but who's a model of what you're actually someone <trunc>you</trunc> older than you who is actually epitomise a little bit of what you've just said they don't have to be a role model but somebody who's been living their life in a way that you've just described</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">well I suppose it's connected in a way to people who call themselves expats and</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262">so who who who who?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261">and an a and examples I can think of are like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> are expats your your aunt and uncle erm in in Cairo they're expats you know they they've lived that lifestyle all of their life and they wouldn't have lived that lifestyle if they were comfortable with being in one place they're not doing it just because of the job they're doing it because they don't mind being posted around the place</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262">you know who's actually probably a good example as well is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's becoming that way</u>
<u n="95" who="S0261">he he yeah he will he will maybe morph into that in a way</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">he has sort of <trunc>no</trunc> modernised version of an expat yeah? he's got quite a lot of choice about where he goes I mean most expats do but actually if you want to climb up the ladder you've got to just take what's really kind of on offer the best that they can give you <event desc="sound of beeping"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">oh fuck what's that? put that out <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="recording skips"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">vital part of it but I don't know if you're ready for that yet yet I don't know if you're really ready for the introspection part cos it's probably cos you haven't actually got to a safe platform in which to sort of feel retrospective I mean sorry introspective you probably don't want to think about it yet but questions will be asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't know if you're going to interview <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is probably a bit more down played but he'll be looking at you going what the fuck are you doing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? you know you could be just like me you could come back to New Zealand you could work with em whatever you could set your own business up you're still a chartered surveyor what is fucking wrong with you just just do what we've been trained to do</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261">yeah but if you don't enjoy it or you don't want to do it then why would you do it?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">you see that's a hard conversation to have <trunc>som</trunc> with somebody who's actually still doing what they were trained to do when they were in their twenties</u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">yeah well it depend on whether they actually still enjoy it or whether they're</u>
<u n="102" who="S0262">but you kind of upset them either way whichever way you announce it</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261">well you can certainly say well is it something that you still enjoy doing</u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">ah but that's confrontational</u>
<u n="105" who="S0261">well you could put it in a different way which is erm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0262">I don't think you want to get righteous about it put it that way</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261">no I don't tend to be want to be <trunc>rid</trunc> I mean there's nothing righteous about trying something new</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262">trying something different</u>
<u n="109" who="S0261">or something different</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262">it's new and different but new er carries this connotation of something original what you're doing is just something different it's not necessarily something new it feels new it's just different for you</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261">it's new for me cos I'm learning new things stuff that I didn't know I'm I'm finding out I'm learning about</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262">okay so in a way you're gonna have to get kind of quite well versed at how do you explain this to your friends so that they understand actually what you're trying to achieve? cos I think your friends will actually be your <trunc>bi</trunc>biggest critics</u>
<u n="113" who="S0261">oh of course they will</u>
<u n="114" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0261">and they'll try and put me to point er well what do you think you're doing? and I well you know these are the reasons why I'm going in this direction why I've left that direction and I'm in a transition which is working towards this and creating something different you know and if you put it in context of the bigger picture which er could be like you were talking about the idea of of the way the education market is working et cetera that one way to learn about how to do something is to talk to people who have already done it or are doing it and if you come across enough of them you're gonna pick up little tit-bits of stuff and you're gonna see a common theme between them and you're gonna look at it and go well okay I can run with those things I don't like those bits but I'll run my way this way and that's the beauty about what entrepreneurialship stuff is that that people all are doing it by themselves they have a common thread that's why they make it work but the reality is is all of us could be ten of us could be doing all sorts of different stuff going in different directions and we will all meet at the same point at the end and that's the great thing about it that there's more one more than one way to skin a cat you know? so if I'm talking to these guys and they're like well why are you doing this? well because I admire what you do which is you're doing it I'm interested in that and I'm interested in more than just telling your story I wanna find out from you about the things that matter to you and how you've gone about it cos I expect to learn something from that and that there's <trunc>v</trunc> always value in learning something from anybody else <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> they might not get that they might not understand my perception of them or my perception of the bigger picture er that they're a part of but I certainly think by the time I get there I'll have a feeling for what that particular moment is about it might not be the bigger picture because one of the questions might be is there a bigger picture? to a certain extent or something like that well my extent will be shorter than what their extent is cos I've already travelled a longer journey</u>
<u n="116" who="S0262">absolutely is there a way that you can erm in a diagram and I don't mean it has to be a diagram of sort of like you know beakers and sort of you know Bunsen burners and whatever but is there something that you can actually send them in a sort of interesting kind of you know way where it actually surmises what you've just said to me without losing them yeah? but just something that you can point to and say the reason why I'm doing this is because I wanna learn this from you this I can actually teach to others and I potentially could make money out of it as in this is probably a new careership for me</u>
<u n="117" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0262">I don't know yet but I'm going to experiment with it</u>
<u n="119" who="S0261"><trunc>ab</trunc>absolutely of course mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0262">so could you <trunc>c</trunc> you know surmising it in such a short way where it's so down pat where they just follow your train of thought</u>
<u n="121" who="S0261">I'll create a cartoon strip</u>
<u n="122" who="S0262">yes</u>
<u n="123" who="S0261">me and them</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262">that's a brilliant idea</u>
<u n="125" who="S0261">de de de</u>
<u n="126" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0262">that is this this this idea of creating a team putting it in a cartoon strip brilliant that's your personal way of getting the message</u>
<u n="129" who="S0261">cos cartoon strips tell us quick stories</u>
<u n="130" who="S0262">yeah look at Tin Tin look at how brilliant everybody else is at doing that</u>
<u n="131" who="S0261">and then New Zealand it used to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="133" who="S0261">or whatever</u>
<u n="134" who="S0262">there you go then</u>
<u n="135" who="S0261">yeah could be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0262">do it like that</u>
<u n="137" who="S0261">the guy who <unclear></unclear></u>
<u n="138" who="S0262">do it in the way that you know how in the way that they will understand best</u>
<u n="139" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0262">but I think it's integral that you get that understanding and backing support from your mates before you go to a video er into and interview with them</u>
<u n="141" who="S0261">oh absolutely of course</u>
<u n="142" who="S0262">they've got to know one hundred per cent that they trust you</u>
<u n="143" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0262">in this new way <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well you've got to be able to erm articulate to them the reasons why you want to do it</u>
<u n="146" who="S0262">yeah and you won't spot them</u>
<u n="147" who="S0261">and they won't do it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0261">comfortably</u>
<u n="150" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0261">without understanding where you're coming from</u>
<u n="152" who="S0262">exactly where you're coming from</u>
<u n="153" who="S0261">and sometimes that might make might take you know and email a chat a product a a a a a discussion document more chat and then you meet them and then you have a chat and you sort it out and away you go you know because with everybody there's stuff they want to say and other things they don't want to say</u>
<u n="154" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="155" who="S0261">you need to know that</u>
<u n="156" who="S0262">that's right and also</u>
<u n="157" who="S0261">because you don't want to be asking the wrong questions</u>
<u n="158" who="S0262">have you thought about if they don't want to participate how you give them the easy way out without offending you have you thought about a way that is actually dead easy if they just don't want to participate for whatever reason that they have which is personal or whatever to themselves that they've got an easy way out and you won't look at them and go what the fuck?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0261">well erm I'll have to work that out</u>
<u n="160" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0261">erm most of the time from my point of view people's reactions say a lot of things and and if they don't connect to it easily then they probably don't want to do it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0261">simply simply that</u>
<u n="164" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0261">you know erm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0262">you can yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0261">so if they don't want to do it well you have to find others who are going to do it it's it's part of it</u>
<u n="168" who="S0262">no I think you're right I think you know your mates that if there isn't a sort of you know little kind of interest</u>
<u n="169" who="S0261">I mean a lot of them would just say straight up look mate it's not what I want to do</u>
<u n="170" who="S0262">yeah yeah some of them will be worried that that no interested to go to give it a go some of them will be worried about <trunc>we</trunc>what's the <trunc>cop</trunc> the copy <trunc>wha</trunc>what's my am I like is my likeness going to be used and you know <trunc>wha</trunc> where am I going to end up?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0261">well you need to understand that</u>
<u n="172" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0261">and you need to understand erm <trunc>we</trunc> how you want to approach it you might simply say well I'm gonna I'm planning to use your likeness or this discussion in this particular product and I'm looking at erm using it in a particular way erm and they might want you to contact them every time you do that others might say carte blanche do whatever you want but make sure you back up my company every time you do it</u>
<u n="174" who="S0262">yep yep</u>
<u n="175" who="S0261">that you put your little pitch in for us like it's a vice versa I'll scratch your back if you scratch mine</u>
<u n="176" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0261">which to me seems absolutely fine</u>
<u n="178" who="S0262">yeah no you have to offer them</u>
<u n="179" who="S0261">of course you do</u>
<u n="180" who="S0262">you have to offer them something</u>
<u n="181" who="S0261">of course you will</u>
<u n="182" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0261">look I'll splash your business all over the net</u>
<u n="184" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah you can't take take take take take</u>
<u n="185" who="S0261" trans="overlap">more than you could do yourself</u>
<u n="186" who="S0262">you've got to give back as well it's got to be two way process</u>
<u n="187" who="S0261">yeah well I mean the reality behind a lot of these guys and and part of it goes back to some of the old school stuff and some of it is just their way of business thinking not they don't really have an interest in the power of the net</u>
<u n="188" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0261">they don't really</u>
<u n="190" who="S0262">yeah so you could be teaching them something</u>
<u n="191" who="S0261">follow</u>
<u n="192" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0261">why you should be interested</u>
<u n="194" who="S0262">yeah yeah so you could <trunc>do</trunc></u>
<u n="195" who="S0261">some of them are starting off with it because they know it's an easy way to be connected to your mates as an example but things like well you know for some people it things like is it going to create more growth for my business well for a lot of people yes you know if you were like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> running a a a a pick up coach bus service type thing for drinking establishments at any time of the day during during during the whole year then the ideal thing for them is an app something on a mobile phone that people can go de de de okay it's going to turn up here I need to be out the door by then and of course these guys probably turn up and somehow let somebody else know and they say well you know the wagon's here guys it's time to go home or whatever but</u>
<u n="196" who="S0262">no you're right you're right you're right</u>
<u n="197" who="S0261">people</u>
<u n="198" who="S0262">you're right but</u>
<u n="199" who="S0261">people would make a better connection are having the choice to make that connection themselves</u>
<u n="200" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0261">rather than you telling them to go all the time</u>
<u n="202" who="S0262">well I was going to say that but the thing is is that if you're moving along with I understand how erm er social media technologies are working because I'm having to because this is part of how my business is gonna be set up equally <trunc>whe</trunc> they're teaching you about entrepreneurship they'll actually go oh right so what do you do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and you're like well this is how I work it because this is the way I've been kind of like you know understood how to do it be like oh right so like is it that easy or is it hard? and you're like no actually it's quite easy so all you have to do is this and I can actually show you how to do it do you want me to show you how to do it? and they're like oh okay so actually they might not realise that they're actually learning something for you only because you're just being you you're not trying to force feed them you're not being sanctimonious about it you're just going oh this is the reason why I'm doing it it's because I'm doing it like this and everyone's like doing like what? oh okay why do you have to do it like that? with so many? like well because actually the way it <trunc>of</trunc> fits together if because if you don't have this bit and you don't have that bit bled ble ble ble ble ble so that's the beauty for it is that not only do they get your name in something on the on the internet but they're actually learning something from you</u>
<u n="203" who="S0261">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="204" who="S0262">potentially learning from you</u>
<u n="205" who="S0261">well that that would be the ideal would be yes and and again it's this idea of a relative expert that you know a bit more than somebody else and you can offer them something because you know that bit more</u>
<u n="206" who="S0262">yeah but they probably also don't think</u>
<u n="207" who="S0261">and that is valid</u>
<u n="208" who="S0262">feel like they're the experts to you but you know it's all relative isn't it? when they think of entrepreneurship they might think of you know somebody big in New Zealand or a name that they they think is a famous person or this this this talk <unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0261">well if if they yeah yeah of course</u>
<u n="210" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you know that no one has to get too big like I don't understand the <unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well if New Zealand has the <unclear/> <unclear>poppy</unclear> thing but I mean they might still have the people the mentors or the people that they look up to</u>
<u n="212" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="213" who="S0261">all of that kind of thing</u>
<u n="214" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so when you say I admire you I admire you want to learn from you they're like get real <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I mean for fuck's sake we're only a couple of couple of years before you you'll catch up if you want your own business of course you're going to be right there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will tell you that straight away</u>
<u n="215" who="S0261">yeah <trunc>o</trunc><trunc>o</trunc>of course absolutely crack on and give it a go but</u>
<u n="216" who="S0262">you will be successful just like us</u>
<u n="217" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0262">because why wouldn't you be?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0262">you're just like fucking intelligent as we are</u>
<u n="221" who="S0261">of course just give it a go</u>
<u n="222" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0262">so they thing is that they way you you really got to get it so many of these angles right cos they're your friends</u>
<u n="225" who="S0261">yes I do appreciate that erm and</u>
<u n="226" who="S0262">I love the strip the comic strip I mean the the cartoon thing I think that is a bloody brilliant way of of of getting their interest trying to understand where you're coming from yeah? and and actually wanting to be part of it not just oh it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I like him he's a good bloke but actually be quite excited about it if you could actually get somebody get somebody feeling quite excited about being <trunc>pa</trunc><trunc>pa</trunc>participant in something wow that will show on the camera</u>
<u n="227" who="S0261">of course erm we will have to play it out and see how it goes</u>
<u n="228" who="S0262">well you've got a big job love</u>
<u n="229" who="S0261">yeah I know erm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0262">you've got a lot of things to think about</u>
<u n="231" who="S0261">there's there's a lot of stiff to follow and learn and lot of hours to put in I think</u>
<u n="232" who="S0262">yeah there is</u>
<u n="233" who="S0261">and erm and and we'll have to work out how to put all that time aside whether it's a case of working together or er that we focus on certain things at a certain time you know but it I expect to get my head down in the evenings and stuff like that</u>
<u n="234" who="S0262">okay well I'll be starting my course soon so you know I'll be I'll be studying as well</u>
<u n="235" who="S0261">when does that start?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0262">second of February officially but I think I can go online end of January</u>
<u n="237" who="S0261">righto</u>
<u n="238" who="S0262">but yeah you're right but <trunc>le</trunc>let's put this into the context of if you were actually studying your your your chosen curriculum in a in a face to face erm composition you'd have maybe eight hours of lectures per week you'd maybe have six <trunc>hour</trunc> six hours of tutorials that's all you get as face to face with someone telling you the rest of the time you go off and do it all on your own that's at that's actually the landscape now of borrowing in education is you don't get a lot of face to face time you get you know</u>
<u n="239" who="S0261">so you're saying <trunc>o</trunc><trunc>ou</trunc>out of let's say what's a full time twenty-five hours a week kind of thing the reality is is now it's only twelve</u>
<u n="240" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0261">cos when I went to uni you got twenty-five hours</u>
<u n="242" who="S0262">I know well I I thought I was at uni every day</u>
<u n="243" who="S0261">which which was sixty per cent of a full working week</u>
<u n="244" who="S0262">but these kids say to me I've got a job here and I've got a job there so I'm going to pile all my lectures into the one day and my tutorials and I'm like how do you do that? oh because I can manage it I can move my stuff into evening classes and they'll have a lecture in the afternoon and go straight I'm like don't you get told that like tutorials <unclear/> no no you can choose now</u>
<u n="245" who="S0261">yeah so they've got multiple time slots that they just say well I'm gonna turn up to the time slot</u>
<u n="246" who="S0262">yeah fucking fuck that</u>
<u n="247" who="S0261">and and they're flexible enough to have one hundred people at that one</u>
<u n="248" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0261">and one person at the other</u>
<u n="250" who="S0262">they'll all bunch up somehow</u>
<u n="251" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0262">get your first dibs in or something I don't know how it works</u>
<u n="253" who="S0261">well it might be limited numbers or whatever</u>
<u n="254" who="S0262">cos I remember having to go to management accounting stroke two on a Friday fucking afternoon and I hadn't had to go in in the morning</u>
<u n="255" who="S0261">well it's a timetable and you turned up at that time otherwise you missed out</u>
<u n="256" who="S0262">yeah it's fine I was always at college I was always fucking around doing something at college I don't remember days on end when I didn't fucking go in unless I just couldn't be fucking arsed to go in but even then I actually still went in cos I lived round the corner from where the college was</u>
<u n="257" who="S0261">well I well I can see a sensible context on one side and and not so sensible context on the other</u>
<u n="258" who="S0262">but these lot they're they're getting the maximum they're going I've got a job at uni I'm volunteering at uni I mean they talk like they fucking know everything and I'm looking at them going jeez man you are serious power fucking players but they're only power players because they're young and they don't actually understand they're still looking into a job it's a completely different kettle of fish they all believe when you're about erm twenty-<trunc>ni</trunc> er twenty-one to twenty-two <event desc="sound of fingers clicking"/> you can have it all and then you get in to our job and go fucking hell why did I think like that I <trunc>ha</trunc> thought expansively and I did everything I wanted to do at uni it's not until people start putting you into fucking pigeon holes that you realise you can't</u>
<u n="259" who="S0261">well and and look you know I think that is part of the problem with with common day business and employment you know that think of like Google who have what is effectively a campus and they operate in the nature of universities so</u>
<u n="260" who="S0262">yeah you turn up when you kind of feel like you can <unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you you you get played and that of course somehow all of that's monitored you turn up you have to be seen to be there for a certain period of time but you can take whatever break and you can mix and match with whoever you want and if you've got a deal then you go and present that to the top geezers and you say well look I've got this idea we've worked together as a team for the last six weeks and we've been able to analyse and come up with we reckon this is a goer give it a go trial it out it goes up on Google they try it out as a product you know check it out it stays or it dies</u>
<u n="262" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but you know these <trunc>youn</trunc> <trunc>the</trunc> you know these youngsters right? these youngsters now the ones I'm talking to they're probably about <trunc>tw</trunc> nineteen twenty twenty-one I think erm I've never asked them their age I mean I just assume but I think they're going to have a bit of shock because they are working the university system as in I turn up do a bit of work for that university then I go off and do a volunteering through university and then I'm actually working in the community anyway and then I'm actually just doing a sort of like part time job at <trunc>j</trunc> like <trunc>h</trunc> JV Hi-fi whatever then I'm doing my studies but I'm actually doing them in the evening cos that's how it works out for me they have totally understood how to maximise their time these are normal third years students by the way and the shock is fuck off you get your first full time fucking job as a fucking <trunc>ru</trunc> grunt you don't have that freedom you don't have that liberty to think in the way that you think you've got to stop thinking like that and you've got to get with what everyone else is thinking which is get in at eight leave at six</u>
<u n="263" who="S0261">yeah but what they get with to start with is that they've got some stuff they do and they deliver whatever they've got to deliver they work for JV Hi-fi and they sell shit they do their education and they submit their assignments and they do their assessment and they get their piece of paper and they go down the community centre and and they shovel a few soup kitchens or something like that I don't know whatever</u>
<u n="264" who="S0262">no that's what people do</u>
<u n="265" who="S0261">you know yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0262">they do that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0261">mm well good on them</u>
<u n="268" who="S0262">all all all in the same fucking week</u>
<u n="269" who="S0261" trans="overlap">good on them yeah good on them <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0261">but what then actually I think on another side is sure you might not have the freedom to do all of those things or operate in that manner when you're at work and you might have to sit in one bloody spot and suffer through it but I'll tell you what having those skills erm will show you up to be rather organised and if you're of that type of ilk you're probably quite sociable and interactive and come across as a bit of a go getter</u>
<u n="272" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0262">so you probably sit there and tap your feet like you're bored cos you want to get on and do something and if you're I expect if you're kind of transitioned into a space then either you will be a lot more free or you will be totally constrained and go and do something else</u>
<u n="274" who="S0262">yeah which is what I'm thinking these lot they won't have the time for it the things that they've actually trained to do in their degree fucking <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0261">so they're more likely to collaborate and create new stuff</u>
<u n="276" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0261">which is the way all all these new erm businesses and products come about they they all go of well this is bloody shit isn't it well why don't we do it like this and we'll go and make a business out of it okay guys somebody gonna give us some money yeah give us some money mate away we go piece of cake now that's the way they think they think I just go and get it</u>
<u n="278" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0262">very good example of that</u>
<u n="281" who="S0261">well is he ready?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0262">let's take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at what is he? twenty-six twenty-seven and put <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as in fucking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the UK <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would be working in the degree he was trained in and he wouldn't be fucking around doing what he is doing because actually the landscape there is very tough if you've bought a degree as in you've bought you're you've import you've paid you've actually done the time and you've actually done quite well all of those things have to align quite nicely don't fucking tell me that I'm going to go off and fucking do some crowd sourcing for free in Melbourne and work quite hard over the weekend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just fucking do the job that you've actually been trained to do cos there's plenty of other people in the world who don't get to fucking do what they're trained to do and I I I'll actually got I was a little bit annoyed with him today but I didn't show it but I will get back to him about it and just like don't fucking tell me that you found it too hard cos that's what work is you feel it's too hard because you're giving your time for free then fucking go out and do what you actually trained to do and earn some money</u>
<u n="283" who="S0261">well if he doesn't like giving his er his time for free then makes sure he gets paid for it</u>
<u n="284" who="S0262">mm what I'm trying to say is that look I know I'm not really the best person to talk to cos I got a business degree and I could have just gone gone corporate blue-chip you know I could have done but I didn't but I went and got a job as a fucking au pair I got paid for it I led a lifestyle in uni that was actually pretty nice it didn't last very long but I stayed in uni and I became an English teacher still got paid for that I fucking made loads of money out of that and it paid for my fucking master's degree so I'm trying to understand the mind set of some of these twenty year olds I'm think great great great you're so fucking cool you do all of these things you're all all there things you you know social networking you're so this I'm not talking about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> no I'm talking about others it's like why don't you actually give a fucking go in the fucking thing that your degree has trained you to be like you did land surveying yes I'm going to be a land surveyor and I will just become a chartered surveyor because that's what I fucking been trained to do why are you pissing around not doing stuff instead of what you're trained to do do you think you're that much better than everybody else? I I don't understand I don't understand why there's so much <trunc>emplo</trunc> unemployment in Europe that these kinds in Australia seem to just go oh well <unclear/> I don't give a fuck</u>
<u n="285" who="S0261">well because they haven't had their they haven't had their base for it they haven't had their pants pulled down they haven't had the shock of their lives you know? the people in Europe have the kids in Europe have people coming out of uni have</u>
<u n="286" who="S0262">but you see what how I could come across?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0261">the reality it's it's it's the standard the standard old human reaction interaction thing</u>
<u n="288" who="S0262">yeah you don't know until it happens to you</u>
<u n="289" who="S0261">you don't know until it happens to you till you're shocked to death you know and and those people in Europe those poor people in Europe are really really having a rough time the reality of it is though in relation to a relative thing that tough time isn't as bad as it really seems yet you know</u>
<u n="290" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0261">it's not like there's not enough food to feed people</u>
<u n="292" who="S0262">no no</u>
<u n="293" who="S0261">you know? the the basic are all there</u>
<u n="294" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no no no I know it's all it's all relative</u>
<u n="295" who="S0261">and all of that kind of thing</u>
<u n="296" who="S0262">I'm just saying I'm I'm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0261">here isn't just quintessentially I'm going to get enough money therefore I'm not gonna do their job that's the kind of attitude</u>
<u n="298" who="S0262">yeah actually you're right that's more the point yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0261">yeah? and and okay I challenge you to try and get more money somewhere else to do that job having just left uni</u>
<u n="300" who="S0262">or or or or or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just a continued student that he likes the freedom when he was an undergrad cos he did a million different types of things and what he loves about being in this job now is he does a million different types of thing but he hasn't knuckled down to that you know one day you have to knuckle down to something you just in your life have to just go fuck it I am this and I will do this</u>
<u n="301" who="S0261">well if you're going to have a string to your bow you need to set your attention in some direction</u>
<u n="302" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0261">and that's that's simply the way it is erm and I don't know what he does but</u>
<u n="304" who="S0262">well whatever he does he does it quite well</u>
<u n="305" who="S0261">well there's probably something that he can continue on doing then</u>
<u n="306" who="S0262">but they want him to stay they want to offer him fucking permanent shit there</u>
<u n="307" who="S0261">right right right</u>
<u n="308" who="S0262">he's just not playing their game either</u>
<u n="309" who="S0261">well he doesn't want to then does him?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0262">he won't play anyone's game and he's not just <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just not it's not him as an individual it's other people as well and I'm just thinking actually you know what there's nothing wrong with fucking turning up for work and being somebody for a couple of years and understanding what that feels like</u>
<u n="311" who="S0261">no there's nothing wrong with that erm and and like any other experience in life that you give something a go for a while and erm then you can turn around and say to somebody well I know what I's like that's why we would chose to go and travel round the world cos you don't know how to do it unless you've done it or you don't know what it's like until you've done it is more the point</u>
<u n="312" who="S0262">that's true and then we've just been like them but we're running away from it in different way we're not running away from it but we're we're</u>
<u n="313" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well no we just we're just exploring the</u>
<u n="314" who="S0262">we're exercising our free our freedom</u>
<u n="315" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the thing our freedom and that's what's important so I don't erm I don't I don't hold him back for doing that if he doesn't want to be focused and fit into a particular role because society expects him to then good on him if he doesn't want to do that and he's got something else to do and he can make his crust and live that way he could be happy living on a baguette and a piece of cheese for the day</u>
<u n="316" who="S0262">you're right <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is just it was just pants this morning normally he's not hat down about things</u>
<u n="317" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0262">but he might have just had something going on that he doesn't want to talk about</u>
<u n="319" who="S0261" trans="overlap">he might he might have been hangover or his sister might have like stolen his shoe or I don't know</u>
<u n="320" who="S0262">or yeah it's just annoying that's true yeah it's true</u>
<u n="321" who="S0261">you know the girls got at him for the day so he's not going to react to the girls very well is he?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0262">yeah normally</u>
<u n="323" who="S0261">whatever</u>
<u n="324" who="S0262">normally he's alright with me</u>
<u n="325" who="S0261">yeah so go give him a hard time next week</u>
<u n="326" who="S0262">I will</u>
<u n="327" who="S0261">when when he gets back</u>
<u n="328" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0261">and and sometime we'll meet up or whatever</u>
<u n="330" who="S0262">yeah he probably just</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
