<text id="S3RN">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0052 S0109</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Making dinner, friends, jobs, interviews, the neighbourhood</topics>
		<activity>Making dinner, friends, jobs, interviews, the neighbourhood</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0052">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Maldon, Essex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Essex</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 years, 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Maths teacher, sixth form college</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0109">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0109">so small <pause dur="short"/> compared to the last one which was absolutely huge</u>
<u n="2" who="S0052">why have you got a new one?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0109">because the old one belonged to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he wanted it for his brother</u>
<u n="4" who="S0052">fair enough</u>
<u n="5" who="S0109">and it cost like two hundred and fifty pounds and I was scared of it</u>
<u n="6" who="S0052">how much did that one cost?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0109">eh thirty</u>
<u n="8" who="S0052">oh</u>
<u n="9" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0052">how <trunc>o</trunc> is his little brother now?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0109">how is he?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0052">yes</u>
<u n="13" who="S0109">I have absolutely no idea</u>
<u n="14" who="S0052">okay</u>
<u n="15" who="S0109">I'm assuming that he's</u>
<u n="16" who="S0052">gone back to university</u>
<u n="17" who="S0109">gone back and he's yes yes yes he is he is cos em <pause dur="short"/> he's gone to visit him in  at university <pause dur="short"/> after Pathfinders last night</u>
<u n="18" who="S0052">oh okay</u>
<u n="19" who="S0109">so that's a five hour walk five hour car journey to be undertaken at half past nine at night</u>
<u n="20" who="S0052">yeah that's odd</u>
<u n="21" who="S0109">to come back on Sunday evening</u>
<u n="22" who="S0052">for Pathfinders? Or is that in the morning</u>
<u n="23" who="S0109">no just just because he's got a work on eh</u>
<u n="24" who="S0052">Monday</u>
<u n="25" who="S0109">Monday <pause dur="short"/> he should have been at Pathfinders on Sunday morning but eh he swapped off</u>
<u n="26" who="S0052">oh I see</u>
<u n="27" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0052">some people's jobs maybe something quite so <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0109">yeah and some people are very very busy <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I I would never drive for a long time like that without a break <pause dur="short"/> cos I just don't think I'd</u>
<u n="30" who="S0052">well actually if I drive two by the time I've driven for about two hours my back really hurts <pause dur="short"/> but if it wasn't for that I could probably drive for quite a long time</u>
<u n="31" who="S0109">like attention span-wise?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0052">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0109">and what about your feet? Don't you get a cramp? Cos you have to hold your feet in the same position the whole time?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0052">mm no <pause dur="short"/> I don't I mean <pause dur="short"/> I don't think my foot <trunc>mi</trunc> my foot minds feet rather <pause dur="short"/> it's just my back it becomes horribly painful <pause dur="short"/> does that look like one amount of food?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0109">eh eh yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0052">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0109">Cos you eat that <pause dur="short"/> but without vegetables with extra vegetable?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0052">oh yeah it's got loads of vegetables in <pause dur="short"/> it's got courgettes and carrots and peppers and onions</u>
<u n="39" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0052">that's good so I've got ten to freeze I've given two away and I've got one to eat <pause dur="short"/> so I've made thirteen <pause dur="short"/> thirteen and one</u>
<u n="41" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0052">oh</u>
<u n="43" who="S0109">that's not many  That didn't come out right <pause dur="short"/> how many is that meant to be that pot? Is it  Is it  like ten?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0052">it is like a really large one well it depends what you're cooking <pause dur="short"/> cos I I mean this is bolognaise so you know you do pasta with it separately <pause dur="short"/> so then you can cook more can't you?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0109">I suppose</u>
<u n="46" who="S0052">do <pause dur="short"/> I'm down to like not very much food <pause dur="short"/> well I'm not now but I was</u>
<u n="47" who="S0109">I have absolutely nothing in</u>
<u n="48" who="S0052">oh but you never do</u>
<u n="49" who="S0109">well I normally have something</u>
<u n="50" who="S0052">I've got one curry one hot pot and ten bolognaise</u>
<u n="51" who="S0109"><unclear/> means that if I prepare food and freeze it and I don't it's not the food that I want on that particular day</u>
<u n="52" who="S0052">ah but if you have a choice then it surely could be</u>
<u n="53" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0052">I don't think I never I normally have much of an opinion I just want food <pause dur="short"/> oh I didn't mean to do that</u>
<u n="55" who="S0109">what did you do?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0052">well I don't want to freeze it all <pause dur="short"/> I want to put some in the fridge <pause dur="short"/> cos then I can eat it even quicker</u>
<u n="57" who="S0109">I mean surely it doesn't take</u>
<u n="58" who="S0052">sorry?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0109">surely it doesn't take that much longer from?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0052">no but <pause dur="short"/> I'll eat two this week so I might as well not be freezing them</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="61" who="S0052">ha <pause dur="short"/> whoa <pause dur="short"/> something isn't going <unclear/> Please may I borrow the tea towel?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0109">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0052">oh dear</u>
<u n="64" who="S0109">so when will you be? <trunc>W</trunc> when is this guy going to contact you?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0052">em well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said next week sometime <pause dur="short"/> so probably one evening next week I guess <pause dur="short"/> hopefully before ideally before Thursday cos if the <unclear/> interview me that will be on Friday <pause dur="short"/> so I would like to know before then when I'll know from <trunc>Heri</trunc> actually I don't need to know but I need to know when I'll know so I can say to them I'm not gonna say yes to any job that you offer me until this date if that means you're not offering me a job at all that's fine</u>
<u n="66" who="S0109">do teaching jobs tend to offer you on the day do they?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0052">yes</u>
<u n="68" who="S0109">ah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0052">they expect you to tell them on the day whether or not you'd accept it if you're offered it <pause dur="short"/> at the end of it the <trunc>in</trunc> the last question of at interview is normally if I offer you this job would you accept it? And if you say  if you say  yes and then don't that's really bad like that's not really done do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's not legally binding you just wouldn't do it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0052" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it's not legally binding but they will want to have appointed someone by the end of the day <pause dur="short"/> em but will do is if I mean if they really like me then I can say I won't be able to accept until the end of next week</u>
<u n="72" who="S0109">mm hm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0052">and then they can either decide they can't wait or they can say okay we'll wait until then</u>
<u n="74" who="S0109">and then you never go to second rounds then?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0052">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0109">that is so much better than all the interviews I've ever been in</u>
<u n="77" who="S0052">but you normally have to teach a lesson so it's like a whole day interview <pause dur="short"/> so you go for a day and you'll have a tour of the school probably meet members of staff and stuff <pause dur="short"/> you'll teach a lesson that lots of people will watch and then you'll have an interview with several people</u>
<u n="78" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0052">and they'll do that with maybe four or five candidates <pause dur="short"/> then they'll decide who they want and then they'll ring all the candidates up that evening and tell them whether or not they've given the job <pause dur="short"/> that's generally what happens</u>
<u n="80" who="S0109">things move quickly in the teaching world</u>
<u n="81" who="S0052">yeah which is why if you apply for a job where they decide not to bother doing it in that way <pause dur="short"/> mixed  makes it all a bit</u>
<u n="82" who="S0109">and when do you have to let your school know that you don't want to to renew your job then?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0052">eh so if I've signed my new contract Easter because I didn't not till the end of July <pause dur="short"/> cos my contract says I have to give one month's notice at the moment which is rather nice</u>
<u n="84" who="S0109">no wonder they wanted to tighten up  on you</u>
<u n="85" who="S0052">well it's a pretty dumb dumb idea in the isn't it? Well I think they should have made it half a term cos that's what state schools are <pause dur="short"/> so in state school you have to give <trunc>onl</trunc> you can only leave at the end of the term and you have to give your notice by half term</u>
<u n="86" who="S0109">okay</u>
<u n="87" who="S0052">in order to leave at the end <pause dur="short"/> so there are only three times you can leave but <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose</u>
<u n="88" who="S0109">and are they changing the the rules about things like that they can make you leave at <trunc>sh</trunc> at a shorter notice now?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0052">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> what in general or just in teaching?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0109">just in teaching <pause dur="short"/> cos I I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I just heard something on the news about it being too difficult to get rid of bad teachers <pause dur="short"/> so they've decided to make it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether they followed that through or whether that was just a <trunc>thou</trunc> thought</u>
<u n="91" who="S0052">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it is really hard to get rid of teachers <pause dur="short"/> could you possibly help me do this?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0109">sure</u>
<u n="93" who="S0052">I want to get this into here but it's so heavy you see if I was to hold it would you be able to scrape it in</u>
<u n="94" who="S0109">eh a spatula <unclear/> back <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="95" who="S0052">this when I realise it's way more food than I need</u>
<u n="96" who="S0109">well you're hungry because you didn't have much lunch</u>
<u n="97" who="S0052">yeah I can have two dinners I think I can have two dinners</u>
<u n="98" who="S0109">one and a half maybe <pause dur="short"/> eh is it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0052">thank you <pause dur="short"/> lovely</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="100" who="S0052">I feel like thirteen meals at a cost of I think it was under twenty pounds is quite good</u>
<u n="101" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0052">I suppose that's without the pasta but that's quite cheap and the cheese <pause dur="short"/> what</u>
<u n="103" who="S0109">and the tuna</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="104" who="S0052">have I told you about my drinking less?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0109">no <pause dur="short"/> drinking less?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0052">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0109">no</u>
<u n="108" who="S0052">I've decided to try and drink less</u>
<u n="109" who="S0109">but that's a bad thing</u>
<u n="110" who="S0052">mm <pause dur="short"/> it depends on how much you're drinking to start with <pause dur="short"/> so I get paranoid that I'm going to get a headache if I don't drink <pause dur="short"/> and it turns out I was actually drinking quite a lot each day <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0109">well you're quite tall</u>
<u n="112" who="S0052">does that make any difference?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0109">well</u>
<u n="114" who="S0052">so I'm now drinking less and I'll probably I'm still drinking <pause dur="short"/> so I didn't drink very much when I was like a child I think</u>
<u n="115" who="S0109">so you're making up for it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0052">and then I started drinking loads and now I just started cos I  cos I  so I was drinking lots in a like paranoid I'm going to get a headache way <pause dur="short"/> but then still having headaches so it's clearly not through dehydration so <pause dur="short"/> I cut down on my ridiculous drinking</u>
<u n="117" who="S0109">how much did you drink a day then?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0052">about <pause dur="short"/> I don't know three litres maybe? But I had a lot and now I'm having about two litres <vocal desc="laugh"/> a day <pause dur="short"/> which I think is more normal</u>
<u n="119" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're meant to drink two litres a day but it's not all meant to necessarily <trunc>co</trunc> come from?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0052">you're meant to drink two litres?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0109">two litres</u>
<u n="122" who="S0052">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0109">but it doesn't all have to come from drink</u>
<u n="124" who="S0052">yeah I think I'm now drawing drinking like the right amount rather than a ridiculously large amount like I was drinking <pause dur="short"/> because I can't you know these big glasses</u>
<u n="125" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0052">I have like <pause dur="short"/> well I drink a litre  I drink a litre  at school and then I drink one of them in the morning and like maybe three in the evening <pause dur="short"/> so I'm still drinking one in the morning and a litre at school <pause dur="short"/> I'm just having less in the evening</u>
<u n="127" who="S0109">that's probably sensible</u>
<u n="128" who="S0052">yeah cos also I go to the toilet every night and that's quite annoying</u>
<u n="129" who="S0109">and then you complain that you can't sleep</u>
<u n="130" who="S0052">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> so just like part of my like you know <pause dur="short"/> improving my life <vocal desc="laugh"/> in crazy ways</u>
<u n="131" who="S0109">I really hope my chicken curry doesn't overflow onto my cake <pause dur="short"/> cos that would be</u>
<u n="132" who="S0052">oh is it on top?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0052">mm that would be unfortunate</u>
<u n="135" who="S0109">well cos I'm <pause dur="short"/> I know that if I don't put the curry on top I'll be paranoid that it hasn't cooked properly</u>
<u n="136" who="S0052">where are you meant to cook cakes in the oven?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0109">on at the top</u>
<u n="138" who="S0052">at the top?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0052">I thought so</u>
<u n="141" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0052">Cos I had a cake in the oven the other day <pause dur="short"/> oh it was that weird crazy it wasn't really a cake it was like my Eve's pudding so it was like cake on top of fruit <pause dur="short"/> eh and then it wasn't really cooking properly basically just went weird <pause dur="short"/> but I think it's cos I just put too much in it was all just a big mess <pause dur="short"/> eh and then Nadia was like oh cos it's at the top of the oven <pause dur="short"/> I was like what? It's meant to be at the top of the oven? Well I mean it wasn't the top it was sort of in the in it was taking up like the entire oven cos I cooked it in that big deep dish which was probably the problem it was too big a dish for one thing <pause dur="short"/> but yeah that made me then go I thought cakes were meant to be cooked at the top</u>
<u n="143" who="S0109">I guess it depends on the type of oven <pause dur="short"/> if it's a fan assisted oven then you don't need to put it at the top theoretically although it seems to be not the case for my mum's</u>
<u n="144" who="S0052">oh I see</u>
<u n="145" who="S0109">although I do have this sort of habit if one thing works well once I just try and repeat it rather than actually working out why it was that worked</u>
<u n="146" who="S0052">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you might as well <pause dur="short"/> oh it's nearly six o'clock it's very acceptable to be eating dinner at six o'clock</u>
<u n="147" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> especially as you're not meant to eat carbs after five</u>
<u n="148" who="S0052">really? Says who?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0109">eh dieticians</u>
<u n="150" who="S0052">that that's silly</u>
<u n="151" who="S0109">that's silly cos if you  if you  don't then you don't sleep very well</u>
<u n="152" who="S0052">you don't eat carbs after five?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0052">Cos you're hungry you mean?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0109">well yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0052">mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0109">I guess</u>
<u n="158" who="S0052">are you sure that every dietician says that?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0109">every single one?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0052">I mean like it's not just some weird ones?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0109">I think generally the the idea is that you have a huge breakfast and eh with lots of carbs and then a medium sized lunch with lots of mm sort of that sort of stuff energy stuff and then by the evening you're not doing very much <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="162" who="S0052">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0109">unless you're going out to play badminton in which case you probably can get away with it</u>
<u n="164" who="S0052">you don't have time at lunch to eat lots of food <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="165" who="S0109">ah you do if you're French</u>
<u n="166" who="S0052">I have a two hour lunch break <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0109">except all the teachers tend to have wine in their lunch break and then go back to lessons</u>
<u n="168" who="S0052">do they actually?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0109">no yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0052">okay</u>
<u n="171" who="S0109">the school I was in it was free so there was free wine with the</u>
<u n="172" who="S0052">that's good</u>
<u n="173" who="S0109">the staff canteen <pause dur="short"/> so all the teachers would have a bit and apparently we only had one teacher who had a problem with it</u>
<u n="174" who="S0052">mm <pause dur="short"/> so they would they have like one glass?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a small glass obviously they wouldn't have much</u>
<u n="176" who="S0052">every day?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0109">well as the mood takes them</u>
<u n="178" who="S0052">that's quite a different attitude isn't it?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0052">did the kids go home at lunch in France?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0109">they can do <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like if they want to <pause dur="short"/> quite a lot of the kids I taught had em they didn't actually get a lunch break cos they were doing extra classes or something crazy</u>
<u n="182" who="S0052">oh <pause dur="short"/> what for two hours?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos that was the only place they could sort of schedule it in <pause dur="short"/> timetabling maybe</u>
<u n="184" who="S0052">oh <pause dur="short"/> what time do they finish in the evening?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0109">so they start at eight and finish at six</u>
<u n="186" who="S0052">six?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0052">and then have homework on top of that?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0109">but you wouldn't always have like some of the time you wouldn't have a a lesson as such you'd have like a homework class</u>
<u n="190" who="S0052">like time to do your homework?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you're supervised</u>
<u n="192" who="S0052">mm <pause dur="short"/> what kind of school was it?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0109">it was a private school <pause dur="short"/> for em I don't really it ran the whole way so from preschool through to</u>
<u n="194" who="S0052">oh right</u>
<u n="195" who="S0109">sort of university entrance exams</u>
<u n="196" who="S0052">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0109">huge</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="198" who="S0052">did the preschool have a two hour lunch break?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0109">no the preschool I wasn't I don't know what their timetable was like at all</u>
<u n="200" who="S0052">okay <pause dur="short"/> is that cos it was an independent school or private school?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0109">which bit?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0052">ends at six?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0109">em <pause dur="short"/> I I think generally they tend to have quite long school days cos they don't in the state schools as well cos they don't do Wednesday afternoons and they don't do Saturday <pause dur="short"/> they do Saturday mornings but not</u>
<u n="204" who="S0052">they all do Saturday morning?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0109">so once you get to I think it's secondary school you start doing Saturday mornings <pause dur="short"/> but before all that you probably don't do Wednesdays at all <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="206" who="S0052">mm hm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0109">it's quite good logic cos like it stops the kids getting really tired but does em  have a weekend</u>
<u n="208" who="S0052">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so would they have to do Saturday morning?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they wouldn't ever do Saturday afternoon</u>
<u n="210" who="S0052">and would they do Wednesday morning?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0109">which age?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0052">the older</u>
<u n="213" who="S0109">yeah they Wednesday morning unless they had they want to have something like study time or sports in the afternoon</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="214" who="S0109">oh I've just <unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="215" who="S0109">what vegetable goes with curry?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0052">with curry?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0052">em <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know? Beans? What kind of curry?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0109">korma <pause dur="short"/> actually it might help if I tell you what I've got cos</u>
<u n="220" who="S0052">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> it's quite a small selection is it?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0052">go on then</u>
<u n="223" who="S0109">carrots peas broccoli eh</u>
<u n="224" who="S0052">peas the most out of them</u>
<u n="225" who="S0109">peas <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> well that's nice and simple</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="226" who="S0109">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="227" who="S0052">I'm full up now</u>
<u n="228" who="S0109">that's the idea</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="229" who="S0109">I might do a <unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0052">it probably doesn't matter that it's not something an Indian would have had</u>
<u n="231" who="S0109">sorry?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0052">probably doesn't matter if it's not something in Indian would've had</u>
<u n="233" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you see I've <pause dur="short"/> when I've cooked it for other people before they give me funny looks cos like</u>
<u n="234" who="S0052">no <pause dur="short"/> well it's only for you <pause dur="short"/> is it?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0109">it is only for me</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<event desc="sound of banging"/>
<u n="236" who="S0109">what is that?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0052">isn't it the hoover?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0109">oh</u>
<u n="239" who="S0052">which I would <trunc>assu</trunc> assume was being used by <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rather than <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0109">that would be good wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0052">it would be quite amusing</u>
<u n="242" who="S0109">I don't know what was going on last night but there were there was a police car <pause dur="short"/> it was going round and round and round the block</u>
<u n="243" who="S0052">I was asleep or was I out?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0109">eh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="245" who="S0052">no I wasn't out last night was I? Was I out <trunc>las</trunc>? What did I do last night? I have no idea</u>
<u n="246" who="S0109">you weren't here when I left <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>you</trunc> your door was closed when I got back <pause dur="short"/> I got back at quarter to eleven</u>
<u n="247" who="S0052">oh I know I came home from work at like seven or something <pause dur="short"/> not cos I was working but cos I was chatting</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="248" who="S0109">I do sometimes wonder about this estate</u>
<u n="249" who="S0052">about what?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0109">this estate</u>
<u n="251" who="S0052">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's eh mostly our two neighbours down you know and her family who partly live across the way</u>
<u n="252" who="S0109">the they're the trouble causers</u>
<u n="253" who="S0052">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0109">what do they do?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0052">em <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure but so one of the neighbours that you know so when I got my phone delivered</u>
<u n="256" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0052">eh it was left at like the neighbour like about ten down that way</u>
<u n="258" who="S0109">as you do yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0052">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I went to get it <pause dur="short"/> it was obviously it was someone I didn't know cos it was so far away <pause dur="short"/> em and she was telling me about we were talking about neighbourhood and she's lived here for ages <pause dur="short"/> so she was telling me about all of them that live two <trunc>yo</trunc> doors down and she said that she her ex-husband? Used to live across the green and they'd have big arguments like on the street and now like she lives there and her sons live across the green and sometimes her daughter who has a baby lives with her and it sounds like they seem to cause most of the trouble in you know between that large family</u>
<u n="260" who="S0109">right</u>
<u n="261" who="S0052">from what she was saying</u>
<u n="262" who="S0109">it sounds a bit claustrophobic</u>
<u n="263" who="S0052">like she was saying oh you know the police often round there <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh I did know the police came here sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know it was all for the family</u>
<u n="264" who="S0109">but I don't know it's wouldn't you want to move out? What's so?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0052">sorry?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0109">what's so attractive about living opposite?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0052">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's her children though</u>
<u n="268" who="S0109">I was in the library the other day and there were people just having a full blown row <pause dur="short"/> I thought they were on the phone but they were actually sitting next to each other <pause dur="short"/> I think they were</u>
<u n="269" who="S0052">you are meant to be quiet in the library</u>
<u n="270" who="S0109">I was just like</u>
<u n="271" who="S0052">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0109">I wouldn't want to do that anywhere but in the library where everyone else is being quiet?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0052">and also it's just rude in the library isn't it?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> although if <unclear/> a text rather than this library thing it's a little less disturbing <pause dur="short"/> ooh what's that little</u>
<u n="275" who="S0052">I think it was one and a half <unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hope so</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="277" who="S0052">how many children will tell me tomorrow that I wasn't there last week? They have a habit of pointing out the obvious <pause dur="short"/> you weren't here last week <pause dur="short"/> oh really?</u>
<u n="278" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0109">wasn't I? I thought I was <pause dur="short"/> eh mm <pause dur="short"/> what did you do with him this week?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0052">eh Jesus is going to feed five thousand people <pause dur="short"/> like lots and lots of people</u>
<u n="281" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't five thousand people</u>
<u n="282" who="S0052">it was five thousand men plus women</u>
<u n="283" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0052">the children don't really understand thousands anyway <pause dur="short"/> it's slightly relevant <pause dur="short"/> it was lots of people it's all we need to know</u>
</body>
</text>
