<text id="S3RZ">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:46:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The countryside, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Walking, flowers, economics, research, cash crops, languages, football</topics>
		<activity>Couple go for a walk in the countryside.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0024">are we going to do the coast to coast?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0144">I'd love to do the coast to coast</u>
<u n="3" who="S0024">you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing another run?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0024">I wonder when that is?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0144">yeah she's doing it for that company she works for <pause dur="short"/> that charity</u>
<u n="7" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0144">what is it? Camfed</u>
<u n="9" who="S0024">no I don't think she works for Camfed does she? Or does she?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0144">well I thought she did</u>
<u n="11" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I'd love to do the coast to coast <pause dur="short"/> maybe in the Summer <pause dur="short"/> after the party</u>
<u n="13" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0144">maybe we could just go up <pause dur="short"/> don't know how far it is but</u>
<u n="15" who="S0024">problem is dropping the car off at one end</u>
<u n="16" who="S0144">well that's the problem isn't it <pause dur="short"/> you do need to carry a lot of the <trunc>stu</trunc> and it's going to be quite expensive</u>
<u n="17" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0144">because the the places to stop on route have kind of monopolised it a little bit</u>
<u n="19" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0144">and they know you've got no other choice but to stay with them <pause dur="short"/> but I think they offer places to pitch tents and stuff so</u>
<u n="21" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0144">if I could carry the tent as well <pause dur="short"/> but that would be carrying twenty or thirty kilos across</u>
<u n="23" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that's what we used to do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0144">yeah but from one side of the country to the other <pause dur="short"/> I know we used to but we're a bit out of practice aren't we</u>
<u n="25" who="S0024">yeah it just depends injury wise</u>
<u n="26" who="S0144">yeah it depends if my foot goes again <pause dur="short"/> no I'd definitely like to do that <pause dur="short"/> or I'd like to go to I'd like to climb Ben Nevis</u>
<u n="27" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0144">something I've always wanted to do</u>
<u n="29" who="S0024">that doesn't take too long to climb does it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0144">no no <pause dur="short"/> it's not that big <pause dur="short"/> if you do it in the Summer the weather will be alright <pause dur="short"/> that will be nice</u>
<u n="31" who="S0024">you've got to get up there</u>
<u n="32" who="S0144">or you know well we could go and do Snowdon or something <pause dur="short"/> but I've always wanted to go up to Scotland and and out on the East er the West sorry <pause dur="short"/> it looks beautiful up there <pause dur="short"/> or even up to erm what's it called that in the North West? What's that island?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what of Scotland?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's that island called? I've forgotten</u>
<u n="35" who="S0024">what the one that you love?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0024">isle of Skye?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0024">is it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0144">looks really beautiful there</u>
<u n="41" who="S0024">do you get a ferry across?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0144">no I think they've got a bridge <pause dur="short"/> they've got a toll bridge</u>
<u n="43" who="S0024">ah but I wouldn't be able to do all the driving all the way up there</u>
<u n="44" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0024">that's impossible</u>
<u n="46" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you can get pretty cheap flights can't you</u>
<u n="47" who="S0024">yeah but then you need a car the other end as well</u>
<u n="48" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but from you can get a flight to er I don't know Inverness?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0024">yeah probably</u>
<u n="50" who="S0144">so how many emails did you sort out today?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0024">there were two <pause dur="short"/> well you see cos the I never wanted to sort them out cos there's just too many <pause dur="short"/> so there was two hundred and <trunc>for</trunc> fifty-three that I hadn't even opened cos they were I don't know <pause dur="short"/> junk mostly or something <pause dur="short"/> but then when I get the new messages they just kind of all blur in and you're just like oh now I've got two hundred and fifty-four <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> and it's difficult to I don't know I've being using that flag option now to like flag the ones I want to answer <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm not very good at answering them straight away</u>
<u n="52" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0024">like Ben's email <pause dur="short"/> I haven't emailed him back <pause dur="short"/> have you?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0144">er I did say <pause dur="short"/> yeah I did write something</u>
<u n="55" who="S0024">yeah?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0024">we need to write them a nice</u>
<u n="58" who="S0144">well there's a couple of people I didn't write back to <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I wrote back to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday today</u>
<u n="60" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0024">yes</u>
<u n="62" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> that's a good chance then to write something <pause dur="short"/> send him a message later</u>
<u n="63" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you know all these people who have said they they'd love to come and see us in the Summer but yeah <pause dur="short"/> we've got to write</u>
<u n="64" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah we're crap at staying in touch aren't we</u>
<u n="65" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm rubbish</u>
<u n="66" who="S0144">yeah we both are</u>
<u n="67" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I think that's mainly because of my disorganisation and then my my thought processes are quite slow so it's like ah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="68" who="S0144">yeah and you think too much of what you're going to write</u>
<u n="69" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I and then I wait a few days <pause dur="short"/> and then I forget that I even had an email or I don't want to go on the computer for a bit <pause dur="short"/> so I don't go on the computer for a couple of weeks unless I'm expecting an important email</u>
<u n="70" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0024">and then  and then  I forget</u>
<u n="72" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0024">and that's the same with with my other social networks as well <pause dur="short"/> I always forget</u>
<u n="74" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="75" who="S0024">ah look at those daffodils</u>
<u n="76" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0024">beautiful</u>
<u n="78" who="S0144">very yellow aren't they</u>
<u n="79" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see are those wild ones?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know do you have a difference between wild ones and other ones?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well they said <pause dur="short"/> yeah there is</u>
<u n="82" who="S0144">well they must be wild <pause dur="short"/> no one would plant them there would they</u>
<u n="83" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0144">but they come up don't they <pause dur="short"/> again <pause dur="short"/> like every year they come up</u>
<u n="85" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's an orange tulip one <pause dur="short"/> well not not tulip <pause dur="short"/> trumpet</u>
<u n="86" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah so if I had a garden I'd plant stuff that comes up every year <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand it when you give yourself so much work and you have to replant it and</u>
<u n="87" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that's a hobby <pause dur="short"/> it's a hobby and then you reap the benefits in the Summer time and go wow</u>
<u n="88" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's very time consuming though isn't it</u>
<u n="89" who="S0024">yeah but if it's a hobby you don't notice it so much</u>
<u n="90" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I mean and if it's something that you do year after year then it just becomes this is what I do in in May</u>
<u n="92" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> see I don't know if I could be bothered</u>
<u n="93" who="S0024" trans="overlap">or in</u>
<u n="94" who="S0144">I'd just like them to come up every year</u>
<u n="95" who="S0024">just buy buy them ready ready made</u>
<u n="96" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't mind doing the work once</u>
<u n="97" who="S0024">look at that fat waddling cat</u>
<u n="98" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0024">she's got some kittens in her oven</u>
<u n="100" who="S0144">go and throw it in that wheelie bin <pause dur="short"/> slow down in our village</u>
<u n="101" who="S0024">yeah they had the magazine come out and they're trying to get everybody to put those on there</u>
<u n="102" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0024">yeah because they're not there all the time <pause dur="short"/> cos there's that research that says and there's when you've got a traffic sign</u>
<u n="104" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0024">and people get used to where it is and then they just start ignoring it if they drive past it every day <pause dur="short"/> whereas if you put the signs on the wheelie bins and they go out at different days <pause dur="short"/> they're different colours</u>
<u n="106" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="107" who="S0024">then you put them in a slightly different place which makes people look</u>
<u n="108" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0024">well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how true that is <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> little primrose</u>
<u n="110" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0024">I'm starting to recognise a lot more flowers and things now since we've been learning a little bit about them</u>
<u n="112" who="S0144">there's a stinging nettle</u>
<u n="113" who="S0024">well done</u>
<u n="114" who="S0144">there's a dandelion</u>
<u n="115" who="S0024">well done</u>
<u n="116" who="S0144">that's about the extent to my knowledge</u>
<u n="117" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> I now know what a primrose looks like</u>
<u n="118" who="S0144">that's hedge and that's grass</u>
<u n="119" who="S0024">what are you doing? You silly bugger</u>
<u n="120" who="S0144">yeah it's still a bit chilly <pause dur="short"/> can't believe it <pause dur="short"/> it was absolutely pissing down about an hour ago</u>
<u n="121" who="S0024">yeah I know</u>
<u n="122" who="S0144">and now it's beautiful</u>
<u n="123" who="S0024">I was worried we'd get caught out in it again</u>
<u n="124" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="125" who="S0024">huh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0144">oh it's good to walk off the dinner</u>
<u n="127" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> god Mum's <trunc>fa</trunc> face bless her <pause dur="short"/> it was too hot for her</u>
<u n="128" who="S0144">it was worth cooking that dinner just to see your mum's face <pause dur="short"/> her eyes nearly popped out her head</u>
<u n="129" who="S0024">she has some funny faces</u>
<u n="130" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0144">well I mean I know it is it would have maybe one or two chillies</u>
<u n="133" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it was hot and you said hot? It's not hot <pause dur="short"/> it was <pause dur="short"/> it was quite hot</u>
<u n="134" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it <pause dur="short"/> well yeah <pause dur="short"/> but she ate it</u>
<u n="135" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0144">quite surprised</u>
<u n="137" who="S0024">thing with those kind of ones though with the little bit of pita bread and stuff if you haven't got something on the side <pause dur="short"/> like guacamole or salad or something</u>
<u n="138" who="S0144">yeah you need the</u>
<u n="139" who="S0024">I think you get hungry again a bit later because <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> they seem quite filling at the time</u>
<u n="140" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that's why you need like a burrito or something and you fill it full of like beef or something don't you <pause dur="short"/> like fills it out <pause dur="short"/> nachos aren't very er fajitas aren't very filling</u>
<u n="141" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh look at that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0144">has someone made that?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0144">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="145" who="S0024">ah a little piece of artwork</u>
<u n="146" who="S0144">that's cool that is</u>
<u n="147" who="S0024">well what animal would you say it is? I'd say it was a fox</u>
<u n="148" who="S0144">A dragon</u>
<u n="149" who="S0024">ah that's really good</u>
<u n="150" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no that's good yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0024">now I'm going to have to look out for more pieces of wood made <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0144">yeah last night <pause dur="short"/> I thought I'd do a bit of research cos I'm I still can't get my head round what the hell a derivative is <pause dur="short"/> and all this like credit default swap stuff and like commodities and and I wish had <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? I wish I had learnt more about economics when I was at school</u>
<u n="153" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> didn't we make a? They do now <pause dur="short"/> they changed the whole of the GCSEs <pause dur="short"/> you take things like that now</u>
<u n="154" who="S0144" trans="overlap">they should <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0144">I wouldn't mind buying like an economics for dummies book or something</u>
<u n="157" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0144">look there's that private jet again</u>
<u n="159" who="S0024">who lives in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0144">that's the same one <pause dur="short"/> well there's loads of military bases round here</u>
<u n="161" who="S0024">yeah but</u>
<u n="162" who="S0144">it's probably some general or something</u>
<u n="163" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="164" who="S0144">it's like that top secret plane that flies around with a big er antenna on the front of it just as it gets dark <pause dur="short"/> flies at really low altitude <pause dur="short"/> have you seen it?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0024">ah they're testing something aren't they</u>
<u n="166" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or it could be coming off like a <trunc>reconanc</trunc> reconnaissance like mission off the  off the  coast <pause dur="short"/> like be just come back at the same time everyday</u>
<u n="167" who="S0024" trans="overlap">hello pheasant <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it looks like the Grouse whiskey advert except it's not a grouse</u>
<u n="168" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="169" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah what do you think they're testing for?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0144">well it could be a reconnaissance of some kind of thing over the coast <pause dur="short"/> or they could be picking up something with it I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit weird isn't it <pause dur="short"/> anyway yeah I was look at Max Keiser was going on about this woman called er Blythe Masters</u>
<u n="171" who="S0024">I've heard of that name</u>
<u n="172" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she was the person basically at the centre of this credit default swap thing</u>
<u n="173" who="S0024" trans="overlap">where's she from?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0144">she works for erm er oh what's? Bloody what are they called? JP Morgan</u>
<u n="175" who="S0024">oh right</u>
<u n="176" who="S0144">erm she's educated in like Canterbury and Oxford and now she's running like the whole of JP Morgan's commodity division</u>
<u n="177" who="S0024">oh right <pause dur="short"/> what does she do?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0144">and she basically set up this credit default swap thing <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> now she's moved on to like commodities like rice and wheat and stuff <pause dur="short"/> basically what he was saying is she's making it <pause dur="short"/> they've bought everything <pause dur="short"/> all the food</u>
<u n="179" who="S0024">what in the world? What in the what?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0144">so well <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>p</trunc> pretty much <pause dur="short"/> this is what I need to look at <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="181" who="S0024">can't have bought everything in the world?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0144">no but</u>
<u n="183" who="S0024">might have bought all the seeds</u>
<u n="184" who="S0144">with all the trillions of dollars they've got <pause dur="short"/> but basically no countries are buying <pause dur="short"/> instead of the market operating where you go into the marketplace and buy the goods</u>
<u n="185" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0144">because the bank owns all the goods they're acting as like a middleman</u>
<u n="187" who="S0024">oh great</u>
<u n="188" who="S0144">or something <pause dur="short"/> so they've they've got control of a lot of the world's food supply</u>
<u n="189" who="S0024">but they can't <trunc>ac</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> they're not acting as a middleman then <pause dur="short"/> they're acting as a behind the scenes erm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah but they can  they can  manipulate the prices of the food</u>
<u n="191" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="192" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I need to look into it <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's quite worrying</u>
<u n="193" who="S0024">I don't really understand what that would do</u>
<u n="194" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to look into it</u>
<u n="195" who="S0024">it makes them more money? Or they control? I suppose oh I don't know whether they control everything</u>
<u n="196" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh yeah of course <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos she went on erm CNN</u>
<u n="197" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0144">erm she's never given like an interview before she's</u>
<u n="199" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024" trans="overlap">hello</u>
<u n="201" who="S0144" trans="overlap">hello <pause dur="short"/> she's never given a an interview before <pause dur="short"/> she's very kind of media savvy <pause dur="short"/> just stays away from all of that <pause dur="short"/> but she she came across as just this like kind of bumbling woman <pause dur="short"/> doesn't really know very much about economics and she's just trying to do some good</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh she's a George Bush</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">but she was very clever in the way she came across</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144">when really she's extremely intelligent and you know quite evil</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">yeah I'm going to research it tonight anyway <pause dur="short"/> hello ducks</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah well that's the thing cos I like all all this stuff I don't have the arguments to</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144">well that's it isn't it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">I know that it's wrong but I can't explain in words what I feel about it or any back up</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you need to do a a degree in banking or finance to understand the basics of what's going on really</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144">and I can approach it from a political or a social aspect and I can <trunc>un</trunc> I can see how it's working but to actually understand the actual</u>
<u n="214" who="S0024">do an A-Level in economics <pause dur="short"/> why not? Like oh with erm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144">no but I don't think that would be good enough <pause dur="short"/> I think it would have to be a degree</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">yeah you need  yeah you need  to go deeper</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144">yeah I mean cos they're not going to teach you the stuff that you want to know anyway <pause dur="short"/> they're only going to teach you how the system works</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but I was just thinking how you could <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah but at university it becomes a bit more <pause dur="short"/> they <trunc>g</trunc> they like to give you a rounded opinion most of the time <pause dur="short"/> well it depends which lecturers you get doesn't it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos that's how most people end up</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I thought they were plastic <pause dur="short"/> oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> I thought they were plastic <pause dur="short"/> aren't they beautiful</u>
<u n="221" who="S0144">what are they?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0024">tulips <pause dur="short"/> but they're really tall <pause dur="short"/> my tulips are only have the the leaves</u>
<u n="223" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="224" who="S0024"><event desc="sound of gasping"/> We should go and have a look <pause dur="short"/> see if ours have grown</u>
<u n="225" who="S0144">well they're getting the sun look <pause dur="short"/> that's why</u>
<u n="226" who="S0024">they're beautiful <pause dur="short"/> you need to get a good <trunc>lec</trunc> like that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> when you look at university courses and stuff like that you don't research the lecturers that are going to be teaching you</u>
<u n="227" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that's very important</u>
<u n="228" who="S0024">it's very <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0144">Cos even the universities teach you like how the system works but you can come out of university and still not be able to like critically view it</u>
<u n="230" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0144">or have an alternative</u>
<u n="232" who="S0024">but yeah well like my <trunc>res</trunc></u>
<u n="233" who="S0144">especially scientific things like that</u>
<u n="234" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah my research that I did for undergraduate <pause dur="short"/> the psychology project that I did <pause dur="short"/> the subliminal messages thing</u>
<u n="235" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0024">and then like that was how many years ago? And nobody had done it before <pause dur="short"/> anything similar</u>
<u n="237" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0024">and I know the and and the lecturers were like oh don't be so stupid <pause dur="short"/> and all they wanted to do was erm eye witness testimonies</u>
<u n="239" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah just go over ground that's all ready been <trunc>trov</trunc> trodden</u>
<u n="240" who="S0024">eye witness <trunc>test</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I'm an expert in eye witness testimonies</u>
<u n="241" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0024">this is all I know about <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="243" who="S0144">exactly</u>
<u n="244" who="S0024">then it's on on the TV and they've made a whole program about it <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if someone <pause dur="short"/> I mean I was seventy-four percent <pause dur="short"/> one percent off of being bloody <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> it would have been good if it was published cos then I could turn round to them and say look <pause dur="short"/> I did this this many years ago</u>
<u n="245" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0024">but ah I just can't believe it <pause dur="short"/> did all of that work and somebody <pause dur="short"/> you don't you just don't know <pause dur="short"/> somebody could have found it <pause dur="short"/> plymouth University looked through it and gone ah I'll just adapt this one a little bit</u>
<u n="247" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and Bob's your uncle <pause dur="short"/> they've got some research</u>
<u n="249" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0024">some psychology graduate came out and then they  and then they  said on the news wow it's been found that that erm different words <pause dur="short"/> I mean they did exactly the same <pause dur="short"/> they did positive words neutral words and negative words <pause dur="short"/> subliminally taken in and how it affected their emotions <pause dur="short"/> but they did it how they walked didn't they <pause dur="short"/> how they walked down an aisle or something <pause dur="short"/> and I did it through the the Stroop test and just some that emotion questionnaire things</u>
<u n="251" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0024">and mine was flawed in many many ways really but it was the whole basis of the idea that hadn't been researched again <pause dur="short"/> it's not  it's not  fair</u>
<u n="253" who="S0144">yeah but I mean subliminal messaging is quite a big topic <pause dur="short"/> I mean it was only a matter of time before someone else did it <pause dur="short"/> it's like you know when you come up with a great idea for something and then a couple of years later someone's made this invention</u>
<u n="254" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but it's not  it's not  fair <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0144">and you go oh bloody I thought of that</u>
<u n="256" who="S0024">yeah that happens all the time</u>
<u n="257" who="S0144" trans="overlap">you know that always happens</u>
<u n="258" who="S0024">but you didn't do anything about it <pause dur="short"/> I wrote a research paper about it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah well that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah but you didn't do anything about it <pause dur="short"/> you didn't you know have courage in your convictions and follow it through and er and <trunc>p</trunc> publish it which you could have done <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="260" who="S0024">I couldn't publish it cos I got seventy-four percent <pause dur="short"/> you have to have seventy-five percent to publish it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0144">oh you could have <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure you could have done</u>
<u n="262" who="S0024">well I was young <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know how to do that kind of thing do you</u>
<u n="263" who="S0144">yeah yeah I know</u>
<u n="264" who="S0024">especially when you've got the lecturer standing there going urgh</u>
<u n="265" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0024">I mean they didn't help me one iota</u>
<u n="267" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the problem I had with like writing stuff like that is cos I always wanted to write something that had meaning</u>
<u n="268" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Cos they weren't interested <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0144">that was kind of pushing for something new <pause dur="short"/> to find something new</u>
<u n="270" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0144">whereas that isn't what a a degree's about <pause dur="short"/> a degree's about just writing a research <trunc>produ</trunc> <trunc>pr</trunc> project in in a good way</u>
<u n="272" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and and the the main thing is is the writing of it even if you <trunc>rep</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and and writing down every single problem whether you generalising or whether your being <trunc>spec</trunc> specific or making all the  all the  flaws in everything clear</u>
<u n="273" who="S0144" trans="overlap">the main thing is making sure the literature review ties in with your like your whatever what are they called? And then you tie it with the conclusion <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that's what the <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0024">yeah you've really got to know how to write one <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> rather than the actual research</u>
<u n="275" who="S0144">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0024">I mean the manipulation of the data <pause dur="short"/> it just drives me mad <pause dur="short"/> you can do anything with it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0144">yeah well that's what  that's what  I was surprised about with</u>
<u n="278" who="S0024" trans="overlap">just just make it a log value <pause dur="short"/> oh look <pause dur="short"/> now it looks better <pause dur="short"/> now we'll analyse it</u>
<u n="279" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0024">just <trunc>ma</trunc> just cut out oh these erm what do you call those? Those points which are far far away from everybody <trunc>el</trunc> from the normality or something?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0024">oh I've forgotten the name of them</u>
<u n="283" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0024">oh we can't use that piece of data <pause dur="short"/> we're we'll just take it out of the equation</u>
<u n="285" who="S0144">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0024">even though it was somebody's opinion somewhere or it's something that happened somewhere</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">well exactly that's why all of these studies are a load of bollocks</u>
<u n="288" who="S0024">they are <pause dur="short"/> especially in the social sciences</u>
<u n="289" who="S0144" trans="overlap">especially and especially when they're you know you've got these big companies which outsource a project to a like a research agency and they know <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean? Even if they don't make it explicitly what they have to find the research agency knows what they want to find and they can massage the data in any way they want to</u>
<u n="290" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah they know what they have to find <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah remember that</u>
<u n="291" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and the same applies to like government agencies or whoever</u>
<u n="292" who="S0024">remember like part of our  part of our  masters was how can you manipulate this data?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0024">and everybody came out with different ideas <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't what you came out with that was the what you got the marks for <pause dur="short"/> it was how you did it and how you wrote it up <pause dur="short"/> and how you explained your actions of how <pause dur="short"/> but everybody</u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">have you got any mints?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">everybody erm everybody <trunc>manipula</trunc> massaged the data in different ways</u>
<u n="297" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0024">and they came out all different directions but everybody who did a good job in writing it up and explaining what they did and why they did it got erm A's or whatever or if they did it well</u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024">oh that's enough of me moaning</u>
<u n="301" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024">I didn't mean to start moaning</u>
<u n="303" who="S0144" trans="overlap">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> we always seem to be moaning when we're recording stuff</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024">I don't mean too</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144">oh <pause dur="short"/> did you just drop all those mints?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0144">thank you</u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">no I don't mean to moan <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="309" who="S0144">apologising to me?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0024">they do do some erm good research <pause dur="short"/> they do do I just it just frustrates me how they put it in the paper and and they're allowed to come out with completely opposing research every other week</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024">eat chocolate <pause dur="short"/> don't eat chocolate <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144">yeah well that's done on purpose as well</u>
<u n="314" who="S0024">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> well exactly <pause dur="short"/> oh I could walk for ever <pause dur="short"/> is there somewhere else we can walk?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144">well we could walk around the other block?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">I said we're going to wash up when we get back</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there's not much to do</u>
<u n="319" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> we could play <pause dur="short"/> have a game of table tennis when we get back?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've got to practise</u>
<u n="321" who="S0144">yeah you do <pause dur="short"/> well if you want to be as good as me one day you need to put the hours in</u>
<u n="322" who="S0024">well I'm going to practise with everybody every day</u>
<u n="323" who="S0144">mhm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0024">so that I get at least three games in a day</u>
<u n="325" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0024">they take longer than you think though don't they</u>
<u n="327" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0024">by the time you've done the three</u>
<u n="329" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I noticed your <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0024">rounds <pause dur="short"/> oh that's half an hour really isn't it</u>
<u n="331" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0024">A game</u>
<u n="333" who="S0144">I've noticed your spinney shots are getting a lot better</u>
<u n="334" who="S0024">yeah? I thought they were getting worse</u>
<u n="335" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="336" who="S0024">it's my erm forehand <pause dur="short"/> I need to work on my forehand cos I've only got one move on my forehand</u>
<u n="337" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0024">my back hand I'm getting better at doing all these different moves but my forehand I just can't seem to</u>
<u n="339" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think the biggest thing you need to work on is your psychology <pause dur="short"/> cos when you lose like a few points in a row you completely lose it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0024">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've got to stay calm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> which way are we going? This way?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0024">this way <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144">it's going to be a long walk</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why not</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144">God <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well I either get too excited or I get too frustrated cos I've done something silly <pause dur="short"/> a silly move</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024">and that that annoys me because I know as I hit it that I've done it wrong</u>
<u n="349" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024">and I think ah I should gave done hit it a different way <pause dur="short"/> but it's so fast the game that you haven't really got time to think <pause dur="short"/> you've got to rely on your own reactions so you've got to train your own reactions as to what you need to do</u>
<u n="351" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0024">so really you can't  you can't  See I thinking too slowly and then do the wrong shot</u>
<u n="353" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it's almost very kind of intuitive isn't it? Your movements and</u>
<u n="354" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144">it's good for your reflexes</u>
<u n="356" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> we should try a left handed game</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I want to work on my speed <pause dur="short"/> cos I remember remember when I erm went to that place in China that that room where I had to practise my stuff</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">and they had  they had  a little section where all these kids were playing table tennis and they were just awesome <pause dur="short"/> they're only they can barely get their heads above the table you know <pause dur="short"/> they were that small</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144">and they were just pinging them back sort of like <event desc="sound of rapid fire"/> sort of like Forrest Gump <pause dur="short"/> and that's</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">yeah and erm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144">that's what I want to I don't know how to do that <pause dur="short"/> how to practise getting to that speed</u>
<u n="364" who="S0024">do you know how fast we're going?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144">huh?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0024">I think  I think  what you need to do is cos remember when I er there was a couple of shots two years ago Dad erm we did some recordings and we recorded us playing table tennis</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024">and we recorded Dad and you playing table tennis <pause dur="short"/> and they are faster than you think</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">yeah look faster</u>
<u n="370" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it's not</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144">when you're playing it seems slower cos your awareness is tuned in and your reactions <pause dur="short"/> when you're observing it yeah it does look faster</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">yeah that's true <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it's not <pause dur="short"/> you know you look at the professionals and stuff and they they can take two three paces back from the table and still be whacking them</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well that's what I've been trying to is step back to back from the table</u>
<u n="375" who="S0144">you know and having proper like rallies like just smashing it to each other</u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144">and then putting in a drop shot</u>
<u n="378" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you've you've still got to be able to jump in and reach those</u>
<u n="379" who="S0144">oh yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024">those short shots</u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">but I haven't got to the stage where I can just whack it from you know a couple of metres from the table</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024">but in <trunc>or</trunc> to practise that we've both got to step back</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> haven't really got the space though have you</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024">Cos what they do those fast players <pause dur="short"/> they almost hit it to each other to each other to each other and then find a spot in the game where they can  find a spot in the game where they can  flick it the other way or gently tap it <pause dur="short"/> you know they really bide their time and wait for the right moment <pause dur="short"/> it's like <event desc="sound of ball going back and forth"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah and they can put the ball right in the spot that they want it in</u>
<u n="386" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144">which I'm getting there <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean though? You should be aiming <pause dur="short"/> you should actually right you should mark a a bit on the table <pause dur="short"/> just a bit of chalk</u>
<u n="388" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144">right on the base line <pause dur="short"/> like a couple of centimetres or a few centimetres <pause dur="short"/> or actually start more than that and aim to hit the ball into that zone <pause dur="short"/> cos that's the key zone <pause dur="short"/> you don't want it bouncing in the middle of the table</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">Cos then it's it's easy</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">too easy yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144">you want to be hitting it on the base line or or just dropping it over</u>
<u n="394" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0144"><trunc>Tha</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> so you should try and you could start couldn't you by <trunc>ju</trunc> putting a couple of chalk marks on and then gradually moving it either way</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024">yeah for the like really work on the precision</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024"><trunc>Preci</trunc> blah blah blah</u>
<event desc="sound of passing car"/>
<u n="399" who="S0024">oh he nodded <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know him</u>
<u n="400" who="S0144">yeah he did nod</u>
<u n="401" who="S0024">what a nice man</u>
<u n="402" who="S0144">that was a proper farmers' nod</u>
<u n="403" who="S0024">yeah it was wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah well maybe instead of having games we should do something like that but the problem is you're so much better than me that I don't know</u>
<u n="404" who="S0144" trans="overlap">Cos I I would <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0024"><trunc>Re</trunc> but</u>
<u n="406" who="S0144">I mean cos the main thing is just playing for fun anyway but I would like to step it up a little bit and try and get to the next level</u>
<u n="407" who="S0024">put some <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that means some dedicated practise at one particular thing or</u>
<u n="408" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean Korea was the prime opportunity to to work on that</u>
<u n="409" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well we weren't into table tennis then</u>
<u n="410" who="S0144">yeah but they had table tennis clubs everywhere didn't they</u>
<u n="411" who="S0024">yeah but we weren't into it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I remember Gregg joined the club in Hwamyeong-dong</u>
<u n="413" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0144">and in in the club was erm that woman who was on the Olympic team</u>
<u n="415" who="S0024">really? In Hwamyeong-dong?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or or an old Olympic team <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>sh</trunc> he was getting taught by her</u>
<u n="417" who="S0024">oh wow</u>
<u n="418" who="S0144">and he became like excellent really quickly</u>
<u n="419" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh you know Korea was such a great place for learning things <pause dur="short"/> learning new things <pause dur="short"/> it was really good</u>
<u n="420" who="S0144">yeah it was good wasn't it</u>
<u n="421" who="S0024">well I know  I know  there's <pause dur="short"/> well India was a great place as well I think <pause dur="short"/> it was like a felt like a place to study something different or do something different</u>
<u n="422" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0024">both of those</u>
<u n="424" who="S0144">well it was kind of a booming country wasn't it</u>
<u n="425" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I hope <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0144">I mean everyone seemed to</u>
<u n="427" who="S0024">everyone had to have that artistic side to them too so the kids had to study an instrument</u>
<u n="428" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but what</u>
<u n="429" who="S0024">that's like a major thing</u>
<u n="430" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what I found with Korea is a large proportion of the country was middle class <pause dur="short"/> you didn't really see that many poor people in Korea</u>
<u n="431" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> or maybe we didn't go in <pause dur="short"/> we did go out in the countryside</u>
<u n="432" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and so they had <pause dur="short"/> everyone could kind of afford for their kids to learn piano or play table tennis or learn English</u>
<u n="433" who="S0024">yeah well it wasn't extremely expensive like here either</u>
<u n="434" who="S0144">no no <pause dur="short"/> that's what I mean it was</u>
<u n="435" who="S0024">so the middle classes could afford it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think was you know probably the height of their economy <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's that good any more <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think it will be for very much longer cos they've sold all their stuff to China</u>
<u n="437" who="S0024">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0144">so they're going to gonna struggle <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's hit them yet but but it was great though wasn't it</u>
<u n="439" who="S0024">yeah it was</u>
<u n="440" who="S0144">I mean you had the</u>
<u n="441" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it's one of those things that you look back on and go ah I wish I'd had more piano lessons cos I really can't play anything <trunc>any</trunc> anymore and what I learnt has gone out of my head</u>
<u n="442" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0024">I wish I did more of this <pause dur="short"/> more of that</u>
<u n="444" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0024">whereas some places we've lived it's been like well there wasn't much to do so</u>
<u n="446" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0024">you know I could have done a few things but more or something</u>
<u n="448" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think we make good use of our time really</u>
<u n="449" who="S0024">oh yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0144">Don't sit around on our arses do we</u>
<u n="451" who="S0024">sometimes I do</u>
<u n="452" who="S0144">yeah but that's usually after a period of like working excessively hard or</u>
<u n="453" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> that's about perfect timing by the time we get back because I don't want it to get too dark</u>
<u n="454" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm <pause dur="short"/> so all of these rape fields</u>
<u n="455" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0144">is that just to provide like rapeseed oil for like vegetable oil for the UK or do we export it?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0024">I don't know but they get a subsidiary <pause dur="short"/> not subsidiary erm <trunc>sub</trunc> they get subsidised by government for it</u>
<u n="458" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0024">which is why <pause dur="short"/> I mean I remember when I was a kid it's just used to be wheat barley and some lavender</u>
<u n="460" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0024">I don't even see lavender fields anymore but Dad said there are some a long way up <pause dur="short"/> but rape just took over</u>
<u n="462" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> it looks nice but you can't eat it though</u>
<u n="463" who="S0024">yeah it's pretty <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no and how much oil can you have?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0024">you can get oil from so so many other things <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if they try to use it as I don't know if they're trying to do something else with it</u>
<u n="466" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> can you use it as fuel?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0024">I think there is a possibility to but who's going to do it? I mean if they  if they  did use that as fuel then every single field would be covered in rape</u>
<u n="468" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well it's like the palm trees or the palm oil trees in Malaysia or Indonesia</u>
<u n="469" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0144">and then they just covered everything with that and then they can't grow their own food so they have to export it and then they're over a barrel</u>
<u n="471" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'll never forget flying over that thing <pause dur="short"/> we were expecting to see jungle</u>
<u n="472" who="S0144">well it was jungle</u>
<u n="473" who="S0024">and then <pause dur="short"/> yeah but we didn't see like we saw some jungle and then it was just cleared out and then there was just plantations</u>
<u n="474" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well no <pause dur="short"/> that was really sad that was</u>
<u n="475" who="S0024">that <trunc>wa</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> where were we flying? Eh? Where did we fly round there? I don't remember flying around there</u>
<u n="476" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> well I think you might be thinking of erm erm in Sumatra we climbed this massive hill and we looked out over the what we were expecting to be jungle</u>
<u n="477" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't in an aeroplane</u>
<u n="478" who="S0144" trans="overlap">Cos it was jungle the first time I went there</u>
<u n="479" who="S0024">rabbit</u>
<u n="480" who="S0144">it was like a virgin rainforest</u>
<u n="481" who="S0024">hmm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0144">and then it was just all palm oil trees</u>
<u n="483" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0144">no that's why I was saying about the rape because that's what we used to do to all these other countries</u>
<u n="485" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah they don't want to <unclear/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0144">we used to make them grow well they used to be like banana republics <pause dur="short"/> we used to say right you're growing cocoa <pause dur="short"/> you're growing bananas <pause dur="short"/> you're growing coffee <pause dur="short"/> and they couldn't grow any they couldn't grow anything else and they had to import all of their food</u>
<u n="487" who="S0024">well I think that's basically what they've told the farmers here because if you don't  if you don't  grow rape then you don't get the the extra money</u>
<u n="488" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and that's what <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0024">so it's it's obviously more financially <trunc>bet</trunc> beneficial to grow this stuff because otherwise otherwise farmers would be growing food</u>
<u n="490" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0024">wheat</u>
<u n="492" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0024">it is pretty isn't it</u>
<u n="494" who="S0144">it does look pretty yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's not <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't like ruin the whole landscape <pause dur="short"/> it's not like they've cut down loads of stuff to do it</u>
<u n="496" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="497" who="S0024">they've just stopped producing food</u>
<u n="498" who="S0144">yeah and they could next year just change it I suppose</u>
<u n="499" who="S0024">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0144">I don't know what it does to the soil</u>
<u n="501" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="502" who="S0144">it might change the PH level or something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="503" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> no idea</u>
<u n="504" who="S0144">ah it's beautiful isn't it</u>
<u n="505" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah look see yellow all the way <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's a really pretty view actually there</u>
<u n="506" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0024">if those clouds were different that would be a lovely photo</u>
<u n="508" who="S0144">yep</u>
<u n="509" who="S0024">oh I might come up here <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="510" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0144">so what do you want to do tonight?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0024">I don't know I feel quite relaxed <pause dur="short"/> I've done all my work</u>
<u n="513" who="S0144">mhm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0024">I've sorted out some stuff <pause dur="short"/> I've got to get organised <pause dur="short"/> yep er play a game?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0024">but this habit of playing a game is is <trunc>awf</trunc> is a distracting thing isn't it</u>
<u n="517" who="S0144">yeah but we've got bugger all else to do at the moment</u>
<u n="518" who="S0024">well we've got books to read <pause dur="short"/> I've got Arabic to learn</u>
<u n="519" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0024">I should at least be learning <pause dur="short"/> I still don't know the alphabet so I should at least be learning one letter a day so that I know the alphabet so that I can read <pause dur="short"/> a little bit</u>
<u n="521" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0024">oh do you want to learn it with me?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> not tonight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0024">oh it will be so much easier if we can test each other and play games and I don't know</u>
<u n="525" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I just can't get into this Arabic <pause dur="short"/> I just think I haven't got the motivation for languages</u>
<u n="526" who="S0024">but</u>
<u n="527" who="S0144">that's my problem <pause dur="short"/> I think I could learn them alright</u>
<u n="528" who="S0024">I think you would have the motivation for it if you got into using them</u>
<u n="529" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's just</u>
<u n="530" who="S0024">you know <pause dur="short"/> car</u>
<u n="531" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of passing car"/>
<u n="532" who="S0024">just think how how beneficial it would be er negotiating for a better price on a house just saying a few I don't know</u>
<u n="533" who="S0144">what in England? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0024">no no</u>
<u n="535" who="S0144">that would work against you</u>
<u n="536" who="S0024">in Oman <pause dur="short"/> if we ever get there <pause dur="short"/> I don't know we could just just for politeness and I mean we already know the polite words and things but they have got a couple of alternatives for hello that we need to learn from the formal Arabic <pause dur="short"/> the Tunisian Arabic was different different</u>
<u n="537" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no well it does <trunc>g</trunc> of course yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0024">so it's not <foreign lang="ara"/> it's <foreign lang="ara"/> something else and I have quite got there</u>
<u n="539" who="S0144"><foreign lang="ara"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0024">yeah er</u>
<u n="541" who="S0144">that's Tunisian isn't it?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0024">er er no I think you can say it but they say it slightly different <pause dur="short"/> so the whole pronunciation we've got to work on</u>
<u n="543" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0024">so we've got to find out how they say it <pause dur="short"/> and they they say a different word for just a general hello <pause dur="short"/> they cos the Tunisians had the French so they didn't</u>
<u n="545" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0024">they didn't have that</u>
<u n="547" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> anyway I don't know if I want to do that tonight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="549" who="S0144">it's a bit too much like hard work to me</u>
<u n="550" who="S0024">well do you want to do it another night then?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0144">yeah I'll do it another night yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0024">mm?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0024">mm maybe I'll try and learn like look at the letters again and try and test myself of what I've studied before to just to refresh my memory of it</u>
<u n="555" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0024">just for five minutes</u>
<u n="557" who="S0144">mhm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0024">I could do that</u>
<u n="559" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I might <pause dur="short"/> if you're going to do that <pause dur="short"/> I might do some finance research or something <pause dur="short"/> try and get my head around it</u>
<u n="560" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well I'd I'd still like to play a game I'm have no idea what time it is so by the time you play a game</u>
<u n="561" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well it's still light</u>
<u n="562" who="S0024">our games are usually last an hour and a half</u>
<u n="563" who="S0144">no they don't <pause dur="short"/> it's about</u>
<u n="564" who="S0024">I thought we'll play Settlers tonight</u>
<u n="565" who="S0144">er could do</u>
<u n="566" who="S0024">we haven't played that in ages</u>
<u n="567" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that is an hour and a half then isn't it</u>
<u n="568" who="S0024">uh-huh</u>
<u n="569" who="S0144">yeah could do</u>
<u n="570" who="S0024">and then we've got a game of table tennis too to fit in so</u>
<u n="571" who="S0144">well that's the night gone then isn't it</u>
<u n="572" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well with our early nights</u>
<u n="573" who="S0144">what's that over there? Is that a scarecrow?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0024">oh I thought <pause dur="short"/> yeah I thought that was a erm they didn't try too hard with that scarecrow really did they</u>
<u n="575" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="576" who="S0024">looks like giant tent ghost thing</u>
<u n="577" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="578" who="S0024">actually that's quite scary now looking at it <pause dur="short"/> looks like it's turning it's head <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> but it doesn't even have a head but it looks like it's turning it <pause dur="short"/> well that was quite some walk wasn't it</u>
<u n="579" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah we're not there yet</u>
<u n="580" who="S0024">oh oh</u>
<u n="581" who="S0144">you do realise where we are?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0024">oh God <pause dur="short"/> I thought we were a bit closer <pause dur="short"/> I thought we were nearly home <pause dur="short"/> yeah well it's not that that far</u>
<u n="583" who="S0144">well hang on <pause dur="short"/> where are we I'm confused</u>
<u n="584" who="S0024">I'm turning pink <pause dur="short"/> we're just coming around the big field <pause dur="short"/> there's <anon type="place"/> Road over there</u>
<u n="585" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="586" who="S0024">and then er <unclear/></u>
<u n="587" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> so what time's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> coming on Saturday?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0024">in the morning cos I said the football's on in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't come round then</u>
<u n="589" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0024">Cos she doesn't like football at all</u>
<u n="591" who="S0144">no well I'm I'm watching football on Saturday and that's that</u>
<u n="592" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yes yes yes yeah yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0144">it's not often we get to the semi final</u>
<u n="594" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I want to watch it too <pause dur="short"/> I want to watch it with you</u>
<u n="595" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0024">mainly cos I want to drink your beer but and you're not letting me have any the <trunc>t</trunc> until Saturday</u>
<u n="597" who="S0144" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> I see <pause dur="short"/> and who are you? Who are you supporting?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I can't believe you're you're saving up your beer for a Saturday <pause dur="short"/> you've been very good</u>
<u n="599" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I'm going to drink it all on Saturday as well</u>
<u n="600" who="S0024">are you? I thought we could have one</u>
<u n="601" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="602" who="S0024">maybe tonight?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no there's only ten in the box</u>
<u n="604" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="605" who="S0144">between three of us</u>
<u n="606" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> now well I <pause dur="short"/> you drink it all on Saturday <pause dur="short"/> I'll just have one</u>
<u n="607" who="S0144" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0024">rationing of the beer</u>
<u n="609" who="S0144">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> should have bought that big box of er Tetley's</u>
<u n="610" who="S0024">that's the one I said to buy</u>
<u n="611" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0024">you said you were off creamy beers</u>
<u n="613" who="S0144">well I'm just a bit bored of drinking like creamy bitter</u>
<u n="614" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0144">it's nice but it hasn't got you know a a twang</u>
<u n="616" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's not many beers <pause dur="short"/> maybe I can ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to bring some over with her</u>
<u n="617" who="S0144">yeah well I could drink <pause dur="short"/> I wish I had bought some Ruddles <pause dur="short"/> that's my favourite</u>
<u n="618" who="S0024">yeah? Oh well</u>
<u n="619" who="S0144">so who's playing on Saturday?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0024">Everton's playing against Liverpool</u>
<u n="621" who="S0144">okay <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="622" who="S0024">in the semi final</u>
<u n="623" who="S0144">Good</u>
<u n="624" who="S0024">of the Premier League</u>
<u n="625" who="S0144">ah not so good <pause dur="short"/> try again</u>
<u n="626" who="S0024">ah damn it <pause dur="short"/> of the Premiership</u>
<u n="627" who="S0144">no that's the league</u>
<u n="628" who="S0024">of the</u>
<u n="629" who="S0144">if we're playing in the semi final it has to be a cup competition</u>
<u n="630" who="S0024">Carling Cup?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> the one that matters</u>
<u n="632" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Barclay's cup? Erm <trunc>Fi</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> something beginning with F?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0024">I want to say financial because we've been talking about finance</u>
<u n="635" who="S0144">how come you know Carling Cup but you don't know this one? Doesn't make any sense at all</u>
<u n="636" who="S0024">I do know it it's just</u>
<u n="637" who="S0144">it's the FA Cup</u>
<u n="638" who="S0024">ah <pause dur="short"/> well I was trying to think of like a long word <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't think of initials <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0144">and who's going to win?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0024">what does FA stand for?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0144">football Association</u>
<u n="642" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> everton's going to win <pause dur="short"/> everton</u>
<u n="643" who="S0144">Good <pause dur="short"/> correct <pause dur="short"/> okay you can watch the football <pause dur="short"/> and you can</u>
<u n="644" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and then they play <pause dur="short"/> in the final they play <pause dur="short"/> once they win</u>
<u n="645" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0024">they play</u>
<u n="647" who="S0144">well they'll be playing Chelsea or Tottenham</u>
<u n="648" who="S0024">Chelsea or Tottenham yeah yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> tottenham hopefully <pause dur="short"/> tottenham Everton that would be good</u>
<u n="650" who="S0024">Chelsea will beat Tottenham wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="652" who="S0024">or not that I know</u>
<u n="653" who="S0144">no Tottenham have got a good team now</u>
<u n="654" who="S0024">aren't Norwich doing well <pause dur="short"/> he he he</u>
<u n="655" who="S0144">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah doing very well</u>
<u n="656" who="S0024">yeah see I knew that <pause dur="short"/> fA Cup <pause dur="short"/> saturday <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah you've shown enough interest to warrant your seat and you're allowed one of my beers <pause dur="short"/> as <trunc>l</trunc> as long as you cheer in the right places</u>
<u n="658" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0144">then that's okay</u>
<u n="660" who="S0024">I can  I can  do that</u>
<u n="661" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0024">I might  I might  need one beer per half</u>
<u n="663" who="S0144"><event desc="sound of sighing"/> Well can't I give you a half pint glass?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Cos that's quite a long time isn't it <pause dur="short"/> forty-five minutes for a half? How big are those cans?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0144">you've got a bottle of wine</u>
<u n="666" who="S0024">no I haven't <pause dur="short"/> that wine was to replace the wine in the cupboard that I drank</u>
<u n="667" who="S0144">well can't you drink that one and then replace it?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0024">well I keep doing that but</u>
<u n="669" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0024">it's not really the way to do it really <pause dur="short"/> because if they go out to dinner they need to take that wine and I can't keep pinching it out the cupboard <pause dur="short"/> drinking it and then saying oh I'll buy you another</u>
<u n="671" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no they they don't take bottles of wine do they?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0024">well it depends where they're going</u>
<u n="673" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0024">is this the radar plane coming?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> the radar plane flies about I don't know about five hundred foot</u>
<u n="676" who="S0024">there was another one that crashed into a a house wasn't there? Another another of those army planes</u>
<u n="677" who="S0144">yeah probably</u>
<u n="678" who="S0024">not in <anon type="place"/> this time <pause dur="short"/> another one <pause dur="short"/> that <anon type="place"/> one got covered up</u>
<u n="679" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0024">well that wasn't a house though was it <pause dur="short"/> that was a telephone line</u>
<u n="681" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0024">that got covered up sharpish</u>
<u n="683" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> what does this sign say?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0024">I wonder if you see something like that they pay you off?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0024">do they?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0144">no they'll probably come along with their black suits and shades and get that thing out and go <event desc="sound of buzzing"/> and you'll forget everything you saw</u>
<u n="688" who="S0024">it's a home watch <pause dur="short"/> home watch area</u>
<u n="689" who="S0144">home watch area <pause dur="short"/> what happened to neighbourhood watch?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0024">we're not that neighbourly</u>
<u n="691" who="S0144">why's that? Is that cos theirs is that because there's so many Portuguese?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0144">well home is a lower level word than neighbourhood <pause dur="short"/> you have to target the er audience don't you</u>
<u n="694" who="S0024">I don't understand</u>
<u n="695" who="S0144">I'm just being facetious really</u>
<u n="696" who="S0024">bunny rabbit</u>
<u n="697" who="S0144">run rabbit</u>
<u n="698" who="S0024">oh look another rabbit <pause dur="short"/> they all come out this time of night <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="699" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well as long as they're eating their geraniums and not ours <pause dur="short"/> bloody rabbits</u>
<u n="700" who="S0024">there is too many</u>
<u n="701" who="S0144">yep</u>
</body>
</text>
