<text id="S3SA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-06-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0422 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The garden and then the car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Window, bonsai, daily routines, shopping, cereal, internet, neighbours, presents, cats, bedhead, air vents, scratch on car, weather, smells, necklaces, Disney, DVDs, laurel and hardy, copyright, Spotify, gramophone/ records, directions/ traffic, areas, </topics>
		<activity>Family talk in the garden (then father and daughter in the car)</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0422">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kosice</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Slovakia</birthcountry>
				<l1>Hungarian</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East European</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0422">the bathroom one is stuck I think what they did they were trying to lock it or something and the <unclear/> locked in now we can't open or close it</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">oh it's stuck on that slightly open thing</u>
<u n="3" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423">well when you have some money just get somebody in who can do repairs on it</u>
<u n="5" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0423">don't say you need a new window ask them if show them what <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0422" trans="overlap">wonder if <unclear>they'll able</unclear> to repair it cos they have to mess about going <unclear/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well they'll tell you won't they they'll just tell you just ask them <pause dur="short"/> it might just need sealing again or something</u>
<u n="9" who="S0422" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423">cos it's like a vacuum isn't it between two windows?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0422" trans="overlap">I don't know how they're going to clean it though because it probably needs cleaning it's got <unclear>marks</unclear></u>
<u n="12" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it would need opening up wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">so they they'd unseal it open it up do what they need to do and seal it again <trunc>may</trunc> I don't know how they how it works is there a <unclear>vacuum</unclear> in there or something?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0422" trans="overlap">cos <unclear/> she had them done not long ago <unclear/> from the side as well <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0423">well yeah they're looking at <unclear/> I like the brown rather than the white as well</u>
<u n="17" who="S0422">no I would have preferred the <unclear/> but it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="19" who="S0422">yeah because it's cheaper <pause dur="short"/> very cheap</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421">that's my window</u>
<u n="22" who="S0423">yeah most other people have white don't they?</u>
<u n="23" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0421">mm with the bonsai that's my bonsai <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was ill but it's</u>
<u n="25" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's looking very big for a bonsai</u>
<u n="26" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know it keeps growing it was really small when I got it but it keeps getting bigger</u>
<u n="27" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're meant to keep clipping it the idea is keep them small and they grow old looking</u>
<u n="28" who="S0421">well it it got erm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0423">they start looking like a tree but it just looks like a plant</u>
<u n="30" who="S0421">well it's a pachira one so they grow it's like a palm tree style</u>
<u n="31" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0421">do you know what I mean? erm so they do <trunc>gr</trunc> they grow really big because it is a tree but erm it was ill so it it's got better now</u>
<u n="33" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0421">and we've chucked</u>
<u n="35" who="S0423">yeah but normally they grow big but that's the whole point of the art of bonsai that you have to you have to know what you're doing as well</u>
<u n="36" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know but I kept chopping the leaves but the leaves just kept growing big <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0423">it's not just the leaves it's the branches</u>
<u n="38" who="S0421">I don't not no but it's not got branches it's got a trunk</u>
<u n="39" who="S0422">it's probably just a cheaper one it was only three ninety-nine</u>
<u n="40" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no it is a bonsai it's a proper one</u>
<u n="41" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but they have things coming off the trunk <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't they?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0423">like when you you cut back quite low maybe to keep it</u>
<u n="44" who="S0421">but then I'd cut all the leaves off</u>
<u n="45" who="S0423">yeah but then it stops it eventually then it starts getting older and</u>
<u n="46" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="47" who="S0423">you know it <unclear/> I don't know a lot about bonsai you'd have to look it up</u>
<u n="48" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't yeah I don't know cos it just</u>
<u n="49" who="S0423">there is a way of doing it properly</u>
<u n="50" who="S0421">cos it said just keep trimming the leaves cos it said this one that I've got is quite easy to look after</u>
<u n="51" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="52" who="S0421">and <trunc>y</trunc>you know like if you water it wrong or something it can be fixed</u>
<u n="53" who="S0423">but it might be better just letting it grow it would be nice if it grows big like</u>
<u n="54" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know I think I'll just because some people have erm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0423">those <unclear>palms</unclear> are nice when they grow <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos some people have erm them you know quite big as a house plant</u>
<u n="57" who="S0423">mm yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0421">but they do actually grow like into a big tree and I don't want it to grow that big</u>
<u n="59" who="S0423">no well you then you clip it down when it's getting a bit</u>
<u n="60" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I think it would be quite nice big <trunc>mo</trunc> a lot of people have them big</u>
<u n="61" who="S0423">yeah they're nice big</u>
<u n="62" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="63" who="S0423">popular the big ones yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0421">it's like erm a plaited trunk or something they like when it's grown when it's small they're like</u>
<u n="65" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so it's like goes round like that</u>
<u n="66" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0423">oh that'll be good</u>
<u n="68" who="S0421">like you can see it a bit</u>
<u n="69" who="S0423">oh yeah yeah you can see it starting to do that oh that'll be lovely <unclear/> big but in in the wild they might be like thirty forty foot they might be those gigantic <unclear/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they are they are really big so</u>
<u n="71" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421">I don't know like it is getting bigger and I don't know how to keep it small so I thought I might let it get a bit bigger but I don't want it to be kind of</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no well keep trimming it as you are</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">I don't want it to be</u>
<u n="76" who="S0422">going to have to bring it out here</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">I know I didn't think it would grow out here yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it would probably die it would die wouldn't it? cos you you that's just an indoor one isn't it? cos it needs to be warm probably <unclear/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0422">keep in the thingy house</u>
<u n="81" who="S0421">in the green a massive greenhouse <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">I expect we'll head off soon what time is it? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0421">erm <pause dur="short"/> fourteen fifty-eight</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423">well we better had cos by the time we get to the shops and stuff there's a recycling place open till eight</u>
<u n="85" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">I was just a bit worried that might be closed</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423">so even if we arrived late we can erm still</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421">well it won't take you long to get a present just go in and pick one and get it</u>
<u n="90" who="S0423">no I know what I'm getting for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0421">yeah? right good because I know what you're like in shops</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423">I don't think I'm going to go to <unclear/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you always you always blame it on me</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423">it is you</u>
<u n="95" who="S0421">it's not me</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423">it was you when I go to the supermarket</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you were you were ages the other day buying them pizzas</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423">how do you know?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0421">cos when you rang me and by the <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="100" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh I told you I was on the way</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">well I was looking for <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and it takes you a whole day to like tidy and like get some shopping and then like the whole day is gone then you yourself admitted I don't you know I don't know where the time goes it takes me such a long time to like do stuff</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423">you have to remember I start late in the day</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0423" trans="overlap">because when I'm working till midnight and I go to bed at like two or three in the morning</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421">yeah and also yeah I can just imagine that you wake up and you're like right I'm going to have my tea and some biscuits going to</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I need at least two cups of tea</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421">going to watch the TV for a bit and like when you do your ironing I can just imagine you iron a shirt then you have a sit down and have another cup of tea or something watch a bit of the TV or do a bit more ironing</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423">have you been spying on me?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421">and that's why <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0423">that's why it takes you a long time so you do things very slowly you have quite a slow paced lifestyle</u>
<u n="114" who="S0422">well he doesn't have to rush is it? he doesn't have kids he's single he can do whatever he wants</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0423">I do have what do you mean I have a child?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0423">but yeah you in the supermarket you drive me mad</u>
<u n="120" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0423">you're not coming with me when I go into the shop <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it took us two hours in Scotland to do the <unclear>mats</unclear></u>
<u n="123" who="S0422" trans="overlap">how come you're always so fast? <unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0423">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're passing by stuff and you start saying get that get this and it starts <unclear/> load of rubbish</u>
<u n="126" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh I think I think the problem is you know when I say stuff to you like oh look at that you just keep walking so I'm just like having a look</u>
<u n="127" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0422">that's smart</u>
<u n="129" who="S0423">and then she start talks non stop and my brain can't think of what I need to say</u>
<u n="130" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0423">drives me mad</u>
<u n="132" who="S0422"><unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0421">I didn't you just just ignore me so it's alright but father's like mm mm like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0423"><unclear/> ignore you</u>
<u n="135" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it's quite good actually</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423">and you're probably thinking oh I'm not being ignored I'm encouraging you</u>
<u n="137" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0423">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're not coming erm I'm going shopping tomorrow for some holiday stuff</u>
<u n="139" who="S0421">what kind of cereal do you think I should get?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423">well why? if I get one porridge you don't want porridge every day but why don't you get like a chocolaty one like <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah what cereals shall I get?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423">Coco Pops</u>
<u n="143" who="S0422" trans="overlap">are you asking me which cereal to get for the holiday?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0423">you're not a toddler anymore you're you're an adult <unclear/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0421">I know but</u>
<u n="147" who="S0422">Weetos with the little toy in it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0421"><vocal desc="misc"/> they don't do they still do toys in cereal? I don't think they do do they?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0422" trans="overlap">I don't think <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0421">I used to love getting a toy in the <trunc>ce</trunc> do you know that people? I was so surprised at this what they used to do cos when I got my box of cereal and it had a toy in it I used to stick my hand in and root around for it and pull it out</u>
<u n="151" who="S0423">well everyone does that</u>
<u n="152" who="S0421">no but do you know how many people they would erm wait to see whose cereal it would come out in? and they'd pour their cereal and they'd wait to see whose cereal it was going to come out in</u>
<u n="153" who="S0423">probably cos their parents wouldn't let them stick their hands in</u>
<u n="154" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0423">and if you're in a family of with children</u>
<u n="156" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0423">it's alright when you're the only child and no one else is going to grab it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0423">so what do you want?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0421">erm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0422">Coco Pops <unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos usually I get like multi cereals cos I get bored of eating one but you might as well get Coco Pops cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh that's what I got you last time <unclear/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0421" trans="overlap">did you? multi cereal?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0423">yeah I think I got the multi ones</u>
<u n="166" who="S0421">the little boxes they're good</u>
<u n="167" who="S0422"><unclear/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0422">he's so good <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but but they said Talktalk said that erm they're going to be regulating it aren't they?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0422">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0421">for for</u>
<u n="173" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what? is it not good here with Talktalk?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0421">no <unclear/> no yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0422" trans="overlap">was good until today</u>
<u n="176" who="S0421">but for ten days they said that your speed and connection can fluctuate while we decide on the best one for you</u>
<u n="177" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="178" who="S0421">while you've just got it installed</u>
<u n="179" who="S0422" trans="overlap">well this is not the best one</u>
<u n="180" who="S0421">I know yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0423">what?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0421">this isn't good whatever they're doing at the moment</u>
<u n="183" who="S0422" trans="overlap">this is not the best one now</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="185" who="S0421">it was good the first day</u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">yeah but as long as they're going to get it right after a while <unclear/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0421">if they don't we'll have to complain <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0422">that's all I'm doing since I moved here <pause dur="short"/> what are you complaining about? <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">do you know what we're having for dinner? mm? no I hope it's something that I like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no I didn't ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0422">look he just made that child cry again this is the third time now</u>
<u n="192" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah do you know all day they just scream at it and it <unclear/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah I thought they have a dog or something they speak they speaking to the child like that</u>
<u n="194" who="S0423">it's only a baby practically isn't it? a little toddler</u>
<u n="195" who="S0422" trans="overlap">it is it's a little toddler I think cos he talks now <unclear/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's not there it's like the one over</u>
<u n="197" who="S0422">the one next door these are the <anon type="place"/> ones they're very quiet you can't hear them <unclear/> cry at all</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah no no never</u>
<u n="202" who="S0423"><unclear/> there's no need to be shouting at children at that age is there?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0422" trans="overlap">them two them two they're not shouting they're yelling</u>
<u n="204" who="S0421">they're like screaming yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0422">that's how he's going to grow up that's how he's going to speak to people and teachers and everybody that's why you get these kids at school yelling at you</u>
<u n="206" who="S0423">that's probably how they were brought up isn't it?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0422">yeah well yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0423">so that's why it goes around you need to get yourself your line sorted here don't you?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0422">a what?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0421">a washing line</u>
<u n="211" who="S0423">you've got you've got the post haven't you? so</u>
<u n="212" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you're going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or rotary there <pause dur="short"/> right are we going? cos otherwise we're going to end up late</u>
<u n="214" who="S0421">yeah yeah with you you need a good day to sort your things out</u>
<u n="215" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no we're going I have to look <trunc>ar</trunc> a little bit in TK Maxx</u>
<u n="216" who="S0421">oh what for?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0423">I want to get some for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s one</u>
<u n="218" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="219" who="S0423">just maybe socks or <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0422" trans="overlap">TK Maxx in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0423">yeah so it's easier to get in there</u>
<u n="222" who="S0422" trans="overlap">pick up a card in Sainsbury's then next to it they've got cards</u>
<u n="223" who="S0423">no I don't know if I'll bother</u>
<u n="224" who="S0422">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can go there and you can go TK Maxx <pause dur="short"/> she'll pick a card</u>
<u n="225" who="S0423">and er then we'll go to <anon type="place"/> and then I know what I'm getting in Argos</u>
<u n="226" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I quite like TK <trunc>Ma</trunc> oh yeah I do like TK I was always in TK Maxx do you know what I like?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah you'll probably be spending about half a day in there</u>
<u n="228" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0421">do you know what I like? the erm food section</u>
<u n="230" who="S0422"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0421">you know where they have all</u>
<u n="232" who="S0423">they don't sell food</u>
<u n="233" who="S0421">they do</u>
<u n="234" who="S0422" trans="overlap">they do</u>
<u n="235" who="S0423">oh all the stuff in jars</u>
<u n="236" who="S0422" trans="overlap">jars</u>
<u n="237" who="S0421">you know like there's stuff from all over the world they have really interesting stuff and like health stuff and I'm always like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0422">how long <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0422">there is though</u>
<u n="241" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0423" trans="overlap">right I'll give you five minutes to hang on then</u>
<u n="243" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0423">you're the one who said you don't want to be long I better go cos I can see you're going to keep me waiting</u>
<u n="245" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what should I get him?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0421">what shall I get him?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0422">something I don't know maybe something like</u>
<u n="249" who="S0421">cos what did? I got him <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0422">I know</u>
<u n="251" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there's one for the bike they do some great bike stuff in there</u>
<u n="252" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no oh</u>
<u n="253" who="S0421">well I don't how it's he's not going to be using it now</u>
<u n="254" who="S0421" trans="overlap">which he's not going to use now is he?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0423">oh is he not?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0421">yeah I know</u>
<u n="257" who="S0422">they have those toffees in the mad boxes or something I don't know</u>
<u n="258" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah sludges or something but I got him sludges you know?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0421"><unclear/> probably get him a bottle when <unclear>he's up</unclear></u>
<u n="261" who="S0422">ah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0421">yeah I'll have a look how much will I spend?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0422">oh for heaven's <trunc>sa</trunc> I don't know don't go spending too much</u>
<u n="264" who="S0421">cos they can be quite pricy those fudges <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0421">wow look at him he's so cute</u>
<u n="267" who="S0422">hello <unclear/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0421">he's having the time of his life</u>
<u n="269" who="S0423">looks like he's very at home already</u>
<u n="270" who="S0422">he is yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah they all are yeah they're all like lying everywhere</u>
<u n="272" who="S0422" trans="overlap">they love it here cos they can hide they couldn't in erm erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0421">they like really like the bushes and stuff like wild cats like in the jungle</u>
<u n="274" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0421">oh do you know? today I was going to lean against that and I was like where's it gone?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0422"><unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0423">why? what have you done to it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0421">it's my bedhead it was just disgusting it was like really dirty</u>
<u n="279" who="S0422" trans="overlap">erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0423">it's to get all the sweat off your head when you <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="282" who="S0422">it's all the moving and all the filthy <unclear/> damp clothes we had and stuff that's why it's</u>
<u n="283" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0422">ah what is this?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0421">yeah is that the ventilation?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0423">you know what? I'm surprised that <unclear/> are allowed to put that there</u>
<u n="287" who="S0422" trans="overlap">why is that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0423">when erm something goes wrong with the <trunc>bo</trunc>boiler and it puts loads of steam out and stuff</u>
<u n="289" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0423"><unclear/> having it by the door</u>
<u n="291" who="S0422">no</u>
<u n="292" who="S0423">but when your boiler is on you will have steam coming out of that</u>
<u n="293" who="S0422">we had the erm thingy as well didn't we? when the heating was on but it was high up</u>
<u n="294" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah the heating</u>
<u n="295" who="S0423">normally they <trunc>ha</trunc> they have it higher or they're back somewhere but to have it here at your doorway</u>
<u n="296" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I don't know</u>
<u n="297" who="S0421">have you got air vents in your house? like</u>
<u n="298" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0421">yeah we've got them as well</u>
<u n="300" who="S0423">well you you should have those cos otherwise</u>
<u n="301" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0423">condensation and damp</u>
<u n="303" who="S0422"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0423">but yeah it's a funny place what's it out by the door?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0422" trans="overlap">I know we didn't know what it was</u>
<u n="306" who="S0423">right come on</u>
<u n="307" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no <unclear>throw that</unclear> away <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0422">have you got your key? in case you come late</u>
<u n="310" who="S0421">yeah I mean we're not going to come that late are we?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we're not going to be that late <unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0422" trans="overlap">god knows what time you're going to get there so by the time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cooks after work I'm surprised she's cooking something fresh</u>
<u n="313" who="S0423">it will be mid evening</u>
<u n="314" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0423">so we won't be eating till after six</u>
<u n="316" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0423">and then we're not going to say right thanks bye</u>
<u n="318" who="S0422">no you'll be playing board games</u>
<u n="319" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0422">right bye</u>
<u n="321" who="S0423" trans="overlap">right see you</u>
<u n="322" who="S0421" trans="overlap">bye <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0423">it's going to be hot in this car</u>
<u n="324" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0423">I saw this this morning I don't know where where they've done while we've been here</u>
<u n="326" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0423">see that big scratch all the length of the car?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0421"><vocal desc="gasp"/> how did that happen?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0423">well somebody would have to put something on it and walk past and scratch it oh unless it unless it was a branch I hit or something</u>
<u n="330" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it comes off</u>
<u n="331" who="S0423">does it?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0421">er isn't it?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0423">well it could have been a branch you know? cos I did hit a branch you know? on that country lane that <unclear>we were on</unclear></u>
<u n="334" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah I think it comes off <pause dur="short"/> oh it's hot in here it's like a sauna</u>
<u n="335" who="S0423">I know get some windows open</u>
<u n="336" who="S0421">it's quite nice though I I really like warm cars I don't know why</u>
<u n="337" who="S0423">do you?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0421">yeah they're good I don't know</u>
<u n="339" who="S0423">oh it's too hot in here</u>
<u n="340" who="S0421">like cos it's got like a a really like warm car smell</u>
<u n="341" who="S0423">warm car smell</u>
<u n="342" who="S0421">yeah I have these like weird smells that I like and people think it's really weird <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0423">right erm just trying to think <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0421">you sure you want these windows open? we're going to get blown away</u>
<u n="345" who="S0423">no you're okay on these roads but when we're on the motorway we won't be able to</u>
<u n="346" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0423">I'll open the back ones let's see what it's like that they get going put the front ones up if you want? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0421">yeah no it was just like I had that erm stuff and I was like <unclear/> and then they went like that</u>
<u n="349" who="S0423">yeah that's nice of you she'll be pleased with that</u>
<u n="350" who="S0421">yeah cos I have little things like that and I'm just like I never know what to do with them and then sometimes if like one of my friends has like a a sibling or like someone else like ah I've got this I I go to visit or something but</u>
<u n="351" who="S0423">yeah it's handy stuff like that you're not going to use them</u>
<u n="352" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0423">so er pass them on do you want your window up?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0421">er no it's alright so far and then yeah and mummy's got like</u>
<u n="355" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> sure where that goes to so</u>
<u n="356" who="S0421">got like loads of beads and things and she's got some Disney princesses so everyone like Disney princesses</u>
<u n="357" who="S0423">yeah everyone loves them don't they? <pause dur="short"/> never gave me a Disney princess have you?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0421">do you like Disney princess?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you just said everyone loves them</u>
<u n="360" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wouldn't have thought you'd wanted one though I know that you like Disney films</u>
<u n="361" who="S0423">oh that's the shop that's near <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0423">wondered where the M6 was <pause dur="short"/> yeah you've got some good what? what have you got Disney that we could bring along? have you got like Invincibles is good isn't it? that type of things</u>
<u n="364" who="S0421">erm I don't have Incredibles</u>
<u n="365" who="S0423">oh Incredible yeah what what have you got?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0423">you've got erm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0421">I've got like them princess ones</u>
<u n="369" who="S0423">no but you've got the one with the hamster haven't you?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0421">yeah well we watched that last time Bolt</u>
<u n="371" who="S0423">oh did we?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0421">yeah well we brought all those</u>
<u n="373" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you got anything else like that?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0421">I've got Bolt and I've got Ratatouille and we watched that last time as well</u>
<u n="375" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh yeah right</u>
<u n="376" who="S0421">and I've got Monsters versus Aliens which we watched last time</u>
<u n="377" who="S0423">did we?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0421">yeah I've brought all these</u>
<u n="379" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I can't remember watching them</u>
<u n="380" who="S0421">and I've got all like <unclear/> films</u>
<u n="381" who="S0423"><unclear/> well you if you see anything you like <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0421">I've got some <trunc>lo</trunc> oh I don't know where my DVDs are at the moment though I've got some Laurel and Hardys you know like feature length ones</u>
<u n="383" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah you said this to I haven't see <unclear/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0421">yeah I'd never <trunc>se</trunc> well if I can find my DVDs then I will but I don't know where they are</u>
<u n="385" who="S0423">yeah don't go <unclear/> we should be alright</u>
<u n="386" who="S0421">yeah they were quite good actually those long films I can't remember what they were now have we not watched them together? I should I brought them round to yours once <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0423"><unclear/> nearly crashed into me then</u>
<u n="388" who="S0421">I know yeah that school bus</u>
<u n="389" who="S0423">yeah why didn't he stay still till I repositioned myself? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0421">I think Laurel and Hardy is so good</u>
<u n="391" who="S0423">yeah well I'll if I bring my boxset that'll that's plenty then isn't it?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0423" trans="overlap">don't need anything else</u>
<u n="394" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know I watched what did I watch? a Laurel and Hardy I think it was a silent one</u>
<u n="395" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0421">erm and I'd never seen it before I don't oh no oh had I? no I hadn't</u>
<u n="397" who="S0423">on that website did you say there was a website?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0421">oh yeah yeah do you know I watched it was really good the erm ah what was it? Robinson Crusoe one it was like I think it was like based on that or something</u>
<u n="399" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0421">erm and Laurel and Hardy yeah on her website with free films on it cos it's got adverts so it's it's legal</u>
<u n="401" who="S0423">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0421">and they just have like some old ones or you know? like ones like small budget films or something like not anything new</u>
<u n="403" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0421">but they had a Laurel and Hardy and it was really good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0421">they went to an island and then it was and then people didn't have then they made it like a country and people didn't have to <trunc>ma</trunc> pay tax so everybody was moving</u>
<u n="407" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0421">and it was like really crowded it was funny</u>
<u n="409" who="S0423">I don't think I've ever seen that one</u>
<u n="410" who="S0421">and then I think they wanted to like bring back tax or something and the like people like rebelled and then</u>
<u n="411" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="412" who="S0421">was funny yeah it was good <pause dur="short"/> I think it was like some kind of Robinson Crusoe <trunc>inspir</trunc> inspired by or something</u>
<u n="413" who="S0423">yeah I wonder if films are going to be like books you know? copyright it must come under the same law mustn't it?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0423">you know they're eventually they they can't they're out of copyright</u>
<u n="416" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0423">so really like old films have come down in price where the only cost is the the actual packaging really</u>
<u n="418" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0423">cos well I guess they make some profit but they don't have to pay anybody the writers and what have you do they?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think so I'm not sure</u>
<u n="421" who="S0423">don't know how it works I don't know how old it is</u>
<u n="422" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I'm not sure how it works</u>
<u n="423" who="S0423">I don't know how old it has to be it's about is it around a hundred years anyway isn't it?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0421">probably but like cos there's some films and things you can watch on Youtube and Youtube's quite strict about copyright and stuff</u>
<u n="425" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0421">so like if it was violating copyright Youtube would take it down</u>
<u n="427" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0421">but there are some on Youtube and you can watch them</u>
<u n="429" who="S0423">what? like old ones?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0421">yeah but I don't know erm I don't know I think there's some cartoons on Youtube that I've watched <pause dur="long"/> because you can get erm lots of free classics <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0423">books?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0421">yeah because they're out of copyright because you can read them online</u>
<u n="433" who="S0423">yeah so that's the same with film <unclear>I think</unclear></u>
<u n="434" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0423">somebody would have a site where they're all free you know? the ones out of copyright <unclear/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0421" trans="overlap">there probably is yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0423">although I mean the way people watch films now most of them go to like a lot of people go to illegal websites and download them anyway don't they <unclear/> copyright</u>
<u n="438" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="439" who="S0423">it's kind of like I suppose with music it has affected music cos so many people do music</u>
<u n="440" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0423">you know? they can't they they they make very little money out of music sales now pop stars I think most of the money is from like concerts</u>
<u n="442" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah the concerts they make the money from yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0423">whereas in the past they used to make most of their money out of record sales</u>
<u n="444" who="S0421">yeah not enough people sell the <pause dur="short"/> yeah not enough people buy their music anymore but <pause dur="short"/> erm there are like ways you can listen to new music for free like is it? like that thing called Spotify?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0423">yeah do you pay a subscription though?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0421">you can either you can have it free with adverts</u>
<u n="447" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0421">which I think I think is like and you also it's like</u>
<u n="449" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="450" who="S0421">you can't you can click on an artist and have all their songs play or an album and have all the songs play but you can't choose like specific songs to play</u>
<u n="451" who="S0423">yeah so it's quite random yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you know what I mean? and you can't you have to listen to them online and if you pay you can er have them on your phone</u>
<u n="453" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you get to choose yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0421">you can listen offline no adverts</u>
<u n="455" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0421">and erm you can choose a specific song but it</u>
<u n="457" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but you never own it do you? you just pay to listen to it yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but <trunc>the</trunc> but you can listen to it and then they'll pay the person</u>
<u n="459" who="S0423">yeah they pay royalties</u>
<u n="460" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah so I think that's quite good like I don't know like that's quite reasonable I think</u>
<u n="461" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0421">so I don't know why people are still like downloading and then like on Youtube you can watch the music video and then they get money from that</u>
<u n="463" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0421">not all of them are on but <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0423">I really don't buy a lot of music but I think I'd rather still buy like a CD and same with like films have the DVD and just have it there and you can put it on when you want <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's probably an old fashioned you kind of get stuck in your habits don't you?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0423">it's like really old people who start like to listen to the music on the wind up gramophone</u>
<u n="468" who="S0421">yeah I kind of want to is that nice? is that a good sound? or is that a bit?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0423">I've never heard it on a wind up gramophone</u>
<u n="470" who="S0421">cos I really like the look of them</u>
<u n="471" who="S0423"><trunc>obvio</trunc>obviously record players electric ones</u>
<u n="472" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0423">have you never listened to it online?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="475" who="S0423">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has one she's got a record player and records</u>
<u n="476" who="S0421">cos I <trunc>li</trunc> cos I like the look of the gramophones</u>
<u n="477" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0421">but I'd want to be buying like Beethoven or something I don't like I don't like the pop ones</u>
<u n="479" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0421">obviously like cos they have pop ones</u>
<u n="481" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but you're thinking like the old fashioned gramophones</u>
<u n="482" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0423">from like victorian era</u>
<u n="484" who="S0421">and put like Mozart on <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos that's what they played on them</u>
<u n="485" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but the difficulty with that would be I don't know how it works do you have to keep winding it? or do you er? do you just wind it up a bit <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think I think you wind it and then once the record's finished I think you <trunc>wi</trunc> I don't know I think you wind it again</u>
<u n="487" who="S0423">because it may be a thing <trunc>th</trunc>the right getting the right speed on that for the records <unclear/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah there is yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0423">to get the right sound but you can probably buy a record player with that style of like speaker <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah that does it itself <pause dur="short"/> because like you when erm you I ever see records in shops they're all like I don't know like fifties and sixties like artists</u>
<u n="491" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0421">they're never erm like classical yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0421">but</u>
<u n="495" who="S0423">yeah there are there is a bit of a comeback for vinyl but people who are starting to buy it sort of buy more recent stuff</u>
<u n="496" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah because new albums come out on vinyl sometimes</u>
<u n="497" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0421">but yeah I've never seen classical ones because I was thinking obviously back in when they had the wind up gramophones what would they be playing? they'd be playing classical</u>
<u n="499" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0421">so they must exist but I've never seen them</u>
<u n="501" who="S0423">yeah you can probably get <unclear/> but you'd have to really shop around that I think people who are into that have to <unclear/> that they like it you know? trying to find</u>
<u n="502" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0423">the places</u>
<u n="504" who="S0421">I couldn't be bothered <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just listen to classic FM <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0423">oh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0421">and obviously all the erm all the classical stuff's free on Youtube <pause dur="short"/> online</u>
<u n="507" who="S0423">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0421">Mozart and stuff</u>
<u n="509" who="S0423">yeah cos it's all out of copyright</u>
<u n="510" who="S0421" trans="overlap">although like you think you'd still have to play the the instrument player</u>
<u n="511" who="S0423">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0421">cos someone's playing that like in modern day aren't they? to be recorded someone's playing the piano someone's in the orchestra</u>
<u n="513" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah well <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> well oh you mean new releases?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0421">yeah cos like well whoever well <trunc>th</trunc>the recordings of Mozarts I don't know whatever aren't actually Mozart are they? it would be very poor quality</u>
<u n="515" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well no I mean you do get new releases orchestras</u>
<u n="516" who="S0421">yeah and you have to like you you pay for those</u>
<u n="517" who="S0423" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0421">but I don't know what are the what are the free ones are on Youtube don't know who that is</u>
<u n="519" who="S0423">oh right I see what you mean yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0423">not sure where you <pause dur="short"/> oh where am I going?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0421">just follow that car in front of us <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0423">not sure where you get this Sainsbury's it's all changed here now since the tram <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm sweating <pause dur="long"/> am I in the wrong lane again? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0421">probably <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0423">I am yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's <unclear/> bloody confusing the way they've done this <pause dur="long"/> ah I'm not sure if I should be in that lane <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0421">well you can't get on that one now wow look at that bridge a glass bridge</u>
<u n="527" who="S0423">Sainsbury's should be here to the left somewhere I think</u>
<u n="528" who="S0421">oh I like Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="529" who="S0423"><unclear/> near <unclear/> TK Maxx</u>
<u n="530" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0423">is it there? can you see it? yeah it's on that road there can we go there? yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0421">don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0423">does it feel strange being back here?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0421">no I like I can't remember it</u>
<u n="535" who="S0423">can you not?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0421">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> like it doesn't seem familiar like</u>
<u n="537" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0421">yeah it's just like any place</u>
<u n="539" who="S0423">well if you're in <anon type="place"/> it probably would wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah like <anon type="place"/> but like older and stuff</u>
<u n="541" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you weren't here that often really you know? around here <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0421">oh TK Maxx and I like their like I always look at their notebooks they have nice notebooks I've only bought one once though because the amount of times that I've seen nice notebooks in TK Maxx if I'd bought one every time I would just I'd just like <unclear/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we don't want to be here for hours</u>
<u n="544" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0423">you were telling me</u>
<u n="546" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0423">you seem to be getting a bit excited</u>
<u n="548" who="S0421">well I need to look for something for grandad</u>
<u n="549" who="S0423">I know <pause dur="short"/> sounds like you've got other things in mind as well</u>
<u n="550" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wouldn't buy anything though I've got no I've got no money</u>
<u n="551" who="S0423">how are you going to get your grandad's?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0421">well I mean I can <trunc>pa</trunc> I can pay for it but I don't have very much money so I shouldn't really buy anything for myself</u>
<u n="553" who="S0423">well I can give you <unclear>expense</unclear> today</u>
<u n="554" who="S0421">no because that's that means I've still have not got much money I'm not <unclear/> things <pause dur="short"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
