<text id="S3TD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:35</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0247 S0248</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Superstitions / good luck / bad luck / sporting rituals, lucky charms, etc.</topics>
		<activity>A discussion about whether luck exists</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0247">
				<exactage>61</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Liverpudlian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0248">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Herts</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern/London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired Quantity surveyor</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0247">so I've been looking at superstitions for a class tomorrow</u>
<u n="2" who="S0248">okay</u>
<u n="3" who="S0247">you believe in <trunc>s</trunc> in good luck and bad luck don't you?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0248">erm I believe in good luck and bad but I know it's something you can just perceive you you can get down on yourself and think erm you know I never get any luck <pause dur="short"/> but I and I and I believe statements like I make your own luck certainly <pause dur="short"/> but just outrageous bits of bad fortune <trunc>y</trunc> don't happen to everyone the an accident</u>
<u n="5" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0248">or something that you couldn't've foreseen <pause dur="short"/> or er but but I do believe that some people if you put yourself in a situation <trunc>d</trunc> too often you <unclear>perceive</unclear> that you're unlucky if bad things happen to you <pause dur="short"/> and if you keep doing the wrong things or things that you know are a fifty fifty you know chance or or worse that you're gonna come and you can you can have a bad run of of doing seemingly</u>
<u n="7" who="S0247">things go wrong yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0248" trans="overlap">things seem <trunc>s</trunc> going wrong <pause dur="short"/> so I think it's just something that if you <trunc>d</trunc> if you do the right things then it will presume or or certainly other people think oh he's a lucky person <pause dur="short"/> because he's he you know he's <trunc>g</trunc> put himself in that position to get luck and and it's more likely to be good than bad</u>
<u n="9" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0248">because the <trunc>p</trunc>ps the place he's put himself is is a good place so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you walk under ladders and things like that?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0248">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> I I yes I I wouldn't say I deliberately do it but I really erm I really don't believe in that sort of thing I mean apart from the fact that if any you <trunc>gr</trunc>go to any <trunc>b</trunc>close to a building site or what have you there's more chance of a bucket falling on you than than than if you were not walking <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="13" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah it's kind of erm you know but but if you broke a mirror for example would you immediately think oh that's good you know that's seven years bad luck?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0248">no I wouldn't</u>
<u n="15" who="S0247">no</u>
<u n="16" who="S0248">I don't think mind you I I've never <trunc>t</trunc> actually tested it on myself</u>
<u n="17" who="S0247"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0248">cos I don't think I've ever actually broken one</u>
<u n="19" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> were your parents superstitious? did they throw salt over their shoulder and stuff like that?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0248">no no</u>
<u n="21" who="S0247">no?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0248">pepper not salt</u>
<u n="23" who="S0247"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you are joking?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="26" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0247">and what about erm <trunc>w</trunc> in gambling what sort of things do you do to bring luck</u>
<u n="28" who="S0248">erm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0247">do you cross your fingers or?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0248">I tell you what actually <trunc>u</trunc> I kept winning and I I give to beggars anyway</u>
<u n="31" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0248">but er not all the time but sometimes and but but I I kept winning and I thought to myself that I go inside of <anon type="place"/> on the same place and <trunc>t</trunc> and gave money two or three times</u>
<u n="33" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0248">to this guy <pause dur="short"/> and one time he wasn't even asking <vocal desc="laugh"/> for any money</u>
<u n="35" who="S0247"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0248">he was just he didn't he didn't have a cup or a bowl or what have you <pause dur="short"/> he was sitting with his legs you know bunched up in front of him</u>
<u n="37" who="S0247" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> and presumably you recognised him did you?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well no I no I'm not even sure it was the same man</u>
<u n="39" who="S0247">oh</u>
<u n="40" who="S0248">but due to the fact that I'd actually thought hello I'm being er you know sort of paid back here for for being er nice and generous</u>
<u n="41" who="S0247">right</u>
<u n="42" who="S0248">but I thought this is absolute nonsense and I didn't wanna go one day through that side and I was a bit later and I wanted to go through the centre of the station <pause dur="short"/> and I was gonna go out to the side to give this bloke some money</u>
<u n="43" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0248">I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't even know if he was there or not and I thought don't be so silly I went down there and still won so</u>
<u n="45" who="S0247" trans="overlap">oh you still won oh okay yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0248" trans="overlap">still won er er so er</u>
<u n="47" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0248">you know that that was good</u>
<u n="49" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0248">that was good that that something had happened yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah that you did it <pause dur="short"/> what about in the betting shop generally do people do things to for luck? you know do you see people going through rituals or anything?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0248">oh they do erm they complain about their back luck by kicking the machine and er swearing at the telly and what have you no I think it's er I think you get it more it it's er in sport where one person always puts always to go out last <pause dur="short"/> or he</u>
<u n="53" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0248">always puts one boot on er you know before the other</u>
<u n="55" who="S0247" trans="overlap">oh like a footballer <trunc>u</trunc>? yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yes footballer</u>
<u n="57" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0248">he'll always do <trunc>s</trunc> things in a certain order</u>
<u n="59" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0248">er all this sort of stuff</u>
<u n="61" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0248">or have a lucky you know what people have a <trunc>l</trunc></u>
<u n="63" who="S0247">I think I remember Bjorn Borg <pause dur="short"/> didn't he</u>
<u n="64" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0247">have a ritual? I think he didn't shave for the whole of Wimbledon</u>
<u n="66" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> they probably</u>
<u n="67" who="S0247" trans="overlap">so he always ended the Wimbledon fortnight with a little beard</u>
<u n="68" who="S0248">yeah they they</u>
<u n="69" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0248">did that I <trunc>d</trunc> I <trunc>d</trunc> you've gotta get out of doing these things I mean they said to Michael Owen I hear you're superstitious and he</u>
<u n="71" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0248">said no I don't actually I don't believe I'm superstitious I just do certain things before a game to ensure that other things don't happen</u>
<u n="73" who="S0247">like what?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0248">well that's he's saying that's exactly what superstitions is</u>
<u n="75" who="S0247" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it</u>
<u n="76" who="S0248" trans="overlap">he's saying he's not <trunc>s</trunc> though then he didn't go on to say what they were</u>
<u n="77" who="S0247">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0248">but it was just the fact was it <trunc>f</trunc> you know it was exactly</u>
<u n="79" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="80" who="S0248">what er</u>
<u n="81" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0248">yeah and so he was saying that he was superstitious yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0248">what about you and luck you don't er?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0247">I don't believe in it at all I just think it's everything's a coincidence really <pause dur="short"/> but some it's it's quite useful to have erm a way to refer to you know bad coincidences and that so <pause dur="short"/> you know if you if if something <trunc>ha</trunc> if you happen to pick the wrong day you know the of of er a month of brilliant sunshine and you you're having a garden party and you happen to have chosen the day that it pours down with rain then</u>
<u n="86" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0247">you'll think of that as bad luck won't you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0248">it's just <trunc>b</trunc> it is bad luck</u>
<u n="89" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0248">though isn't it but it's not</u>
<u n="91" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0248">there's nothing <pause dur="short"/> no no one's</u>
<u n="93" who="S0247">but you haven't brought it upon yourself or</u>
<u n="94" who="S0248" trans="overlap">no one you haven't brought on yourself no one's picking</u>
<u n="95" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0248">on you it's just some things good happen to you and some things bad happen to you</u>
<u n="97" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah and you can't do anything about it so you</u>
<u n="98" who="S0248" trans="overlap">but if keeps happening to you start getting to think oh god dear why's this?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0247" trans="overlap">you know do you remember that erm friends of mum and dad's called unlucky <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0248">yes <pause dur="short"/> I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I never met him I heard you say it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0247" trans="overlap">no I <trunc>d</trunc> I think I only met him once or twice but he had erm all his life had had the most awful bad luck and you know if if he tried to do anything that when he <trunc>w</trunc> I think they told us when he was in the army the soldiers used to get up to all sorts of you know little things erm bending the rules and that sort of thing you know but if ever this unlucky <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tried it you know he would</u>
<u n="102" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0247">always get caught or he'd he'd choose the night that they were being inspected or you know things like that and erm and he was forever in plaster you know he'd turn up to meet them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><unclear>sound the</unclear> <trunc>f</trunc> I remember I don't I remember you saying about him or I remember your dad saying about this unlucky <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0248">I don't know if you</u>
<u n="107" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0248">you <pause dur="short"/> but the fact is whether they were laughing with him at him or whether they actually believed it or you know whether</u>
<u n="109" who="S0247" trans="overlap">no they said you <trunc>c</trunc> you can't believe how unlucky somebody that you <trunc>kn</trunc> so many things went wrong in his life that he he</u>
<u n="110" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0247">and he was about sixty or so so you know he was just used I suppose</u>
<u n="112" who="S0248" trans="overlap">he trades on <trunc>h</trunc> you know on the end er in the end doesn't he you know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but you know it was it made good chats you know good good stories and so on but</u>
<u n="114" who="S0248" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0247">maybe they weren't all true</u>
<u n="116" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0247">erm a <trunc>d</trunc> a lot of people have lucky colours and lucky numbers for doing the lottery and that kind of thing</u>
<u n="118" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0247">erm <pause dur="short"/> and obviously when you get married you have the something old something new something borrowed something blue stuff and and horse shoes and things like that</u>
<u n="120" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I really</u>
<u n="121" who="S0247">but</u>
<u n="122" who="S0248">cos once you get into those things</u>
<u n="123" who="S0247">well they're just symbols really they're not actually you know nobody really believes they're going to bring luck <unclear>and if the</unclear> oh if you haven't got the something borrowed or</u>
<u n="124" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0247">something blue that's gonna be erm you know bad luck for the future</u>
<u n="126" who="S0248" trans="overlap">just actually it's erm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0247" trans="overlap">it's just like a ritual isn't it?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><unclear/> in the end you think look why don't I just go along with it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0248">you know</u>
<u n="131" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you know and then really because if something did happen</u>
<u n="133" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="134" who="S0248">I might find myself thinking well I was a bit silly why didn't I just you know I</u>
<u n="135" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0248">I don't <trunc>b</trunc> I know it's all daft but er you just don't really wanna get into those things</u>
<u n="137" who="S0247" trans="overlap">no and and of course to prove how daft the whole thing is</u>
<u n="138" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0247">if you ask people internationally about black cats</u>
<u n="140" who="S0248">mm mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0247">you know they're they're mostly bad luck but in our country they're good luck</u>
<u n="142" who="S0248">and and we have say lucky number seven or what</u>
<u n="143" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0248">have you or the <trunc>un</trunc>unlucky thirteen but</u>
<u n="145" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="146" who="S0248">they're not exactly the same the world over apparently</u>
<u n="147" who="S0247" trans="overlap">er well I don't know about the other countries other than Italy but in Italy it's erm <trunc>th</trunc> the unlucky day is seventeenth not thirteenth</u>
<u n="148" who="S0248">mm kay</u>
<u n="149" who="S0247">and I've <trunc>g</trunc> I might be making this up by I've got an idea it's Tuesday not Friday <pause dur="short"/> so Tuesday the seventeenth not Friday the thirteenth</u>
<u n="150" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0247">but I don't know if you know</u>
<u n="152" who="S0248"><trunc>cr</trunc> <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>d</trunc> erm Australians used to have a unlucky number at cricket</u>
<u n="153" who="S0247">oh right what was that then?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><trunc>ei</trunc>eighty-seven or something <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc> or or it or or it came to <trunc>s</trunc> if it wasn't eighty-seven seventy-eight so</u>
<u n="155" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0248">either they would lose a wicket at eighty-seven or what have you</u>
<u n="157" who="S0247">I'm sorry I'm not quite sure what I whether I understand that</u>
<u n="158" who="S0248" trans="overlap">well when they <trunc>s</trunc> when the team had scored eighty-seven they <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="159" who="S0247">oh okay</u>
<u n="160" who="S0248">was worried until they got off the number</u>
<u n="161" who="S0247">right</u>
<u n="162" who="S0248">because it's something would seem to happen when they scored eighty-seven <pause dur="short"/> someone someone had actually suddenly realised kinda we'd just scored hundred <trunc>s</trunc> I'm just out what's the score? hundred and seventy-four</u>
<u n="163" who="S0247">right</u>
<u n="164" who="S0248">and someone'd go well someone'd go that's two eighty-sevens innit?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0247">oh <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>u</trunc> right okay</u>
<u n="166" who="S0248">or or two hundred and sixty-one</u>
<u n="167" who="S0247">yeah that that's like three eighty-sevens</u>
<u n="168" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0248">so you can make what you want of that but you know</u>
<u n="171" who="S0247" trans="overlap">you'd have be good at arithmetic</u>
<u n="172" who="S0248" trans="overlap">but or or or any Australian at cricket <pause dur="short"/> well actually it might not be eighty-seven it might be eighty-nine but <unclear>I don't think</unclear></u>
<u n="173" who="S0247" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so it's a number like that</u>
<u n="174" who="S0248">there is a number</u>
<u n="175" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0248">that you know if you think oh Christ now eighty-seven you know</u>
<u n="177" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you know you'd be very pleased <pause dur="short"/> if you've personally scored eighty-seven and you get a single to take you onto eighty-eight</u>
<u n="179" who="S0247">right</u>
<u n="180" who="S0248">you'd be very pleased</u>
<u n="181" who="S0247"><trunc>ve</trunc> right and what about</u>
<u n="182" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0247">erm other sports is it just cricket or?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0248">no well that's just different things and I suppose some of</u>
<u n="185" who="S0247" trans="overlap">you know is it? but is it like a general number?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0248" trans="overlap">some of them back erm erm probably said do you know do you know the number of times we've lost a wicket or at the number eighty-seven? and then you know it just gets one of those things that that just escalates you know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0247" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0248">I mean obviously there's nothing in it</u>
<u n="189" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="190" who="S0248">but the fact is you know</u>
<u n="191" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0248">it's cricketers boringly they've scored ninety you know to get to a hundred at cricket</u>
<u n="193" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sure</u>
<u n="194" who="S0248">to get to a hundred is a milestone</u>
<u n="195" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0248">so blokes play quite beautifully freely until they get to ninety</u>
<u n="197" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="198" who="S0248">and then suddenly they get worried</u>
<u n="199" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0248">because they've gotta score the last ten runs they call it the nervous nineties</u>
<u n="201" who="S0247">right okay</u>
<u n="202" who="S0248" trans="overlap">okay so the fact is you could put that <unclear>batter</unclear> like like I was I was down I was on ninety-five and I got out because you're not playing your normal game because you're worried er that you'll get</u>
<u n="203" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yes cos of because of the</u>
<u n="204" who="S0248">as soon as you get to a hundred and one you start playing normal cricket</u>
<u n="205" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0248">what how daft is that?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="208" who="S0248">and the same is same with someone says Christ boy chap you're on eighty-seven so you start playing daft you wanna get off you wanna hit a ball you shouldn't hit or it</u>
<u n="209" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="210" who="S0248">so it's <trunc>i</trunc> everything <unclear>compounds them I think</unclear></u>
<u n="211" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I and I think that's a bit like in erm in snooker matches was it Terry Griffiths who always wore his red shirt because he'd had a couple of wins wearing this red shirt?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0248" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah I don't know how many he had of these red shirts</u>
<u n="213" who="S0247"><trunc>w</trunc> it wasn't just the one then?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0248">well no but the thing is that they lose as well obviously</u>
<u n="215" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0248">don't they</u>
<u n="217" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0248">there was a horse race trainer who would always wear a red shirt</u>
<u n="219" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0248">now the fact is well you know but the fact is he must've had bad days when he if he wore it all the time</u>
<u n="221" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0248">he must've had a lot of bad days when he was wearing the red shirt</u>
<u n="223" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0248">you know so in the end it's all a bit</u>
<u n="225" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="226" who="S0248">you know I suppose he has even worse luck if he doesn't wear it <unclear>I don't know</unclear></u>
<u n="227" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> but but I suppose if you're and you want to give you maximise your chances then you know</u>
<u n="228" who="S0248">you'd you would</u>
<u n="229" who="S0247" trans="overlap">you'd wear your lucky red shirt yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you'll feel happy I suppose with yourself no I <trunc>c</trunc> I can't no if I don't do well but I can't least I can't blame my shirt <pause dur="short"/> I had <trunc>tho</trunc>these fortuitous underpants didn't I do you remember?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0247" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh yes your lucky underpants that's true but they weren't red though were they?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I <trunc>s</trunc> forgot what they were and in fact I don't think there was cos obviously you know I think I had more than one pair</u>
<u n="233" who="S0247">I know and you <trunc>f</trunc> you forgot in the end which one will they were</u>
<u n="234" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah I don't yeah yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0248">so you can imagine how easily it can get a grip of you know this sort of stuff</u>
<u n="237" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yes yes I'm glad I'm not a slave to it but the erm Mrs <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I used to erm go berserk if anybody put an umbrella up in the office <pause dur="short"/> really <trunc>d</trunc> you know she <trunc>w</trunc> she would've said I <trunc>d</trunc> she didn't believe in superstitions but if anybody put an umbrella up she'd go put it get it down get it down <pause dur="short"/> you know so some of it's just kind of ingrained you know</u>
<u n="238" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0247">training or something</u>
<u n="240" who="S0248" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
