<text id="S3UC">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:15:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0203</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In a bar</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Sports, music</topics>
		<activity>Chatting in a pub</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0203">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0203">are you recording?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> audio audio tape</u>
<u n="3" who="S0203">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0202"><unclear/> like a tape</u>
<u n="5" who="S0203">I think it might be digital memory <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0202">digital memory</u>
<u n="7" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0202">I'm so fucking scared <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0203">of what?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0202">of being engaged</u>
<u n="11" who="S0203">why?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0202">like don't take this the wrong way</u>
<u n="13" who="S0203"><unclear/> that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0202">I'm twenty years old right so I mean well</u>
<u n="15" who="S0203"><unclear/> anyway</u>
<u n="16" who="S0202">I know but</u>
<u n="17" who="S0203">you should be ready for it</u>
<u n="18" who="S0202">I am in a way ready for it</u>
<u n="19" who="S0203">but you said it's not gonna be for six years or so anyway</u>
<u n="20" who="S0202">yeah it's gonna be from it's not gonna be for ages yet but <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <unclear/> being awkward so just prepare to feel awkward for the next few minutes but like I really want to fuck you and that and shit like that like there's there's only</u>
<u n="21" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/> awkward</u>
<u n="22" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I told you</u>
<u n="23" who="S0203"><unclear/> going</u>
<u n="24" who="S0202">but but like <pause dur="short"/> I would</u>
<u n="25" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I don't think it's necessarily a new thinking to you know what I think it's slightly <unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0202">I know but it's like do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/> all the girls</u>
<u n="28" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah like all the girls wanna <unclear>fuck</unclear> you</u>
<u n="29" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0202">no but like do you know when you're told you can't I don't know if you're the same but I am very malcontent like I <unclear>have</unclear> something and I want it and I want and I want it and I get it and then I don't want it any more</u>
<u n="31" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0202">and I'm like that and I'm thinking yeah I could do this and I could do that</u>
<u n="33" who="S0203">I'm not I'm not a <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0202">no but like</u>
<u n="35" who="S0203">I've got a lot more of <unclear/> stuff about you</u>
<u n="36" who="S0202">yeah but I have every single human in the world has</u>
<u n="37" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0202">but the thing is like basically now I have committed to spending the rest of my life with one person and don't get me wrong I love <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to pieces and I could never ever imagine cheating on him but I want to do it so bad but I just don't I could never live with the guilt</u>
<u n="39" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0202">and I could never do it but I really want to because I can't and it's not even just that I can't it's like the fact that I'm twenty-three years old like do I really want to settle down with one person now for the rest of my life? and I have I've got two choices I can either <unclear>split</unclear> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that'll be it or I can stay with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and get married to him and and</u>
<u n="41" who="S0203">the difficulty is is <unclear>we</unclear> don't have a lot of friends that are getting married</u>
<u n="42" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0203"><unclear/> I don't know how it would feel to be <unclear>married to</unclear> someone so obviously it's quite scary but obviously there is a part of it where you love it and you think it's amazing</u>
<u n="44" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0203">everything that happens like that is it it happens and there will be obstacles that come up</u>
<u n="46" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0203">like mixed feelings</u>
<u n="48" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0203">I don't know where they come from but er</u>
<u n="50" who="S0202">no I have I've already I've already and it's probably the wine the wine making me say this but I have always found you attractive when I first met you I thought you were attractive and I fancied you and I have always fancied you and we have <unclear/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0203">I have <unclear>thought</unclear> about that to you as well</u>
<u n="52" who="S0202">you know and it's like it's so difficult and I love <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> I really do and I've never met anyone so unlike me and I've never wanted to be with anyone so much but my dilemma is he's twenty-eight I'm twenty-two and</u>
<u n="53" who="S0203">he's probably ready to do this</u>
<u n="54" who="S0202">he's ready to do it and I don't know if I am</u>
<u n="55" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="56" who="S0202">and I don't know if I and he wants children and shit like that and I don't think I do like don't get me wrong right now I don't want children ever like right now I think my life <unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0202">it would stop everything it would stop everything</u>
<u n="59" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0202">it's different for a man</u>
<u n="61" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0202">like they can <trunc>ac</trunc> they can have a child with someone but they don't have to put in nine months</u>
<u n="63" who="S0203">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0202">they don't have to breast-feed they don't have to do all that shit and like to me it's so scary because like I'm gonna graduate university when I'm twenty-six and I'm doing a year in industry so the next four years I've got another</u>
<u n="65" who="S0203">you've got everything planned out that you're doing so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0202">I'm doing stuff and my plan when I finish uni will always be travel always <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s happy to come travelling with me or let me go travelling we've already had this discussion like <unclear>well</unclear> what if we split? what if we split up for six months say? what if we had a break and I <unclear>slept around? would you ever take me back</unclear>?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0203">no</u>
<u n="68" who="S0202">what if <unclear>I cheated on you when I was drunk</unclear>?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0203">no</u>
<u n="70" who="S0202">what if blah blah what if <unclear/> of our relationship now and it's just like I have no choices the two choices that I have is stay with him for the rest of my life</u>
<u n="71" who="S0203">or er and you don't wanna do either of em</u>
<u n="72" who="S0202">and I don't wanna do either</u>
<u n="73" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0202">I don't wanna cheat and I don't wanna like</u>
<u n="75" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0202">I mean awful like cos er <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0203">what I will do is erm you go away for a while don't don't be in contact for like a month or whatever and then see if <unclear>you still feel the same</unclear> cos it might just be a phase <unclear/> cos it's here right now</u>
<u n="78" who="S0202">yeah <unclear>I see I see your point</unclear> yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/> so hard it is so fucking hard it's like me saying to you right you've gotta be with this menu for the rest of your life you can't eat anything else</u>
<u n="79" who="S0203">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0202">you can eat off this menu and that's it</u>
<u n="81" who="S0203"><unclear>trouble is</unclear> everything everything you want is not on that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0202"><unclear>I mean</unclear> it's so fucked up</u>
<u n="85" who="S0203">I I <unclear/> magnified <unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0203">er a greater extent but it is nothing I can relate to I suppose</u>
<u n="88" who="S0202">so anyway let's get off the personal things and</u>
<u n="89" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0202">I'd like to talk about erm so you want to be a music teacher?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0202">don't you don't you think <unclear/> what what do you think of your band? cos I have always listened to your music and I know that I've not seen you many live many times and blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I know <unclear/> once once was enough for that</u>
<u n="94" who="S0202">no I know but it's not cos I don't want to it's because every time you have something going on I have something going on and I'm always devastated</u>
<u n="95" who="S0203" trans="overlap">don't <unclear/> in</u>
<u n="96" who="S0202">no but I'm always devastated and whether you make it or not I'm always devastated that I can't get <unclear>there</unclear> cos of whatever but</u>
<u n="97" who="S0203">there's a there's a lot of fans out there yeah and what I will say there's a lot of <unclear/> bands that are all technically better than us that are all like have got great singers have got great all the musicians are great and stuff but there's only a certain amount of room for everyone you can't just you can't just trudge along and be <unclear/> I think we are kind of <unclear/> I thought</u>
<u n="98" who="S0202">you are different</u>
<u n="99" who="S0203">and I think</u>
<u n="100" who="S0202">like I can't put erm I can't stick a genre on you do you know when <unclear/> play on someone</u>
<u n="101" who="S0203">I call it I say like indie rock but some of the songs aren't that so I <unclear>don't know</unclear></u>
<u n="102" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="103" who="S0203">er my favourite band is the Red Hot Chili Peppers yeah?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0203">and I've always loved them because</u>
<u n="106" who="S0202">me too</u>
<u n="107" who="S0203">yeah really?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0202">I love the Red Hot Chili Peppers absolutely fucking adore them I've grown up with them and I fucking</u>
<u n="109" who="S0203">like I I wasn't quite like that the thing I love about them is like every album's different they're not just rock like there'll be a song full of like</u>
<u n="110" who="S0202">different innit?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0202">every single thing they do from the first to the current album every single album is different it offers something else</u>
<u n="113" who="S0203">but that that's what I love about them that's why my <unclear>band's</unclear> like that because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> also love them yeah that's why it kind of works it</u>
<u n="114" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0203">we all <unclear>love them</unclear> we all improvise loads live and not many other bands do that sort of thing so I think that's the sort of thing that would be</u>
<u n="116" who="S0202">they stick with one thing don't they? like Kasabian's latest album is the same as every other album they've ever done</u>
<u n="117" who="S0203">yeah I hate that one as well</u>
<u n="118" who="S0202">I fucking hate it</u>
<u n="119" who="S0203"><unclear/> forty-eight</u>
<u n="120" who="S0202">forty-eight thirty-three or something</u>
<u n="121" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0202">like why <unclear>is it</unclear> so shit</u>
<u n="123" who="S0203">got erm they've got one song on it so like easy which was a single which I thought were alright and I listened to the entire album like</u>
<u n="124" who="S0202">shit</u>
<u n="125" who="S0203">oh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0202">yeah it's the same it's the same as all the rest right?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0203">do you know who I think's really good at the moment? <unclear/> Ed Sheeran's new album it's brilliant it's brilliant</u>
<u n="128" who="S0202">it I I love Ed Sheeran cos like he does like a song he'll do one song say he'll do a really slow song and be really downbeat and like really like life affirming or whatever and then you'll listen to his next song</u>
<u n="129" who="S0203"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0202"><unclear/> well two actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0202">erm and then you'll listen to the next one like completely different the ones that you've heard the first time and that's what I love about him he's different he doesn't stick to oh I'm so depressed and I hate everyone and I'm singing melancholy songs and it goes up and it then goes back down but oh I love that about him really do like that he changes but you listen to pop songs and they all sound the same</u>
<u n="133" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0202">like don't get me wrong I love pop songs I love listening to like</u>
<u n="135" who="S0203">you a top forty pop person?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="137" who="S0203">oh so</u>
<u n="138" who="S0202">I love really obscure bands like I love The Smiths</u>
<u n="139" who="S0203">oh right</u>
<u n="140" who="S0202">Blur Chili Peppers have you ever heard erm Crash Test Dummies?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0202">they were like erm all the songs sound the same in a way but that's because the singer the lead singer has got a distinct voice</u>
<u n="143" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="144" who="S0202">so so all his songs they don't sound the same the melody the melody's different the chords or whatever they are</u>
<u n="145" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0202">they all sound different</u>
<u n="147" who="S0203">you learn</u>
<u n="148" who="S0202">yeah I'm learning but his his voice is so distinct that this this <unclear/> you know that it's him they don't sound the same but you know that it's him you know it's that that band</u>
<u n="149" who="S0203">the only real <unclear/> now Ed Sheeran's got a really unique voice but it's also technically brilliant as well like he can he</u>
<u n="150" who="S0202">he can rap and sing</u>
<u n="151" who="S0203">yeah he can do everything he is brilliant</u>
<u n="152" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0203">but there's not a lot of people out there right now that are different there's a lot of people that have similar voices or something like that and what I wanna do is I don't have a great natural voice I want to make my voice something different</u>
<u n="154" who="S0202">special</u>
<u n="155" who="S0203">I want to make it stand out</u>
<u n="156" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0203">even if I can't <unclear/> I'd love to but it's using that even though I used to hate that I used to <unclear/> now I realize <unclear/> use it more <unclear/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0203"><unclear/> I'd love to be able to erm like <unclear/> last year were like</u>
<u n="160" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0203">but I can't do it but I can I can compromise <unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0202">I can't sing so</u>
<u n="163" who="S0203">I bet you could do it I bet</u>
<u n="164" who="S0202">I can't sing</u>
<u n="165" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I know I know four songs</u>
<u n="166" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I can't sing</u>
<u n="167" who="S0203"><unclear/> no right people say that everyone can sing everyone can sing it's just about finding the right sort of <unclear/> you and what I'd say to you is have you ever heard of <unclear>Norah Jones</unclear></u>
<u n="168" who="S0202">yeah I love <unclear>Norah Jones</unclear> I saw her live last year</u>
<u n="169" who="S0203">really?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0202">yeah erm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0203">but I would say you'd be good at you've really got a</u>
<u n="172" who="S0202" trans="overlap">really? cos I can't sing I'm not gonna sing right now so don't ask me</u>
<u n="173" who="S0203">please <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0202">no I'm not gonna do it but I'm so tone-deaf like</u>
<u n="175" who="S0203">it's not a it's not a thing like you'll disagree with me</u>
<u n="176" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no but I am</u>
<u n="177" who="S0203">you'll disagree with me <unclear/> be like complete <unclear/> but I've been doing this for like five years now so I've got <unclear/> about my voice or about something like that yeah you've got to <unclear/> and you will have that embarrassment but you can guarantee I could make you sing a song and you <unclear/> oh that's nice <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has the world's worst voice</u>
<u n="178" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0203">he cannot sing he recently when we were driving to <unclear/> forty-minute drive we listened to an album and he nailed there are all these albums <unclear/> he knows them all of the words <unclear/> that's how good <unclear/> get we'll be finding that song he can sing and now we'll make him sing it more and now he can sing now we get into <unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0202"><unclear/> pitch and so</u>
<u n="181" who="S0203">using his voice <unclear>more</unclear> is all about doing it getting over cos I've got I know a girl at uni called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whose got a brilliant voice but she refuses to sing in her flat because she sings like she hates <unclear>practicing</unclear> she hits a <unclear/> note <unclear/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0202">yeah do it again oh</u>
<u n="183" who="S0203">yeah it's like so what? like can't you get <unclear/> cos I did it in my flat at uni</u>
<u n="184" who="S0202"><unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0203">I did it in my flat at uni yeah? like <unclear/> used to sing quite quiet and I think that's <unclear/> loud like oh <unclear/> hear it and then I got about halfway through like what <unclear/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0203">I sing <unclear/> on there so you can hear me loud as <unclear/> from anywhere</u>
<u n="190" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0203">people might go oh what's he doing here? but I'm getting better doing and I don't care if I don't know I don't know any of the people that I <unclear/> it doesn't matter if they hear it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0203">what matters is in three or four years time I've got a <unclear/> voice like them everyone'll be like oh well they used to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah they were fucking terrible I've listened to them for four years</u>
<u n="195" who="S0203">yeah but I don't care now like</u>
<u n="196" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0203">like it's the same with everything like you have to practice you have to use your skills to get better at them so</u>
<u n="198" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0203">there's no like <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0202">do you want a drink? you need to drink something stronger cos I'm drinking wine you're drinking lager</u>
<u n="201" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I know you're gonna you're gonna get pissed</u>
<u n="202" who="S0202">this is like six percent higher and that</u>
<u n="203" who="S0203">I've had no I've had no <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="204" who="S0202">that's alright then but you need something stronger what do you want? tell me</u>
<u n="205" who="S0203">what <unclear/> wine</u>
<u n="206" who="S0202">yeah but you don't like white I don't like rose</u>
<u n="207" who="S0203">you don't like rose? I'll do white I'll drink <unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0202">no look drink a bit of that drink a bit</u>
<u n="209" who="S0203">what?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0202">drink a bit of that and tell me</u>
<u n="211" who="S0203">I'll have it</u>
<u n="212" who="S0202">no cos I'll buy it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0203">no no</u>
<u n="214" who="S0202">no cos two of those is like no cos yours last time I <unclear/> at the same time the bottle is two of those</u>
<u n="215" who="S0203">doesn't matter if we get a bottle now that's it we're equal</u>
<u n="216" who="S0202">no no</u>
<u n="217" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0202">try me no I mean if you can take if you can drink it if you <unclear/> bottle of wine and that then I'll buy it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0203"><unclear/> a lot worse than that I tell you</u>
<u n="220" who="S0202">Jägerbombs</u>
<u n="221" who="S0203"><unclear/> try it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="223" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<event desc="0203 leaves"/>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="224" who="S0202">hi are you free? can I have a bottle of Pinot grigio please?</u>
<u n="225" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0202">can I have erm a portion of curly fries and a portion of chips as well please?</u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="227" who="S0202">chips please <pause dur="short"/> and can I just have one one please? I've got one up there you can keep the five pence just gimme eight <pause dur="short"/> thank you I'm so generous <unclear/> okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0202">thank you</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
