<text id="S3VM">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:10:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0428 S0486</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Cambridge Law Faculty</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Strangers</relationships>
		<topics>Talking on the radio, yellow pages, study, Yorkshire, school, alumni day</topics>
		<activity>Alumni Day 3</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0428">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Eastern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0486">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Well, Somerset</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/Wales</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>I may have a slight Somerset accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Taunton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40 years on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>retired artist and antique dealer/gallery owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0428">put it on and then we can start talking</u>
<u n="2" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah we'll talk and then I'll do this</u>
<u n="3" who="S0428">yeah so you talk quite often on the local radio?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0486">yes well I seem to have a lot of opinions about things and erm they've got my name and quite often they ring me up when they haven't got anyone else to talk about anything basically so that's what I do erm and er I did start in my early life because I went to eight different schools and erm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="6" who="S0486">my whole education was completely messed up erm I relied on my spoken voice and I ended up doing drama and <trunc>beco</trunc> erm I was an actress for a little while and erm went to drama school and did all that thing erm because erm you often find that people who haven't got a lot of erm intellectual background they tend to erm get round it by talking so I ended up with a career in advertising for sixteen years selling advertising to people erm and er out of the three three girls who went to drama school with me erm two of us ended up working for Thompson Yellow Pages</u>
<u n="7" who="S0428">oh wow</u>
<u n="8" who="S0486">where you have to smile and dial and erm do the steps of the sale attention interest desire and action</u>
<u n="9" who="S0428">oh wow</u>
<u n="10" who="S0486">and <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's really quite important when you're erm trying to sell advertising</u>
<u n="11" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0486">er as a result of being almost indoctrinated and brain washed my Thomson's Yellow Pages</u>
<u n="13" who="S0428">so what is <anon type="place"/> Yellow Pages?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0486">well it it was erm you know the Yellow Page directory it's not so prevalent now</u>
<u n="15" who="S0428">like Yellow Pages?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0486">Yellow Pages yes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0428">oh okay</u>
<u n="18" who="S0486">and erm in those days they did a lot of erm research into the best-selling colour</u>
<u n="19" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0486">and the best-selling colour was actually yellow so that's why</u>
<u n="21" who="S0428" trans="overlap">that's why we have we have a lot of yellow on our yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><trunc>exac</trunc> yes</u>
<u n="23" who="S0428">it's really eye-catching</u>
<u n="24" who="S0486">exactly and I do <anon type="place"/> Art Week sometimes in <anon type="place"/> and we all our all our signs are yellow with black print erm which you put at the end of the road to attract people in to come and look at the studios so that's quite er an important thing</u>
<u n="25" who="S0428">so are you local to <anon type="place"/> when you said?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0486">no unfortunately not erm I live in <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> my husband's here for his alumni erm he was at <anon type="place"/> Hall and I erm always wanted to come to <anon type="place"/> because my father was at <anon type="place"/> and my brother-in-law was at <anon type="place"/> and now my husband's at <anon type="place"/> and erm I'm sixty-five and I only got my erm BA honours degree five years ago</u>
<u n="27" who="S0428">oh congratulations</u>
<u n="28" who="S0486">with <anon type="place"/> university</u>
<u n="29" who="S0428">oh congratulations</u>
<u n="30" who="S0486">but I always found I had to work really hard and I'd love to come to <anon type="place"/> and do some sort of further course er for instance an MA or some research</u>
<u n="31" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0486">but erm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it's the place to be and the place to do it</u>
<u n="34" who="S0486">yeah it is exactly it definitely is</u>
<u n="35" who="S0428">or you said that you're from erm that you live in <anon type="place"/> I went to uni in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah oh did you?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0486">oh it's a very good on isn't it? in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0428">I absolutely loved it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0486">did you?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0428">I had an absolutely fantastic time there</u>
<u n="42" who="S0486">right and what did you read there?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0428">erm Spanish Italian and European Studies</u>
<u n="44" who="S0486">oh right so language is your thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0486">oh that's great and er recently I thought about doing an MA erm the historical erm there's there's erm I can't remember the <trunc>co</trunc> complete name of the course but it's all to do with heritage</u>
<u n="47" who="S0428">er</u>
<u n="48" who="S0486">erm history and heritage course and it's at <anon type="place"/> university but unfortunately they do that at a <anon type="place"/> er a place called erm <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/>'s a very long way away from <anon type="place"/> and it's almost inaccessible by</u>
<u n="49" who="S0428">I've heard of <anon type="place"/> is it a village or?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yes and it's got erm and the er it's a listed building and it's a historical building where they do the course</u>
<u n="51" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0486">and so obviously it it sort of fits with the ethos of the course so but unfortunately trains er cars it was just an nightmare journey so I had to pass my they offered me an MA place erm so I I'm not doing that erm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0428">it's a shame</u>
<u n="54" who="S0486">yes it's just impractical it was so I don't want to stay away you know from home cos obviously I've got a lot to do at home we all have to do the gardening and the cooking the cleaning and all that sort of thing</u>
<u n="55" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah mm yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0486">and we do have a big house so it's a bit <trunc>in</trunc> unfortunate but you can't do everything in your life can you?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0428">yeah no it's it was such a fantastic place I was there for four years</u>
<u n="58" who="S0486">yes were you? yes</u>
<u n="59" who="S0428">and I absolutely loved it and just so beautiful the architecture</u>
<u n="60" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0428">I loved erm I loved the hills I'm from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0486">oh are you? yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0428">so erm that's where all my family live</u>
<u n="64" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0428">and I absolutely just live seeing the rolling hills and</u>
<u n="66" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="67" who="S0428">rather than here which is very flat so</u>
<u n="68" who="S0486">yes yes did you erm whereabouts in <anon type="place"/> were you?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0428">er my family are erm in in the Dales</u>
<u n="70" who="S0486">yes oh yes</u>
<u n="71" who="S0428">so in <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and they're up in the Dales</u>
<u n="72" who="S0486">oh right oh right well I was at school one of my eight schools was in <anon type="place"/> and I went to <anon type="place"/> college for <trunc>ski</trunc> for girls which has now closed and is now a pizza bar</u>
<u n="73" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0486">but I went to <anon type="place"/> recently cos my husband was working up there and we had erm a reception up in the museum the transport museum</u>
<u n="75" who="S0428">it's <trunc>fascin</trunc> I I really like the transport museum</u>
<u n="76" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I think or was it the steam museum? yeah was it the transport museum or the steam museum I think they call it</u>
<u n="77" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0486">and we were having a dinner dance or a dinner up there was was a <trunc>wo</trunc>wonderful because you actually sort of eat on the platforms you know but it it it you've got to wrap up warm because it's not always that warm there in the evening</u>
<u n="79" who="S0428">it's never warm in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0486" trans="overlap">particularly in October no it not it's not I remember when we went to school you know but erm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0486">so what er what's the time doing? oh not too bad erm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0428">no my my grandad lives up in erm the Dales</u>
<u n="84" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="85" who="S0428">in erm in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0486">right oh right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0428">which erm so it's absolutely stunning</u>
<u n="88" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="89" who="S0428">and I love it up there so here I find it's very flat</u>
<u n="90" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes that's right</u>
<u n="91" who="S0428">and I miss the hills and the sea</u>
<u n="92" who="S0486">yes I I can understand that I actually love <trunc>fl</trunc>flat erm vistas because erm I actually was born initially in <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> which is on the <anon type="place"/> levels and the <anon type="place"/> levels are extremely flat and if you drive across them to go the <anon type="place"/> from <anon type="place"/> you get this wonderful view going across the erm the levels and it's a bit of the same looking around the erm topography of <anon type="place"/> area</u>
<u n="93" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0486">erm but going back to the Dales er I was there at the beginning of the year at <anon type="place"/> now did you hear about Jeremy Clarkson hitting his producer?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0428">yes</u>
<u n="96" who="S0486">well he hit him in our the hotel we stayed at at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0428">oh really?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0486">although we weren't there at the time but it was a wonderful hotel it's called the <anon type="place"/> hotel and we're going back for Christmas erm and in fact I bought a jacket yesterday to wear over Christmas at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0428" trans="overlap">ooh nice here in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0486">yes here in <anon type="place"/> at erm <anon type="place"/> it's erm sort of like erm a Scottish I think it's called <anon type="place"/> because most of the fabric comes from Scotland I think I don't know whether the garments are actually made in Scotland but erm it's er a sort of more economical way to buy er cloth and made up cloth that's got some aetiology towards the er the land of Scotland <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0428">you'll have a fantastic time in Yorkshire at Christmas it's I it's so</u>
<u n="102" who="S0486" trans="overlap">thank you yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0428">it's so close to my heart and</u>
<u n="104" who="S0486">yes it is it is</u>
<u n="105" who="S0428">it's really really beautiful</u>
<u n="106" who="S0486">my best friends at school the only two girlfriends I ever made at school erm were my Yorkshire friends and one was a farmer's daughter and the other one was her her her her father taught at the local school and they were the thing I like about Yorkshire people is they say what they mean</u>
<u n="107" who="S0428">yes</u>
<u n="108" who="S0486">and there's no messing about with it and once you're locked into that you and you're in that zone and not sort of faffing about pretending something else then you you're on a straight line to success and friendship whereas in England and I when I went to <anon type="place"/> cos that was erm my <trunc>penultim</trunc>penultimate school when I went to <anon type="place"/> I erm found that the girls were much more devious and unfortunately</u>
<u n="109" who="S0428">oh really?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0486">yeah I didn't enjoy it at all I was very very sad and very miserable and I missed living in Yorkshire I really did</u>
<u n="111" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0486">erm we were very isolated we lived in <anon type="place"/> erm near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I've heard of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0486">yeah beautiful place beautiful place my father was the local vicar</u>
<u n="115" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="116" who="S0486">and er well he he he was in the army and the church you know a combination of the two and we were all over the place so erm I think in a minute I've got to go</u>
<u n="117" who="S0428">yeah do you know where? what's your next lecture on?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0486">erm I it's probably along here somewhere I expect</u>
<u n="119" who="S0428">is it? okay yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0486">erm have we done ten minutes yet? just about?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0428">er nearly</u>
<u n="122" who="S0486">nearly oh come on keep going for another minute cos I know you want want ten minutes don't you?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0486">erm do we we come every year because we enjoy it this is the fifth year we've come to the alumni celebrations</u>
<u n="125" who="S0428">oh really?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0428">so you've <trunc>be</trunc> erm so the so the lectures are always different every year and</u>
<u n="128" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0428">and this year what you know what kind of interests you what do you normally pick to?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0486">well I always look for the arts subjects</u>
<u n="131" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0486">I'm interested in anything to do with mental health erm and philosophy</u>
<u n="133" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0486">erm yesterday I had an amazing er find I didn't realise it was going to be as good as that er yesterday I saw erm a collection of er statues erm and art classical sculpture museum tour casting classical sculpture in a new light and I wish I'd taken my sketch book</u>
<u n="135" who="S0428">was that the one just near here where they've got they've got all the plaster casts of</u>
<u n="136" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah it's just round the corner yes yes</u>
<u n="137" who="S0428">it's amazing</u>
<u n="138" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="139" who="S0428">I went in there and I was just overwhelmed by what <anon type="place"/> has got</u>
<u n="140" who="S0486">exactly</u>
<u n="141" who="S0428">it's incredible yeah it's really incredible</u>
<u n="142" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and I said to her next year if there aren't any lectures that immediately strike me that may I come with my sketch book and just draw and she said yeah anybody can do that you can just come in an draw</u>
<u n="143" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0486">so I thought well that's alright then isn't it? so erm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0428">that'll be lovely</u>
<u n="146" who="S0486">that will be yeah so I might do that next year</u>
<u n="147" who="S0428">yeah alright well I'll turn this off so that you can get to your next lecture</u>
<u n="148" who="S0486">yes okay now I haven't got</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
