<text id="S3XC">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0679 S0680</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s living room, Leeds </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Tidying out a cupboard, Memories of our ‘gardening set’ toy, Memories of our ‘Bako’ building set, Issues around tidying out, Weather</topics>
		<activity>Talking about some childhood toys</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0679">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kent, Margate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired (University manager)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0680">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Margate, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Mostly Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, West Yorks.</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>42 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- School</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0679">so what do you want to do this afternoon when we get over to your house?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0680">well we can have a look in one of those another one of those top cupboards</u>
<u n="3" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0680">to see what erm <pause dur="short"/> ancient treasures there are</u>
<u n="5" who="S0679">mm I favour that top cupboard on the right because I think there might be toys in there <pause dur="short"/> and could it be possible that the garden set is in there? you know what I mean by the garden set?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0680">mm with the little pieces of er brown er well rectangles of brown plastic with holes in but but er</u>
<u n="7" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it was quite like chocolate really wasn't it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0680">yes well it was a bit undulating</u>
<u n="9" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0680">and which you use a little erm plastic <pause dur="short"/> thing that looks like a fork or spade handle</u>
<u n="11" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0680">with a point on</u>
<u n="13" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0680">because all the flowers had a little erm sort of dimple in them at the bottom so that you could push them in with this implement and make them stand up like tulips and</u>
<u n="15" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="16" who="S0680">daffodils and and all sorts of plants</u>
<u n="17" who="S0679">well I think the tulips and the daffodils actually had that little hole <pause dur="short"/> but I think some of them you just pushed in with your fingers</u>
<u n="18" who="S0680">mm cabbages you did because they were little heart things</u>
<u n="19" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh yes I remember the cabbages</u>
<u n="20" who="S0680">like tiny Brussels sprouts</u>
<u n="21" who="S0679">yes <pause dur="short"/> we may have had something a bit tall that might have been Brussels sprout we had something <pause dur="short"/> would a Brussels sprout have a sort of a a small cabbagey head at the top?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0680">well a Brussels sprout grows up a stem it would have leaves at the bottom and it might have a bit of that on the top but I don't know that we I don't think we had the runner bean because I didn't remember the frames</u>
<u n="23" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm I remember something that kept falling over</u>
<u n="24" who="S0680">I don't know I can't remember that</u>
<u n="25" who="S0679">but the vegetables all came in my time with the garden pond</u>
<u n="26" who="S0680">they were later yes</u>
<u n="27" who="S0679">whereas you had the erm you had the flower borders and the flowers</u>
<u n="28" who="S0680">I think I had the crazy paving</u>
<u n="29" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0680">greenhouse did I have the greenhouse?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0679">I think so I I do</u>
<u n="32" who="S0680">because the greenhouse had little tiny seed trays with I think they had little lines of green things in them or you could put or you could put little lines of green in there but there were some</u>
<u n="33" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> a bit like false eyelashes</u>
<u n="34" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="35" who="S0679">obviously in green I wonder what happened to my false eyelashes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0680"><trunc>they</trunc> they'd be dead once</u>
<u n="37" who="S0679">yes I was going to say it was before that time when I was in that false eyelash era</u>
<u n="38" who="S0680">and you got little tiny individual flower pots you could push the plants in as well</u>
<u n="39" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> and they stood they were erm brown you know the terracotta and they stood in little grey bases with holes in didn't they?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0680">I think they might have done because they were a bit toppley-over otherwise I do believe we I think <pause dur="short"/> I think there may have been the odd imported farm animal like rabbits and I think the little farm animal rabbits used to go on there and also maybe even the the sheep dog on occasion</u>
<u n="41" who="S0679" trans="overlap">gosh <pause dur="short"/> the swan <pause dur="short"/> oh yes <pause dur="short"/> and the swan the swan went and I think the round pond was used prior to getting the artistic pond</u>
<u n="42" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> well it was an improvised turquoisey blue one of the tin lids that push in rather than a pushes out so that it had got colour inside yes I remember that yes I think that was an improvised pond</u>
<u n="43" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yes yes yes <pause dur="short"/> I imagine that I was given the pond after we got the pond in the garden</u>
<u n="44" who="S0680">quite possibly</u>
<u n="45" who="S0679">or somewhere linked in that era</u>
<u n="46" who="S0680">I didn't start off with a pond because I had the garden set to go with my Bayko set which would be considered as a a very dangerous thing for small children to play with now because it had rods metal rods you put in holes and slid the bricks down so there's all those spikey things you can stick yourself on</u>
<u n="47" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> and the flooring that sort of brown sort of not really plastic but something a bit earlier</u>
<u n="48" who="S0680">it was green the erm base was a greeny</u>
<u n="49" who="S0679" trans="overlap">the <unclear/> oh the big green base but I meant</u>
<u n="50" who="S0680">you put the poles in</u>
<u n="51" who="S0679">you put the poles in and then you put the first floor in</u>
<u n="52" who="S0680">yes you had the poles</u>
<u n="53" who="S0679">then you put some brown stuff in to support your corners</u>
<u n="54" who="S0680">oh yes you you had erm I don't know what it was made of it was it wasn't exactly plastic it was sort of a cross between plastic and a a kind of like erm oil cloth in it it was sort of</u>
<u n="55" who="S0679">they probably hadn't invented plastic as we know it we are pre Lego here</u>
<u n="56" who="S0680" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> it looked a bit like it looked like a bit something you might <unclear>like carburettor</unclear> things with punched holes in <vocal desc="laugh"/> the old days erm I think yes you put those in for the <trunc>fl</trunc> to support just to keep the you had to keep your poles in because if you were doing something tall you had to keep slip they had all little punched holes in so you slid them over your poles so that your upper storey the poles were in the right place to retain the bricks as they slid in because otherwise if you got got taller they could possibly not be as tight at the top as they were at the bottom until you actually put the roof on so you needed some sort of erm intervening strengthening oh and that's right and and it had the different the different roofs and you could have erm er what do you call it? you could have erm <pause dur="short"/> a thing over a bay window er what do you call them? a <trunc>dor</trunc> not a dormer window erm I've forgotten the term</u>
<u n="57" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> velux?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0680">no it was er like you have over a bay window that you've got the roof coming down and then you've got the the angled piece that sticks out over the bay I've forgotten what they are called now</u>
<u n="59" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> me too me too</u>
<u n="60" who="S0680">one of those anyway you put those fancy bits on the roof to build out a a bay window</u>
<u n="61" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> oh yes yes <pause dur="short"/> you actually stood the roof was a whole thing wasn't it? a roof</u>
<u n="62" who="S0680">well the big roofs were solid</u>
<u n="63" who="S0679">so you had to buy <trunc>roo</trunc> you had to build houses to fit your roofs</u>
<u n="64" who="S0680">yes but you could only build houses that were on the right grid on a grid pattern you couldn't make a an odd half inch somewhere so it had to be in the proportions of that but you could make up your own there's a whole book of erm designs of houses and castles and things you could garages and all sorts of things you could build but you could do freehand as well as long as you considered what components you'd got because I did have several roofs and there were also flat bits that you could make that you could possibly use as a garage or flat or you could put two of them together to make a small er pitched roof I mean pitched you know with a yes and there were different bays and things but I don't know how old that was because it was used before me I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had Bayko because he's the only person I've ever talked about Bayko with because he's only well he's the same age as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so he was what? maybe two years younger than me but he's got older sisters or they may have had it I don't know</u>
<u n="65" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes because families if you if you are the eldest or youngest it would make a big difference wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0680">you know so thinking that it was really from another era because I used to play with it when I was quite small you used to play with it when you were quite small didn't you? because I used to make houses for the likes of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and small erm the small pipe cleaner dolls from the dolls' house and things I think I used to put those in you know</u>
<u n="67" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> you see I had I had Lego too</u>
<u n="68" who="S0680">and you had Lego yes</u>
<u n="69" who="S0679">but Lego wasn't as wasn't as adaptable when it first came out because you only had the big size bricks but there's hundreds of ways that they erm but the what are we calling it? the building set</u>
<u n="70" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> you get Lego people now don't you? mountains and all sorts <pause dur="short"/> bayko</u>
<u n="71" who="S0679">Bayko would be dangerous</u>
<u n="72" who="S0680">well there was all the small pieces because you could get they were they were quite thin or maybe half inch half inch square but only about quarter of an inch thin they were the ones that slotted in in red and white and then you could get ones that were just half the size of that or even thinner just for doing different bits stripes in brickwork or bits to fill in bays and they were very tiny</u>
<u n="73" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes yes yes <pause dur="short"/> I didn't like the the poles those metal poles</u>
<u n="74" who="S0680">and you got different size poles because you are going to need shorter poles for some things</u>
<u n="75" who="S0679">yes there was quite a lot to it wasn't there?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0680">mm that's right because dad made that nice erm box</u>
<u n="77" who="S0679">I wonder where he got it from?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0680">I don't know</u>
<u n="79" who="S0679">perhaps somebody at school had it</u>
<u n="80" who="S0680">it's possible it could have come from the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> because they were quite well off because it wasn't a cheap toy</u>
<u n="81" who="S0679">was he older than you?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="83" who="S0679">oh that would possibly be it then</u>
<u n="84" who="S0680">and he was a boy I don't know so it may have come that way I don't think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s because it was quite an expensive toy</u>
<u n="85" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it might have come from the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0680">or somewhere somebody in that neck of the woods erm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wouldn't necessarily pass it on because he'd have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0680">mm that's right</u>
<u n="89" who="S0679">but the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is a possibility isn't it? because he was more into more into motors wasn't he that boy?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0680">and he was an only boy and he hadn't got a brother</u>
<u n="91" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> when the boy got fed up with it he would pass it on</u>
<u n="92" who="S0680">mm <pause dur="short"/> because it all came in it came in various bits of cardboard boxes and things and father father made that</u>
<u n="93" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and did father <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="94" who="S0680">well he got all the things out and saw how many there were and then constructed the box so it would fit in because you had to put it back in the right compartments</u>
<u n="95" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps his screws or has kept his screws in a box of a sort of a similar but had the handle but I think he now keeps them in something because it's alright if you are working all the time on them but there are all sorts of problems like if you you know it doesn't have a top and things</u>
<u n="96" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> there are two upstairs with tops of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="97" who="S0679">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s tried lots of different kinds</u>
<u n="98" who="S0680">it says transistors up the side but it is er I think he was putting stuff gradually things into them</u>
<u n="99" who="S0679">yes well if you have any that will get thrown away it's worth offering them and it's worth thinking around if you could use them for other things like cottons or needles or something</u>
<u n="100" who="S0680">mm yes well this is it I mean I've got I've got loads of erm nuts and bolts and screws and nails and things that I need to sort of my own because some of my stuff is here and some of my stuff is at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and the same with my tools they are in two different places oh I must bring those tools up from the cellar to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s you know hammers and pliers</u>
<u n="101" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yes lots to do</u>
<u n="102" who="S0680">yes I don't want to throw any tools away well not throw them away I don't want to give them away necessarily</u>
<u n="103" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no you need to sort them out</u>
<u n="104" who="S0680">because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s engineer's tool kit thing he took around with him has got really useful little types of erm long nose pliers and pliers with bent noses which are really useful because you can put them in and pick something out that's not immediately in front of you and so on if you're because they were for going in you know if you want to move little wires in a jumble of wires inside a a computer box you could actually get hold of things so I would like to keep those because I don't know anybody who I could pass them onto really</u>
<u n="105" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no it's all about finding good homes for things</u>
<u n="106" who="S0680">I was always using his tool kit so I don't think he would mind</u>
<u n="107" who="S0679">anyway I guess we probably ought to be getting ready for going out now what do you think?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0680">I think so yes if we don't get blown away getting into the car</u>
<u n="109" who="S0679">gosh it is really rough out there today isn't it?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0680">mm I'm not going to go along the road with the big trees</u>
<u n="111" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="112" who="S0680">that occasionally fall down and bits come off</u>
<u n="113" who="S0679">enough trouble with your own trees but we can go round the back can't we?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="115" who="S0679">well okay let me just er tidy this off then</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
