<text id="S3YZ">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:37:19</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-18</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0046 S0086 S0169</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics></topics>
		<activity>Friends cooking and eating dinner, chatting, watching a movie</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0046">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Labourer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0086">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cuckfield, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0169">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Roofer</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0086">yeah she said</u>
<u n="2" who="S0046">I was a bit off with her</u>
<u n="3" who="S0086">yeah cos we <pause dur="short"/> I suppose because you were trying to distance yourself after that</u>
<u n="4" who="S0046">yeah so you know <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sh</trunc> she wants something out of it <pause dur="short"/> she's just not pushing she's not rushing which is fine which is fair cop</u>
<u n="5" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0046">I don't want to rush <pause dur="short"/> it's the last thing I want to do</u>
<u n="7" who="S0086">Cos you were going to go to the em gig weren't you? On Friday wasn't that the plan?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> shit <pause dur="short"/> should have gone <pause dur="short"/> wish I had have done?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0086">yeah how come you didn't? Just got stuck drinking here?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0046">em <pause dur="short"/> no just didn't really sort of talk about it nearer the time and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just wanted to stay and play X Box so I thought let's do that <pause dur="short"/> I'm happy with that</u>
<u n="11" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="12" who="S0046">I really want to pull this tooth out</u>
<u n="13" who="S0086">well you might as well</u>
<u n="14" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh my god please no</u>
<u n="15" who="S0086">you might</u>
<u n="16" who="S0041">did I just hear pull tooth out?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0086">yeah but you might as well because it's going to fall out <pause dur="short"/> it's not going to magically</u>
<u n="18" who="S0046">it's not in the gum  It's not in the gum</u>
<u n="19" who="S0041">it <trunc>to</trunc></u>
<u n="20" who="S0046">the actual tooth is in the gum</u>
<u n="21" who="S0086">just yank</u>
<u n="22" who="S0041">how can even <unclear/> how can you even see it?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0086" trans="overlap">stop it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stop it <pause dur="short"/> because it's hanging <pause dur="short"/> it must be so awful to have it hanging on</u>
<u n="24" who="S0046">shh shh shh shh shh</u>
<u n="25" who="S0086">yeah but it's there's there's there's no  there's no  saving the tooth <pause dur="short"/> what do you want to do jam it back in with super glue? Cos at this point if it  if it  was out you'd</u>
<u n="26" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh fuck <pause dur="short"/> oh fuck</u>
<u n="27" who="S0046">there is a few nerves holding on to it <pause dur="short"/> that is it <pause dur="short"/> that's why it's hurting so much</u>
<u n="28" who="S0086">stop it you're making it worse <pause dur="short"/> stop it <pause dur="short"/> ninny <pause dur="short"/> it's not your mouth <pause dur="short"/> imagine how he feels</u>
<u n="29" who="S0041">yeah just do it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know we'll get a bit of string <pause dur="short"/> start Lola <pause dur="short"/> attach <unclear/> to Lola <pause dur="short"/> hold still don't cry</u>
<u n="31" who="S0046" trans="overlap">do it <pause dur="short"/> you won't need to go very far</u>
<u n="32" who="S0086">we'll knock you out</u>
<u n="33" who="S0046">the easiest way to do it is just pin it to a door</u>
<u n="34" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> does anyone actually ever do that? Is that true?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I did that as a kid</u>
<u n="36" who="S0086">oh no I never did it</u>
<u n="37" who="S0046">what am I doing? Wake up</u>
<u n="38" who="S0041">my dad encouraged me to do it a lot <pause dur="short"/> cheers dad</u>
<u n="39" who="S0086">that's love</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041">that's love</u>
<u n="41" who="S0046">yeah you can do it <pause dur="short"/> you just literally tie it to a door and just push the door shut</u>
<u n="42" who="S0086">that's pretty rank <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="43" who="S0041">yeah pretty sick</u>
<u n="44" who="S0086">but it depends if you <trunc>ha</trunc> so you think there's nerves hanging on in there as well?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0086">Cos that would fucking kill</u>
<u n="47" who="S0041">what have you been doing to your face?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0046">nothing?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0041">where have all the scabs gone?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0046">eh they they they they they came off on the walk to work this morning <pause dur="short"/> it rained</u>
<u n="51" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0046">it rained <pause dur="short"/> sorry I caught my tooth</u>
<u n="53" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> okay you're going to have to take it out <pause dur="short"/> and I can't be here when you do it but you're going to have to do it</u>
<u n="54" who="S0086">that's a bit serious <pause dur="short"/> that's the reaction every time you touch your tooth</u>
<u n="55" who="S0046">yeah it doesn't hurt <pause dur="short"/> it's just a horrible feeling</u>
<u n="56" who="S0041">ooh yeah I know I can imagine the feeling I can remember cos I lost a tooth no long ago only a couple of years ago</u>
<u n="57" who="S0086" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="58" who="S0046">it is just a horrible feeling</u>
<u n="59" who="S0086">oh I thought that was from pain?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">and you can feel it hanging you can feel the string <pause dur="short"/> I know I know  I just pulled mine out <pause dur="short"/> no in fact I didn't that's a lie I just didn't touch it and it fell out itself</u>
<u n="61" who="S0086">did the <trunc>fe</trunc> the tooth fairy come?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I was at a conference in Germany <pause dur="short"/> and I had to literally go to the bathroom <pause dur="short"/> it was in my mouth it had come out and I had to go to the bathroom and spit it down the toilet <pause dur="short"/> it was so awful</u>
<u n="63" who="S0046" trans="overlap">I don't know where <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's connected at the back <pause dur="short"/> it's not connected at the front</u>
<u n="64" who="S0086" trans="overlap">can you just  Can you just  <trunc>g</trunc> can you just go to the dentist and say look it's hanging out please just pull it out <pause dur="short"/> like the swelling has really gone down</u>
<u n="65" who="S0046">oh I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can  I can I can  <trunc>l</trunc> I can see my gums now</u>
<u n="66" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0046">and eh it's just cool I can lift the whole lot up <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0086">oh look at the tooth  the tooth Man you should look <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0041">is it bad? Is it ready for me to look now?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0086">it's not bleeding or anything <pause dur="short"/> that one's pretty bad at the front</u>
<u n="71" who="S0041">ooh</u>
<u n="72" who="S0086">that one's like half a tooth <pause dur="short"/> did I tell you that my friend's got shark teeth? She had to have some teeth pulled and there was a whole other line of teeth that came down that grew down into her adult teeth and they did an X-Ray of her head and there's a third set of adult teeth</u>
<u n="73" who="S0046">shit</u>
<u n="74" who="S0086">she's a shark <pause dur="short"/> it's true <pause dur="short"/> an actual shark</u>
<u n="75" who="S0041">do you reckon that's how we're going to evolve? I always think when people get these things <pause dur="short"/> like there's quite a few people with extra fingers as well <pause dur="short"/> I think we're going to have another finger and I think we're going to have another row of teeth <pause dur="short"/> because as we're evolving</u>
<u n="76" who="S0046">what do we need another finger for?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0041">our diet's changing we need more teeth cos we're damaging the teeth that we've got <pause dur="short"/> I think we're going to get a third set of teeth that are going to come in around age thirty-five forty I think <pause dur="short"/> because we used to die at forty didn't we? So I think we're going to evolve and have another set of teeth that come down at forty</u>
<u n="78" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or just when you need them <pause dur="short"/> because they're probably always going to be there just like your adult teeth are there and they come down when your baby teeth go and then when they go your next row come down</u>
<u n="79" who="S0041">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0086">just like a conveyor belt of teeth</u>
<u n="81" who="S0041">shark teeth</u>
<u n="82" who="S0046">the thing is  The thing is though it's we're we're preserving them a hell of a lot better than what they used to</u>
<u n="83" who="S0041">they're still not meant you're teeth still aren't meant to love till as long as a hundred are they? If people are living</u>
<u n="84" who="S0086" trans="overlap">and we're <pause dur="short"/> our diet's very different <pause dur="short"/> if you think about what we used to eat as carnivores compared to what we eat now <pause dur="short"/> you know pure purely like cavemen</u>
<u n="85" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0046">mm <pause dur="short"/> true</u>
<u n="87" who="S0086">like ripping meat off bones</u>
<u n="88" who="S0046">Don't cos I really really still fancy chicken</u>
<u n="89" who="S0086">em</u>
<u n="90" who="S0046">or spicy spuds <pause dur="short"/> I can eat them</u>
<u n="91" who="S0041">spicy spuds</u>
<u n="92" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> with lots of garlic sauce</u>
<u n="93" who="S0086">just go to the dentist tomorrow and say look if you don't pull it out I'm going to and I'm going piss blood all over the floor <pause dur="short"/> so sort it</u>
<u n="94" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> have they told you they won't?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0046">no they couldn't get in there <pause dur="short"/> too swollen</u>
<u n="96" who="S0041">it's really scaring me <pause dur="short"/> the thought of its really going through me cos I know exactly what you're talking about</u>
<u n="97" who="S0046">but I don't know if it's cracked at the back <pause dur="short"/> if it's cracked at the back Ill pull it <pause dur="short"/> if it's not</u>
<u n="98" who="S0086">man alive <pause dur="short"/> what is that noise?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0046">that's me sucking up</u>
<u n="100" who="S0086">why? Cos you're scared the tooth is going to fall out?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like me filtering everything</u>
<u n="102" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="103" who="S0046">Cos I'm dribbling a hell of a lot more as well</u>
<u n="104" who="S0086">is it because you're not so because of that tooth you're not closing your mouth?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0046">pretty much yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0041">you're not swallowing properly</u>
<u n="107" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because I I it feels unnatural</u>
<u n="108" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0046">cos it feels uncomfortable</u>
<u n="110" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0046">so I'm trying to find the best way forward <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0086" trans="overlap">are you meant to be working tomorrow?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0041">did you go to work today?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0046">mm hm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0086">special trousers  Special trousers</u>
<u n="116" who="S0046">no <pause dur="short"/> these these are like going out trousers <pause dur="short"/> but I got my security van pass</u>
<u n="117" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> I thought they were work trousers</u>
<u n="119" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so what happened?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0046">it's just filling in paper <pause dur="short"/> legislation</u>
<u n="121" who="S0086">Cos you can't go on the shop floor like with your <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0046">no not really <pause dur="short"/> I can't anyway <pause dur="short"/> I'll scare the customers off</u>
<u n="123" who="S0086">yes <pause dur="short"/> it was kind of  kind of  the idea</u>
<u n="124" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="125" who="S0086">with security but yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0046">well yeah it just kind of sets the wrong impression though doesn't it? You know you imagine walking into ASDA the first thing you seeing is a eat up face <pause dur="short"/> in an ASDA uniform <pause dur="short"/> what are you instantly going to think?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> bruiser</u>
<u n="129" who="S0046">oh he's a thug</u>
<u n="130" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0046">so that's that's that's got to be sorted out <pause dur="short"/> in all fairness I won't need to stand at the  stand at the desk <pause dur="short"/>  I could  I could I could  go in ASDA sit behind the CCTV desk within half an hour find a thief</u>
<u n="132" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="133" who="S0046">so easy  So easy to find a thief</u>
<u n="134" who="S0086">well the one with the food in their pocket</u>
<u n="135" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">I've been there</u>
<u n="137" who="S0046">or the empty rucksack</u>
<u n="138" who="S0086">well no because take rucksack to Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="139" who="S0046">do you?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0046">and walk out with them full</u>
<u n="143" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0046">tut tut</u>
<u n="145" who="S0086">yeah cos I'm saving the planet man <pause dur="short"/> I've never been stopped</u>
<u n="146" who="S0046">no?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0086">but then I do have <unclear/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'll tell you what if somebody ever stopped me when I wasn't stealing something I would be fucking pissed off</u>
<u n="149" who="S0086">probably because you've got a backpack full of food that you have just pad for it's quite heavy you're trying to get home</u>
<u n="150" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0046">receipts are the way forward</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">I usually leave mine though <pause dur="short"/> I'm rubbish <pause dur="short"/> I take it off her and I <trunc>ne</trunc> I never know where I've put it</u>
<u n="153" who="S0086">yeah I put it in a safe place but then if they stop me and then you've got bags of stuff and you're trying to find your receipt yeah <pause dur="short"/> you'd be really annoyed</u>
<u n="154" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0046">bu then there's other questions that they can ask as well <pause dur="short"/> how much did you pay for it? And what till did you use?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0046">and then they can just search the computer <pause dur="short"/> and find out</u>
<u n="158" who="S0041">I read half a book last night</u>
<u n="159" who="S0086">are you enjoying it?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0046" trans="overlap">half a book</u>
<u n="161" who="S0041">about a hundred and thirty pages of summat</u>
<u n="162" who="S0046">what are you reading?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0041">just can't put it down</u>
<u n="164" who="S0041">it's called Hunger Games <pause dur="short"/> yeah I couldn't put it down <pause dur="short"/> so I've only I've got a quarter left</u>
<u n="165" who="S0046">what's it about?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0041">it's set in the future and basically <pause dur="short"/> the Americans had a war and broke broke down into districts <pause dur="short"/> a bit like states I suppose but they're all segregated <pause dur="short"/> nobody is allowed to cross the borders and they all produce different things for the country so one's agriculture one's mining</u>
<u n="167" who="S0046">okay</u>
<u n="168" who="S0041">blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and every year because they revolted basically the main people in the capital say right just to prove that this will never happen again we're going to each year you have to give two tributes like like a sacrifice basically <pause dur="short"/> two two people from each district one to twelve have to go to fight in the hunger games <pause dur="short"/> so they put them all in an arena and every year it changes what the terrain's like and whether it's a jungle or it's a desert or anything at all <pause dur="short"/> and they're just basically made to fight till they die <pause dur="short"/> they just leave them there and the idea is that when one person's left they're the winner</u>
<u n="169" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they give them like <pause dur="short"/> at the very beginning there's a big of the hunger games there's a big like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0046">do you not want to go and see the film?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0041">yeah I do but I need to read it first <pause dur="short"/> from all different weapons and supplies <pause dur="short"/> a piece of plastic or water bottle or stuff <pause dur="short"/> and they all  they all  have to stand on this like round thing till the gong finishes chiming then they're allowed to go <pause dur="short"/> but obviously if you're going for the stuff then some of these people some of the districts have people that really want to go and fight the hunger games and they train the kids up so that they're all huge <pause dur="short"/> whereas other districts they're really poor would do anything not to be chosen and they they still have to go</u>
<u n="173" who="S0086">so you have to make a decision when you're on those little plinths do you run for the forest?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0086">or do you run and get the weapons? Cos if you try and get the weapons and someone beats you to they're going to blow your head off</u>
<u n="177" who="S0046">they're going to actually there and then</u>
<u n="178" who="S0086">whereas if you run into the forest <pause dur="short"/> you might survive a bit longer but you haven't got any of the stuff because you've left the stuff behind</u>
<u n="179" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0086">it's a real <pause dur="short"/> like when you watch it and I imagine when you read it it's really gut wrenching cos you</u>
<u n="182" who="S0046">have you seen it?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0086">yeah I saw it in the cinema</u>
<u n="184" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0086">you <trunc>e</trunc> I think you're always putting yourself in that position like even though it's obviously it's fantasy <pause dur="short"/> what would you do? And it I don't know whether you get the sense of it in the book but in the film obviously it really question like our obsession the reality TV <pause dur="short"/> because everybody's watching it <pause dur="short"/> everybody watches on the big screen so they're also saying like you you would be able to get rid of it <pause dur="short"/> all the kids they think you could be able to banish it if people just stopped watching <pause dur="short"/> but there's this sick fascination with everybody tuning in and everybody watching it <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of you wonder how far we are off that</u>
<u n="186" who="S0046" trans="overlap">and she she starts to play the game a bit like she starts trying to like smile to the cameras and show her face if she's done something good or bad so that it gets people watching so it's <pause dur="short"/> it's like she doesn't want to be their end she doesn't want to kill people but she has to them</u>
<u n="187" who="S0086">Cos then she gets sponsors and she gets little presents and stuff when she's out there <pause dur="short"/> like things to help her</u>
<u n="188" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just got the bit where she's found em Peter</u>
<u n="189" who="S0086">oh okay</u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">she just found him when he was camouflaged in the river and she saved him</u>
<u n="191" who="S0086">that bit in the film oh my god <pause dur="short"/> but then I but then the film you're like how do they? Why would he even have the stuff with him to be able to camouflage him?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0041">no he's got it out he's made it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0086">oh I see</u>
<u n="194" who="S0041">he's been taught how to use wood and all that stuff</u>
<u n="195" who="S0086" trans="overlap">make it from what you've got</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">yeah and because of <unclear/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0086" trans="overlap">they gloss over that in the film</u>
<u n="198" who="S0041">he already knew how to do it with icing and stiuff so he already had the skill <pause dur="short"/> he just didn't know the material of saying <pause dur="short"/> before they go into the games when they have the three days of trails they kind of all work together don't they? Have three days of training <pause dur="short"/> one of the stations they could go to was camouflage <pause dur="short"/> so he learned it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0086" trans="overlap">oh I see  I see  Because they do have that bit in the film like there's like two minutes of him like painting his hand like a tree bark and then the bit when they're in the jungle and you can see him all camouflaged it's so expertly done that you think where would he have got this stiff from? It's not really explained like how why what? Don't understand</u>
<u n="200" who="S0041">yeah she says that she looks in the book it says she look down and she doesn't even realise it's him and she's like what the <trunc>fu</trunc> what? And he opens his eyes and smiles and she's like holy fuck</u>
<u n="201" who="S0086" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0041">so she just rescued him and basically carried him cleaned him up got the pus out of his leg and managed to plop him somewhere in this  really looks like it's manmade so if we get spotted we're fucked but he would have come looking for me so <pause dur="short"/> and then he's talking and she has to shut him up so she kisses him and then they get sent and sponsor of stew and so then she clicks like this is what <unclear/> wants <pause dur="short"/> to see them like <unclear/> they're in love <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> oh god <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0086" trans="overlap">they want to see</u>
<u n="204" who="S0046">it gets really good write ups doesn't it?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really really good to read <pause dur="short"/> it's like on the same level as Twilight books</u>
<u n="206" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> not a challenge</u>
<u n="207" who="S0041">like you can <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not challenging at all <pause dur="short"/> it goes in really easy you never have to reread a sentence lie you can just go through quite quickly</u>
<u n="208" who="S0086">but quite a page turner</u>
<u n="209" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0046">how far in the future is it set? Is it like real future future?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0041">eh</u>
<u n="212" who="S0086">they don't give you any date do they?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0041">they gave me a date in the book <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what it was <pause dur="short"/> like twenty <pause dur="short"/> twenty-seventy or something</u>
<u n="214" who="S0086" trans="overlap">it's this century isn't it?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0041">yeah it's still in twenties</u>
<u n="216" who="S0046">so yeah it's not like ridiculously far on then?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> but the way that <pause dur="short"/> I'm really excited <pause dur="short"/> I really hope it happen is real life <pause dur="short"/> I like that she gets up in the morning and she goes to the shower and she just pushes the buttons what she wants <pause dur="short"/> whether she wants it to be hot cold jet whether it has lemon stuff or <pause dur="short"/> whether she's going to have exfoliator and then she just presses all these button she says there's like a hundred different offers for the shower <pause dur="short"/> she just stands there and does it and when she gets out of the shower to dry her hair she just puts her hand on this little screen and it sends and electric current through her hair and dries it all</u>
<u n="218" who="S0046">yeah done <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0041">how good would that be for this hair?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0086">pretty nice</u>
<u n="221" who="S0046">see I I I don't like films that are set too far in the future because they tend to go over the top ridiculously <pause dur="short"/> like Total Recall</u>
<u n="222" who="S0086">that's hilarious</u>
<u n="223" who="S0046">they're <trunc>re</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> they're remaking it aren't they?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0086">are they?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're remaking it</u>
<u n="226" who="S0086">ah it's a classic <pause dur="short"/> especially when it becomes Earth at the end</u>
<u n="227" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I don't think I've seen it</u>
<u n="228" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is a good film</u>
<u n="229" who="S0041">so cult classic <pause dur="short"/> it's very eighties</u>
<u n="230" who="S0046">but that that was set in twenty twenties or something like that wasn't it?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0086">yeah but they made it forty years ago</u>
<u n="232" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="233" who="S0086">late seventies wasn't it? Or early eighties</u>
<u n="234" who="S0046">early eighties</u>
<u n="235" who="S0086">so it's thirty year ago</u>
<u n="236" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0086">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> they I think they thought that by the twenty-first century we we would be living one the moon</u>
<u n="238" who="S0046">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> proper ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> it was Mars weren't it?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0086" trans="overlap">hasn't quite worked out <pause dur="short"/> that's Mars <pause dur="short"/> well I don't think it is even Mars I think it's just another planet that's uninhabitable if you go out of the bubble of oxygen</u>
<u n="240" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0086">hilarious <pause dur="short"/> and at the end they <unclear/> are about to explode <pause dur="short"/> they're like coming out their face <pause dur="short"/> it's so funny <pause dur="short"/> like the effects are so shit</u>
<u n="242" who="S0046" trans="overlap">Arnold Schwarzenegger film</u>
<u n="243" who="S0041">I want to see it</u>
<u n="244" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0086">you've got to watch it <pause dur="short"/> it's very much of its time</u>
<u n="246" who="S0041">I think this one's set just enough far in the future so that you can believe it <pause dur="short"/> they don't go too crazy</u>
<u n="247" who="S0086">well I think a lot of it it does isn't beyond the realms of possibility</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0086">you know our fascination with reality TV <pause dur="short"/> you think where will that end?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0041">yeah I <trunc>e</trunc> it could happen</u>
<u n="251" who="S0086">civil war that could happen</u>
<u n="252" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0046">people were stunned when at the Snoop Dog and Dr Dre concert and Tupac came up on stage</u>
<u n="254" who="S0086">right <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0046">this weekend Tupac turned up on stage</u>
<u n="257" who="S0086">really? No</u>
<u n="258" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> he dead</u>
<u n="260" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he turned up on stage <pause dur="short"/> they they made  they made  a 3D hologram of him</u>
<u n="263" who="S0086" trans="overlap">so someone who looks like him <pause dur="short"/> oh I see</u>
<u n="264" who="S0046">they recreated him</u>
<u n="265" who="S0041">you did not explain yourself properly there at all</u>
<u n="266" who="S0046">no no <pause dur="short"/> but it's technology <pause dur="short"/> tupac turned up on stage <pause dur="short"/> no one knew about it everyone was freaking out</u>
<u n="267" who="S0041">but he didn't did he? It was only <unclear/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0046">well no</u>
<u n="269" who="S0086">and nobody would have thought it was actual him cos you can tell a hologram</u>
<u n="270" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0046">apparently not with this <pause dur="short"/> and I saw pictures of it one the news as well and it looks amazing</u>
<u n="272" who="S0086">going to have to Google that</u>
<u n="273" who="S0046">yeah me too</u>
<u n="274" who="S0086">I want to see what it looks like</u>
<u n="275" who="S0046">it looked amazing <pause dur="short"/> god knows I god knows what I'd be like if I saw Tupac turned up on stage <pause dur="short"/> unexpectedly</u>
<u n="276" who="S0041">I don't think I'd know who he was if he smacked me in the face</u>
<u n="277" who="S0046">no?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0086">I might recognise his voice <pause dur="short"/> certainly wouldn't recognise his face be like who's that? Who's that just wandered out on to the stage</u>
<u n="279" who="S0046" trans="overlap">no I'd <trunc>re</trunc> I'd recognise him <pause dur="short"/> same with the Notorious BIG though</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">oh that's</u>
<u n="281" who="S0086">that's that's a small person</u>
<u n="282" who="S0046">that's that's fags <pause dur="short"/> that is fags that is <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="283" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello gorgeous</u>
<u n="284" who="S0046">you alright?</u>
<u n="285" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you're talking</u>
<u n="286" who="S0046">I am talking</u>
<u n="287" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm not  I'm not  <unclear/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0041">so yesterday I decided I should run home from work</u>
<u n="289" who="S0086">what?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> I've decided I should run home from work <pause dur="short"/> cos it's  <unclear/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0086">right? With all your stuff on your back?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0041">no no no I left it all at work</u>
<u n="293" who="S0086">oh okay</u>
<u n="294" who="S0041">em <pause dur="short"/> yeah so <pause dur="short"/> running home <pause dur="short"/> really crap a keeping pace stopped like three times four times <pause dur="short"/> fine yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know dying a little bit <pause dur="short"/> and then thought my carbs are fucking burning <pause dur="short"/> my claves are fucking brining to fuck <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't my breathing so much but my legs felt like they were going to die <pause dur="short"/> that might be I got to using the weight thing on the legs and decided I wanted to <unclear/> from my usual forty-five to seventy</u>
<u n="295" who="S0086">what?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0041">so yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0086">seventy kilos?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I that's my body weight so I should be doing that anyway <pause dur="short"/> that's just like it's like you doing the <pause dur="short"/> this <pause dur="short"/> the keeping your knees back <pause dur="short"/> I can't really do it</u>
<u n="299" who="S0086">it's pretty hard <pause dur="short"/> you've got to keep your back straight as well otherwise you fuck your back up</u>
<u n="300" who="S0041">yeah it's like that except for you in a chair so there' no way of cheating <pause dur="short"/> there' s no way of putting your knees too far forward</u>
<u n="301" who="S0086">okay <pause dur="short"/> seventy kilos sounds a bit intense <pause dur="short"/> and you have gone running twice on Monday <pause dur="short"/> poor little legs</u>
<u n="302" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so obviously on the way home I'm dying so I got here and I was like fuck my legs are burning ouch</u>
<u n="303" who="S0086">are they massive? Did they not swell up?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0041">eh no <pause dur="short"/> but I thought I'd go for a walk round the two miles here</u>
<u n="305" who="S0086">oh okay</u>
<u n="306" who="S0041">and walk them off <pause dur="short"/> and then I ran that as well <pause dur="short"/> I stopped more but on both I averaged a ten minute mile</u>
<u n="307" who="S0086">do you think you might be losing your mind? Do you think you might have actually goes bananas?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0041">eh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would go again tonight</u>
<u n="309" who="S0086">but but but <pause dur="short"/> maybe this is because you're really enjoying it <pause dur="short"/> like are you enjoying the buzz that you get from it? Or are you just so determined to get your times up</u>
<u n="310" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no I just really want to win</u>
<u n="311" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">I just really want to win</u>
<u n="313" who="S0086">that wills it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="314" who="S0041">so that's why I thought let's not run today <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0086">let's not run <pause dur="short"/> just sit</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041">and it really took <unclear/> I was going to go to the gym after work</u>
<u n="317" who="S0086">you're mad</u>
<u n="318" who="S0041">I know I think I'm getting a bit addicted</u>
<u n="319" who="S0086">you are getting a bit addicted <pause dur="short"/> this has <trunc>ha</trunc> this happened to stu <pause dur="short"/> that's why he goes three times a day</u>
<u n="320" who="S0041">did it? I would go twice a day</u>
<u n="321" who="S0086" trans="overlap">because and he's fucking mental <pause dur="short"/> yeah well he does <pause dur="short"/> he goes three times a day <pause dur="short"/> because he's just gone wrong in the head <pause dur="short"/> so he goes running he goes swimming and then he goes and does weights</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041">if my <trunc>le</trunc> if my  if my  muscles could keep up I would go twice a day</u>
<u n="323" who="S0086">em</u>
<u n="324" who="S0041">but hey hurt a lot</u>
<u n="325" who="S0086">I I mean I'm complaining and all I did was weights and a bit of running <pause dur="short"/> on Monday</u>
<u n="326" who="S0041">yours might be a bit more extreme though</u>
<u n="327" who="S0086">no I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd like to maintain that they is that it is <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="328" who="S0041">hello</u>
<u n="329" who="S0169">you alright <pause dur="short"/> good to see you</u>
<u n="330" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0086"><unclear/> She just told me all the stuff that she's been doing so</u>
<u n="332" who="S0169">oh is she?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="334" who="S0041">it was my own fault I went a bit over board yesterday</u>
<u n="335" who="S0169">I thought you had the day off?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0041">I was going to and then I</u>
<u n="337" who="S0169">you changed your mine</u>
<u n="338" who="S0041">yeah well I was sat all day</u>
<u n="339" who="S0169">typical woman</u>
<u n="340" who="S0041">I get this  I get this  funny feeling my chest sometimes <pause dur="short"/> so I was sat at work and when I hear people cos the gyms right next to work I hear people on the treadmill and I get this kind of anxious feeling <pause dur="short"/> I think it's part worry that it's three weeks and part I really should be doing that</u>
<u n="341" who="S0169">guilty</u>
<u n="342" who="S0041">and part  And part  I really want to do it <pause dur="short"/> so I sat all day and I was just fidgeting all day <pause dur="short"/> so then I decide it would be a good idea to run home from work <pause dur="short"/> which is just over two miles <pause dur="short"/> it's only like two point two but I walked from the hotel to the bus station to Drummer street <pause dur="short"/> so that must be nearly the point two bit</u>
<u n="343" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0169">yeah bleugh <pause dur="short"/> so yeah did that <pause dur="short"/> can't keep pace at all <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> so I stopped like three three <trunc>ti</trunc> three of four tines on the way home <pause dur="short"/> not stopped still but stopped and like walked maybe ten paces <pause dur="short"/> then started again</u>
<u n="345" who="S0046">half a mile</u>
<u n="346" who="S0169">every half a mile</u>
<u n="347" who="S0046">ten paces is half a mile</u>
<u n="348" who="S0041">ten paces is not half a mile</u>
<u n="349" who="S0169">no no its</u>
<u n="350" who="S0086">he's talking shit</u>
<u n="351" who="S0169">no no just winding you up</u>
<u n="352" who="S0041">I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> thought before it was by breathing I couldn't breathe <pause dur="short"/> this time my legs were burning to fuck <pause dur="short"/> so I decided early that day before I went to work to go to the gym and doing the thing where you push the weights <pause dur="short"/> to up that to seventy kilos and before was only doing forty forty fifty-six <pause dur="short"/> I thought fuck it you're going to have to learn to to do it and just did it</u>
<u n="353" who="S0086">man alive</u>
<u n="354" who="S0041">so and then I did this one and this ones and this one's as well <pause dur="short"/> so and I got home and obviously my legs were burning <pause dur="short"/> burning <pause dur="short"/> and I couldn't stretch out my calves at all no matter what I did they still hurt <pause dur="short"/> so I thought right tell you what we're going to do <pause dur="short"/> we'll go for a little walk <pause dur="short"/> round the two two miles here <pause dur="short"/> so I started doing that <pause dur="short"/> then I couldn't do that either and started to run that as well <pause dur="short"/> stopped more often but still managed to overage a ten minute mile <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just obviously shit at keeping my pace and my legs were burning to fuck <pause dur="short"/> so today come hell or high water I'm not doing it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0086">sit down <pause dur="short"/> make sure you don't leave <pause dur="short"/> we'll just barricade you in your room</u>
<u n="356" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0086">you can't come out</u>
<u n="358" who="S0041">so I thought that was probably wise <pause dur="short"/> and I haven't been to the gym at all <pause dur="short"/> although I was going to go this morning except for I overlaid so I haven't been</u>
<u n="359" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I should have knocked for you this morning <pause dur="short"/> but I just thought you were <pause dur="short"/> there was a <trunc>reas</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> cos you do different shifts everyday so I never want to knock for you in case you're not starting and I'm waking you up</u>
<u n="360" who="S0041">yeah so that's why <pause dur="short"/> that's why I can't run</u>
<u n="361" who="S0169">how's his face? Alright?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0086">huh?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0169">is it getting better?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0086">his face his <trunc>be</trunc> he's picked all the scabs off though <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit of a  bit of a  issue <unclear/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0041">it's going to scar your face though</u>
<u n="366" who="S0086">Cos it needs  it needs  the scarring yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="367" who="S0169">should have just left it shouldn't he?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think he was worried <pause dur="short"/> he started work today so he was a bit worried about eh impression that he could give I think or something like that <pause dur="short"/> not sure <pause dur="short"/> cos he's either either way he's got scars or he's got scabs <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="369" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0086">comme ci comme cça</u>
<u n="371" who="S0041">I guess that's why I can't <unclear/> today <pause dur="short"/> we're going to do it in the abs instead</u>
<u n="372" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0041">and I printed off some more exercises as well</u>
<u n="374" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> bark like a seal maybe <pause dur="short"/> that's what <unclear/> in Pilates <pause dur="short"/> I think that's what you should do</u>
<u n="375" who="S0041">yeah I <pause dur="short"/> ah I've got a Pilates DVD <pause dur="short"/> I could do that</u>
<u n="376" who="S0086">D V B</u>
<u n="377" who="S0041">D B B <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0041">D B B <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos I keep getting on the stupid scales every morning at work and they're not moving <pause dur="short"/> and it's annoying me now <pause dur="short"/> three days  Three days  and they've not moved</u>
<u n="380" who="S0169">Don't weigh yourself so often <pause dur="short"/> once every week <pause dur="short"/> max</u>
<u n="381" who="S0041">I know but I wanted to keep a track on the progress cos I want those three pounds gone this week <pause dur="short"/> cos that takes me under the next stone block</u>
<u n="382" who="S0086">ah okay</u>
<u n="383" who="S0041">yeah so they need to go</u>
<u n="384" who="S0086">they need to be gone now</u>
<u n="385" who="S0041">yeah now</u>
<u n="386" who="S0086">em are you em transferring it to muscle?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0169">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's probably what's happening <pause dur="short"/> see when you first start doing any sort of weight training you gain weight quite quickly <pause dur="short"/> you'll gain like a I can't work it <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what it is bit it's something  it's something  ridiculous like you gain a kilo if you 'redoing weight training regular <pause dur="short"/> you can gain a kilo a week</u>
<u n="388" who="S0041">shit</u>
<u n="389" who="S0169">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because you're building muscle you see which you've not had before <pause dur="short"/> so that's going to be sort of the fat you lose your replacing with muscle <pause dur="short"/> so you're not going to lose any weight</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041">I'm going to get guns soon <pause dur="short"/> I can feel them</u>
<u n="391" who="S0086">you're going to definitely get guns</u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">they're better than the last time I tried for guns <pause dur="short"/> look at this arm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0086">it's amazing how quickly they change though the arms <pause dur="short"/> jesus look at that</u>
<u n="394" who="S0041">it's not very hard</u>
<u n="395" who="S0086">see that's what I do and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> comes along and goes like that <pause dur="short"/> oh look that's very impressive look you haven't got any em wobble there at all <pause dur="short"/> look at that</u>
<u n="396" who="S0169">yeah yeah she's got good triceps actually</u>
<u n="397" who="S0086">it's good <pause dur="short"/> I've got <trunc>load</trunc> I've got loads of wobble on my bingo wings</u>
<u n="398" who="S0041" trans="overlap">on this arm as well <pause dur="short"/> this arm is better <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why cos I'm right handed <pause dur="short"/> look at this one</u>
<u n="399" who="S0086">yeah I find that <pause dur="short"/> my arm <pause dur="short"/> my left arm is stronger <pause dur="short"/> that's why when I do bench presses it's like that</u>
<u n="400" who="S0169"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0086">but I'm right handed <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> it's weird <pause dur="short"/> unless you deliberately overcompensate</u>
<u n="402" who="S0169">compensating yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0086">it's a bit strange <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> my I've still got very much bingo wings</u>
<u n="404" who="S0041">I've got bingo wings normally</u>
<u n="405" who="S0086">no even when I flex <pause dur="short"/> I've still got bingo wings</u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">maybe it's  pushing <pause dur="short"/> don't know <pause dur="short"/> I just do them all</u>
<u n="407" who="S0086">that's very impressive</u>
<u n="408" who="S0041">and the now <pause dur="short"/> and the ones that you push this way where you sit like this and you push this that ones' on twenty-eight <pause dur="short"/> the one when you go sit like this and push it up with your hands <pause dur="short"/> that way <pause dur="short"/> is twenty-one <pause dur="short"/> the leg one is seventy <pause dur="short"/> fuckers <pause dur="short"/> probably going to do it on a bit less <pause dur="short"/> and the one that you pull down is twenty-eight</u>
<u n="409" who="S0169">that's quite a lot you know <pause dur="short"/> seventy <pause dur="short"/> it's only your own body weight you know <pause dur="short"/> how much do you weigh?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0041">yeah well that's what I said</u>
<u n="411" who="S0086">that's a  That's a  hell of a lot</u>
<u n="412" who="S0169">Don't don't <trunc>l</trunc> <unclear/> straight out of that one <pause dur="short"/> quickly</u>
<u n="413" who="S0041" trans="overlap">about that <pause dur="short"/> it's about that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well basically I choose the</u>
<u n="414" who="S0086">Don't ask a girl her weight</u>
<u n="415" who="S0041">I choose the  one <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm never going to tell you that <pause dur="short"/> I choose the one that's close to my body weight <pause dur="short"/> it's not exactly that but it's pretty close</u>
<u n="416" who="S0086">that's a little bit serious mate <pause dur="short"/> seventy kilos <pause dur="short"/> that's like that's like a child more than a child</u>
<u n="417" who="S0169">it's a smallish child</u>
<u n="418" who="S0041">but I need to be able to do more than that</u>
<u n="419" who="S0086">see that's just <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>cou</trunc> I couldn't do it</u>
<u n="420" who="S0041">yeah it's alright <pause dur="short"/> I can't run</u>
<u n="421" who="S0086">it's boring as hell</u>
<u n="422" who="S0041">isn't it? Isn't it really? D'you know what I thought about <pause dur="short"/> maybe <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> putting like a podcast on the iPod like a story</u>
<u n="423" who="S0086">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> storybook</u>
<u n="424" who="S0041">like story book and I could run and just listen to the story</u>
<u n="425" who="S0086">that would help</u>
<u n="426" who="S0169">might work for you</u>
<u n="427" who="S0086">certainly <trunc>w</trunc> when I was in the gym the other day <pause dur="short"/> the girl was there with a magazine</u>
<u n="428" who="S0041">yeah I <trunc>n</trunc> mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0086">which is a bit intense <pause dur="short"/> but she was on the constrainer think as opposed to the treadmill <pause dur="short"/> so it's less quick</u>
<u n="430" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd still get pissed off</u>
<u n="431" who="S0086">I might <trunc>fe</trunc> you might feel sick as well <pause dur="short"/> like a bit sea sick cos of the movement and trying to keep your eye line steady <pause dur="short"/> might break your leg as well if you got a bit carried away <pause dur="short"/> of you really love it</u>
<u n="432" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah definitely</u>
<u n="433" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> man alive</u>
<u n="434" who="S0041">I think I'm going to be a granny</u>
<u n="435" who="S0169"><unclear/> or is that the same one?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0086">no that's just a friend</u>
<u n="437" who="S0169">ah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0041">who is a twin by the way <pause dur="short"/> so if you see two people at the same same place <pause dur="short"/> I can't tell them apart can you?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0086">no no</u>
<u n="440" who="S0041">one of them used to have red hair <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if she does any more</u>
<u n="441" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> I think he's more friends with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0041">so that was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0086">but that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know that that looks different to the last time I was here <pause dur="short"/> slightly</u>
<u n="444" who="S0041">so that might be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0086">that'd be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was the one that had the red hair</u>
<u n="447" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was the one who was here a lot</u>
<u n="448" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> would you like anything to eat or drink? I was going to make a bit of food later but em</u>
<u n="450" who="S0169">I'll have a drink</u>
<u n="451" who="S0086">I'll have a shower <pause dur="short"/> would you like a beer?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0169">yeah I wouldn't mind <pause dur="short"/> I haven't had a beer for a while</u>
<u n="453" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you want a beer?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0041">I would like but no thanks</u>
<u n="455" who="S0086">ah aren't you good? Em em <pause dur="short"/> how was the job hunt today?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0169">shit</u>
<u n="457" who="S0086">Good good</u>
<u n="458" who="S0169">yeah great</u>
<u n="459" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="460" who="S0169">it's the <unclear/> out there though innit? It's really really</u>
<u n="461" who="S0041">I want to play I'm going to play job hunt at the weekend</u>
<u n="462" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you're welcome</u>
<u n="463" who="S0169">mm thank you</u>
<u n="464" who="S0041">seeing as I <unclear/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0169">thank you <pause dur="short"/> oh the recordings on <pause dur="short"/> thanks for the heads up</u>
<u n="466" who="S0041">just just for the standard <pause dur="short"/> I got my em <pause dur="short"/> I got my letter today form work about please full in your employer survey</u>
<u n="467" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="468" who="S0041">time stopped<unclear/> completely</u>
<u n="469" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="470" who="S0041"><unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> eh then yes we are pleased to announce that everybody achieved bonus this year <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't quite what we expected but everybody is entitled to it so <pause dur="short"/> my bonus for the year <pause dur="short"/> for the year <pause dur="short"/> two hundred and twenty-five pounds</u>
<u n="471" who="S0086">ah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0041">for the year <pause dur="short"/> I was like what the fuck is that</u>
<u n="473" who="S0086">is that? So what percentage is that of your salary? Like three per cent or something</u>
<u n="474" who="S0041">no nowhere near that</u>
<u n="475" who="S0086">one per cent</u>
<u n="476" who="S0041">yeah like one per cent or something <pause dur="short"/> or like one point something per cent <pause dur="short"/> something crap</u>
<u n="477" who="S0169">what's that?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0041">my shit bonus</u>
<u n="479" who="S0086">well it's about  it's about  two per cent isn't it?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0041">it should have been at least three per cent <pause dur="short"/> minimum</u>
<u n="481" who="S0086">that's shocking <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we're going to get a bonus this year</u>
<u n="482" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like fuck that <pause dur="short"/> and I'd said and then the worst part is that takes me over the threshold start paying all the shit back</u>
<u n="483" who="S0086">right so you <pause dur="short"/> in fact you're not going to see that are you?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0041">so no <pause dur="short"/> in fact I went to HR and said if I get my payslip and I'm worse off can I decline my bonus and she said yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0086">oh really?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0041">so I might actually have to decline the bonus to be better off</u>
<u n="487" who="S0086">oh what the hell</u>
<u n="488" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">alright girls <pause dur="short"/> boy <pause dur="short"/> I will see you guys later <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
<u n="489" who="S0086">bye</u>
<u n="490" who="S0041" trans="overlap">bye</u>
<u n="491" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">right give us a squeeze</u>
<u n="492" who="S0046">see you later treacle <pause dur="short"/> thank you very much <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> so that's fun</u>
<u n="494" who="S0046"><unclear/> shut at the weekend</u>
<u n="495" who="S0086">hang on wait a minute <pause dur="short"/> that's what I thought you said about jobs but what about the navy? Is this just a plan B</u>
<u n="496" who="S0041">well I <unclear/> as well <pause dur="short"/> this is just  This is just  for now</u>
<u n="497" who="S0169">what the fuck was that?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0086">she's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0169">yes but whispered</u>
<u n="500" who="S0041" trans="overlap">ah my legs</u>
<u n="501" who="S0086">well it was like stage whisper though wasn't it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0169">A stage whisper</u>
<u n="504" who="S0086" trans="overlap">the kind of whisper that isn't a whisper</u>
<u n="505" who="S0041">it wasn't an inside voice was it?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0086">that wasn't <trunc>y</trunc> that wasn't your quiet voice <pause dur="short"/> you won't <trunc>lo</trunc> we know that you don't have a quiet voice <pause dur="short"/> what is  What is  this?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0041">what is that?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0086">that's my knee coming through <pause dur="short"/> hiya</u>
<u n="509" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Hiya</u>
<u n="510" who="S0086">it's gone got say hello <pause dur="short"/> I was in a three hour meeting his afternoon <pause dur="short"/> that was a piss take</u>
<u n="511" who="S0041">holy shit</u>
<u n="512" who="S0086">yeah yep</u>
<u n="513" who="S0041">three hours</u>
<u n="514" who="S0086">yep yep yep <pause dur="short"/> yep yep yep <pause dur="short"/> they're just really a disorganised rabble quite frankly <pause dur="short"/> all my editors <pause dur="short"/> you're supposed to have one come in and one go out? And it's supposed to be on time and efficient and none of it is</u>
<u n="515" who="S0041">did you not think to hang up the phone while you were next to it?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0046">no not really <pause dur="short"/> it can only be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0041">ah shit it does my head in</u>
<u n="518" who="S0046">she is a piss take</u>
<u n="519" who="S0041">I put the phone down</u>
<u n="520" who="S0086">she text me the other night at ten o'clock to ask for the cheque</u>
<u n="521" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0086">I didn't look out</u>
<u n="523" who="S0169">alright mate <pause dur="short"/> new trousers on?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0046">yeah I had a interview well new job</u>
<u n="525" who="S0169">oh right</u>
<u n="526" who="S0046">new job</u>
<u n="527" who="S0169">how did it go?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0046">not too bad not too bad <pause dur="short"/> I eh officially start on Sunday I do believe</u>
<u n="529" who="S0169">that's alright you got it then?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0046">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0169">oh good for you mate <pause dur="short"/> good for you</u>
<u n="532" who="S0046">who was it?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0041">sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> please continue</u>
<u n="534" who="S0086">is that was that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on the phone cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is calling me now</u>
<u n="535" who="S0041">ah just put the phone down</u>
<u n="536" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0041">I don't answer it</u>
<u n="538" who="S0046">are you at home? No</u>
<u n="539" who="S0086">hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/><pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Alright well that's fine <pause dur="short"/> I've left it out in the hall for you so just come and get it whenever is convenient <pause dur="short"/> no she's still at work <pause dur="short"/> she working late this week <pause dur="short"/> I think she finishes about six but then she goes running after work <pause dur="short"/> she is keep fit yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you want me to get her to call you? Okay <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so it's just whether that's a good day? So so they were going to do it during the day <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> mm hm <pause dur="short"/> it's strangers <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> and how long do you think it will take? Do you think? Half a day okay that's fine I'll let her know <pause dur="short"/> and I'll get her to call you I'll get <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure she's got credit on the phone so if not I'll get her to call you on my phone <pause dur="short"/> oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll em I'll speak to her about it then and I'll let you know or she'll let you know <pause dur="short"/> alright thanks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> speak to you later <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
<u n="540" who="S0169" trans="overlap">so what's the job?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0046">security</u>
<u n="542" who="S0041">she's trying to put  in my bedroom  in my bedroom  isn't she?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0041">little fucker</u>
<u n="545" who="S0086">em just just refugees <pause dur="short"/> just going to move them in <pause dur="short"/> she's going to put a curtain in your room and em an extra bed in there</u>
<u n="546" who="S0041">eh yeah <pause dur="short"/> straight down the middle <pause dur="short"/> lovely yeah <pause dur="short"/> looking forward to it</u>
<u n="547" who="S0086">to replace the French doors finally on Monday</u>
<u n="548" who="S0041">what while my bed's there?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0041">yeah nice</u>
<u n="551" who="S0086">so I think that probably means she might need you to move your things <pause dur="short"/> she said I can understand if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to be there but can she let me know today <pause dur="short"/> she says it's going to be half a day's job <pause dur="short"/> she's going to be there and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is going to be there to protect your things <pause dur="short"/> not that they'd give two hoots <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether they're going to have to come</u>
<u n="552" who="S0041">cheers for all the notice and that</u>
<u n="553" who="S0086">well she said I just found out this minute <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="554" who="S0041">what a load of lies</u>
<u n="555" who="S0046">I knew she got the doors</u>
<u n="556" who="S0086">well she said she's going to come round later to pick up my cheque so</u>
<u n="557" who="S0041">Great</u>
<u n="558" who="S0086">I mean so long as she doesn't come round now and you miraculously got home in the last two minutes <pause dur="short"/> cos I thought she was going to be asking about your rent and I know you you don't get paid for till the end of the month</u>
<u n="559" who="S0046">you're going to have windows as well apparently</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">am I now?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0086">you're going to what?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0046">have windows</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041" trans="overlap">what a big privilege</u>
<u n="565" who="S0046">Windows</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041">she'd better put a blind in there or summat</u>
<u n="567" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think you might be asking a bit much now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> it is encouraging to find out that it's not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> fitting the doors</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s handyman who is not qualified in any regard</u>
<u n="571" who="S0169">right</u>
<u n="572" who="S0086">and whenever there is a problem with the boiler gas electricity water <pause dur="short"/> any kind of handy stuff  she just sends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0046">and he just can't cope with it</u>
<u n="574" who="S0086">well he's just a really old man who gives it all that when he's here <pause dur="short"/> he's just not qualified <pause dur="short"/> that's my biggest issue with him <pause dur="short"/> is that when the boiler goes out he comes round <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't know what he's doing</u>
<u n="575" who="S0046">no I can sort that out now but</u>
<u n="576" who="S0086" trans="overlap">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> if it was something major</u>
<u n="577" who="S0041" trans="overlap">you're not gas qualified either</u>
<u n="578" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you're not  You're not Corgi registered <pause dur="short"/> you don't know really what you're doing</u>
<u n="579" who="S0041">gas us all out</u>
<u n="580" who="S0086">gas us out <pause dur="short"/> that to look forward to</u>
<u n="581" who="S0041">in the crack house <pause dur="short"/> the house of crack</u>
<u n="582" who="S0086" trans="overlap">she's just such a <unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0041">I think I'm all up to date with my rent now as it happens</u>
<u n="584" who="S0086">oh winner</u>
<u n="585" who="S0046">I was <pause dur="short"/> I was</u>
<u n="586" who="S0041">em</u>
<u n="587" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm hungry <pause dur="short"/> are you hungry?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0169"></u>
<u n="589" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> I've got tuna</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">oh I have tuna I forgot about that</u>
<u n="591" who="S0046">are you sure?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">I really wanted pasta</u>
<u n="593" who="S0046">are you sure we didn't put it in our curry?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">ah yeah we put it <pause dur="short"/> I think I've got more</u>
<u n="595" who="S0046">ah okay</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">I em I really wanted tuna pasta <pause dur="short"/> forgot about that <pause dur="short"/> I just really wanted pasta generally or any type of carb to be honest was required</u>
<u n="597" who="S0086">tinniest dinner in the world <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> just putting it out there</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">well I thought if I just have this</u>
<u n="599" who="S0169">I just assumed you're feeding the cat</u>
<u n="600" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="601" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0041">you know but sometimes <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I had a <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> tuna take the piss</u>
<u n="603" who="S0169">are not going to put any rice with that though?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0041">I was going to say I had a cracker with peanut butter on before I left work</u>
<u n="605" who="S0086">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="606" who="S0041">no it was oatcake and chunky peanut butter</u>
<u n="607" who="S0086">right <pause dur="short"/> I think you might be losing your mind <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0041">I mean there's dedication and then there's</u>
<u n="609" who="S0169">you're starving yourself it's not good for your brain either</u>
<u n="610" who="S0086">it's not good for your working out ether because you're not putting anything in your body you're just sweating it all out</u>
<u n="611" who="S0041">I had a rice care for breakfast</u>
<u n="612" who="S0086">A rice cake?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0041">two salt and vinegar rice cakes <pause dur="short"/> I usually have yoghurt with oat bran in but I forgot my yoghurt</u>
<u n="614" who="S0169">do you know what I listened to yesterday on the tele it wasn't on the tele <trunc>m</trunc> my friend related to me off the tele? Basically a banana a tin of tuna and a yoghurt takes fifty-five minutes to burn off</u>
<u n="615" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0086">A yoghurt a banana and a tin of tuna?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0169">A yoghurt a banana a tin of tuna fifty-five minutes to burn it off</u>
<u n="619" who="S0041">I like all those things</u>
<u n="620" who="S0086">that's not even bad stuff</u>
<u n="621" who="S0169">no <pause dur="short"/> but you still need to burn it off don't you?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0086">well only if you're losing weight</u>
<u n="623" who="S0169">mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0086">em that's a bit intense though</u>
<u n="625" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0086">em bananas are the worst kind of carbs apparently</u>
<u n="627" who="S0041">the worst kind of fruit you mean?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0086">the worst kind of yeah fruit <pause dur="short"/> cos they're <trunc>re</trunc> they've got loads of carbs in</u>
<u n="629" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> then for lunch I ha d a cup of soup</u>
<u n="630" who="S0169" trans="overlap">but then <pause dur="short"/> bananas should be eaten at lunch time not before <pause dur="short"/> cos of the potassium in them</u>
<u n="631" who="S0086">ah I love them for breakfast though</u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">me too</u>
<u n="633" who="S0169">if you have them for breakfast you give yourself a flash high <pause dur="short"/> you don't need it</u>
<u n="634" who="S0086">yeah that's fine that's fine  that's when I like my highs</u>
<u n="635" who="S0169">you crash</u>
<u n="636" who="S0086">no I like them in the morning</u>
<u n="637" who="S0041">what <unclear/> I had for lunch</u>
<u n="638" who="S0086">what did you have for lunch <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0041">I had a cup of soup</u>
<u n="640" who="S0086">cup of soup <pause dur="short"/> it's not very very exciting</u>
<u n="641" who="S0041">I had something else as well <pause dur="short"/> oh a slice of brown bread with tomatoes on</u>
<u n="642" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="643" who="S0041">and then a cracker before I come home <pause dur="short"/> so I'll be just be eating little things just throughout the day <pause dur="short"/> and I had some a piece of fudge</u>
<u n="644" who="S0086">and a yum <pause dur="short"/> where is my <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0041">yeah it was good <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is I'm alright not eating through the day but when I'm sat then I want to eat more <pause dur="short"/> so if I have a small one of these then I won't feel so bad when I have apricots wheat's later</u>
<u n="646" who="S0086">have you got any Coco Pops left?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0041">mm mm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0086">no?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0041">no they've gone now</u>
<u n="650" who="S0086">what are you going to have for your second dinner?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0041">apricot Wheats</u>
<u n="652" who="S0086">ha <pause dur="short"/> I've run out of Apricot Wheats</u>
<u n="653" who="S0041"><event desc="sound of shock"/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0086">I know I meant to get some more from the Co-op just now and I forgot <pause dur="short"/> like a fool  Like a fool</u>
<u n="655" who="S0041">I need to go to the Co-op</u>
<u n="656" who="S0086">to the Co-op? Really? I don't know <trunc>re</trunc> actually if they even sell them in the Co-op but em</u>
<u n="657" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="658" who="S0086">if you don't mind having a look to see</u>
<u n="659" who="S0046"><unclear/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0086">ah don't even start <pause dur="short"/> no one's voice actually sounds like that</u>
<u n="661" who="S0169">no</u>
<u n="662" who="S0086">it's very false</u>
<u n="663" who="S0169">do you think? I don't think it is <pause dur="short"/> some people just sound like that</u>
<u n="664" who="S0086">no they don't</u>
<u n="665" who="S0041">I think she just</u>
<u n="666" who="S0169">I know a girl in <anon type="place"/> and her voice is exactly the same <pause dur="short"/> and she's got a boyfriend and I was just looking and thinking are you deaf? He's got to be</u>
<u n="667" who="S0041">how the fuck do you put up with that</u>
<u n="668" who="S0169">he's got to be  deaf in one ear do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0086">or she's great in bed</u>
<u n="670" who="S0041">there's also that</u>
<u n="671" who="S0169">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I thought he was queer as well <pause dur="short"/> he's got a  voice</u>
<u n="672" who="S0086">I don't know if that's necessarily the PC term <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0169">sorry <pause dur="short"/> for the dictator <pause dur="short"/> homosexual</u>
<u n="674" who="S0086">oh that's quite a lot of rice <pause dur="short"/> we don't need all that rice <pause dur="short"/> I thought a person had a cup half a cup full of rice</u>
<u n="675" who="S0041">A third of a cupful</u>
<u n="676" who="S0086">right okay that's why <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> in you go</u>
<u n="677" who="S0169">and that that isn't a cup it's a mug</u>
<u n="678" who="S0086">what?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0169">that's a mug</u>
<u n="680" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> are you being pedantic?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0169">just putting it out there</u>
<u n="682" who="S0086">right <pause dur="short"/> in they go <pause dur="short"/> ooh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="683" who="S0041">it's definitely burning my face off right now</u>
<u n="684" who="S0086">are you?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0086">well <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it's very good for you</u>
<u n="687" who="S0041">I'm sure it's just brining some extra extra off</u>
<u n="688" who="S0086">yeah just exfoliating</u>
<u n="689" who="S0041">ah ah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0041">I know I never learn <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> See I hiccup I don't burp <pause dur="short"/> they take the mickey out of me at work now <pause dur="short"/> that's because you're crazy <pause dur="short"/> cos you're crazy</u>
<u n="692" who="S0086">ha <pause dur="short"/> is it Friday yet?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0041">oh I wish <pause dur="short"/> so do you want to go running tomorrow or do you want to go sometime over the weekend?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0086">thanks</u>
<u n="695" who="S0169">can't escape?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0086">huh?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0169">there's no escape</u>
<u n="698" who="S0086">no escape</u>
<u n="699" who="S0041">you can't take the mick out of me though? And you can't shout at me</u>
<u n="700" who="S0169">I won't <pause dur="short"/> it's not like that <pause dur="short"/> I'm encouraging <pause dur="short"/> are you coming for the run?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0086">if you're talking to me the answer is no</u>
<u n="702" who="S0169">oh</u>
<u n="703" who="S0086">mainly because I don't want to hold you up <pause dur="short"/> because I run really slowly and you need to</u>
<u n="704" who="S0041">you won't be holding me up at all</u>
<u n="705" who="S0086">no I will cos I'm rubbish</u>
<u n="706" who="S0041">no believe me you really won't <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where you've got this in your head from <pause dur="short"/> but as far as people who run are concerned I'm like the worst that you get</u>
<u n="707" who="S0086" trans="overlap">no no I am <pause dur="short"/> I'm much slower <pause dur="short"/> no no cos you've been running really quickly <pause dur="short"/> I'm a mile at fourteen minutes I can tell you that</u>
<u n="708" who="S0041">yeah well I can't do it in forty minutes anymore turns out</u>
<u n="709" who="S0086">well</u>
<u n="710" who="S0041">tried it twice on the treadmill I can't  I can't  get better than that</u>
<u n="711" who="S0086">I'll come with you but I won't run at your pace if you need to run faster</u>
<u n="712" who="S0041">I really won't need to run faster <pause dur="short"/> I promise you</u>
<u n="713" who="S0086">you will and I might die <pause dur="short"/> but yeah we could do that <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> what am I doing?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0041">eh is my washing dry? Anybody know?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0086">em I'm going to say yes</u>
<u n="716" who="S0041">I hope yes</u>
<u n="717" who="S0086">I'm going to say yes <pause dur="short"/> if you ask me on a Tuesday I say yes</u>
<u n="718" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I really you know what I really want to watch <pause dur="short"/> intrude</u>
<u n="719" who="S0086">intrude</u>
<u n="720" who="S0041">where is the roast beef?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0086">french <unclear/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0041">that is roasted</u>
<u n="723" who="S0086">I wish I had it on D V B</u>
<u n="724" who="S0041">yeah that would be so good</u>
<u n="725" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="726" who="S0041">it's Putneska <pause dur="short"/> what did you call me?</u>
<u n="727" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0086">I don't speak monkey</u>
<u n="729" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="730" who="S0169">what the fuck are you going on about?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0086">ah it's a brilliant film</u>
<u n="732" who="S0169">what is it?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0086">it's called em <pause dur="short"/> what's it called? The curious</u>
<u n="734" who="S0041"><unclear/> A Series of Unfortunate Events</u>
<u n="735" who="S0086">yes <pause dur="short"/> a Series of Unfortunate Events <pause dur="short"/> exactly what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you mind if I chav some garlic <pause dur="short"/> I will buy some more</u>
<u n="736" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> take some</u>
<u n="737" who="S0086">thank you madam <pause dur="short"/> it's from a children's book and it's hilarious</u>
<u n="738" who="S0041">it's fantastic</u>
<u n="739" who="S0086">it's got Jim Carey in it and anything that he's in <pause dur="short"/> he's amazing</u>
<u n="740" who="S0169">ah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0041">he is the best</u>
<u n="742" who="S0169">yeah he's very funny isn't he?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0086">wow that s pure garlic in my face</u>
<u n="744" who="S0169">it's a lot of garlic</u>
<u n="745" who="S0086">I know I love it <pause dur="short"/> it's really good for you <pause dur="short"/> anti-aging</u>
<u n="746" who="S0169">really?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0169">bit late for that</u>
<u n="749" who="S0086">I don't have a spoon <pause dur="short"/> spoon <pause dur="short"/> spoon</u>
<u n="750" who="S0041">I didn't to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s last weekend did I? No <pause dur="short"/> I was here last weekend</u>
<u n="751" who="S0086">last weekend <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0041">the weekend before I was at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s cos that was Easter</u>
<u n="753" who="S0086">so are you going to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s this weekend?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0041">two weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> so then the weekend before that I was at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> that's three weeks ago</u>
<u n="755" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0041">eh no I'm not</u>
<u n="757" who="S0086">what are you trying to work out love?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0041">how like how long ago it was from the first time I went to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and started walking</u>
<u n="759" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="760" who="S0041">I think we're looking at four weeks</u>
<u n="761" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="762" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> two weeks</u>
<u n="763" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0041">I went two three and a half  three and a half  weeks <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="765" who="S0086">three and a half weeks <pause dur="short"/> yeah that sounds about right <pause dur="short"/>  so lazy aren't they? Lazy ginger lazy garlic</u>
<u n="766" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah garlic done</u>
<u n="767" who="S0086">I put loads <pause dur="short"/> I squeezed about that amount out last tie mans it was really really gingery <pause dur="short"/> it's really strong</u>
<u n="768" who="S0041">see I'm not really a fan of ginger</u>
<u n="769" who="S0086">no but it was nice</u>
<u n="770" who="S0041">I don't understand  I don't understand  it <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? Like it's sweet?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0086">it is sweet yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's nice <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0041">what's that?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0086">right drink <pause dur="short"/> juices <pause dur="short"/> where are the jogging bottoms?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0169">sorry?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0086">I said where are the jogging bottoms?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0169">at home</u>
<u n="777" who="S0086">you managed to put proper clothes on</u>
<u n="778" who="S0169">yes</u>
<u n="779" who="S0086">wow</u>
<u n="780" who="S0169">at least</u>
<u n="781" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="782" who="S0169">do you em</u>
<u n="783" who="S0086">I see it's like that <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0041">I need to go to the  and I think if I  if I  settle down</u>
<u n="785" who="S0086">if you sit you might not ever get up again</u>
<u n="786" who="S0041">might never go</u>
<u n="787" who="S0086">I would have text you mate <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise <pause dur="short"/> what did you need?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0041">oh just some milk and to go to the cash machine</u>
<u n="789" who="S0086">ah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0041">snoozers</u>
<u n="791" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0086"><unclear/> Ah blush <pause dur="short"/> quite frankly</u>
<u n="793" who="S0041">get into be bed and read like <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday right <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got in the bath I got in and I'm sweaty to fuck <pause dur="short"/> really wanted to get in the shower</u>
<u n="794" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s was like oh I'm just about to get in the bath <pause dur="short"/> I was like right okay so I want to get in the bath too and burn my legs off</u>
<u n="796" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0041">so do you want to get in first I was like you can go first fine <pause dur="short"/> I'll have <trunc>some</trunc> something to eat now</u>
<u n="798" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0041">so he goes out <pause dur="short"/> got in a quick shower jumped out and ran the bath <pause dur="short"/> got rid of all the sweat first obviously</u>
<u n="800" who="S0086">obviously yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0041">and then ran the bath <pause dur="short"/> so I get in the bath <pause dur="short"/> reading my book <pause dur="short"/> I was in there for about an hour and a half <pause dur="short"/> didn't realise the time at all</u>
<u n="802" who="S0086">nice</u>
<u n="803" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knocked on the door <pause dur="short"/> em are you okay</u>
<u n="804" who="S0086">oh I'm fine thanks</u>
<u n="805" who="S0041">I thought oh that was nice of her <pause dur="short"/> no I got out the bath she said eh you know you've been in there for aver and hour and half</u>
<u n="806" who="S0086">you're joking</u>
<u n="807" who="S0041">and I was like no <pause dur="short"/> cos I thought she was being nice and I was like oh no I didn't realise the time sorry <pause dur="short"/> that isn't sorry for worrying you</u>
<u n="808" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0041">she said well you know somebody else might want to get in there <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't think cos she eh <trunc>a</trunc> as soon as she said it she closed the bathroom door like the toilet door <pause dur="short"/> and I felt like saying what? So you mean you want to get in bathroom at a time that people aren't all in bed <pause dur="short"/> I thought you only used to shower when everyone else was trying to sleep <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then she didn't even use the shower so I got out the bathroom at nine o'clock <pause dur="short"/> she didn't go in the bathroom at all until quarter past elven <pause dur="short"/> shower goes on <pause dur="short"/> half past eleven she decides to get a shower</u>
<u n="810" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> shit</u>
<u n="811" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what a piss take</u>
<u n="812" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't give a shit</u>
<u n="813" who="S0041">I said well Friday mornings I'm going to make sure we're all up and <unclear/> and then I'm going to turn the music on really loud and wake the fucker up cos it's her day off</u>
<u n="814" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0086">fine</u>
<u n="816" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> won't be here <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> it worse when we wake her up <pause dur="short"/> and I will continue to wake her up every Friday until she gets the message</u>
<u n="817" who="S0086">Good good <pause dur="short"/> so our house will be like a war zone <pause dur="short"/> well the thing is I don't talk to her at all now because I just think I've got nothing to say to you and you're incredibly rude</u>
<u n="818" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="819" who="S0086">so <pause dur="short"/> there's no point</u>
<u n="820" who="S0041">I don't talk to her either <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to continue to take very long baths just to piss her off <pause dur="short"/> as long as nobody else needs the bathroom you know?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0086">at that time</u>
<u n="822" who="S0041">and by anyone else I mean you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that's it</u>
<u n="823" who="S0169">it must be a nightmare</u>
<u n="824" who="S0086">what? This many people in this house?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0086">there's a lot of us <pause dur="short"/> but but it's fine if you respect each other <pause dur="short"/> and no that there's any respect coming from her <pause dur="short"/> they expect everything from us</u>
<u n="827" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0086">ooh cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0041">they're doochy</u>
<u n="830" who="S0086">that's bad</u>
<u n="831" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0086">I've never heard that before</u>
<u n="833" who="S0041">why does she give a shit?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="835" who="S0041">she walks round here like the frigging mother of the house just cos she's old enough to be</u>
<u n="836" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just cos she's an old hen</u>
<u n="837" who="S0041">when's the last time you saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0086">em it's been quite a while I must confess</u>
<u n="839" who="S0041">do you think she's moved out?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0086">I hope so</u>
<u n="841" who="S0041">bye <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
<u n="842" who="S0086">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would have insisted somebody else moves in almost immediately so</u>
<u n="843" who="S0041">do you reckon she'll move <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> back in?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0086">oh hells bells <pause dur="short"/> I hope not <pause dur="short"/> mainly because she smells bad</u>
<u n="845" who="S0041">yeah that's my problem with her <pause dur="short"/> apart from <pause dur="short"/> yeah apart from the smoking thing</u>
<u n="846" who="S0086">and the sisters might come round more often</u>
<u n="847" who="S0041">the sisters</u>
<u n="848" who="S0086">the voice</u>
<u n="849" who="S0041">I've told her  I've told her  before she needs to move a chef in</u>
<u n="850" who="S0086">yeah that need to happen <pause dur="short"/> cos we've seen what happens when you try to cook</u>
<u n="851" who="S0041">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> I' made that chilli how long ago?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0086">weeks ago</u>
<u n="853" who="S0041">three weeks</u>
<u n="854" who="S0086">months</u>
<u n="855" who="S0041">still fine I'm sure</u>
<u n="856" who="S0086">that chilli would survive Armageddon <pause dur="short"/> I'm not joking</u>
<u n="857" who="S0169">are you actually eating that?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0086">it just gets better <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't last weekend <pause dur="short"/> it was the wakened before</u>
<u n="859" who="S0041" trans="overlap">last weekend <pause dur="short"/> weekend before last</u>
<u n="860" who="S0169" trans="overlap">you watched you made it in front of me <pause dur="short"/> are you still eating that?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> easter weekend yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0169">what the fuck what have you been eating? What have you been eating?</u>
<u n="863" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="864" who="S0086">chilli</u>
<u n="865" who="S0041">chilli <pause dur="short"/> nearly every day <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0086">apart from the days when you have a whole chicken</u>
<u n="867" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="868" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0169">yeah the whole chicken</u>
<u n="870" who="S0041">we do eat the whole chicken</u>
<u n="871" who="S0169">yeah yeah well done <pause dur="short"/> you don't need any carbs cos you ate half a chicken</u>
<u n="872" who="S0086">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> that's good that's protein</u>
<u n="873" who="S0041">we ate half a chicken</u>
<u n="874" who="S0086" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0086">and cabbage</u>
<u n="876" who="S0041">and cabbage and broccoli <pause dur="short"/> broccoli</u>
<u n="877" who="S0086">so it was a very healthy dinner apart from the <unclear/> and ice-cream</u>
<u n="878" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0086">ah la la la la</u>
<u n="880" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah la la la la la</u>
<u n="881" who="S0086"><unclear/> here</u>
<u n="882" who="S0169">this is some information for you <pause dur="short"/> just os you know</u>
<u n="883" who="S0086">broadcast</u>
<u n="884" who="S0041">getting ready</u>
<u n="885" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="886" who="S0169">just so you know <pause dur="short"/> protein you you for every two grams of protein you know your body weight?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="888" who="S0169">okay <pause dur="short"/> for every kilo of your body weight</u>
<u n="889" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="890" who="S0169">you can absorb two grams of protein <pause dur="short"/> every two hours <pause dur="short"/> yeah? So just just say for example you can have twenty-eight grams of protein? If you have seventy grams of protein after twenty-eight you're just going to poo it out <pause dur="short"/> it's actually useless to you <pause dur="short"/> yeah no there's no point over indulging in protein <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing</u>
<u n="891" who="S0041">yeah there is cos it will fill you up and you just poo it out</u>
<u n="892" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly you're not  you're not  storing it</u>
<u n="893" who="S0041" trans="overlap">you're not storing it <pause dur="short"/> if you're not storing it that's great isn't it?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0086">it's better than carbs because carbs stick to you</u>
<u n="895" who="S0169">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit of a waste though innit really? You should at least eat a few carbs</u>
<u n="896" who="S0041">I don't think see I understand the I understand this logic but I just can't afford for any extra carbs</u>
<u n="897" who="S0086">the thing is you I think it's you</u>
<u n="898" who="S0169">you need some carbs</u>
<u n="899" who="S0086">you need some</u>
<u n="900" who="S0169">you need carbs to burn off your</u>
<u n="901" who="S0086">but she's having carbs but you're having brown bread you're having a cracker you're having</u>
<u n="902" who="S0041">I had an  I had an  oat cracker <pause dur="short"/> I had a slice of brown bread <pause dur="short"/> I have this</u>
<u n="903" who="S0086">and there's lots of you know fruit and veg that have carbs</u>
<u n="904" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> carbs <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> had an orange today</u>
<u n="905" who="S0169">you always intake carbs after exercise <pause dur="short"/> always</u>
<u n="906" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="907" who="S0169">honestly</u>
<u n="908" who="S0041">I know but I just can't bring myself to</u>
<u n="909" who="S0169">your body goes into starvation <pause dur="short"/> and it just holds on to everything</u>
<u n="910" who="S0041">I I still eat <trunc>e</trunc> enough <pause dur="short"/> I'm not just being silly</u>
<u n="911" who="S0169">I don't know</u>
<u n="912" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I had a shake before I run</u>
<u n="913" who="S0169">I just watched you eat a bowl of cat food <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="914" who="S0086">that's two weeks old</u>
<u n="915" who="S0169">and some rice crackers <pause dur="short"/> you had some rice crackers today <pause dur="short"/> you had a you ate some rice <unclear/> cat food that's probably going straight through you <pause dur="short"/> cos if it's age</u>
<u n="916" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I have some Apricot Wheats later</u>
<u n="917" who="S0086">which is nothing but pure health</u>
<u n="918" who="S0169">no because there's none in the cupboard</u>
<u n="919" who="S0086">pure health <pause dur="short"/> no I haven't got any <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got some</u>
<u n="920" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="921" who="S0169">oh well <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> both walking</u>
<u n="922" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0169"><unclear/> Wheats</u>
<u n="925" who="S0041">I don't think they'd last very long if they shared the wheats</u>
<u n="926" who="S0086">have you seen the size of the box <pause dur="short"/> it's tiny</u>
<u n="927" who="S0041">and I had Coco Pops the day before that <pause dur="short"/> I tell you but do have carbs when I after exercise don't I? I come in and the first thing I do is have a bowl of Coco Pops</u>
<u n="928" who="S0086">coco Pops or MacDonald's</u>
<u n="929" who="S0041">or MacDonald's <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> oops</u>
<u n="930" who="S0086" trans="overlap">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> we fell over</u>
<u n="931" who="S0041">we fell over face first in MacDonald's</u>
<u n="932" who="S0086" trans="overlap">we accidently impaled MacDonald's</u>
<u n="933" who="S0169">Fell on a Big Mac  Big Mac  Choked on a Big Mac</u>
<u n="934" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="935" who="S0086">can you imagine the wound</u>
<u n="936" who="S0041" trans="overlap">are you seeing the irony?</u>
<u n="937" who="S0086">oh so that was your last meat <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah you'd be fucked <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> you piss<unclear/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0041">are you gonna  Are you gonna  eat more broccoli then?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0086">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm just going to chuck it in with the rice</u>
<u n="940" who="S0041">oh fine</u>
<u n="941" who="S0086">I'm not going to eat it raw <pause dur="short"/> although I do like it pretty crunchy</u>
<u n="942" who="S0041">I'm becoming quite quite keen on the broccolis now <pause dur="short"/> I can feel I can see your like likeness of it</u>
<u n="943" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty fun <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty good for you <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> cook my pretties <pause dur="short"/> I am actually starving now <pause dur="short"/> I want to have a shower first <pause dur="short"/> oh well <pause dur="short"/> what time is it?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0041">em</u>
<u n="945" who="S0169">six</u>
<u n="946" who="S0086">six?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0169">fifteen</u>
<u n="948" who="S0086">ah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0041">that's my bedtime <pause dur="short"/> I need to put some shoes on to go to the store don't I?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> are you <unclear/> just drugs <pause dur="short"/> just <unclear/></u>
<u n="951" who="S0169">just vitamins</u>
<u n="952" who="S0086">vitamin <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I really needed that beer <pause dur="short"/> had such a stressful afternoon <pause dur="short"/> it's the first day this morning when I really didn't want to go to work <pause dur="short"/> normally I quite look forward to it <pause dur="short"/> I quite like it <pause dur="short"/> but it's so busy at the moment and I feel quite on my own because my boss is in New York and I'm quite new still <pause dur="short"/> I feel like cos it's so busy if I <unclear/> or something it's going to be really bad <pause dur="short"/> and I had one of those days where everything seems to be wrong or I'm missing something or I'm chasing round <unclear/> The more project that you take on the more chance there is for something to go wrong <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just worried that something is gonna get missed <pause dur="short"/> but it's not my problem really if it does because we've got too much work on <pause dur="short"/> too much work for the number of people <pause dur="short"/> and they're not extending their temporary contracts to people that were here for a few months <pause dur="short"/> there's two people who were here on a six month contract and there not extending them so we're going to be even more fucked <pause dur="short"/> depends is they <unclear/></u>
<u n="953" who="S0169">what is it?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0086"><unclear/> the budget <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's a bit of a pisser</u>
<u n="955" who="S0169">I'm tired <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0086">did you bring my D V B s back?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0169">shit</u>
<u n="958" who="S0086">you've got two of them now</u>
<u n="959" who="S0169">fuck <pause dur="short"/> I haven't watched the other one</u>
<u n="960" who="S0086">Taco Ville</u>
<u n="961" who="S0169">no</u>
<u n="962" who="S0086">it's really good</u>
<u n="963" who="S0169">yeah I've got to get in the mood for it</u>
<u n="964" who="S0086">eggs</u>
<u n="965" who="S0041">home reared</u>
<u n="966" who="S0086">from someone at work?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0041">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has chicken and she brings me the eggs</u>
<u n="968" who="S0086">ah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0041">she's sold them at work for a pound</u>
<u n="970" who="S0086">that's so good</u>
<u n="971" who="S0041">and the money goes to charity too</u>
<u n="972" who="S0086">that's a really good<unclear/> money</u>
<u n="973" who="S0041">I'm volunteering</u>
<u n="974" who="S0086">for what?</u>
<u n="975" who="S0041"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="976" who="S0086">right <pause dur="short"/> what are you going to be doing?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0041">Don't really know yet <pause dur="short"/> helping the people helping old people</u>
<u n="978" who="S0086">helping old people <pause dur="short"/> where?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0041">eh in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="980" who="S0086">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="981" who="S0041">helping all the people <pause dur="short"/> not the <trunc>o</trunc> not the old people <pause dur="short"/> all the people</u>
<u n="982" who="S0086">just everybody</u>
<u n="983" who="S0041">just yeah the people</u>
<u n="984" who="S0086">Cos you're not an ageist</u>
<u n="985" who="S0041">Cos I'm not an ageist <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I volunteered today</u>
<u n="986" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="987" who="S0041">an email went round work and I thought well I should help the people cos I'm pretty lucky</u>
<u n="988" who="S0086">you are pretty pretty nice <pause dur="short"/> like that</u>
<u n="989" who="S0041">and so <pause dur="short"/> then Fiona got really excited <pause dur="short"/> apparently I was the only one that volunteered out of the whole staff of a hundred people <pause dur="short"/> how selfish are they?</u>
<u n="990" who="S0086">shit <pause dur="short"/> they're all going to hell</u>
<u n="991" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's exciting</u>
<u n="992" who="S0086">yey</u>
<u n="993" who="S0041">but I hope I don't have to touch any dirty people but</u>
<u n="994" who="S0086">you might have to touch old dirty people which is much worse</u>
<u n="995" who="S0041">wow no can't do that</u>
<u n="996" who="S0169"><unclear/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0041">I am</u>
<u n="998" who="S0086">this is just in the interim</u>
<u n="999" who="S0041">this is just to do some good in the world in the interim period</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0041">it's only like one day a week or something <pause dur="short"/> you know feed some homeless people or look after some babies and stuff</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0086">look after babies <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that's actually what they do but yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> you might</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1004" who="S0086">I think you need to learn <pause dur="short"/> I think you learn need to learn how to play a brass instrument as well cos they have a band <pause dur="short"/> but you have to be in a band</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0041">no I'm not joining the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm volunteering for <unclear/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah no I think you still have to join the band</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0041">right great <pause dur="short"/> do you have anything that I can borrow?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0086">em</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0041">french Horn</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0086">tuba</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0041">tuba <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> That is what I want to</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0169"><event desc="sound of tuba"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0086">I reckon you're going to be really good at the tuba</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0041">the tuba sounds a bit off</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0086">I <trunc>re</trunc> I think you need to retune</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1019" who="S0086">there's something not quite right there</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0169">Don't <unclear/> really it's</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0086">A piece of shit <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> your jacket</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0041"><event desc="0041 leaves"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0086">isn't it hanging up? Is it in Lola?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<event desc="0086 leaves"/>
<u n="1025" who="S0086"><unclear/> The spring time one</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0169">so has he got  has he got  another job now then?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0086">spring time</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0169">has he how come he's gotten a job for security?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0086">he used to be a security guard</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0169">oh right</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0086">Don't get too excited<unclear/></u>
<u n="1032" who="S0169">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0086">and it actually</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0169"><unclear/> badge or something?</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0086">yeah for ASDAs</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1037" who="S0086">yeah it's not going to go well <pause dur="short"/> well <unclear/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0169">oh no as soon as he going to go for that car <pause dur="short"/> has he got a car too?</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0086">I don't he did have one but I think Penny has got one now</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0169">he's got an SOA license already <pause dur="short"/> but he hasn't</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0086">there's still check</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0169">I work on the doors in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> years ago <pause dur="short"/> and I faked it so I scanned <unclear/> Seriously <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0086">is it that  Is it that  easy to do?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0169">not anymore Not anymore  it's only cos well really the government he eh knew it was fake and he just knew you know now to put em in the front doors but upstairs in the <unclear/> Have you been to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0086">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I've been to <anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> such a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1046" who="S0169">so your day was pretty <unclear/> then?</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0086">it was pretty shit <pause dur="short"/> but d'you know what else I bought in the Coop today?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0169">what's that?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0086">my second favourite thing after Apri Wheats</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0169">crumble</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0086">do you remember they were really nice?</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0169">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0086">two pound off</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0169">oh really?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0086">or one pound thirty off</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0169">bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> bargain</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0086">so toady should have been a really good day <pause dur="short"/> I got paid today and I got pad for some of my recording <pause dur="short"/> so I've got an extra three extra four hundred pounds in my bank account</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0169">paid for some of the recordings?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I should take you out for dinner really</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0169">you <unclear/></u>
<u n="1061" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1062" who="S0086">I should take everyone out for dinner really</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0041">here's your <unclear/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0086">ah let me give you some money</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0041">what's required from the Coop?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0086">em just Apri Wheats <pause dur="short"/> hang on I'll get some cash <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="0086 leaves"/></u>
<u n="1067" who="S0041">I'm <unclear/> for Apri Wheats</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0169">fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> she's paid for the recordings as well</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0041">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0169">what a liberty <pause dur="short"/> we should ask for commission</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1072" who="S0169">she takes the piss</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1074" who="S0169">I whispered things on that as well <pause dur="short"/> I've whispered things on it <pause dur="short"/> they're going to be listening to it thinking</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0041">when you're out of the room</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0169">what's that pervert saying?</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0041">that's quite enough now</u>
<u n="1078" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> left the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1081" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0086">it's true</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1084" who="S0169">so how long have you been  so how long have you been  wetting the bed then?</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Three hundred and sixty-two days</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0086">of my life</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0041">of my life exactly <pause dur="short"/> should you em require anything alternative if there is no Apri Wheats?</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> that's fine I'll just have to take bloody</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0041">what's that?</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0086">what's is it called? Weetabix</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0041">cack</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0086">yeah actually I can't  I can't  cope with Weetabix <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> just something like All Bran <pause dur="short"/> just just Co-op own</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0041">I'll take the phone</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> take the phone that's safe <pause dur="short"/> pretty <pause dur="short"/> I thought I told you that I got paid for them</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0169">no I thought you were doing them for using them for yourself work</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0086">it is for work</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0169">I thought you were using yourself at work <pause dur="short"/> like listening to it and just getting words out of it and I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I have no idea</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> that to <pause dur="short"/> ticket's money passport</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0169">I didn't read</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0086">read read the small print</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0169">no I didn't read anything <pause dur="short"/> I tended to</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0086">well I hope this is nice <pause dur="short"/> it might be a bit dry cos I haven't got a sauce to go on it but you can put more soy sauce on maybe <pause dur="short"/> I had it a few weeks ago and it it was really nice</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0169">it smells actually beautiful</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0086">shit <pause dur="short"/> well I hope so</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0169">that <unclear/> the fish now has been cooked</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1107" who="S0086">what's the matter my love? What have you lost Bertie?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0041">cheers  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> no I've got Bertie <pause dur="short"/> remember that guy</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0086">narrow it down for me</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0041">that had a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1111" who="S0086">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0041">send a <unclear/> text me today</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0086">ooh madam</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0041">yeah and some other one <pause dur="short"/> in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> they must have all had a boring week <pause dur="short"/> I'm not replying to them though</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0086">that was pretty fun</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0041">that's pretty funny <pause dur="short"/> pretty funny <pause dur="short"/> I'm going now bye for ever <pause dur="short"/> do you need anything from Slow-op</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0169">no Slow-op</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0041">okay <pause dur="short"/> bye forever</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0086">bye love thank you</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0041">Cos yesterday it really was slow-op <pause dur="short"/> we used to have a slow-op and we used to have to put like an hour and a half aside just to get a weekly shop</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0086">oh hells</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0041">it was horrendous</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0086">by the Italy</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0041">bye for now</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0086">bye love see you in a bit <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0041">you're welcome <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> it</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0169">thanks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this in a absolutely scrummy</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0086">well you haven't tasted it yet <pause dur="short"/> I hope it is</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0169">going to be fine <pause dur="short"/> bit of soy sauce on the rice <pause dur="short"/> lovely <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0086">you're welcome <pause dur="short"/> take these to move them <pause dur="short"/> you got enough beer left?</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0086">am I going to turn his thing off? Everything? Yes <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="1133" who="S0169">water beach <pause dur="short"/> where I can type in just sitting on a computer all day for pharmacy an online pharmacy <pause dur="short"/> just tying numbers in a stiff like that</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0169">em <pause dur="short"/> but even that says I you need experience blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> a A-levels would be good but not essential <pause dur="short"/> and I said to the bloke I said well have you  have you  seem what they writ there? He said the there's a there's like a thirty day period for this so they wait for all the applications <pause dur="short"/> so I said I'm going to send mine in <pause dur="short"/> and I said there's so many educated people that are unemployed in Cambridge with A levels that will go for this job <pause dur="short"/> I won't get a look in <pause dur="short"/> I'm a realist d'you know what I mean <pause dur="short"/>? I'm optimistic but I'm also a realist <pause dur="short"/> I try to explain to him cos he's trying to get me to send the CV for it <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0086">the guy in the job centre</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0169">no the guy at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> which is the job centre and <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I've been been everywhere <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I mean? I'm trying to put every foot down <pause dur="short"/> so I said to him I said you know I'm not going to apply for it cos I know I'm not going to get it <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I mean? I'm not  I'm not doing that <pause dur="short"/> I had an argument with him before in there <pause dur="short"/> you know? Cos he's I think he just likes to fuck you around</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0086">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> mm hm</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0169">D'you know what I mean? Rather you send loads of CVs out just for the sake of it <pause dur="short"/> well I'm not that sort of person <pause dur="short"/> you know? I'll send a CV off if I think I'm going to get the job <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0169">doesn't make <trunc>a</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> do you think it's a waste of time? I don't like wasting my time</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0169">you know?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> it's so competitive now the jobs market isn't it?</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0169">of course it is</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0086">shit it this tuna is a bit tough</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0169">it tastes lovely</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0086">it's difficult to catch</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0169">what tuna?</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0086">yeah cos you're not supposed to cook it for too long the stakes</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0169" trans="overlap">they're quite <pause dur="short"/> just a pst pst</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0086">it's alright though <pause dur="short"/> I quite like it</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0169">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's tasty <pause dur="short"/> tasty</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0086">like me</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0169">mm</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0086">was you next line</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0169">Sugar tits</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0086">Sugar that was so funny <pause dur="short"/> I was reading it in the kitchen as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was standing next to me <pause dur="short"/> he was facing me though <unclear/> couldn't see <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1159" who="S0169">very very funny looking</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0041">I like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bottom</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0086">mm hm</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0169">it looks a bit like a mushroom</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0086">yeah it's a bit weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0169">it's a very strange <unclear/></u>
<u n="1165" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0169">it would be very funny to see that naked <pause dur="short"/> like I'm trying to figure it out <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0086">yeah cos she's got good legs <pause dur="short"/> so I don't think there's much fat there <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's saggy I just don't think there's anything there</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0169">mm <pause dur="short"/> your arse for that matter is really nice</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0086">it's massive <pause dur="short"/> I could suction some of mine into hers</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0169">black black men could go mental over your arse</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0086">they have done yeah</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0169">yeah <pause dur="short"/> of course they would</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0086">what was I going to say? Can't remember</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0169">they have done yeah <pause dur="short"/> ooh</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0086">it's alright</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0169">beautiful</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1178" who="S0169">so he's not working for the insulation company any more then?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0086">well that's it's a guy he knows through his mum and who was really rubbish about letting him  he had work cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is not qualified in anything <pause dur="short"/> so he just had work when he could l get it really</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0169">right yeah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0086">so this job is a bit more stability but it's only twenty hours a week so if work comes up with the insulation guy he'll go and do that as well try and supplement</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0169">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what I was trying to think about doing <pause dur="short"/> I applied for the that job in the cleaning company anyway</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0086">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0169">I done it yesterday</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0169">did I tell you?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0169">did I see you yesterday?</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0086">mm mm</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0169">no I <unclear/> Get a foot I the door there <pause dur="short"/> I found out in a couple of days whether or not I've been put on the shortlist again <pause dur="short"/> d'you know it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0086">so where's this?</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0169">when I first left school I'd walk into <pause dur="short"/> walk in walk to anywhere knock on the door <pause dur="short"/> have you got a job? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? That's what it was like</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0086">yeah but there's so many people unemployed now</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0169">I know</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0086">that's why my parents they keep going on at me <pause dur="short"/> you shouldn't em</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0169">never give up your job</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what they say</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0169">find another one first</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0086">well I want to go away</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0169">what travel? Where do you want to go? India?</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0086">I'd quite like to go to India but only short term <pause dur="short"/> cos I think it would be crazy <pause dur="short"/> it could be a real head fuck</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0169">you need to get em get qualified so you can work for</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0086">hello my love <pause dur="short"/> em could I please have em <pause dur="short"/> is there like an all All Bran or something like that? Oh like the Branflakes? Oh <pause dur="short"/> lines <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's pretty boring but I think I'll probably go for the old Branflakes and ta least it's safe and it's not going to have bits in it <pause dur="short"/> can I just have the small box please love? <trunc>O</trunc> of of of Bran flakes <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>r</trunc> bran Branflakes <pause dur="short"/> em yeah just just the Co-op ones <pause dur="short"/> it's fine <pause dur="short"/> oh okay well that's fine <pause dur="short"/> yes see that's <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I like it <pause dur="short"/> yeah? Oh I need that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> all bran Branflakes <pause dur="short"/> those ones <pause dur="short"/> is that Co-op own? Ah sounds a winner <pause dur="short"/> thanks mate <pause dur="short"/> are you going to have the em fake Special K <pause dur="short"/> are you going to have enough money? Okay <pause dur="short"/> brill <pause dur="short"/> thanks mate <pause dur="short"/> see you soon <pause dur="short"/> bye <pause dur="short"/> there's no Apri Wheats</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0169">oh <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1205" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0169">yeah you should get qualified for working for Red Cross or something</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0086">I was thinking about doing English as a foreign language <pause dur="short"/> you know teaching</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0169">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0169">I got a couple of <unclear/> friends who are going to do that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know the ones that live next door but one <pause dur="short"/> she can't find a job cos they've been in university for the last two or three years <pause dur="short"/> at <anon type="place"/> and all that <pause dur="short"/> they're getting they're going to get qualified but there's an it's a useless qualification to them <pause dur="short"/> because they know they're not going to get jobs so they're going to go traveling and teach English <pause dur="short"/> I think they're talking about going to Korea</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0086">well it's a good idea lots of people <trunc>d</trunc> lots of people do it <pause dur="short"/> I just don't think I'd be very patient</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0169">patient</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0086">if that rice is really boring don't eat it</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0169">no it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> I'm eating it aren't I?</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't want you to be polite</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0169">soy sauce <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll see  we'll see  I just want to go and have some adventures</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0169">I don't blame you <pause dur="short"/> you only live once don't you? You're only on this planet for a certain amount of time <pause dur="short"/> just go an experience it and enjoy the time</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0086">mm hm</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0169">perhaps have memories if you live long enough <pause dur="short"/> if you don't at least you enjoyed yourself</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0086">that's the idea</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0169">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but garlicky <pause dur="short"/> hot <pause dur="short"/> how can yours be hot? Cos you put mine I the freezer</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0086">is it cold?</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0169">no just <unclear/> it wasn't that hot</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0086">just <unclear/> mouth off from the middle</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0169">ah</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0169">liberty</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0086">what did you say?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0169">I washed my clothes and stuff in that</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0086">I'll listen to it again tomorrow</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0169">I would if I was you</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0169">so are you going to take it up the arse tonight then?</u>
<u n="1235" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1236" who="S0086">you ben thinking about your fantasies again <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0169">not at all <pause dur="short"/> you're always grabbing hold of it and sticking it up there yourself</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0086"><unclear/> I'm a lady</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0169">I'm a lady don't you know</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> this is going to sound a bit strange but did you take the kids to Aldi on Friday to go food shopping?</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0169">I did <pause dur="short"/> why?</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0086">Cos my one of my good friends from work she lives she's the one that lives opposite you <pause dur="short"/> monday morning she's like I think I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with his kids in Aldi cos obviously I talk about you <pause dur="short"/> I'd obviously said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s go the kids this weekend <unclear/> Like some passing comment I hadn't thought about <pause dur="short"/> she said what are you doing? Are you seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? I said no <pause dur="short"/> and then she's like I swear from the description I saw him in Aldi <pause dur="short"/> and I was like I can't have described him that well <pause dur="short"/> like how would you know <pause dur="short"/> she was like I I'm absolutely positive and I stalked him around Aldi <pause dur="short"/> go and ask him if here was some girl who keep staring at him <pause dur="short"/> and I was like I'm not going to say that to him because he's going to think I'm mental <pause dur="short"/> he's going to think I talk about him all the time <pause dur="short"/> but now you've got to ask him it's like okay fine <pause dur="short"/> and obviously I didn't ask on Monday because I thought that you'd think I was mental <pause dur="short"/> but today she was speaking to me again she was like did you ask him? I said no I don't want to ask him</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0169" trans="overlap">yeah I was in Aldi with them cos I just tried to get them it it was a other journey</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0086">well she was saying what's the name of his kids and I couldn't remember the names of the girls <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>cou</trunc> could remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1245" who="S0169" trans="overlap">callum <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0086">and what's the other one called?</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0169"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1248" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> and em I was saying yeah because he want to take his kids there because he doesn't know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> eats she's really fussy <pause dur="short"/> and she was like like you could see it was all the dads who had their kids for the weekend <pause dur="short"/> they're all going do you like tuna? Do you like this? Do you like this? Do you like this? She said it was really really funny <pause dur="short"/> she said that you'd smiled at her or something I don't know <pause dur="short"/> she said you seem really nice <pause dur="short"/> but I dunno <pause dur="short"/> weird anyway <pause dur="short"/> so and then she said that she followed you all the way home cos obviously you live opposite each other</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0086">so it's a bit weird</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0169">she followed me all the way home?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0086">well she lives opposite your house so</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0169">bloody hell</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0086">it's a bit weird isn't it? Like how she would have seen like known it was you from my description <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what I must have said <pause dur="short"/> I said well you know <pause dur="short"/> small ferrety</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0169" trans="overlap">she must have been spying on me for a while <pause dur="short"/> yeah cheers</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0086">I don't think she was spying on you <pause dur="short"/> she just seems <pause dur="short"/> she was absolutely convinced that it was you</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0169">what does she look like?</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> brown hair to about here <pause dur="short"/> like five five <pause dur="short"/> curvy <pause dur="short"/> she has a black rain mac <pause dur="short"/> and a sort of orangy sparkley scarf</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0169">no <pause dur="short"/> was she with anybody herself?</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> she was on her own <pause dur="short"/> she was <unclear/> must buy beer <pause dur="short"/> she said that you did smile at her</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0169">if she was looking at me I probably did</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0086">you probably thought why the fuck is that girl staring at me</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0169">I just smile at people if they look at me <pause dur="short"/> try to be just polite and be nice do you know what I mean</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0086">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit weird though</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0169">you need to show me a picture of her <pause dur="short"/> you must have a picture of here on your phone</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0086">I can show you on Facebook</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0169">yeah here you are <pause dur="short"/> I want to know who this spy is</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0086">spy <pause dur="short"/> you think  You think  that I've sent her out</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0169" trans="overlap">is a spy <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> bloody hell it's a bit canny wannit that he knows I was in Aldi <pause dur="short"/> she never she <trunc>ne</trunc> she's never actually seen me before <pause dur="short"/> maybe you showed her a picture</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0086">that was really weird</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0169">had you showed her a picture of me <pause dur="short"/> have you?</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0086">from where? I don't have any photos of you</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0169">oh like I thought you might have took her on the Badoo site and showed her <pause dur="short"/> r did you not mention online dating</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0086">no I told her <pause dur="short"/> she knows pretty much everything really <pause dur="short"/> about me <pause dur="short"/> she's we're really similar <pause dur="short"/> I feel really lucky to have net her actually because we met on the same day we started work on the same day <pause dur="short"/> and we're really similar characters <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice to find someone that you get on with really <trunc>we</trunc> really well</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0169">yeah you bunch off each other sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> I like that myself <pause dur="short"/> when I meet someone <pause dur="short"/> I I <unclear/> my barber <pause dur="short"/> I've been friends with my barber <pause dur="short"/> I'm always going there sitting there chatting to him you know <pause dur="short"/> he's a lovely</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0086">just hanging out?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0169">lovely fellah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought he was younger he seems like he seems he look about twenty-two but she's twenty-nine you know?</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0086">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1279" who="S0169">mm</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0086">you alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0041">doesn't fit in the fridge hole</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0169">he has ADHD <pause dur="short"/> and he and we bounce off each other</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0041">fake special K</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0086">amazing <pause dur="short"/> how much do I owe you cos that's probably more than two pounds</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0041">it was only two pound twenty-nine</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0086">oh I'll get you the <pause dur="short"/> what is this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0041">I think I've left it there</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> the pixies</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0041">the pixies leave it there</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0086">thanks mate <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> am I going to look like Kate Moss when I eat this yeah?</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0086">amazing <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0169">Kate Moss is minging</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0086">well I just want her body really</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0169">why?</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0086">actually she's got cellulite hasn't she?</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0169">she's awful <pause dur="short"/> honest to god <pause dur="short"/> no bloke fancies that</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0086">well probably her fellah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0169">that's cos she's Kate Moss</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Kate Moss you can just eat some burgers</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0169">that's cos <pause dur="short"/> that's because she's Kate Moss</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0086">those <unclear/> burgers <unclear/> crack</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0169">she only skinny <pause dur="short"/> she eats yeah basically yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's on coke <pause dur="short"/> probably chase the dragon <pause dur="short"/> smokes loads of fags and weed and hardly eat because of her drug addict <pause dur="short"/> that's why she's so slim</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0086">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> I could do that  I could do that</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0169">let's get a party going then <pause dur="short"/> get the lines on</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0041">my em a friend of mine started having speed for breakfast <pause dur="short"/> I think I don't know if she's still doing it</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0086">as a lifestyle choice? Just for fun? Shits and giggles?</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0041">just to lose weight <pause dur="short"/> so every morning before she went to work speed for breakfast</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0086">is that normal?</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0041">em she used to be a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1314" who="S0169">it would work</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0041">it works</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0169">look <trunc>e</trunc> used they used to sell it <pause dur="short"/> they used to <trunc>ba</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> my my friends dad when I was my friend's mum when we were sixteen we used to do speed <pause dur="short"/> and his <trunc>mu</trunc> a <trunc>mu</trunc> his mum sort of liked clocked <pause dur="short"/> she goes are you two on speed? And we were we got all nervous <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? She goes listen when I was young we used to buy it from the pharmacy crush it up and crush it up and sniff it in five pounds notes <pause dur="short"/> don't call me don't make me out to be my name is not my cunt <pause dur="short"/> she said <pause dur="short"/> really like put it on us like you know <pause dur="short"/> scared the life out of us <pause dur="short"/> she said we used to do it really young</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0086" trans="overlap">she sounds like a charmer</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0169">yeah she was a bit <pause dur="short"/> she's from a place called March <pause dur="short"/> ever heard of it?</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0169">it's like they've got six toes and all that there <pause dur="short"/> and you know</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0086">six toes</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0169">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they used to buy it out of chemists and stuff years ago and crush the tablets up</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0041">they used to put it in diet tablets until not long ago</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0169" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0086">mm?</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0169" trans="overlap">yeah and they used to crush the tablet up and sniff them</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0041">it's only the last twenty years that they're not allowed to do it anymore</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0169">mm</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0041">you used to be able to get speedo prescription when my like when our parents were our age <pause dur="short"/> you used to get it prescribed <pause dur="short"/> it's summat <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember the name of it now cos it's they've banned it</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0169">amphetamine</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0169">amphetamine sulphate</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0041">now you can get another version of it <pause dur="short"/> like Centime is legal</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0086">Cos they're highly addictive though aren't they Dieting tablets</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> centime is legal but it's not as good as</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0169">speed</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0041">the real one</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0169">how do you know?</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0041">I wouldn't know</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0169">you used to chew gum when you were younger</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0041">no I'm just surmising</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0169">that was really nice that was</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0086">I'm glad you enjoyed it</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0086">but boring</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0169">no it was nice <pause dur="short"/> not boring at all <pause dur="short"/> don't put yourself down</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0086">well I like boring food</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1351" who="S0086">the tuna is nice though</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0169">mm <pause dur="short"/> I liked it</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> what do I need? I think I need more beer?</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0169">do you want me to get one? Was that  Was that  a massive hint then?</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0086">it was a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will you get me some more beer please?</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0169">are you having a nice tea?</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0086">contraband tea</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0041">contraband tea</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0086">because it's not it's liberated</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0041">it's liberated</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0169">really where from?</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0086">from my office</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0169">ah</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0041">I'm going to liberate us some more form my office cos I'm the first one in tomorrow cos I think I will be</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0169">do you liberate the toilet rolls from work as well?</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0086">no but that's a brilliant idea <pause dur="short"/> I can't though cos it's not toilet rolls it's like a holder</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no I can't</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0169">dispenser thing</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0169">dispenser</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0041">I did think of <unclear/> it <pause dur="short"/> and actually one of them at the moment is unlocked</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0169" trans="overlap"><unclear/> dispenser</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0086">oh and they're locked <pause dur="short"/> devastating <pause dur="short"/> I can get contraband sweetener <pause dur="short"/> goes behind the bin please</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0169">behind the bin?</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> until someone takes it out for recycling <pause dur="short"/> the can opener is on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cupboard by the sink</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0169">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1379" who="S0086">have you heard from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> not since the weekend</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0086" trans="overlap">not since the weekend</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0086">probably best is it?</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0041">yeah I think so too</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0086">thank you</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0169">thank you</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0041">I find myself getting a bit hooked when I speak to him <pause dur="short"/> like we watched The Proposal at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that before?</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it was funnier than I thought it was going to be</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0041">yeah it really made me laugh <pause dur="short"/> it thought it was going to be shit</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0086">yeah I had really low expectation which I think is why I enjoyed it because it is a bit shit <pause dur="short"/> but if you're expecting it to be really rubbish then everything else is a bonus</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0041">there's quite a few bits that I really laughed out loud</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0086">I like the bit where they run out of the shower <pause dur="short"/> you're fucking naked <pause dur="short"/> why are you naked?</u>
<u n="1393" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1394" who="S0041">I like it when she's throwing the dog in the air</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1396" who="S0041">take the dog <pause dur="short"/> em but yeah it was <pause dur="short"/> you know at the end when she kind of gets a <unclear/> and she's like I forgot I'd forgotten what it was like to have a real family</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0041">and the granny gives her that necklace <pause dur="short"/> it really like choked me up <pause dur="short"/> cos <unclear/> Grandma was trying to give me jewellery <pause dur="short"/> and obviously wouldn't take it <pause dur="short"/> but she used to say like say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know if you ever propose to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then I want you to propose with this ring</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0086">oh god</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0086">well it it is hard watching stuff like that and not comparing it to your own life <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the only serious relationship you have to look at your own life and think what would've happened if</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0041">I mean it would have been crazy if like I know really that I would have ended up with his face off</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0086">it's usually when you're on your won that you sort <trunc>o</trunc> sort of think oh if we'd stayed together we would be that couple <pause dur="short"/> like when I look at Will I think if we'd stayed together I would co-own a house I'd probably have a baby <pause dur="short"/> but I'd be living in Hastings and I really we would really one of us would be dead</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0041">yeah pretty much</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0086">but you do it do it makes you evaluate your own life</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0041">I felt a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0169">with an ex?</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0086">you're not doing it right <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0169">never do do I ever can do anything right as far as you're concerned <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0086">stop it</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0169"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1412" who="S0041">I'm quite glad I haven't heard from the Matt</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0086">oh he's gone quiet has he?</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0041">yeah so</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0086">he's such a toenail</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0041">isn't he?</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0041">he's such a retard so</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0041">last time I heard from him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was at the weekend and I haven't heard from em Chrissie and then<unclear/> this week</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0086">Good for a bit of distraction</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0041">no I don't know if I can be arsed <pause dur="short"/> and oh my god I have a a big conference in in two weeks and turns out the fucking audio visual company that <unclear/> hired to come in and deck the place out is a stupid absolute audio visual where the child works <unclear/></u>
<u n="1423" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so and they're coming in to bass to do a and set up and set up and make sure things are good and then they'll come in and actually <unclear/> for the event itself</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0086">that's a bit awkward</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0041">em <pause dur="short"/> so that's going to be fun</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0086">I think you might me contract some sort of horrible disease <pause dur="short"/> malaria</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> I hear that's on the rise</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0086">there's definitely mozzies out now so</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0041">I think I may have a swift word with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saw my face drop when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said the name of the audio visual company I was like oh fuck <pause dur="short"/> he was like what? I was like I'll tell you later <pause dur="short"/> so I might be able to get him to just</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> be the buffer</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0041">yeah usually <pause dur="short"/> we do a bit of a trade-off and usually I'm the trade hat I get is I have to do his wedding appointments</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0041">Cos he hates that so I'm clearly accepting another wedding</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0086">unless they've got a <trunc>re</trunc> you know it's a bigger company than you realise and the chance of it being him is small</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0041">are pretty high</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0169">what is it you do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0041">I arrange conferences and wedding for a hotel</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0169">what you work in a hotel?</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just in the back so I don't have to deal with all the people</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0169"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1442" who="S0041">then they just ring up and tell me what they want and then I give them advice and then if they don't like it I negotiate it or say no fuck off this is what it costs</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0041">and then they come in or fly in and arrange stuff and have a look round <pause dur="short"/> I show them round the hotel show them all the bedrooms and then just sign the contract and then I basically do all of it like take payment for it send them the bills and like profile the<unclear/> Do everything so that before they arrive the week before we have like a meeting with the whole hotel <pause dur="short"/> so the manager of every department comes and I have to go we have to go through each event that we've got coming each day and tell them all everything that we've arranged <pause dur="short"/> so like if we've got a wedding we have to go through it all and say you know you're going to be doing this <pause dur="short"/> you're going to be doing this foods and this time so chef says he needs this and then when they come then I stand there <pause dur="short"/> hello nice to meet you I'm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> lovely to put a face to the name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> and then I smile and then that's it <pause dur="short"/> and then they go home and never say thanks</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0169">oh so I've got the idea that you like set the tables and all that</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0041">oh no we don't have to set the tables</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0169">with all the confetti round them you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0086">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0041">no I tell somebody else how the table is supposed to be set so they they arrange the <unclear/> with me and I hand over to operations and say okay so we need this okay so we need this many tables for this many people</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0086">she's the planner</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0041">I'm the planner</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0169">yeah you're the brains behind it all sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0041">Don't know if it takes much brains to do that</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0169">you you you're the you relay the messages</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0041">yeah I relay the messages and I sort out the money <pause dur="short"/> that's about it</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0169">that's different innit?</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0086">if you like weddings</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0041">huh?</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0086">if you like weddings</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0086">do you get to go to all the weddings and all that</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0041">I have to host them <pause dur="short"/> so I have to be the person that says please welcome the bride and groom and</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0169">ah really?</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0041">all that crap <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0169">cool</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0041">hate it</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0169">that would be so funny</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had never been to a wedding</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0041">I have to be the person that does the music for when they walk down the aisle and I'd never been to a wedding before <pause dur="short"/> I still haven't <pause dur="short"/> I've only been to the ones that I've arranged</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0169">at least you know what the crack is</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1473" who="S0169">at least you know what you want now on your own wedding day</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0086">none of that</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> none of the above <pause dur="short"/> except the dress <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna have a dress</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0086">just parade around the house in it <pause dur="short"/> look at me  Look at me</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1478" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> have you actually got enough money to live on for the rest of the month</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0041">that's not an option so it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0086">what <trunc>ha</trunc> was was your card rejected for for a reason?</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0041">em no</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0086">is it because you've got no money? Because it which case I can happily wait until the end of the month <pause dur="short"/> it's not a problem</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0086">are you sure? Are you alright? Okay</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0041">it's fine <pause dur="short"/> I won't <unclear/></u>
<u n="1486" who="S0086">em</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0041">that's fun so that's why I need a new job</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0086">that is why you need a new job</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0041">I have to do a hell of a lot for the pittance that they pay me</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0086">it's <trunc>ju</trunc> it's just ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> you're the salaries that they offer there versus what you actually do <pause dur="short"/> considering it's such an important day in somebodies life</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0041">well considering that some of the contracts are in a thirty grand and I don't get to see a penny of it</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1493" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1494" who="S0086">it should be commission</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it should be actually commission based <pause dur="short"/> cos we have to fight for a lot of the business</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0041">Cos they'll quote us and they'll quote all the other hotels and so we have to <pause dur="short"/> a lot of it comes through agencies and they get ten per cent commission <pause dur="short"/> we don't get any commission</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0086">Jesus</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0169">you should do if you  if you  got if you're competing you should get commission <pause dur="short"/> simple as that</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they say that it's reactive sales not active sales that</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0041">I don't qualify for it <pause dur="short"/><unclear/></u>
<u n="1504" who="S0169">I wouldn't be bothered then <pause dur="short"/> I'd be lie yeah yeah d'you know what? You're better off going to this hotel because they've got a better function room <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I mean? Don't come here</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's when they go eh goodbye <pause dur="short"/> you're fired with regret <pause dur="short"/> you're fired</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0041">it is with regret that we are going to have to let you go <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I can have? <unclear/></u>
<u n="1507" who="S0169">get your stinky feet off my</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0086">my what?</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0169">stinky feet <pause dur="short"/> are you going to get in the shower?</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0041">right I'm going to read my book again</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0086">ice pops</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0041">ice pops <pause dur="short"/> ice pop time</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0086">enjoy</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0169">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I want to see this spy please?</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0086">oh he's talking to me</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0169">ah <pause dur="short"/> if I em <pause dur="short"/> if I fall asleep have a nice eve</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Alright mate see you later</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0169">see you</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0041">bye</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0169">Don't forget tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> no excuses</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0041">no excuses <pause dur="short"/> I'm there</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0086">right <pause dur="short"/> not you <pause dur="short"/> oh my god  Oh my god I've got five notifications on Facebook <pause dur="short"/> this is how often I go on here <pause dur="short"/> I've returned from Africa <pause dur="short"/> who is she? Em right not you <pause dur="short"/> search search  Doctor <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't actually know how many photos she's got on here?</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0169">kid doctor?</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0086">em PhD yeah</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0169">oh really? Smart one then</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0169">smarter than you</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0086">much smarter than me</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0169">no I'd want to see a picture without a bit of paper in front of her face <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1530" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> alright well it's very difficult <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't really do photos <pause dur="short"/> that's her getting her <trunc>doc</trunc> her PhD</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0169">when you say across the road</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0086">you know those new flats that are two tory houses opposite <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> on the other side of the road</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0169">yeah</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0086">those <pause dur="short"/> she's number one</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0169">brand new ones</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0086">brand new ones <pause dur="short"/> she's the first one</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0169">wait until I see her</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0086">why?</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0169">I want to say oi you spy</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0086">just don't say it in a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1541" who="S0169">start egging her windows</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0086">why? Ha ha <pause dur="short"/> that's my friend's little girl</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0169">ah <pause dur="short"/> she looks like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1544" who="S0086">funny that <pause dur="short"/> she is so cute <pause dur="short"/> how does this work?</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0169">they're growing aren't they?</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> are you just flicking them?</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0169">yep <pause dur="short"/> you should stick them outside</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0086">it's too cold at night too cold</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0169">bring them in</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0086">well I need to report it I think <pause dur="short"/> I think that's why it's em a bit sad <pause dur="short"/> I think that's what I need to to do</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0169">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0086">hello</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0041">alright <pause dur="short"/> a nice healthy dinner</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0086">yah <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm in your way</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0041">have wheat flakes did you?</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0086">not for dinner</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0086">they're for breakfast <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> I suppose one of us needs to wash up</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0169">I'll wash up while you get in the shower <pause dur="short"/> how does that sound?</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0086">sounds perfect <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> those go in the cupboard <pause dur="short"/> can you do the washing up?</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0169">the bollocks</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1563" who="S0169">aren't you having that tuna?</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0086">no it's hard <pause dur="short"/> you have it for me</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0169">it's gone <pause dur="short"/> it's the first time I've had <trunc>tu</trunc> tuna steaks</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0086">yeah I only had them <pause dur="short"/> that's the second time <pause dur="short"/> d'you know at Aldi <pause dur="short"/> two ninety-nine for five steaks <pause dur="short"/> really really good I just keep them in the freezer defrost them when I need them</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0169">you're shitting me</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0086">ah no I'm being serious <pause dur="short"/> so good for two ninety-nine <pause dur="short"/> so cheap at Aldi <pause dur="short"/> it's my favourite thing <unclear/> Apart from Apri Wheats obviously <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I can get Apri Wheats in Aldi cos I haven't been for a while</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0169">I imagine you can they've got all sorts of shit in there</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0086">mm?</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0169">I imagine you can they've got all sorts of shit in there</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0086">but they do their own things</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0169">it is a bit chilly but it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1574" who="S0086">it is a bit chilly <pause dur="short"/> the flavour's nice yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was so easy wasn't it? Garlic ginger and dark soy sauce</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0169">mm <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0086">oi</u>
</body>
</text>
