<text id="S46J">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:14</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Kitchen, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Obstacle course race, doing new things, being fit and attractive, a book called Witch Wars, dressing up as Peter Pan for a school assembly</topics>
		<activity>Family talking about obstacle course races</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0653">so I just wanted to tell you guys about the fact that I have done an obstacle course race today which is the first time I've ever done one and I did it all on my own and I'm very proud and it was five kilometres and I got very muddy and very wet there were lots of things to jump through and under and over and climb up erm but mainly it was very muddy and I got a medal at the end which is the first sporting medal I have ever received in my entire life so there you are it just shows you that even at the age of thirty-nine you can still like achieve new things erm and as I was saying to you before I have a special one just for kids in September which is a mini version of it and I totally want you guys to do it what is your opinion <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0655">well I think it should be a small one cos it should be for kids and grown-ups cos not all grown-ups are as fit as you</u>
<u n="3" who="S0653">do you know that's a totally valid point and in fact one of my friends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is the horror writer who you know of he is desperate to do something erm like that but he is very unfit now in fact it was a really relaxed race today and there were people who were quite old erm and lots of people were just walking it but one of the people erm injured themselves going up the hay bale because it was too difficult so I completely agree with you and I in fact I did say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he was like oh it looked like so much fun and I really want to go but I can't cos I'm so unfit and that's what I said to him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said take your daughters to the one on that the child-friendly one and cos you have to go around with them so if I if you guys both go then I have to go around with you of course and it'll be lots of fun erm and that that's a way of him seeing what he can do and also just seeing what it's like and then making him less scared cos it was a bit scary driving there on my own this morning obviously I didn't have anyone else to go with and I just thought gosh what is it going to be like? you know I just didn't have any I was I was really nervous but now I've done one I totally want to do heaps and heaps more and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is doing quite a scary one in September the Spartan Race and that's really full on and they've got a fire and stuff in it but I'm now thinking do you know what? I think I'm gonna have a go cos at the end of the day it's gonna be no more than an hour and a half of my life and if I can't do you know all of the obstacles it doesn't really matter but it just made me realise today getting up those hay bales and how easy it was that I'm actually really quite strong so I can do the running and I can do the pulling up of the arm stuff so I reckon I've got a good chance of succeeding that so I'm gonna give it a go <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what are your thoughts?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0654">I think</u>
<u n="5" who="S0653" trans="overlap">do you want yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0654">you should do it mum</u>
<u n="7" who="S0653">the Spartan one?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0653">yeah do you think I'll manage to succeed a little bit</u>
<u n="10" who="S0654" trans="overlap">also yeah and also you might be the only girl who has ever done it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0653">oh no <trunc>ha</trunc> girls have done it before erm and I've always looked at their photographs and thought wow they look really fit but do you know what? I'm actually really fit</u>
<u n="12" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0653">I am not like attractive fit if that's what you mean</u>
<u n="14" who="S0654">you are</u>
<u n="15" who="S0653">I am obviously attractive fit as well erm but what erm what are your thoughts <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on you doing the muddy one?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0654">woo hoo mud</u>
<u n="17" who="S0653"><trunc>be</trunc>because normally you don't like getting dirty and that's my only issue but you will literally be covered from your nose to your toes you have to jump into</u>
<u n="18" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mud</u>
<u n="19" who="S0653">huge muddy muddy muddy deep puddles like Peppa Pig and my</u>
<u n="20" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0653">I don't know if you noticed but my trainers are on the washing line I had to wash my trainers in the washing machine cos they were absolutely covered in mud</u>
<u n="22" who="S0654">I didn't see them</u>
<u n="23" who="S0653" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="24" who="S0655" trans="overlap">did you have to wash the rest was the rest of your clothes?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0653">I had to wash everything everything everything everything they were so disgusting</u>
<u n="26" who="S0655" trans="overlap">even your eyelashes?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0653">do you know what? I had a big shower and I I was in the shower for ages and I thought thank goodness I've sorted out and then I was getting dressed and I noticed that I still had had loads of mud on my back</u>
<u n="28" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0653">cost it's so kind of soaked in cos you do spend all of it totally submerged in mud</u>
<u n="30" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mum did you did you get mud on the thing here?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0653">the vagina?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0653">er I don't think well probably cos I was wearing very short shorts I was wearing pants as well obviously</u>
<u n="34" who="S0654">did you get dirty?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0653">that everything got completely muddy</u>
<u n="36" who="S0655" trans="overlap">did the shorts look like pants on you?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0653">well you I haven't <trunc>s</trunc>shown you a photo no they just looked really really really really muddy</u>
<u n="38" who="S0654">but like the pants are they muddy? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0653">they are super muddy so you have to wear old clothes that you don't mind getting trashed cos they will be destroyed so I wore my old pair of trainers and I wore an old sports bra and an old top and an old pair of shorts and they</u>
<u n="40" who="S0655" trans="overlap">will they die?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0654">er mum I need</u>
<u n="43" who="S0655">would they like go poof?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0653">they well the sports bra was white and now it is still looking a little bit muddy even though it's washed so it's it's but the trainers have come up fine but you do well what I was also</u>
<u n="45" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I I need to get some more shorts</u>
<u n="46" who="S0653">you need to get some okay yes you do that's true well you need to get PE type shorts for this anyway but yes you do need to get some what I was also thinking was that when your Brownies has finished <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or in the summer holidays I want to start and there is no ballet I would if you were okay with me doing this if it's on a weekend when I've got you guys I want to go back to the fortitude fitness centre where they do obstacle course practice and you could watch me go around or you could come around with me</u>
<u n="47" who="S0654">okay</u>
<u n="48" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah I think watching you go around something no</u>
<u n="49" who="S0654">okay</u>
<u n="50" who="S0655">doing it with you booyah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and mum</u>
<u n="53" who="S0653">so is that hang on there is that big thing watery thing to jump in <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0654">can we do Witch Wars can we talk about Witch Wars now?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0653">erm but hang on no but you definitely for sure definitely want to do the thing in September <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0655">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0655">can we talk a bit about your party?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0653">well no no let's talk about Witch Wars what do you want to say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0654" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="61" who="S0653">this is a book isn't it?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0655">it's a really good one</u>
<u n="63" who="S0653" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="64" who="S0654">I've <trunc>orig</trunc> I've just I've read this kind of a long time though <unclear/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="66" who="S0654">and shall I tell you what it's about?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0653">yes please</u>
<u n="68" who="S0654">it's about a girl who doesn't have any parents but was found in the sink that means</u>
<u n="69" who="S0653">found in the sink?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0654">she was found in the sink</u>
<u n="71" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="72" who="S0654">which means somebody must of sent her up there</u>
<u n="73" who="S0653">must have not must of then</u>
<u n="74" who="S0654" trans="overlap">must somebody</u>
<u n="75" who="S0653">sent her up there?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="77" who="S0653">must have sent her up there do you mean into a sink?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no into the human world</u>
<u n="80" who="S0653">well what I don't know anything about her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0654">so her name is <trunc>T</trunc>Tigger</u>
<u n="82" who="S0653">what is it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0654">Tigger</u>
<u n="84" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0654">it's T I G A T I G A</u>
<u n="86" who="S0653">oh Tiga</u>
<u n="87" who="S0654" trans="overlap">Whicabim</u>
<u n="88" who="S0653">Tiga I would imagine</u>
<u n="89" who="S0654" trans="overlap">Tiga Whicabim I've always <unclear/> I always have called her Tigger</u>
<u n="90" who="S0653">Tiga Whicabim that's a very hard word name to say isn't it?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yes and</u>
<u n="92" who="S0655" trans="overlap">Tiga Whicabim</u>
<u n="93" who="S0653">is she a witch?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0654" trans="overlap">that look she doesn't look</u>
<u n="95" who="S0655" trans="overlap">Whicabim</u>
<u n="96" who="S0653" trans="overlap">shh</u>
<u n="97" who="S0654">well at the in the story</u>
<u n="98" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0654">it doesn't actually tell you she's a witch but since all the witches live below the sinks</u>
<u n="100" who="S0653">right oh</u>
<u n="101" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0654">and she must she must have lived there</u>
<u n="103" who="S0653">are they tiny then?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yep</u>
<u n="105" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="106" who="S0653">why are you laughing at me like I'm a mad person? cos if they live under the sink they must be small</u>
<u n="107" who="S0654">no the pipes are big they're really big</u>
<u n="108" who="S0653">so they live underground?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0653" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="111" who="S0654">no actually they just go down in the pipes and then there's a wholly lovely place with skies</u>
<u n="112" who="S0653" trans="overlap">so so that's their other world</u>
<u n="113" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and jam</u>
<u n="114" who="S0653">okay so</u>
<u n="115" who="S0655" trans="overlap">don't forget the jam</u>
<u n="116" who="S0653">shh so she's born in a sink is she raised by adults normal people?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0654">she's raised by a witch</u>
<u n="118" who="S0653">I'm really confused</u>
<u n="119" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0654">so</u>
<u n="121" who="S0653">how can she be raised by a <trunc>wi</trunc>witch if she's born in a?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0654" trans="overlap">all of the bad witches</u>
<u n="123" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="124" who="S0654">so let me tell you so all the bad witches go up and they and one and one witch tortures the children by inventing Brussel sprouts</u>
<u n="125" who="S0653"><vocal desc="nonsense"/> one witch what?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0655" trans="overlap">tortures</u>
<u n="127" who="S0654">one witch tortures children by inventing Brussel sprouts</u>
<u n="128" who="S0653">by inventing Brussel sprouts</u>
<u n="129" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="130" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and homework</u>
<u n="131" who="S0654">and homework</u>
<u n="132" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0654">and then so she</u>
<u n="134" who="S0653">that's funny</u>
<u n="135" who="S0654" trans="overlap">she she was one of the witches who <trunc>le</trunc> who left in the big leave which and</u>
<u n="136" who="S0653">and why was there a big leave?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0654">because all the witches thought look I don't want this place any more I want to go up there</u>
<u n="138" who="S0653">right so they are living</u>
<u n="139" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and they <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="140" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and Brussel sprouts and homework</u>
<u n="141" who="S0653">hang on they are living amongst humans?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="143" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0654">but they took all of the colour with them there's only</u>
<u n="145" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="146" who="S0654">there's only a few books which if the witches came back they wouldn't be able to touch any of those colours in the whole room</u>
<u n="147" who="S0653">I don't get that what?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0654">there's</u>
<u n="149" who="S0653">how can you take colours? by magic?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no just that if er witches leave forever</u>
<u n="151" who="S0653">where? the downstairs bit?</u>
<u n="152" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0653">I'm sorry I'm not keeping up with it</u>
<u n="154" who="S0654" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="155" who="S0653">what are you laughing at me for?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0655">sorry it's just</u>
<u n="157" who="S0654" trans="overlap">when all the <trunc>w</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> the bad witches</u>
<u n="158" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0654">must of</u>
<u n="160" who="S0653">must have</u>
<u n="161" who="S0654">must have</u>
<u n="162" who="S0655" trans="overlap">must've</u>
<u n="163" who="S0654">must have some kind of connection so that whenever when they leave the colours just drained out because</u>
<u n="164" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="165" who="S0654">erm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0653">perhaps the world was unhappy</u>
<u n="167" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0653">what? it's not funny</u>
<u n="169" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0653">so there are not very many colours down below?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0654">there's not colours there's no</u>
<u n="172" who="S0653" trans="overlap">there's no colours?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0654">except for four books which the witches</u>
<u n="174" who="S0653" trans="overlap"><trunc>ha</trunc> why do you keep saying books cos books aren't colours that's what I'm getting confused about?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0654">oh because those are those are all the rulers who once ruled those are all the facts about the rulers</u>
<u n="176" who="S0653" trans="overlap">what? like a measuring thing? mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0654">who ruled</u>
<u n="178" who="S0653">what's that got to do with colours though?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0654">well once that happens all the <trunc>w</trunc> once that once that happened all the rulers go into that book which a sign which erm if there's enough books then I think there might be new new colour</u>
<u n="180" who="S0653">oh okay I'm with you now</u>
<u n="181" who="S0655">and is there new colour?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0653">don't reveal it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0654" trans="overlap">not yet not yet</u>
<u n="184" who="S0653">so is this one of many</u>
<u n="185" who="S0654" trans="overlap">that's only what I think</u>
<u n="186" who="S0653">is this a series?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0654" trans="overlap">this is the first book</u>
<u n="188" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="189" who="S0654">and then there's one which is called Witch Switch which I think the four</u>
<u n="190" who="S0653">have we got it?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="193" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="194" who="S0653">well we need to don't tap that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0654" trans="overlap">sorry</u>
<u n="196" who="S0653">we need to get the <trunc>co</trunc> er coins sorted at the post office so we can go and buy some books for each other</u>
<u n="197" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yes and anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/> enough about that erm a fairy called Fran</u>
<u n="198" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="199" who="S0655" trans="overlap">Fran Fran</u>
<u n="200" who="S0654">goes up through the pipes</u>
<u n="201" who="S0653" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="202" who="S0654">to get Tiga</u>
<u n="203" who="S0655"><trunc>T</trunc>Tiga</u>
<u n="204" who="S0653" trans="overlap">Tiga</u>
<u n="205" who="S0654">Tiga Whicabim</u>
<u n="206" who="S0653">Tiga Whicabim</u>
<u n="207" who="S0654">to go down to the pipes to compete in the witch wars and</u>
<u n="208" who="S0653" trans="overlap">why? why? why? why? why? why her?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0654">cos because Miss Heks</u>
<u n="210" who="S0653">who's Miss Heks?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0654">she's the bad witch</u>
<u n="212" who="S0653">right is she looking after Tiga?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0655">she loves cheese</u>
<u n="215" who="S0653" trans="overlap">does Tiga know that she's a bad person? does she like her?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0654">she doesn't like her at all</u>
<u n="217" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="218" who="S0655">yeah because she likes cheese</u>
<u n="219" who="S0654">no Tiga</u>
<u n="220" who="S0653" trans="overlap">but why is Tiga put upstairs?</u>
<u n="221" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0654">because she's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0653">stop laughing at me why was she put in the sink?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0654">I don't know</u>
<u n="225" who="S0653">why is nasty witch raising her and looking after her?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0654">well she was found in the sink but I think somebody like one of the bad witches</u>
<u n="227" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0655">stole her</u>
<u n="229" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="230" who="S0654" trans="overlap">stole her and put her in the sink like that lady</u>
<u n="231" who="S0653" trans="overlap">does she know that does she not know that she's a witch?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0654">she does not</u>
<u n="233" who="S0655" trans="overlap">she does know</u>
<u n="234" who="S0653">and Tia or that lady comes up Fran?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0654">well</u>
<u n="236" who="S0655" trans="overlap">she doesn't know</u>
<u n="237" who="S0653">she doesn't</u>
<u n="238" who="S0654">Fan's a fairy and also</u>
<u n="239" who="S0653" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="240" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0653" trans="overlap">so Fan comes</u>
<u n="242" who="S0654">in that story she doesn't even know she's a witch until the end</u>
<u n="243" who="S0653">ah so you've just spoilt it for me</u>
<u n="244" who="S0654" trans="overlap">but she's kind she thinks she's a witch but she may not be a witch so I don't even know</u>
<u n="245" who="S0653">so she oh good grief</u>
<u n="246" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0653">so Fran the fairy says come down and into this world and do some witch wars?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="250" who="S0654">she said you have to compete in witch wars and Miss Hex signed her up so she could get rid of her cos she thought</u>
<u n="251" who="S0653" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0654">that maybe she'll win witch wars and then she would go and be gone forever</u>
<u n="253" who="S0653">now hang on a moment is this the call to adventure in the hero's journey?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0653">does she refuse it first?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0654">yep</u>
<u n="257" who="S0653">and then does she accept?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0653">there we are then marvellous</u>
<u n="261" who="S0654" trans="overlap">she does it in a few minutes</u>
<u n="262" who="S0653">oh well that's fine but she still</u>
<u n="263" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0653">she's still following the hero's journey</u>
<u n="265" who="S0654">otherwise she'll go</u>
<u n="266" who="S0653">marvellous</u>
<u n="267" who="S0654">otherwise she will go and drink some cheese water <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0653">drink some cheese water?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0653">I wonder what cheese water's like delicious I expect</u>
<u n="271" who="S0655">water-flavoured as cheese</u>
<u n="272" who="S0654" trans="overlap">shall I just shall I just read you a</u>
<u n="273" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I do understand</u>
<u n="274" who="S0654">shall I read you a chapter?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0653">can I just pause you for a moment?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0653">erm at thank you at the insane terrain the running race today there was a DJ doing lots of music to entertain the people hanging around and there was lots of kids hanging around watching their parents and they were playing some sort of old-fashioned music and then the DJ said just to let you know it is going to be cheese hour in two minutes</u>
<u n="278" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0653">because when you get really naff music they call it cheesy music so we were having cheesy music for the whole hour there we are and that's what just from memory continue please</u>
<u n="280" who="S0654">okay shall I read you a chapter?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0653">no you can't read a chapter cos we're having a discussion about it</u>
<u n="282" who="S0655"><unclear>temper temper</unclear></u>
<u n="283" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I know but can I just read one page so you get the idea?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0653">no because you can do that later now can I just say we are going to this book launch not this Thursday but next Thursday by my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and the person that erm is publishing it for him he was the publisher that that discovered JK Rowling and he has said that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s book reminds him of Harry Potter and that my friends is a very big phrase where the accolade indeed isn't it? so I cannot wait to read his story I think that's going to be amazing and that's a witchy story erm and there's and he's now found out today that he's gonna do two more books so it's going to be a trilogy</u>
<u n="285" who="S0655">no you cannot say that</u>
<u n="286" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0653">did I ask did I say can I say it?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0655">yeah go on please say</u>
<u n="289" who="S0653">shall I take it <vocal desc="nonsense"/> okay I won't say it</u>
<u n="290" who="S0654">say it to me say it to me say it to me</u>
<u n="291" who="S0653" trans="overlap">now</u>
<u n="292" who="S0654" trans="overlap">say it to me</u>
<u n="293" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got a good idea for your birthday cake I'm not going to tell you what it is but you've just got to trust us that it is going to be brilliant</u>
<u n="294" who="S0654">okay</u>
<u n="295" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="296" who="S0654">what is it going</u>
<u n="297" who="S0653" trans="overlap">well don't ask me</u>
<u n="298" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0653">I'll have to kill you and then you wouldn't have a party</u>
<u n="300" who="S0654">what is it?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0653">don't ask me to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know I can't keep secrets to save my life don't ask me but it's going to be very good and I can finish marking my cursed er exams on Thursday then I will lie in a corner of drool for about an hour</u>
<u n="302" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0653">and then I will try and start baking your cake on Friday so it's ready for Sunday</u>
<u n="304" who="S0655">so that's made <unclear/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0654" trans="overlap">don't ask me what?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0653">so it's ready for the party don't ask you what what?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0654">don't</u>
<u n="308" who="S0653" trans="overlap">what proper?</u>
<u n="309" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0654">what do you not want me to ask you?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0653" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're now going to give yourself hiccups now</u>
<u n="312" who="S0655" trans="overlap">she already has</u>
<u n="313" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="315" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0653">can you tell me a bit more about your special assembly on Wednesday please? but don't spoil it for me otherwise we'll have to stop the recording if you're going to be silly</u>
<u n="317" who="S0654">well it's about all the things that we've done</u>
<u n="318" who="S0653">this year?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0654">yeah and also we need to find a green T-shirt and green</u>
<u n="320" who="S0653" trans="overlap">a green T-shirt? mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0654">and green leggings</u>
<u n="322" who="S0653" trans="overlap">we'll use your</u>
<u n="323" who="S0655">what for Brussel sprouts?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0653">right when were you going to mention that?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0654">I've already mentioned that to you</u>
<u n="326" who="S0653" trans="overlap">you did not mention it to me when did when did you what do you need that for? what are</u>
<u n="327" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I'm gonna I'm gonna be a <unclear>captain</unclear> for Robin Hood and they offered me <unclear/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0653">oh we don't have the Peter Pan outfit any more do we?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="330" who="S0653">well I don't have green leggings and a green T-shirt for you you'll be surprised to know cos I don't have a magic box that allows me to just request things surely you can wear your PE T-shirt which is green?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0655">yeah turn it inside out</u>
<u n="333" who="S0653">and the leggings that we used to have for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s Peter Pan thing are long gone so I don't have those but I'm wondering if we've got any brown</u>
<u n="334" who="S0655" trans="overlap">well brown leggings</u>
<u n="335" who="S0653">leggings or brown trousers from one of the nativity type things? why are shaking your head? don't you say to me now it has to be</u>
<u n="336" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I've got Brownie ones</u>
<u n="337" who="S0653">right cos what you aren't going to say to me is that it has to be green because we've got three days to sort this out but yes you're right it could be erm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0655" trans="overlap">green</u>
<u n="339" who="S0653">your Brownie leggings</u>
<u n="340" who="S0654">I also need to find a little hat</u>
<u n="341" who="S0653">but again we don't have any of that any more</u>
<u n="342" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0653">we used to</u>
<u n="344" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0653">I will have a look upstairs to see if we've got any in the <trunc>w</trunc> dressing up</u>
<u n="346" who="S0655">Robin Hood doesn't always have a hat though</u>
<u n="347" who="S0654">yeah but that one does <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0653">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't be so difficult</u>
<u n="349" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just draw moustache then they'll know</u>
<u n="350" who="S0653">no well no no who has a moustache in Robin Hood?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0655" trans="overlap">obviously the sheriff</u>
<u n="352" who="S0653">nobody</u>
<u n="353" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0653">well who are you <trunc>play</trunc>?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0654" trans="overlap">it is the story of Robin Hood he has a moustache</u>
<u n="356" who="S0653">no he doesn't who are you playing?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0654">Robin Hood</u>
<u n="358" who="S0653">you're playing Robin Hood yourself?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0654">I'm going</u>
<u n="360" who="S0655" trans="overlap">she's going</u>
<u n="361" who="S0654">to read out a little note and we have to dress up as Robin Hood</u>
<u n="362" who="S0655">yeah with a moustache</u>
<u n="363" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0653">well as I say I I may have kept <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s Peter Pan costume for nostalgic reasons</u>
<u n="365" who="S0655">what does nostalgic mean?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0653">you know when you <trunc>rem</trunc>reminisce about something that happened and you're like ah I don't think I would have sold it but where it's gonna be upstairs I've no idea what about a tricorn hat? one of my hats?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0654">yeah that would be good</u>
<u n="368" who="S0655">oh a tricorn what is a tricorn? what's a tricorn?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0653" trans="overlap">what about is there anything</u>
<u n="370" who="S0655">a unicorn hat?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0653">ah well okay think about what tri and uni means? how many <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="372" who="S0655">unicorn</u>
<u n="373" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0653">how many horns does a unicorn have?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0655">one</u>
<u n="376" who="S0653">okay how many points does a triangle have?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0655">three</u>
<u n="378" who="S0653">yes so what do you think a tricorn hat how many points might it have?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0655">four</u>
<u n="380" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0653">seriously though <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0655">so is it a hat that goes like this?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0653">it's like the hat the one I had for my highwayman thing it's got a three points cos it's a tricorn</u>
<u n="384" who="S0655" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="385" who="S0653">as opposed to a unicorn which has one point you're now being too silly</u>
<u n="386" who="S0655" trans="overlap">sorry I just didn't get it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0653">can you calm down? you need to calm down <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have I got anything in my dressing up that you would be able to use?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0654">let me see you can keep on doing the recording now</u>
<u n="389" who="S0653">I can keep on doing the recording? thanks well no you need to stay here really can you not be Maid Marion? I've got loads of things for that I'm sure</u>
<u n="390" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="391" who="S0653">you have to be Robin Hood?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0654">cos we've <unclear>writed it</unclear> in the role of Robin Hood</u>
<u n="393" who="S0653">well listen I can look in the loft tomorrow night to see if we've got anything of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s from the other day I mean the other year</u>
<u n="394" who="S0655">and if not just tie her hair up</u>
<u n="395" who="S0654" trans="overlap">huh I've got that</u>
<u n="396" who="S0655">and then paint it green</u>
<u n="397" who="S0653">nice</u>
<u n="398" who="S0654">I've got an idea mum <unclear/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0653" trans="overlap">can you come over <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what is your idea?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0653">I beg your pardon? sorry?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0654" trans="overlap">do you know what</u>
<u n="403" who="S0655">sorry</u>
<u n="404" who="S0653">no no no no stop it what did you say I need to record it?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0655">oh</u>
<u n="406" who="S0653">what did you say?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0655">you could tie your hair up</u>
<u n="408" who="S0653">no no before or after that?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0655" trans="overlap">oh was it stick a pigeon feather in?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0653">stick a pigeon feather in thanks for that <trunc>u</trunc>useful thing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0654">it doesn't have to be in the right colour because I could get your little sparkly hat</u>
<u n="412" who="S0653">what little sparkly hat?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0654">you know it's kind of like</u>
<u n="414" who="S0655" trans="overlap">erm the hat you got at this</u>
<u n="415" who="S0653">no that is a top a baby silver top hat</u>
<u n="416" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0653">yeah well Robin Hood didn't wear one of those did he?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0655">he did when he was meeting Prince John for the first time</u>
<u n="420" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0653">mm my goodness me I will try and find the thing upstairs in the loft tomorrow</u>
<u n="422" who="S0654">okay</u>
<u n="423" who="S0655">wait this is what he did</u>
<u n="424" who="S0654">is it green?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0653">you do need a little bit of Lincoln green what did he do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0655">he said hello Prince John and it's what the prince does and ah the <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="427" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0653">mm ah now before I forget <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has asked us when he celebrates his birthday at the end of July so we will be in the school holidays he most wants to go to Legoland for the day</u>
<u n="429" who="S0655">again?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="431" who="S0654">can are we gonna go with him?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0653">yes so we're gonna go meet him there erm obviously we're all I'm paying well you guys get in cos of the Blue Peter thing and we'll get the Q-bot thing which means that we can</u>
<u n="433" who="S0655">it takes a while to get it</u>
<u n="434" who="S0653">no you can order it online</u>
<u n="435" who="S0655">ooh</u>
<u n="436" who="S0653">that only means you just can skip the queues and stuff for the popular rides</u>
<u n="437" who="S0654" trans="overlap">also because</u>
<u n="438" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I have a Q-Bot</u>
<u n="439" who="S0654">erm that might be very that'll be really nice because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wouldn't want to spend his birthday just waiting in the queue for really awesome rides</u>
<u n="440" who="S0653">that's right they really want to push the boat out for his <trunc>bir</trunc> and also <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she really needs to talk sparkly rings with you</u>
<u n="441" who="S0655">sparkly rings?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0653">well because you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked her to marry her asked her to marry him a couple of weeks ago did you know that?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0655">yes I did</u>
<u n="444" who="S0653" trans="overlap">so he proposed to her so she's got a sparkly ring and she's never been married before you see so it's very exciting and er she wants to show <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her sparkly ring</u>
<u n="445" who="S0654">oh</u>
<u n="446" who="S0653">it's ooh la la</u>
<u n="447" who="S0655">ooh la la la</u>
<u n="448" who="S0653">right it's now time for bed</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
