<text id="S4MV">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:35:15</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0607 S0644</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc> in the car travelling along the coast of California on holiday</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>The conversation centres around what happens when you no longer wish to see friends and how to deal with this. </topics>
		<activity>Car journey discussion between friends about how to phase out friends</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0607">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Pembury, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern/ 'BBC' English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Battle</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 month</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Translator/Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0644">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English/British</nat>
				<birthplace>Enfield, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London/ South-East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Office worker (temp)</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Brazilian Portuguese -- basic</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0644">that's it it's recording</u>
<u n="2" who="S0607">okay</u>
<u n="3" who="S0644">I dunno if it's gonna be <trunc>le</trunc> oh it's only a test isn't it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0644">it doesn't have to be</u>
<u n="6" who="S0607">erm so shall I tell you about my erm ditching someone?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0607">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I feel a bit guilty about it actually erm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0644" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0607">so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear>did it feel</unclear> cathartic?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0607">there was this girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0607">in Germany and erm so she was the one who me and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> had made friends with this couple</u>
<u n="17" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="18" who="S0607">and we'd met them at somebody else's party</u>
<u n="19" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><trunc>coup</trunc> I remember this couple you didn't really you weren't mad on them were you?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0607">no we'd met them at someone else's party</u>
<u n="21" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and wasn't <trunc>sh</trunc> one of them English?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0607">yeah the bloke the husband was English</u>
<u n="23" who="S0644" trans="overlap">was one of them English? <pause dur="short"/> she was what German?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0607">German</u>
<u n="25" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="26" who="S0607">when I say we met them at someone else's party it makes it sound like we had a real social life <vocal desc="laugh"/> but we didn't we went to one party</u>
<u n="27" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="28" who="S0607">and we met this couple</u>
<u n="29" who="S0644" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0607">and then because of the husband I joined book club <pause dur="short"/> erm and erm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0644"><unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0607">and then erm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0644">why did you join it because of him? just cos he said I've got I go to book club do you wanna come?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0607">well I just I'd been looking for a book club and I was like what? you go to book club? I'm coming and that's</u>
<u n="35" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0607">when I read Perfume erm anyway so</u>
<u n="37" who="S0644">sorry to keep interrupting you did you keep going to book club?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0607">I did I went for at least five books erm and I really really enjoyed all of them we did <trunc>Ern</trunc>Ernest Hemmingway</u>
<u n="39" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0607">erm what's that one? have you read any Ernest Hemmingway?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0644">erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0607" trans="overlap">the one where he catches the big fish?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0644">no</u>
<u n="44" who="S0607">by the way you know for this recording thing <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not meant to be a monologue and I'm sort of setting off on a monologue</u>
<u n="45" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> soliloquy that's alright</u>
<u n="46" who="S0607">erm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0644">once you get going I'll be able to interject with a bit of er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0644"><unclear/> but I've gotta stop interrupting for you to do that so go on</u>
<u n="50" who="S0607">well so basically we started going they invited us round for dinner with this other couple <pause dur="short"/> and that and that first night</u>
<u n="51" who="S0644" trans="overlap">did you ever like them?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0607">yeah that first night was really great and we all got on really well and even though I like to go to bed early it was like one AM before I knew it and all this stuff</u>
<u n="53" who="S0644"><unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0607">and then I said at the time oh I got <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to buy me Frankfurt Monopoly for for Christmas <pause dur="short"/> do you guys wanna come round and play it?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0607">erm and it felt like oh new friends</u>
<u n="57" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0607">and so they all went yeah let's come round and play Frankfurt Monopoly so erm <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah so they all came round to ours and we played and then we all went round to the third couple's and and we played another game <pause dur="short"/> and then we went back to the first couple and played again but gradually it was getting a bit like no so it doesn't really matter what what it was like with the couples cos the point is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she sort of like latched onto me and was like me and you'll meet for coffee</u>
<u n="59" who="S0644">okay</u>
<u n="60" who="S0607">so me and her met for coffee or a drink or dinner or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s really nice but she would just go on and on and do I have to erm? <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if I have to go get a bit like <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I know yeah one 0 one</u>
<u n="62" who="S0607"><unclear/> they're all doing it erm <pause dur="short"/> they're all doing it and now I can't do it</u>
<u n="63" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0607">come on guys get out the way</u>
<u n="65" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> if we were in a field you'd just pull you'd just pull over</u>
<u n="66" who="S0607">doing it I'm doing it I'm doing it</u>
<u n="67" who="S0644">go on go on</u>
<u n="68" who="S0607">do I need to go even one more?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="70" who="S0607">I'm not sure maybe I can still be in this one <pause dur="short"/> erm so but when when I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for these things it would be like so she didn't know whether to marry him or not</u>
<u n="71" who="S0644">why?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0607">erm because he's got four children already <pause dur="short"/> and she was saying to me I'm used to having money because my parents are well off and I'm like</u>
<u n="73" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0607">and and I want my children to have been privileged as well and she said I don't wanna be like <trunc>n</trunc> I can't afford driving lessons for my kid because he's got four other kids already and and I don't wanna be like struggling and</u>
<u n="75" who="S0644">it's fair enough <unclear/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> he's gonna basically have to become CEO of the company for us to be able to have the lifestyle that we're used to</u>
<u n="77" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0607">and cover all the kids kind of thing</u>
<u n="79" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0607">and so we went on and on and on like this for hours where she was like he's the guy for me but I just don't know if I can do this</u>
<u n="81" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0607">and it's fair enough like it was a genuine problem but then she would sit there and go he's definitely the right guy for me and I would be like well then there's your answer I'm <trunc>s</trunc> it's a shame about them four kids but they are in England and you're in Germany</u>
<u n="83" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0607">and erm anyway she did marry him in the end but the thing is that she I would meet her and she would she would thrash this problem out</u>
<u n="85" who="S0644">again and again and again</u>
<u n="86" who="S0607" trans="overlap">or <trunc>a</trunc> the thing is that's what I'd do so I I don't know why like it's a bit double standards to go bloody hell you really really thoroughly cover it don't you? but it's just that I</u>
<u n="87" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0607">it's just that after I left her and went home I just felt drained of all energy you know how I think I hope that when we talk about stuff it's funny</u>
<u n="89" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0607">so we just go oh my god my life is so shit ha ha ha you know whereas with her it was like I was drained and depressed after I met her so even though she's really nice I started to think oh shit I don't really want to meet her erm and then with the couples thing when we were meeting <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> in the couples group</u>
<u n="91" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0607">her bloke <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was really starting to get on my nerves and the two blokes work together and they used to leave <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out so they would be all like</u>
<u n="93" who="S0644">chatting</u>
<u n="94" who="S0607">chatting and and being in their in group and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really shy so they were leaving him out so I started to get a bit annoyed about how cool <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought he was and I just thought you're actually not that cool and then my Canadian friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this is probably way too gossipy erm she said erm that he came onto her at a Queen concert when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was pregnant with their with their first child</u>
<u n="95" who="S0644">really?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0607">and I just thought do you know what? I just don't even wanna and the thing is though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s really nice but I just didn't want to meet her</u>
<u n="97" who="S0644" trans="overlap">do you believe that that happened?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0607">well that's a whole other topic</u>
<u n="99" who="S0644">because just that it just occurred to me cos sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's it's really difficult to say on one hand I found it difficult to believe that anyone would do that but then I know that they do and then I think when other people actually tell someone else do do the other people believe them?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0607">I know cos you sort of think unless you were there and could she have misunderstood?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0644">that's it but then do you know her well enough this girl to to know if?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0607">well the problem with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is that I she's a very genuine person and I don't think she would lie but sometimes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would be telling us this stuff <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would like pick holes in the story and go but like what exactly</u>
<u n="103" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that didn't happen</u>
<u n="104" who="S0607">or <trunc>d</trunc> you know but couldn't it have been this? and couldn't it have been that? and it was like a bit painful you know to listen to and <pause dur="short"/> I dunno it was a bit he put his arms around her from behind and snuggled right up <pause dur="short"/> at this <unclear>Queen</unclear> concert</u>
<u n="105" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I suppose you don't do that do ya? your girlfriend's pregnant at home</u>
<u n="106" who="S0607">oh also he hadn't told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that they would they'd got pregnant so then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came and picked them up from this Queen concert and and erm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were thinking the three of us could go and see Maroon Five cos they're gonna be on in like July or whatever and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went erm I can't really go in July</u>
<u n="107" who="S0644" trans="overlap">don't think so</u>
<u n="108" who="S0607">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went why not? and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went because I'm due then and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went what you're pregnant? and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you didn't tell her I'm pregnant? and they had a row</u>
<u n="109" who="S0644" trans="overlap">see that is weird innit?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0607">they had a row in the front of the car and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was sat in the back going erm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0644" trans="overlap">what was the row though like? what can you <trunc>s</trunc> cos I'd say why did you say it? and he'd say what?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0607">oh sixty-five okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah erm she</u>
<u n="113" who="S0644" trans="overlap">but does the row go?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0607">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knew that it was weird that he had not told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that they were pregnant</u>
<u n="115" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that he hadn't said anything <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="116" who="S0607">and it fits in with the story of him hugging her from behind and stuff</u>
<u n="117" who="S0644" trans="overlap">cos all of this stuff when you hear these stories I think aren't it's all a little bit like a soap opera like you can't believe it actually goes that people do things like this but then I know that they do</u>
<u n="118" who="S0607">I know but you can't believe it can you?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0644">no I can't believe like</u>
<u n="120" who="S0607">but guess what? guess how he got together with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he had an affair with her when he was married</u>
<u n="121" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="122" who="S0607">she <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the girl in the office</u>
<u n="123" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="124" who="S0607">this is so so hilarious erm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0607">but yeah he had a he had an affair with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the office and his wife</u>
<u n="127" who="S0644">cos of it</u>
<u n="128" who="S0607" trans="overlap">cos of it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0644"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0607">cos I said at one point to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at least <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows at least like he chose <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said no that's not the way it went</u>
<u n="131" who="S0644">she left him</u>
<u n="132" who="S0607">he had an affair with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and did not choose <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but the wife found out and left him</u>
<u n="133" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="134" who="S0607">and then he just stayed with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so the wife moved all four kids back to England <pause dur="short"/> it's just like <pause dur="short"/> but the <trunc>poi</trunc> I think sort of got into the story but the point was that with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> even though she's a really nice person I used to feel exhausted after I met her and I <trunc>d</trunc> and I didn't feel natural like when I was telling her my stuff so I'd listen to all this stuff over and over and over and really agonising over all the problems and then</u>
<u n="135" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0607">I would try and tell her my stuff and it would make me feel worse about my stuff instead of like when I talk to you and I feel like</u>
<u n="137" who="S0644" trans="overlap">why did it make you feel worse?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0607">I can't explain it's like the the dynamic between us</u>
<u n="139" who="S0644">is not good</u>
<u n="140" who="S0607" trans="overlap">it didn't didn't work even though you just can't force it can you? am I still on the one 0 one?</u>
<u n="141" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0607">maybe this chatting thing is a bad idea</u>
<u n="143" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0607">erm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0644">yeah we're going the right way it's four five seven no it's four six seven</u>
<u n="146" who="S0607">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="147" who="S0644">we've only got about another ten junctions</u>
<u n="148" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0644">is this gonna be like a half an hour trip?</u>
<u n="150" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0607">supposed to be three hours</u>
<u n="152" who="S0644">oh it's so expansive America is fantastic</u>
<u n="153" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but basically so I ditched <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0644" trans="overlap">god bless America <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="155" who="S0607">I I ditched her</u>
<u n="156" who="S0644">did ya?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0607">cos I just did it I didn't wanna meet her</u>
<u n="158" who="S0644" trans="overlap">don't worry cos when she's had the baby she wouldn't have had time to talk to you anyway</u>
<u n="159" who="S0607">but she still did she used to text and go do you wanna meet up?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0644" trans="overlap">what even when she had the baby?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0607">yeah shall we have a drink? do you wanna meet up? shall we go for a coffee? <pause dur="short"/> and I kept saying no cos I just really didn't want to when I thought about doing it I was I felt like oh no I don't want to so I put her off and put her off and put her off until I left the country <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and then in <trunc>j</trunc> is that the one that you replied and said oh I'm moving country now?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0607">yeah bless her I did text her in January and said erm by the way it was really terrible but like I used my situation to get out of it so when she was always texting and me always saying no at one point I said to her look me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are on the rocks so I'm going through something so</u>
<u n="164" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> leave me alone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and I felt a bit bad do you know what I mean? cos I was like getting out of it that way but it was true</u>
<u n="166" who="S0644">well</u>
<u n="167" who="S0607">but it was also partly cos partly I didn't wanna see anyone</u>
<u n="168" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0607">but also partly I definitely didn't wanna see her and it's <unclear/> but it's not because she's not nice it's just that</u>
<u n="170" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0607">didn't didn't click</u>
<u n="172" who="S0644"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0607">so I did text her in January and say erm I'm like in the UK now and I've left so bye</u>
<u n="174" who="S0644" trans="overlap">all the best</u>
<u n="175" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0607">but bless her she replied</u>
<u n="178" who="S0644" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0607">cos I was thinking you know when you work yourself up and think they're gonna be annoyed</u>
<u n="180" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0607">and they're gonna like <pause dur="short"/> ignore me and stuff well she replied immediately which by the way I hate that</u>
<u n="182" who="S0644" trans="overlap">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0607">but she but she said oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm thinking of you and I really hope that you enjoy this year</u>
<u n="184" who="S0644" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0607">and erm and it would be lovely to keep in touch and all this stuff so I was like ah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0644">it's really sweet</u>
<u n="187" who="S0607">so what do you think?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0644" trans="overlap">but it's not</u>
<u n="189" who="S0607">is it a good example?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0644">yeah but I think erm you've always been a lot better at that anyway like</u>
<u n="191" who="S0607">just not seeing people yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think you always just not don't care yeah don't really really care <pause dur="short"/> you were talking about it years ago <pause dur="short"/> with someone who lived in Manchester or went to Manchester and you didn't you liked her but you didn't you didn't you couldn't be arsed and when they moved to Manchester or or do you know who I'm talking about? it was the girl who was a bit quiet out of that bunch <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0607">was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0644">I think it might have been <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was small with dark hair</u>
<u n="195" who="S0607">yeah and it just was a she was lovely but it was a nothingy friendship because</u>
<u n="196" who="S0644" trans="overlap">you were you was already starting to get a bit arsy about things like this years ago like</u>
<u n="197" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0644">couldn't be bothered <unclear/> hassle</u>
<u n="199" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah it just wasn't enough of a friendship so and the thing is I can't when I was in Frankfurt it wasn't like I could go oh I'd better meet up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos otherwise I won't be meeting with anybody I just thought I would rather not meet with anybody because</u>
<u n="200" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think that's good though I think that strength of character when you have the <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean like to say well I it ain't actually worth this it's not</u>
<u n="201" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0644">a genuine thing and I'd rather be</u>
<u n="203" who="S0607" trans="overlap">it doesn't fill me with joy the thought of doing it</u>
<u n="204" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you're saying that and I'm totally agreeing with you but it's like a completely new concept to me this</u>
<u n="205" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0644">it's only really been in the last year or so <pause dur="short"/> it's a completely new concept that it has to be <pause dur="short"/> a proper thing or it's it's really not worth the what it is see when you're you meet people all the time and you go out with people all the time and it's not a big deal and you just go out with this lot and then you go out with that lot you meet more people and and there's something about your time being diminished or you haven't got so much time</u>
<u n="207" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0644">and all and you start to really evaluate what who you're spending time with and all the rest of it and it's amazing it was with me it was all to do with with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and all the stuff that happened last year and I started thinking about people that you really do give a monkey's about</u>
<u n="209" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0644">and who you can talk to <unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0607" trans="overlap">quality time</u>
<u n="212" who="S0644">and what's the point in all the rest of it? what is the point?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0644">and now but the worst part of it is not the worst part of it at all in fact it's been wonderful but</u>
<u n="215" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0644">it has been wonderful because it's obviously sort of mutual with my ones because</u>
<u n="217" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0644">I haven't heard from them either</u>
<u n="219" who="S0607">I think that's that's quite a key point whether it's mutual or not</u>
<u n="220" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0607">cos I always feel like I think I'm like attracting people even more by being a bit erm aloof</u>
<u n="222" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0607">and it's not what I'm trying to do but it's like making them keener and then I sort of think why do you wanna meet up with me? cos I'm awful</u>
<u n="224" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0607">I'm a terrible person <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know</u>
<u n="226" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0607">and I don't listen it's not like I remember what your problems are</u>
<u n="228" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0607">just waiting for you to shut up <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I can tell you my story</u>
<u n="230" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0607">but by the way a key point is what about this feeling of obligation that that you get with some people? so it's like oh I should meet them and like and I should this and I should that cos I had another friend in Frankfurt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's really she's sort of a bit of a step up from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I sort of enjoyed her company a bit more</u>
<u n="232" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0607">but she got really clingy really quickly so <pause dur="short"/> four seven two erm <pause dur="short"/> so she would be like erm <pause dur="short"/> so we used to meet for lunch cos I met her she came to our office to work just for two weeks</u>
<u n="234" who="S0644">mm mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0607">she only works up the road so we used to meet for <trunc>l</trunc> so when we first met each other we had one of those conversations where you can't stop laughing</u>
<u n="236" who="S0644">ah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0607">so we like our we click you know</u>
<u n="238" who="S0644">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0607">and erm we had another couple of those we were in a restaurant and I couldn't stop laughing so we used to meet for lunch on a Friday and it was really nice</u>
<u n="240" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0607">and then one time just one time I I agreed to go for a drink in the evening which for me was a really big deal</u>
<u n="242" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> big deal</u>
<u n="243" who="S0607">and erm I actually let myself go and we stayed out till like one</u>
<u n="244" who="S0644"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0607">but the problem was this opened up something in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she was like right next time we go out we'll do this and I was like uhu <vocal desc="misc"/> it's back to lunch now</u>
<u n="246" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0607">and erm but the thing is she started saying things when we met up like erm I think we need to meet up more often</u>
<u n="248" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="249" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so I would like to see you in a few weeks and I was a bit like</u>
<u n="250" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh what a shame</u>
<u n="251" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm talking three months from now dude</u>
<u n="252" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0607">even though I really like her</u>
<u n="254" who="S0644">this is the thing I think some people <pause dur="short"/> equate our weirdness with thinking that sometimes it's it's really really not them is it? it's just you genuinely haven't got the energy or the inclination to see people that often you've got too much to do or you're and as soon as people start to kick up about it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0644">it has the opposite effect because don't you think though that's the most simple thing in the world ever? this was this would be your total worst nightmare and it doesn't happen any more but my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to be the worst culprit ever ever</u>
<u n="257" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0644">and she would guilt you and it's only cos I've been friends with her so long and I didn't realise it was happening and it crept up on me but in the end it got to a really bad level of guilting you if you didn't go and see her</u>
<u n="259" who="S0607"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0644">and then I went round to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one day cos you know I'm always well you wouldn't know this any more but I'd always go round and I'd go can't stop I've gotta do this and I've gotta do that and I've gotta do this</u>
<u n="261" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0644">I wouldn't stop <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went one day and she said oh she said it's lovely to see you she said come back whenever you want to like cos I said I've gotta go I can't do this I can't do that</u>
<u n="263" who="S0607" trans="overlap">sorry sorry <anon type="place"/> next exit no hang on cos the thing is</u>
<u n="264" who="S0644" trans="overlap">four seven nine</u>
<u n="265" who="S0607">it it could it be the one? cos <anon type="place"/> is on our route so do you think we should follow what the sign says or follow what I got on the internet? <pause dur="short"/> shit</u>
<u n="266" who="S0644">take exit four seven nine for <anon type="place"/> then left onto</u>
<u n="267" who="S0607">but I just wonder if if the <anon type="place"/> exit that they're saying is different to four seven nine do we get it or do we follow the four seven nine? <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> four seven nine</u>
<u n="269" who="S0607">is like below where we're going so we are we are going past <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0644">I think then it doesn't matter like you can go either <pause dur="short"/> by the sounds</u>
<u n="271" who="S0607">oh oh hang on <pause dur="short"/> that just said one one six we don't wanna get the one one six</u>
<u n="272" who="S0644">does that mean we're on the one one six?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0607">no I think it's like well I hope not <pause dur="short"/> do you think we're on the one 0 no wait a minute we're on the one 0 one so west one one six that must mean it's coming up</u>
<u n="274" who="S0644">so we don't get on it</u>
<u n="275" who="S0607">I wonder if the one that they're sending us on if on their sign is the one one six? <pause dur="long"/> do you think we should press pause?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0644"><unclear/> if you could</u>
<u n="279" who="S0607">no I mean on there <pause dur="short"/> do you think we should stop the thing?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="281" who="S0607">is it still on?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0644">is it still on? it's probably <pause dur="short"/> oh it's gone off again like the the whole thing</u>
<u n="283" who="S0607">oh <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="long"/> will you remember where you were at? what you were saying there?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah no don't worry about that I mean that's fine it's more you've gotta be <unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0607" trans="overlap">this is typical me chatting and I missed the exit</u>
<u n="286" who="S0644">but we didn't miss it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0607">we didn't did we?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0644" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="289" who="S0607">so even though it says four seven nine</u>
<u n="290" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0607">I <trunc>rea</trunc> what I really really want to happen is that their sign for <anon type="place"/> is the four seven nine</u>
<u n="292" who="S0644">I bet it is</u>
<u n="293" who="S0607">what <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0644" trans="overlap">we're about due for the four seven nine almost</u>
<u n="295" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that sign that we saw that said <anon type="place"/> exit was it then? like has it gone now? or</u>
<u n="296" who="S0644">perhaps it's just a really <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> a warning that's really early</u>
<u n="297" who="S0607"><anon type="place"/> highway one mile <unclear/> road no that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0644" trans="overlap">got three three things to go that's exit four seven four seven six <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0607">by the way just really quickly there was one other thing about meeting up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> started to feel like you're not proper friends till you've actually done things together because me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> only ever met up for dinner or lunch</u>
<u n="300" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0607">and I started to feel like it was an empty friendship because we got on and everything but we didn't have any any common experience</u>
<u n="302" who="S0644" trans="overlap">you said that to me once that's what makes people friends like it's when you've done stuff</u>
<u n="303" who="S0607">like me and you we worked together then we did like</u>
<u n="304" who="S0644">holidays</u>
<u n="305" who="S0607" trans="overlap">drinks together and went out together and</u>
<u n="306" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0607">I don't know if it's the holiday that cemented it all though or whether we would have been fine even without a holiday <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="308" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think when you've when you've been friends with and it's work or it's studying or school or something I think that's when you sort friends cos you really you're not just on your best behaviour over dinner like for an hour and a half or something</u>
<u n="309" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0644">but you've really got to see to know them a bit so I think that's</u>
<u n="311" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> go through things together sort of thing</u>
<u n="312" who="S0644">yeah <pause dur="short"/> actually all my <trunc>fr</trunc> yeah I suppose all my friends have been that</u>
<u n="313" who="S0607">and I think that's why I had a bit of a problem with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because I just didn't feel <pause dur="short"/> like we were close <pause dur="short"/> imagine if we were staying there? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0644">that's alright innit?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0607"><unclear/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think that looks really good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0607">it would be nice to do just a sort of like <pause dur="short"/> trip where you just drive until you're fed up and then you get <unclear/> one of them</u>
<u n="318" who="S0644" trans="overlap">stuck <pause dur="short"/> but that's what I'm saying actually like you know how we were worrying that we wouldn't get anywhere I reckon there's loads of those things</u>
<u n="319" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0644">we could just pull and say I wanna stay here cos there's it's so vast isn't it?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0644">so they've gotta have erm <pause dur="short"/> options like that <pause dur="short"/> it is a serial killer hangout but it nonetheless you could stop couldn't you if you wanted to?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0644">this is a little bit like Austria or something don't you think? it reminds me of Austria</u>
<u n="325" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="326" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0607">it sort of feels <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what it feels like <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna carry on saying what you're saying and then if another sign comes up I'll just cut you off again?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0644">it's it <trunc>di</trunc> it's up to you cos I think sometimes it's annoying to have other people when you're trying to concentrate sometimes I can't if I'm driving I can't <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0607" trans="overlap">cos we can't tell how long it is till the thing</u>
<u n="330" who="S0644">let's wait until we've got onto that bit</u>
<u n="331" who="S0607">okay</u>
<u n="332" who="S0644">that was a lovely cookie by the way <pause dur="short"/> thank you I think that was better than the erm yesterday's one</u>
<u n="333" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you think it was fresh again?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0644">yeah <pause dur="long"/> do you remember Wisbit?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0607">Wisbit?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="337" who="S0607">on television?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0644">er</u>
<u n="339" who="S0607">that <trunc>r</trunc>rings a bell</u>
<u n="340" who="S0644">that erm little triangle thing</u>
<u n="341" who="S0607">oh yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0644">you remember?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0607"><anon type="place"/> one mile</u>
<u n="344" who="S0644">woo hoo</u>
<u n="345" who="S0607">is that it?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0644">left onto <anon type="place"/> so we're gonna have to mince over that way</u>
<u n="347" who="S0607">oh <pause dur="short"/> but I was hoping that they would that it would <pause dur="short"/> that we would exit here and then go left let's see what happens</u>
<u n="348" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh is it?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0607">did it say one mile?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0644">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0607">I hope it says <anon type="place"/> but never mind if it doesn't <pause dur="long"/> would you be able to pass me my sunglasses?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0644">in the bag?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0607">don't know they're in your erm <trunc>pan</trunc> your side panel <unclear/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="355" who="S0607"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I've got to tell you about this wrinkle here I'll tell you later <pause dur="short"/> oh thanks <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0644">no this is fab all of it</u>
<u n="357" who="S0607">right here we go <anon type="place"/> doesn't mention <anon type="place"/> but never mind</u>
<u n="358" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0607">I really hope that it that it might <pause dur="short"/> four seven five</u>
<u n="360" who="S0644" trans="overlap">two out of three's not bad</u>
<u n="361" who="S0607">eh</u>
<u n="362" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0607">ah so probably this is where we go left <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0644">there was a vineyard back there</u>
<u n="365" who="S0607">oh yeah we're in wine country I forgot</u>
<u n="366" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> country now</u>
<u n="367" who="S0607">right driving on the right <pause dur="long"/> that's the kind of time when you need to remember</u>
<u n="368" who="S0644">remember yeah I would have totally gone</u>
<u n="369" who="S0607">what's the next thing? cos I think it's really soon the next turn</u>
<u n="370" who="S0644">go onto <anon type="place"/> left onto <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/>? <anon type="place"/>? what's?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0607">what was the <anon type="place"/> one?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0644">turn right onto <anon type="place"/> I think this is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0607">I think this is <anon type="place"/> one <pause dur="short"/> hey this is cool</u>
<u n="374" who="S0644">this is lovely <unclear/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0607" trans="overlap">we're accidently in wine in wine country <pause dur="long"/> so right onto <anon type="place"/> if we haven't already and then <trunc>bu</trunc><trunc>bu</trunc>bub <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0644">right onto <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0607">okay excellent <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0607">look at this it's hilarious <pause dur="short"/> and then was it left onto?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0644" trans="overlap">beautiful <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0607"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> this is great</u>
<u n="382" who="S0644">left onto <anon type="place"/> right onto <anon type="place"/> then continue onto the CA one</u>
<u n="383" who="S0607">oh okay that's when we're at the coast</u>
<u n="384" who="S0644">eh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0607">yeehaa <pause dur="short"/> it is it is a little bit annoying that we couldn't just have the car for as long as we wanted and then see what happens isn't it?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0644">mm <pause dur="short"/> I thought they'd be a bit more chillaxed about it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0607">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos then you could just like go okay well it's actually not snowing so we'll keep going a bit</u>
<u n="388" who="S0644">you probably could I mean <pause dur="short"/> not that I think we should now cos I think the train's a good idea but probably could alter it if you needed to</u>
<u n="389" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0644">when you're hungry and you want to stop for something <pause dur="short"/> do <pause dur="short"/> just been sitting here stuffing my face and like looking out the window and chillaxing</u>
<u n="391" who="S0607">maybe there'll be a diner where we could have a coffee</u>
<u n="392" who="S0644">oh man <pause dur="short"/> oh man <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0607">maybe maybe this is it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0644"><anon type="place"/>? no it's not here</u>
<u n="395" who="S0607" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="396" who="S0644">it'll tell us <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0644">oh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0607"><anon type="place"/> excellent</u>
<u n="400" who="S0644">left onto <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0607">is that <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0644"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0607">driving on the right so I don't know what to do about him</u>
<u n="404" who="S0644">just <unclear/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0607">go? <pause dur="short"/> thank you <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh look at this</u>
<u n="406" who="S0644">oh lovely look</u>
<u n="407" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you like it? I like this erm scenery</u>
<u n="408" who="S0644">I I actually <pause dur="short"/> this is what I really imagined look at the hills</u>
<u n="409" who="S0607">do you feel like it's not enough of an adventure? cos I've written down all of the directions</u>
<u n="410" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0644">well it was either write it was probably either too much erm <trunc>pla</trunc> like you planned it properly down to the writing the directions or it'd be me going erm <pause dur="short"/> let's just drive</u>
<u n="413" who="S0607" trans="overlap">the thing is</u>
<u n="414" who="S0644" trans="overlap">let's see what happens</u>
<u n="415" who="S0607" trans="overlap">if you do the adventure way where you don't know where you're going it's fun to a point and then you start to get pissed off</u>
<u n="416" who="S0644">yeah when you when you <pause dur="short"/> stayed in one of those motels at night and getting shot at</u>
<u n="417" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0644">ah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this is beautiful can I put the window down?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what was the next one?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0644">right onto <anon type="place"/> so onto <anon type="place"/> coming up</u>
<u n="421" who="S0607">we could maybe stop at <anon type="place"/> if we go past the</u>
<u n="422" who="S0644">could do</u>
<u n="423" who="S0607">for the diner experience</u>
<u n="424" who="S0644" trans="overlap">we're doing very good for time</u>
<u n="425" who="S0607">oh my god it's like summer ah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0644">spring innit? it's proper spring now</u>
<u n="427" who="S0607">ah <pause dur="long"/> I'm gonna live there</u>
<u n="428" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0607">this reminds me of when I was a waitress in the south of France for some reason cos even there's pine trees that's why <pause dur="short"/> it's like pine tree smell</u>
<u n="430" who="S0644">I can't smell pine trees</u>
<u n="431" who="S0607">cos even though it was a horrendous experience</u>
<u n="432" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh it's a bit cold</u>
<u n="433" who="S0607">I actually it was still a wonderful adventure</u>
<u n="434" who="S0644" trans="overlap">why were you there again?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0607">that was my short story do you remember?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0644">yeah I do I do remember it but I can't remember why you were doing that now like what was the in between bit?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0607" trans="overlap">to practise my French</u>
<u n="438" who="S0644">can you speak French as well?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0607">well <pause dur="short"/> not really <pause dur="short"/> erm saying that I speak French is slight over exaggeration cos I haven't spoken it for so long</u>
<u n="440" who="S0644">but you can obviously</u>
<u n="441" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but I can yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0644">because you went there to practise it</u>
<u n="443" who="S0607">oh <anon type="place"/> what was ours <anon type="place"/> something?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0644">er <anon type="place"/> and it's a right</u>
<u n="445" who="S0607">oh I really like it here</u>
<u n="446" who="S0644">it's proper American innit? <anon type="place"/> no</u>
<u n="447" who="S0607">I missed that sign there was a sign saying happy birthday to somebody like a proper sign with letters on <pause dur="short"/> look at these mailboxes</u>
<u n="448" who="S0644">look at those verandas what people sit out on oh look at this it's stunning</u>
<u n="449" who="S0607">this is crazy</u>
<u n="450" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> stunning stunning</u>
<u n="451" who="S0607">you see I I I totally feel like I <vocal desc="laugh"/> wanna live somewhere like this and <pause dur="short"/> you <trunc>wou</trunc> some people think there's something wrong with me cos I wanna live away from people</u>
<u n="452" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I don't think it's that dissimilar to <pause dur="short"/> but to England I don't think it's that dissimilar to England like certainly some looking over there now and the cows and</u>
<u n="453" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0644">I know it's a bit more vast and bumpy but</u>
<u n="455" who="S0607">but do you know what? I mean somewhere where it's away and it's a bit like remote that's what I like</u>
<u n="456" who="S0644">why is that <trunc>s</trunc> why's that so bad though?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0607">no I know I think it's fantastic</u>
<u n="458" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0607">course I'd probably do it and then go ah <pause dur="short"/> it's crap</u>
<u n="460" who="S0644" trans="overlap">could murder a latte</u>
<u n="461" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0644">that's why really and truly what I think I would like is somewhere a bolt hole like we were talking about somewhere <pause dur="short"/> quiet</u>
<u n="464" who="S0607">yeah so then you could have a boat</u>
<u n="465" who="S0644">would you live on a boat? real boat?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0644" trans="overlap">would you? yeah but</u>
<u n="468" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I'd like that</u>
<u n="469" who="S0644">I'd find them a bit claustrophobic</u>
<u n="470" who="S0607">my friend is thinking about buying a houseboat but she said to me it's it's the opposite of when you property you know when you buy property it's an investment houseboat's just <pause dur="short"/> eat the money and don't <trunc>accru</trunc> don't accrue any value and just decrease in value sort of thing</u>
<u n="471" who="S0644">what houseboats do?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0607">mm apparently I can't remember the full story but you know what I mean</u>
<u n="473" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I can see that yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't live on one they're too pokey I'd like to go on a a canal holiday you know</u>
<u n="474" who="S0607">it'd probably be something to do for a week wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0644">and then you'd get sick of it</u>
<u n="476" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> get back to your house <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0644">thank god I didn't actually buy one</u>
<u n="478" who="S0607"><shift new="singing"/> de de de de de de <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0644">have you been to the New Forest <pause dur="short"/> in England?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0607">er I can't remember I don't think so I think I've gone past it can you just remind me where it is again?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0644">New Forest?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0644">Hampshire Hampshire</u>
<u n="484" who="S0607">okay <pause dur="short"/> this is so great oh my god <pause dur="long"/> I think it's easier to like get around here than in England I dunno I've been I've been in England before in my own country and been like I can't work out where I'm going and it's complicated and there's traffic this just seemed a bit rather easy but</u>
<u n="485" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0607">let's not speak too soon I guess we'll find out we're completely <unclear>wrong</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0644">oh it's lovely though isn't it? just lovely</u>
<u n="488" who="S0607">so do you think this is the wine country? I don't know if we're like driving through Sonoma County which is like all wine stuff I dunno</u>
<u n="489" who="S0644">don't know <pause dur="short"/> it all looks very remote doesn't it?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0644" trans="overlap">very <pause dur="short"/> very <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> farm like really like like a farming community or agricultural ah there's deers down there</u>
<u n="492" who="S0607">I'm driving on the right yes exactly</u>
<u n="493" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's funny how you can get used to it like just adapting</u>
<u n="494" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I didn't <trunc>ex</trunc> I didn't expect this I don't know what I thought it would be like on the road to the coast</u>
<u n="495" who="S0644">I didn't think it'd be so farm like</u>
<u n="496" who="S0607">well actually I was worried that it would be mountain passes</u>
<u n="497" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0644">mind you this is we're not on it though are we? we've gotta get back on the the motorway <pause dur="short"/> cos this isn't <anon type="place"/> or is it <anon type="place"/>? it feels like it should be called <anon type="place"/> to tell you the truth</u>
<u n="499" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I think we're still we're still on that <unclear/> one</u>
<u n="500" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0607">I wonder if we've missed the <anon type="place"/> turning? I don't know how far to go before deciding <unclear/></u>
<u n="502" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0644">I'm enjoying it too much to <unclear>wanna go</unclear> back</u>
<u n="504" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0644">let's just keep going</u>
<u n="506" who="S0607">see where we end up <pause dur="short"/> if I get a chance to pull in I will cos all these poor locals are just totally stuck behind me</u>
<u n="507" who="S0644">oh really? <pause dur="short"/> they could take over to be fair like you can see there's nothing coming <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0644">we've done loads of trips <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0607">oh <unclear>man</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I don't really want to properly pull over <unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh piss off</u>
<u n="512" who="S0607">I don't wanna get into the</u>
<u n="513" who="S0644">oh is that skunk?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0607">actually I'm just gonna check because on here I had how many miles it was to the turn off <pause dur="short"/> right we're still going</u>
<u n="515" who="S0644">mm? what? no?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
