<text id="S4PC">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:31:24</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0017 S0018</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Money, Government policy</topics>
		<activity>A father explaining tax and government policy to his daughter.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0017">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Woburn, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>35 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Accountant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner; German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">so can you explain to me what is the fifty P tax rate?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0017">the fifty P tax rate was instituted I think by the Labour government erm to tax people earning over a hundred and fifty thousand a year <pause dur="short"/> erm to try and recognise that they were suffering far less under any sort of restraints than those of us at the lower end of the scales</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">so what that means they get? Why is called the fifty P tax rate?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0017">because they pay fifty P on every pound taxed</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">do they have a limit tax free first? So they can</u>
<u n="6" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yes so <pause dur="short"/> everybody well nearly everybody gets a tax free allowance <pause dur="short"/> I think mine is something like eight thousand and seventy or something like that at the moment <pause dur="short"/> and so we all get that amount free but we were talking with your mother this morning <pause dur="short"/> she gets her teachers' pension and she gets a state pension and she gets her earnings <pause dur="short"/> and she's always worried because she ends up paying a lot of tax on her teachers' pension because the state pension is taxable but they don't deduct tax from it <pause dur="short"/> so they have to take twice as much tax from your teachers' pension to make up for it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">where's the logic in that?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0017">it makes sense <pause dur="short"/> it's an relatively straight forward way of doing it <pause dur="short"/> the tax <pause dur="short"/> the income tax system in the country is not over complicated <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> the complications come in all the provisions and allowances and offsets and things around it</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">so why won't they? Why if it's taxable they don't deduct tax from it?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0017">because it's an interesting question <pause dur="short"/> I don't know the true answer <pause dur="short"/> I guess it is that it is much simpler for the pensions the state pensioner part of the organisation just to pay out an an amount on a regular basis rather than have to do any computations <pause dur="short"/> so they know how much pension you're entitled to each week <pause dur="short"/> so they pay out that amount every week and leave the individual to sort out her tax <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">and how does one sort out one's tax in this country?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0017">it depends on how you're getting your income <pause dur="short"/> if you're employed in a company and you receive a wage or salary then it is your employer's responsibility to calculate and deduct the tax and pay it over to the Inland Revenue</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh</u>
<u n="14" who="S0017">erm if you are self employed it is then your responsibility to estimate in advance how much income you're going to have and calculate from that how much tax you're going to be due to pay and to make payments on account <pause dur="short"/> so that you don't end up having a massive tax arrears</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">okay and if you are employed by a company and you're paid a wage do you still have to declare your taxes every year? Or do some kind of form filling?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0017" trans="overlap">the <pause dur="short"/> you <pause dur="short"/> if you have very straight forward income in other words just a wage or salary from employment from one employment then it is very likely they won't ask you to complete a tax return every year</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018" trans="overlap">tax return <pause dur="short"/> that's what it's called yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0017" trans="overlap">if you have <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you have erm investment income erm somebody pays you rent for a property then you have different classes of income that are all taxed under different rules <pause dur="short"/> and then you would have to complete a tax return so that they can sort out what code to give to your employers to deduct tax and what arrangements you have to make about any other income that you're earning <pause dur="short"/> and you would then have to make payments on that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0017">and your expected to estimate ahead and make payments on account <pause dur="short"/> not just wait until the end of a year and work out how much you've earned and then pay the tax on that afterwards <pause dur="short"/> so being employed by somebody else is from a tax point of view the simplest way of dealing your tax affairs if you don't have lots of other sources of income</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">erm if you're earning like twenty grand</u>
<u n="22" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">apart from <pause dur="short"/> aside from the eight thousand tax free or whatever</u>
<u n="24" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">how many pence in the pound will you be paying?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0017">you you'd be paying <pause dur="short"/> if you were earning twenty thousand and you've got eight thousand tax free allowance then you're taxed on twelve thousand and you pay twenty percent on that which is</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">er that's not to bad</u>
<u n="28" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> twenty-four hundred <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018" trans="overlap">and if you're three thirty thousand?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0017">then you would still only pay at twenty percent <pause dur="short"/> I think the limit above which you start paying forty percent is thirty-four thousand <pause dur="short"/> something like that</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="32" who="S0017">erm <pause dur="short"/> so so you have to have an income of forty-two thousand before you start paying forty percent tax because you then take off from your gross income your tax free allowance</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018" trans="overlap">that's a big jump though isn't it <pause dur="short"/> sorry wait there <pause dur="short"/> so once you get above thirty-six thousand a year you get forty percent? You have to pay forty percent tax?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0017">once you're earning</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">so once you're earning forty-four thousand forty-two <pause dur="short"/> what did we say? Thirty-four or thirty-six?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0017">I can't give you the specific amount I'm working from memory but in general</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018" trans="overlap">okay but  do you mean  do you mean on top of the eight thousand tax free?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0017">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">oh so you would have to be earning forty-two thousand a year to</u>
<u n="40" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> before before you start paying tax at forty percent</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="42" who="S0017">and you pay tax at forty percent on your earnings above that so you still pay tax on your basic amount less after your free pay at twenty percent</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018" trans="overlap">huh? What? What's free pay?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0017">the tax free allowance</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> oh okay <pause dur="short"/> so that's eight thousand?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0017" trans="overlap">it's also called free pay <pause dur="short"/> it's the same as  There are different words that mean the same thing</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Er so but then you'd pay a certain amount up to twenty thousand <pause dur="short"/> a a certain amount of twenty percent</u>
<u n="48" who="S0017" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> you'd pay <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">oh so that so for example</u>
<u n="50" who="S0017" trans="overlap">so every everything up to thirty-four thousand you'd pay twenty percent <pause dur="short"/> everything above that you'd pay forty percent</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">ah okay</u>
<u n="52" who="S0017">you don't suddenly go on to paying everything at forty percent</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh right that's what I thought was the deal <pause dur="short"/> that seems quite logical</u>
<u n="54" who="S0017">mm <pause dur="short"/> and then the tax code that they give you <pause dur="short"/> if they work out that you're due to pay something like mm fourteen thousand pounds in tax then they would give you a tax code and that tax code then refers to tables and tells you you can work out the monthly amount of tax or the weekly amount of tax you're going to have to pay just from that code</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018" trans="overlap">and does that work <trunc>ou</trunc>?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0017" trans="overlap">without having specific figures I couldn't describe it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018" trans="overlap">but does that tax code work it out for the future or for the <trunc>p</trunc> retrospectively?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0017">it works it out <pause dur="short"/> it's essentially short term future</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0017">in other words it will work within a tax year</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0017">as long as you stay within the bounds <pause dur="short"/> if you <trunc>sudden</trunc> if you for the first half year you're earning twenty thousand and if the second half year you're earning seventy thousand then it wouldn't cope with that <pause dur="short"/> erm you would end up with having either an over or an under payment by the end of the year</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018">hmm <pause dur="short"/> and when they send you notification of a tax rebate</u>
<u n="64" who="S0017">mm mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">is that something that is generated from some kind of form that you have to fill in?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0017">not always <pause dur="short"/> sometimes if you're aware that you have over paid tax you can make a claim for a tax rebate</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0017">normally the tax rebates come because the Inland Revenue calculate your tax at the end of the year from a tax return and find that you have paid more because they had estimated you would pay more and your tax code was set higher <pause dur="short"/> for example when I stopped</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0017">paying higher rate tax <pause dur="short"/> they still assumed I would be paying higher rate tax so my code was set on that basis so I ended up getting a tax rebate at the end of the year</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">and is that the end of the calendar year or financial?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0017" trans="overlap">no the end of the tax year which ends on the fifth of April each year</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0017">it's not like some well there are loads of countries that do work their tax year to match the calendar year</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">hmm <pause dur="short"/> but do they also generate those tax rebates if you haven't done a tax return? If you are in a situation where you are supposedly being paid a wage by a an employer</u>
<u n="76" who="S0017" trans="overlap">if <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>on</trunc> they will normally send you the statement at the end of the year <pause dur="short"/> erm saying this is how we compute your tax code for next year</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0017">and that would give you a clue as to whether you in fact had over or under paid <pause dur="short"/> it's only if they acknowledge they have made a mistake in your coding for some reason and discovered it erm that they would then possibly make a rebate without you claiming</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0017">so it's always wise to keep an eye on your tax and make sure that you're paying roughly the right amount of tax</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and what other things are taken into account? Because in Spain I know it's er things like if you are renting or if you're paying a mortgage <pause dur="short"/> if you've made a charitable donation <pause dur="short"/> if you blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> blah blah blah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0017" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> when we were first married we used to get mortgage interest tax relief <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that's given to anybody at all now</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0017">erm I know it was reduced substantially and there may be some small element erm but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> if you're paying into a pension privately rather than through your employment then you get tax relief on your pension contributions <pause dur="short"/> if it's a recognised pension that you're paying into</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018" trans="overlap">so does that mean that the amount that you're paying into your pension gets it does that that amount doesn't get taxed?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0017">correct</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="88" who="S0017">it gets taxed when they pay you your pension <pause dur="short"/> not <unclear/> time</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> They'll get you in the end</u>
<u n="90" who="S0017">yes but that's <pause dur="short"/> I was arguing with your mother over this this morning <pause dur="short"/> she was getting all up tight that she's getting taxed on state pension and we've paid for it and so it is <pause dur="short"/> basically it's the same for everybody other than the extremely rich who can find ways around paying tax on all their moneys <pause dur="short"/> erm the rest of us <trunc>ex</trunc> pay very much the same sort of tax <pause dur="short"/> my mother <pause dur="short"/> one of the reasons she went to Australia was because she hated the tax system over here</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">why?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0017">erm mainly because I think she didn't fully understand it</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0017">and just thought it was unfair <pause dur="short"/> the tax that she paid on a fairly small income when she was working after my dad died</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">why was she paying? Why was she not happy with what she was paying?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0017">she just thought it was not right that as a widow and doing a a job and earning a relatively small amount that she shouldn't be paying tax on it <pause dur="short"/> so she used to get all worked up about it</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">but was it? I mean was</u>
<u n="98" who="S0017" trans="overlap">we're all in the same boat</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">but she still got her tax free sum and then  and then  I imagine that the tax that she paid was calculated in the band of her earnings no?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0017" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah she wasn't treated any differently to anybody else who worked or was in employment</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">so why did she feel it was unfair?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0017">erm <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">just because she was a widow</u>
<u n="104" who="S0017">there was never a completely logical reason for it just like there is never a completely logical for your mother gets upset about it so</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> there's women for you</u>
<u n="106" who="S0017">that's right yes <pause dur="short"/> one of the things arguments that's going on in the background at the moment <pause dur="short"/> we may hear more about it today in the budget is erm this child allowance <pause dur="short"/> when you were born and when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was born we were your mother used to be able to go to the post office and draw a child allowance every week <pause dur="short"/> and she had a a book with coupons in and</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0017">erm they're now trying to restrict child allowance to families earning less than the twenty percent tax rate entitles you to</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">well I agree</u>
<u n="110" who="S0017">so saying that anybody who was paying tax at forty percent should not have</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018" trans="overlap">so  anyone earning  anyone earning over forty-two grand say</u>
<u n="112" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that then discriminates <pause dur="short"/> if you have a husband and wife both working both earning say thirty thousand so together their income is sixty thousand they would get child allowance but a husband and wife or a couple living together where the husband is earning forty-two thousand say and the wife is not earning anything <pause dur="short"/> they would loose the child allowance <pause dur="short"/> so I can understand the arguments that it's unfair</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> well I mean we <pause dur="short"/> despite being you know the era of single parent families and stuff <pause dur="short"/> it's still assumed that the kids going to have two parents so why don't they just do it? Like calculate it on the basis of what the parents earn together</u>
<u n="114" who="S0017" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> well that's that is my thoughts of the solution to it <pause dur="short"/> again going back quite a few years it we used to have the option of couples could opt to be taxed <pause dur="short"/> the wife taxed with the husband <pause dur="short"/> so that their income was considered jointly <pause dur="short"/> and what they ought to do is say erm for parents who are receiving child benefit <pause dur="short"/> they should be <trunc>a</trunc> have the option of saying we wish to be taxed as a couple rather than as two individuals</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0017">most of the time it was an advantage for people to be taxed as individuals but if they're deciding to tax or limit child allowance to those paying the lower rate of tax then the couples ought to be able to use their individual free pay</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0017">you know tax free allowance <pause dur="short"/> because if a woman stops work or if either partner stops work and has no income they effectively loose that eight thousand odd tax free allowance</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0017">so it makes sense <pause dur="short"/> it's more equitable</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0017">if they are able to use their tax free allowance even if they're not working</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">complicated running a country isn't it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">and what do you think about the fifty odd abolition of the fifty percent ie the fifty P tax?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0017" trans="overlap">I I I do not believe that paying ten P a pound more in tax <pause dur="short"/> whether it's the difference between forty P and a fifty P rate at a hundred and fifty thousand makes people decide not to invest in businesses <pause dur="short"/> not to start new businesses erm or to want to leave the country</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0017">I don't believe that is sufficient motivation to make people make those decisions so I think the arguments about it are spurious</u>
<u n="129" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> so you'd keep it?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0017">yes <pause dur="short"/> in the present  in the present  climate I wouldn't change it</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0017">I I think it is an unnecessary argument and it's been made into a political argument but it's not <pause dur="short"/> it it's spurious again</u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">it's quite heavy though having to pay half of your income</u>
<u n="134" who="S0017">there were people paying in excess of eighty percent of their income of tax in the days when I first started work <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't one of them <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0018" trans="overlap">blimey</u>
<u n="136" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">you're just a slave then <pause dur="short"/> you might as well be on Jobseeker's benefit stacking shelves at Tesco's <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0017">ah well I'd cut that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0018">and what do you think about the other measures that they're erm allowing more tax free chunks of money for?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0017" trans="overlap">I I agree with erm improving increasing the tax free allowance at the lower rate <pause dur="short"/> they had I can't remember which government introduced it and it was probably ten or twelve years ago they introduced a ten P tax rate <pause dur="short"/> and that made sense <pause dur="short"/> it gave more relief to people that they were the lower end of the scale</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018">but shouldn't everybody just pay fifteen percent of their earnings in tax?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">isn't that fair?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0017" trans="overlap">we we are in a welfare state and the money has to come for the welfare state <pause dur="short"/> it's not reasonable for somebody who can barely exist on their income to pay the same because they end up paying a much higher proportion for cost because they are both taxed and paying National Insurance</u>
<u n="145" who="S0018" trans="overlap">true <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0017">erm so I agree with the lower level incomes being taxed at a lower rate and people who are earning more being taxed at a high rate <pause dur="short"/> I don't believe that a fifty percent tax rate is a disincentive to people starting and running businesses <pause dur="short"/> erm moving on from that I think it is outrageous that people who are risking other people's money <pause dur="short"/> in other words you know senior managers in business are risking nothing but their career should be paid these obscene bonuses and share deals and so on</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0017">erm at one time I had some sympathy for the view that everybody who worked to their maximum ability whether they were sweeping the road or running a business should earn the same <pause dur="short"/> and I think that's almost a Communist</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018" trans="overlap">you little Communist</u>
<u n="150" who="S0017">yes <pause dur="short"/> reds under the bed <pause dur="short"/> erm but I why should somebody whose skills enable them to manage thousands of people be greater than somebody whose skills enable them to manage a broom? You know there should be a small increase for responsibility but the main payment should be for effort and the effort proportional to their ability</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018">yeah if you say that there should be a reward for ability that kind of goes against what you said earlier because it you know people aren't born</u>
<u n="152" who="S0017">there should be <pause dur="short"/> when I say for ability for degrees of responsibility there should be some reward</u>
<u n="153" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0017">but it it has got totally out of proportion</u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I agree</u>
<u n="156" who="S0017">yeah I I think that a a bonus of fifteen percent of anybody's salary is a perfectly adequate erm motivating reward</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018" trans="overlap">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I think  I think  it's important because knowing human nature we're motivated by incentive <pause dur="short"/> and in this kind of society I think we are motivated by money because that's that helps you buy things and people seem to want to buy things more than they want to be morally competent</u>
<u n="158" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I only agree to a limited extent <pause dur="short"/> different people are driven more or less by money but for me the amount of money at the end of the day as long as I've got enough to pay my mortgage and have a holiday and run a car and so on has never been that critical</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0017">erm <pause dur="short"/> what I objected to was where I thought erm I was being unfairly discriminated against <pause dur="short"/> and I remember having a long discussion when on another occasion <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were out in America in a company in America and he I knew salary reviews had been done <pause dur="short"/> and I asked him what mine was <pause dur="short"/> and I thought it was unfair <pause dur="short"/> and I said l think that is unfair</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">what had he given you a a rise?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0017">A much lower rise than I believed was merited and I believed was reflected in what others on the same sort of level and the same sort of responsibility were getting</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">hmm mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0017">and I made it very clear that I thought it was personal <pause dur="short"/> and ultimately it proved it was</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0017">erm but I I didn't erm having made that objection I then sort of just carried on as normal <pause dur="short"/> it didn't affect my work because I enjoyed the job I was doing and that I think is a much greater motivating factor than the money</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> true <pause dur="short"/> and I see what you mean but I think if if you take away the incentive of a little bit more money for more responsibility there would be a lot of people that weren't motivated to go for it <pause dur="short"/> I think it would be nice if we could all live in a world where everyone was the same and everybody was treated the same but I think that a lot of</u>
<u n="168" who="S0017" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018">I mean for example scientists and people who have a passion for a certain field will get their you know their recompense at their how do you say it? Their erm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0017" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> reward for their abilities?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018" trans="overlap">their yeah <pause dur="short"/> they'll get their reward from from the scientific discoveries and scientific investigation and er kudos in their field as opposed to getting the money</u>
<u n="172" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">and I don't think money there is so much of a of an incentive <pause dur="short"/> and your musicians who do it out of love of music and you know but</u>
<u n="174" who="S0017" trans="overlap">but I I think there are I I think in in each of those categories you've described and in the rest of the categories of people you will find there are those who enjoy their job and who work well because they enjoy it <pause dur="short"/> there are those</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018" trans="overlap">but maybe what I am saying is that maybe a lot of the cutting edge things that we've got <pause dur="short"/> the improvements in technology <pause dur="short"/> then again <pause dur="short"/> do we really need them? Have brought have come from an incentive to earn money and to make as much money as possible</u>
<u n="176" who="S0017" trans="overlap">I  I would  I would be very interested if it was possible to get statistics on that</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0017">I I would believe that a higher proportion would come from those who were motivated by the search rather than by what they were being paid for the search</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">but a lot of people would be doing it to be paid the money <pause dur="short"/> that their whole <unclear/> would be</u>
<u n="180" who="S0017">erm even if you look at entrepreneurs erm starting businesses  I don't  I don't think many of them would be motivated by just being able to earn unlimited amounts of money based on the success of their venture <pause dur="short"/> because they are also taking a risk <pause dur="short"/> erm difficult to put into words <pause dur="short"/> I think in in our community as many people other than those who consider work to be a drudge and go in and just want to switch off when they get there <pause dur="short"/> go through the day <pause dur="short"/> come away as soon as the bell goes <pause dur="short"/> erm are having once got into the job and got to the point where they're managing to live or just managing to live on the money they get <pause dur="short"/> I don't think their effort is going to change much long term for the opportunity of getting more money</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I guess you've got a broad spectrum of personalities and how they react to motivation incentives and</u>
<u n="182" who="S0017" trans="overlap">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>am</trunc> ambition irrespective of motivation elsewhere <pause dur="short"/> they motivate themselves because they want to do more and more and more</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0017">the more they learn the more they see the opportunities of doing more things <pause dur="short"/> not necessarily in terms of generating money but in terms of getting satisfaction from the job</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0017">is this a convenient point to pause? How many have we done?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">yeah just a little bit more</u>
<u n="188" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">erm so yeah it was more important to get a job that you enjoy than one that you that pays a lot of money <pause dur="short"/> but what do you think is a necessary salary nowadays to be able to say what you know to be able to provide for a family? To run a car? To pay a mortgage? To have a holiday once a year?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0017">er lot depends on where you're living and how much you can get your basic accommodation for <pause dur="short"/> and whether you're doing it as an individual or as a family</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0017">erm <pause dur="short"/> if it was a family I would say you probably need a joint income of thirty thousand to be able to have some form of house car holiday</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">and as a single person to be able to afford a house and a car and a holiday once a year?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0017">oh <pause dur="short"/> fifty thousand a year</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">fifty thousand? Are you joking?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0017">well single people have a much more expensive lifestyle than couples</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0017">erm I <pause dur="short"/> the the whole thing is you you can manage to have all those things at most levels say above twenty-four thousand <pause dur="short"/> erm depending on how you manage your life</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0017">erm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">and do you imagine that you'll be spending a third of that on your accommodation? Because obviously in some areas accommodation is a lot more expensive than that?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0017" trans="overlap">yeah yeah obviously <pause dur="short"/> but  that is  that is probably the biggest variable of the things where you have no choice <pause dur="short"/> you've got to have somewhere to live somehow <pause dur="short"/> whereas with food you can eat cheap <pause dur="short"/> you can eat expensive</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0017">erm holidays you can have economic and be expensive <pause dur="short"/> cars you can go and have a new car when you when your other one gets dirty</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0017">it it's very difficult to say what is an acceptable living wage</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
</body>
</text>
