<text id="S4RF">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0162</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Writing a job application (for a media post), work, job interviews</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about a job application that ANON is going to apply for.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0162">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Leeds, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Producer/journalist (radio)</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Hindi -- Advanced; Spanish -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">so what do you think is one of the most important key responsibilities or competencies involved in the job?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0162" trans="overlap">an an understanding of what multimedia is and showing I'm I've gotta show um my experience in different</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018" trans="overlap">and what? What like multimedia being <trunc>s</trunc>?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0162">being audio um podcasting video <pause dur="short"/> film <pause dur="short"/> stills <pause dur="short"/> using um social media sites</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0162">um websites an understanding of websites I guess <pause dur="short"/> their website <pause dur="short"/> it'd probably be good actually to reference their website a couple of times</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">well well you said  well you said  that you'd been looking at it on a regular basis for a long time haven't you?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0162" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah and they they want</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">and what what kind of stuff do they put on their websites? Is it about their projects?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0162">it's it's about their <trunc>pro</trunc> projects and because it's a a charity they kind of have to show what they're doing it's like it's an issue of accountability basically <pause dur="short"/> so they'll have either you know <trunc>s</trunc> photos or short videos or audio um which is kind of showing what the project is <pause dur="short"/> so for example if they've set up a radio station in Iraq</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0162">they would have some of the audio of a a discussion that was held or something like that</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0162">but that I think that links into accountability</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">well you've got  you've got  experience in radio broadcasting and social network media haven't you <pause dur="short"/> what about cos the filming aspect seems quite important have you got experience in that?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0162">well I worked at um I've worked at two <pause dur="short"/> I've worked at one I I did some freelance work at a TV company but it was a while ago <pause dur="short"/> and I also did some freelance work with a TV journalist <pause dur="short"/> so I've done shooting <pause dur="short"/> editing</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018" trans="overlap">when was that?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0162">that was when I was trying to get a job at the BBC <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">was that in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0162">it was all over the place <pause dur="short"/> it was kind of like round the Midlands mostly</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">ah cool <pause dur="short"/> how long did you do that for?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0162">I just did a few I think I did about five or ten <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember about five five or six times I just helped out a guy who was making pieces for TV and I'd just go and help him</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> what was that? What was he doing it about?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0162"><trunc>N</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> normally news items <pause dur="short"/> so newsy kind of stories <pause dur="short"/> quite a lot of Asian stories</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0162">um so that was really good <pause dur="short"/> and also you know I'm practising editing and shooting in my own time with the help of a multimedia husband</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But I guess those skills are transferable cos you've been editing radio pieces for what ten years?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0162">mm about five six years but</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">but isn't it transferable?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0162">it is transferable but it's completely different software</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0162">and editing stills is er editing sorry visuals is is very different to just having one line of audio</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> but I guess the software changes so frequently nowadays though that if you</u>
<u n="34" who="S0162" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I think  I think  also that um you know it's about I think in some ways you're right they're transferable skills because it's about story boarding it thinking about what you know what is it gonna look like as an entire piece <pause dur="short"/> what's the story you're telling <pause dur="short"/> scripting it which I  which I  do <pause dur="short"/> um and you know I want to brush up on my film and editing abilities and the way to do that would be to be in a job where I was doing it or had the opportunity to do it</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0162">but I think also a big part of the roll is actually devising some of the teams about what they could do <pause dur="short"/> what they could make</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">where would the team? <trunc>Wh</trunc> is this like teams in different countries?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0162">yeah teams in different countries <pause dur="short"/> so it might be like you know you could oh you've gotta um it could be something like they're making a radio drama to um talk about health issues <pause dur="short"/> right? But the radio drama's going to be the vehicle to kind of inform people <pause dur="short"/> but they could then perhaps film one of the  one of the  days when they're all recording and they're in the studio they could do a really short film showing you know and then it would show the faces of the people involved and them all getting together and recording and um you know where they're recording how they're doing it <pause dur="short"/> or it could be that they talk to somebody about the radio drama <pause dur="short"/> who says how it's connected with them and inform them on health issues um</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">and how do they get that out there through radio and TV or internet or all of them?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0162">they're all different projects in different countries <pause dur="short"/> so they've actually like in some countries they'd have actually gone in and used erm the money to set up a radio station so</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">oh cool</u>
<u n="42" who="S0162">they'll you know pay for the  for the  place of the studios the equipment</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">ah and you'd be in charge of like the um training the people there too</u>
<u n="44" who="S0162">I'd I'd be there to help and advise them but also I'd be my main responsibility I think would be to get them to make material that I could then that could then go on the website <pause dur="short"/> so erm but yeah also help and support them and give them ideas just stuff and</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">that sounds like your perfect job it really does</u>
<u n="46" who="S0162">exactly it sounds really good</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">and they given an given you an idea of how much travel is involved?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0162">no it's mostly based in London it's saying but it it asks for an ability or willingness to travel to Asia and Africa <pause dur="short"/> they have projects in thirteen countries</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">what are the countries?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0162">um Iraq <pause dur="short"/> okay well actually we should probably think about if it says Asia and Africa <pause dur="short"/> in Africa I know they've got projects in like Somalia recently <pause dur="short"/> asia they've just done something in Cambodia India um</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">right so Somalia is when the whole sort of <trunc>risk</trunc></u>
<u n="52" who="S0162">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018"> part of the job description</u>
<u n="54" who="S0162">but that's a good question actually <pause dur="short"/> I need to brush up on that where are the? I think that kind of question though is going to be more of an interview question</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0162">not in an application form question</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">true <pause dur="short"/> true</u>
<u n="58" who="S0162">what do you think?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">no definitely cos you don't <pause dur="short"/> I mean you can say in your application form how you have that you do sympathise a lot and you're enthusiastic in the you know that you're <trunc>re</trunc> really interested in what they're doing and that you can  you can  say that you've been checking out their website on a</u>
<u n="60" who="S0162">and I can also say that I've travelled extensively um particularly in India <pause dur="short"/> I've lived abroad <pause dur="short"/> I've worked</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018" trans="overlap">and you've trained people and</u>
<u n="62" who="S0162">I've trained people and I've worked abroad <pause dur="short"/> so that shows a kind of</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> but you've trained people in Spain and the Czech Republic haven't you</u>
<u n="64" who="S0162">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">so that's that kind of covers that base</u>
<u n="66" who="S0162">um and I've travelled <pause dur="short"/> I did the <trunc>ki</trunc> I did the Cambodia thing last year so</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">I did the Cambodia thing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0162">yeah you know <pause dur="short"/> but it's er but it's showing that there's kind of an understanding of the world I think</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0162">and that I've visited developing countries and um you know cos for some people it's not an easy thing to go to a developing country</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">well that's what I was saying about this job in Thailand</u>
<u n="72" who="S0162">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">I mean I know it's not that much of a <trunc>develop</trunc> developing country but still when you're in a culture that you don't know anything about you don't speak the language it's an enormous challenge to be able to operate you know do your job to the best of your abilities when you're in situation that's completely alien to you</u>
<u n="74" who="S0162">exactly</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">so</u>
<u n="76" who="S0162">exactly um so and you know I haven't lived in India but I've been there for like I went that time for about six weeks or something</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0162">which I think is a a pretty solid period of time</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">definitely and you've lived <pause dur="short"/> how long did you live in Spain?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0162">about three years <pause dur="short"/> three years</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">that shows that you've lived in a different culture and</u>
<u n="82" who="S0162">exactly</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">and worked</u>
<u n="84" who="S0162">exactly</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">and learnt the language and</u>
<u n="86" who="S0162">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018">so</u>
<u n="88" who="S0162">I'm just wondering whether there could be something in there about thinking about India and travelling and Cambodia and travelling but like when we were in Cambodia we went to a lot of kind of social projects and that kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> so maybe there's something in that isn't there about</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018">definitely <pause dur="short"/> or you could say as a personal <trunc>in</trunc> a-blob-lob-al-a as a personal interest um I enjoy travelling and it um not just visiting the touristic sites but <trunc>a</trunc> finding out what's happening on a grass roots level in different social projects <pause dur="short"/> for example in Cambodia last year we duduluduludula whatever</u>
<u n="90" who="S0162">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we should well I think that's an interesting point actually  I think that's an interesting point actually</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0162">um so yeah you know you've just gotta go for these things really haven't you?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">definitely <pause dur="short"/> and what else did they say? With the competencies you've managed to I reckon that you're you've had experience and you've demonstrated quite a lot of the competencies <pause dur="short"/> um like you've led teams you've worked in teams <pause dur="short"/> influencing and persuading</u>
<u n="94" who="S0162">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">I think is probably quite important <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>co</trunc> communication? I don't know whether you should mention actually focus on communication because it your job over the past six years has been facilitating communication and broadcasting so maybe</u>
<u n="96" who="S0162">oh yeah and having to find people speak to them convince them to do radio so that's all about communication</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">and creative thinking</u>
<u n="98" who="S0162">that's something I need to talk about creative thinking</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">definitely but not only the creative thinking but to be able to transform those ideas into practical reality <pause dur="short"/> then again you've talked about that a lot in the first question</u>
<u n="100" who="S0162">yeah cos that's</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">on the application</u>
<u n="102" who="S0162">that's exactly what that question is about isn't it</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">what about editorial judgement? I guess that's <pause dur="short"/> are you?  Are you?  I mean you have an editor no? Or do you do a lot of the <trunc>edit</trunc> editing?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0162">yeah but I have to have editorial judgement because the piece that you know I have to be making it in an editorial way <pause dur="short"/> I do have an editor who then will listen to stuff but you know it's my responsibility basically <pause dur="short"/> she may  she may  advise me on on things <pause dur="short"/> but then I also advise people on editorial as well</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0162">so people in the  I'll talk to them about how they so the story how to balance it how to that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0162">so um it <trunc>w</trunc> and this isn't this is not like a senior producer's job it's a producer's job so there would be somebody that I'm reporting to if you like</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm just wondering whether you can say talk about your job and kind of cover a lot of these requirements</u>
<u n="110" who="S0162">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018">in a short paragraph <pause dur="short"/> for example your job already encapsulates sharing skills with others <pause dur="short"/> experience of delivering training as a teacher trainer <pause dur="short"/> um understanding the values and the the guidelines</u>
<u n="112" who="S0162">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">um health and safety</u>
<u n="114" who="S0162">well yeah I think it's quite a consideration because if the projects are in developing countries obviously um and not just developing countries in terms of poverty but also often in politically unstable countries</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="116" who="S0162">so you have to have an understanding <pause dur="short"/> so if you're advising a team to do something you know you can't you have to take into consideration the fact that there could be a curfew or you know</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="118" who="S0162">they can't go out at <trunc>n</trunc> night because there's trouble at the moment or that</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018">I was thinking more along the lines of don't put your cup of tea too close to your laptop</u>
<u n="120" who="S0162">well that's also important as well <pause dur="short"/> um cos it says look delivering output in risky contexts</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0162">so</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">yeah well it seems that you've got <pause dur="short"/> oh it just sounds like your dream job though <pause dur="short"/> cos do you remember when you were thinking of applying for a job with Oxfam?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0162">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">Cos I could</u>
<u n="126" who="S0162">I did apply for it actually <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't like this <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't so kind of hands on and</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018">well it didn't have media</u>
<u n="128" who="S0162">it was I think it was a press officey job or something</u>
<u n="129" who="S0018">oh I guess that's quite media related isn't it?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0162" trans="overlap">just selling press selling stuff to press really <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so it it's it's an exciting time <pause dur="short"/> it's a very exciting time</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018">ee <pause dur="short"/> and how long to you reckon you'd have to spend in London? Do you think you'd you'd move down there? Would <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> be able to move down</u>
<u n="132" who="S0162">well</u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">with you?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0162">it I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I think we'd probably still base ourselves here because it says three or four or five days <pause dur="short"/> but so I'm assuming there's some kind of um discussion around that</u>
<u n="135" who="S0018">they're flexible</u>
<u n="136" who="S0162">they're flexible <pause dur="short"/> so um if it was for example just three or four days a week I'd just I'd have to look at renting somewhere for three days a week <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">haven't you  haven't you  got any friends down there you could crash on their floors?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0162">this is it We've got I've got friends and stuff that I could ask and also</u>
<u n="139" who="S0018">have you have your has your brother still got the flat in London? Or is he renting it out?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0162">he's still got the house but as far as I know all the rooms are rented out <pause dur="short"/> but I can always ask</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018">or sleep in the bath</u>
<u n="142" who="S0162">or sleep in the bath <pause dur="short"/> and yeah between me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we've got loads of friends down there <pause dur="short"/> so it could be you know sometimes other people are working away or whatever or they wouldn't mind renting out a room for three nights a week</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">yeah true</u>
<u n="144" who="S0162">I don't  I don't  see that as a big issue and <trunc>ev</trunc></u>
<u n="145" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ooh <pause dur="short"/> would the  would the  salary be London weighted?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0162">probably I don't know anything about the salary</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">that would be cool</u>
<u n="148" who="S0162">but even even say er I had to commute at the beginning it is only one and a half hours on the train to London and you know plenty of people from <anon type="place"/> that I know go down to London two three times a week</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018">Wendy does it yeah quite a lot doesn't she?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0162">exactly <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does it</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018">then it <pause dur="short"/> when I was working in on the other side of <anon type="place"/> it I used to <trunc>l</trunc> yeah I used to allow an hour and forty-five minutes just to be sure</u>
<u n="152" who="S0162">exactly <pause dur="short"/> so and I you know in fact maybe it's I don't know do you think it's something I should mention in the cos they can see my address so they know I'm based in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0018">yeah but they will probably assume that you are based in <anon type="place"/> because of your job and</u>
<u n="154" who="S0162">oh yeah you're right  you're right  so they wouldn't really need to</u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">then again I mean if you're thinking about commuting three days a week you'd probably save <pause dur="short"/> it would probably cost just as much to commute as it would to rent out</u>
<u n="156" who="S0162">yeah it's true <pause dur="short"/> I mean I ideally I'd like to find you know a friend's room that I could you know</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018">where's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0162">she's in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and er she used to have a house where there was a spare little room and we always used to joke about it cos I was like and I stayed there a few times and and she was like you know it would be perfect if you got a job here cos you could just rent it but she hasn't got it any more <pause dur="short"/> but there's enough of a network of people and even you know at the beginning I don't mind crashing on someone's floor a bit</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0162">so you know <pause dur="short"/> I think it's about the job I mean I location doesn't worry me at all <pause dur="short"/> but I don't and and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in London like two <pause dur="short"/> he'll be in London at least two days a week</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0162">from now <pause dur="short"/> this week he was there from Wednesday to Thursday Friday working</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">but so they pay to put him up when he's there?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0162">yeah he gets paid</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh cool <pause dur="short"/> and what about his friends? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0162"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/><pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they wouldn't mind if I crashed on their floor <pause dur="short"/> there's quite a few of them actually so um <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>th</trunc> I I you know I'm I'm it's pretty I think it'll be pretty okay <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">it'll be doable definitely</u>
<u n="168" who="S0162">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018">are you still thinking of er buying a place up here though if?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0162">yeah I think we'll still buy somewhere here so we'll still <pause dur="short"/> we're always gonna have a <anon type="place"/> base cos we've got family here <pause dur="short"/> so yeah we'll definitely still buy something up this way and um yeah you know spend a bit of time in London <pause dur="short"/> I think it'd be nice to work in London</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018">it would be <pause dur="short"/> ar it's such a <pause dur="short"/> it'd be nice to have a a base here but be able to</u>
<u n="172" who="S0162">exactly work in  work in  London and get a bit of the London vibe</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0162">for a few days of the week and um it's a bit more exciting I think to work in London</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018">definitely it's more things are more creative <pause dur="short"/> there's more opportunities <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot more I mean up here if you wanna go out and see something or do something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it kind of like seems that you have to wait until something is on whereas in London you just say okay I wanna go out tonight</u>
<u n="176" who="S0162" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018">you just check what's on and</u>
<u n="178" who="S0162">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> I think for media it's a good place to be <pause dur="short"/> I think in terms of the industry there's so much going on in London that it's a good place to be <pause dur="short"/> but I'm not you know I'm not going to think about the practicalities of it yet</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0162">I'm just going to concentrate on it stage by stage and you know if if I get an interview that's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> if I don't then I can go back to them and talk to them about <pause dur="short"/> I've made a contact now so</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">yep I think that's important <pause dur="short"/> especially if you if you're able to er even I mean even if you don't get an interview maybe you could ask just to come in and chat to them because you're really interested in what they're doing</u>
<u n="182" who="S0162" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018">and maybe collaborate on a freelance <pause dur="short"/> would would your boss?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0162">even ask just to shadow</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0162">so you know whoever did get this job offer to shadow or</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">could you not get an attachment? If you <trunc>did</trunc> if you weren't to get the job could you not get an attachment?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0162">it has to be advertised <pause dur="short"/> the job has to still be advertised <pause dur="short"/> there has to be an attachment for you to go for</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0162">um <pause dur="short"/> but who knows <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? Who knows? I think it will be a very competitive job but um</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">do you know anyone else who's applying for it?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0162">no <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really wanna tell lots of people in case <pause dur="short"/> in case they haven't seen it and they decide to apply for it</u>
<u n="193" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0018">shh top secret</u>
<u n="195" who="S0162">although it is on a web you know on the website so we'll see what happens <pause dur="short"/> so what about you? How's your job hunting going?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0018">yeah fine <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad actually to see the process that you're going through writing your job applications <pause dur="short"/> cos I just thought it was me that took so long over them</u>
<u n="197" who="S0162">oh no I take I'm taking ages <pause dur="short"/> I've been really slow but it's good <pause dur="short"/> it's and I don't think you should rush them do you?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> no no definitely not rush them but I was just surprised at how many hours you have to put in into writing it and then editing it as well and then proof reading it <pause dur="short"/> and then checking the content checking this</u>
<u n="199" who="S0162">it's a job to get a job</u>
<u n="200" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the one that I was going for was um a lot of proof reading and copy editing <pause dur="short"/> you know it had a big  a big  part of the job was proof reading and copy editing eh editing <pause dur="short"/> so I thought if my CV and application aren't well written and I'm not even going to get a chance to get invited for interview but</u>
<u n="201" who="S0162">it's pretty hard nowadays applying for jobs</u>
<u n="202" who="S0018">well I just think it's yeah it's it's even more important cos there are so many people going for the jobs it's even more important to get your job application and your CV and your covering letter to</u>
<u n="203" who="S0162">it's like</u>
<u n="204" who="S0018">to convey exactly what you</u>
<u n="205" who="S0162">what they say <pause dur="short"/> but also what is it about your application that's gonna be different? Say there's like a hundred people going for this job <pause dur="short"/> they've all got the skills</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0162">you know what is it? There's got to be something in there that shines out <pause dur="short"/> there's got to be something that they connect with because if they just go through all of them going yep same kind of experience same kind of skills</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0162">what is it? So</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018">definitely but I found cos you have to write it in quite a formal tone <pause dur="short"/> you know you were saying try and make sure you sound enthusiastic and</u>
<u n="211" who="S0162">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0018">it's quite difficult to convey that when you're still trying to follow the the formality of the <pause dur="short"/> cos er like a covering letter is a formal letter isn't it and</u>
<u n="213" who="S0162" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I bet you did I mean the bit we saw you did sound enthusiastic you just needed to up it a bit and you did <pause dur="short"/> it's just by it doesn't mean that you have to be um you know kind of too cheesy <pause dur="short"/> but it's just some of the terms that you put in and some of the</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I love your company</u>
<u n="215" who="S0162">you know it's understanding like the brand or whatever it is and showing that you understand it <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="216" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0162">um you know saying why you're passionate about it <pause dur="short"/> I guess</u>
<u n="218" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> would you use that word passionate?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0162">it's a good question because I think I have put it <pause dur="short"/> I might have put something about <pause dur="short"/> well I've written I would love to work for you innit</u>
<u n="220" who="S0018">innit as in?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0162">isn't it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0162">um that's that obviously that's not gonna go on the final edit but um er I think I've put somewhere that I have also had a passion for the work</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">oh that's okay <pause dur="short"/> that sounds better that I am passionate about <pause dur="short"/> I dream about it every night</u>
<u n="225" who="S0162">and I've talked about how I've always you know I've been aware of their work for a long time <pause dur="short"/> um visiting the website <pause dur="short"/> keeping up to date with the work of the charity</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0162">looking at ways for promoting the stories for the audiences I work with <pause dur="short"/> so I have actually done pieces on some of the projects that World Service the World Service um that the organisation um has done in India <pause dur="short"/> and kind of tried to relate that to British Indian communities</u>
<u n="228" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0162">so yeah you know <pause dur="short"/> I think there's a fine line between you know you've got you've just gotta be careful not to be too cheesy but you have to be honest</u>
<u n="230" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think the enthusiasm is something that probably comes over more in interview though doesn't it</u>
<u n="231" who="S0162">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">it's very difficult to put yourself over on paper <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot easier to communicate that face to face</u>
<u n="233" who="S0162">sometimes but sometimes interviews can be a complete nightmare</u>
<u n="234" who="S0018">oh God yeah I'm a shivering wreck in interviews <pause dur="short"/> then again I think the experience teaching and getting up and <trunc>stand</trunc> getting up standing up in front of you know thirty odd people <pause dur="short"/> not odd people but</u>
<u n="235" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0018">thirty odd people um helps you develop those skills of not not minding so much being in the focus and</u>
<u n="237" who="S0162">exactly you know and I mean what I don't like about interviews is or the interviews I've been to most recently is that kind of feeling as you walk in and there's a panel of people say three or four <pause dur="short"/> and they're all making notes and like every time you say something and they're like scribble something down or they tick something or they but they don't show any emotion at all</u>
<u n="238" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0162">and you're just it's it's kind of weird <pause dur="short"/> it's like someone once told me that if they're writing things down after you um answered a question it's a good sign</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0162">because it means that they're taking notes and and obviously you've said something right</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">nowadays isn't it all about ticking boxes though and not actually writing</u>
<u n="243" who="S0162">yeah that's true ticking</u>
<u n="244" who="S0018">tick tick cross</u>
<u n="245" who="S0162">but um I went for this one job where I had to go for three interviews</u>
<u n="246" who="S0018">three?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0162">yeah <pause dur="short"/> an application form and then three interviews</u>
<u n="248" who="S0018">that's a bit excessive</u>
<u n="249" who="S0162">I know <pause dur="short"/> one of them was like a practical session <pause dur="short"/> the there was a panel interview and then there was a one to one interview which I failed on</u>
<u n="250" who="S0018">what were they three separate occasions or three?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0162">three separate occasions</u>
<u n="252" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="253" who="S0162">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was quite crazy actually</u>
<u n="254" who="S0018">I was surprised at the different that it's very task-based a lot of interviews nowadays <pause dur="short"/> it's obviously formal chats when they're asking you about your CV and you know you can expect questions like what would you do in this circumstance or what what do you think about this aspect of blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but I had to do actual tasks <pause dur="short"/> I had to give a I had to prepare and give a presentation <pause dur="short"/> oh you remember?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0162">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> and that was crazy because they they asked me to to <trunc>critic</trunc> critically evaluate their products</u>
<u n="257" who="S0162">oh no</u>
<u n="258" who="S0018">and obviously you don't want <pause dur="short"/> you you have to fulfil the task but then you're thinking okay I have to my feedback has to be critical <pause dur="short"/> so you know you have to give some suggestions for improvement though but also you don't wanna completely slate the company that you're trying to get a job with</u>
<u n="259" who="S0162" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> say how rubbish they are <pause dur="short"/> yeah that doesn't really  that doesn't really  help at all <pause dur="short"/> I always think that actually sometimes the hardest thing is even though you know it in your head is just when they say why why do you want the job? Or why would you be good for the job?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0162">you know <pause dur="short"/> and it's like oo</u>
<u n="262" who="S0018">but those are kind of questions that you can prepare for <pause dur="short"/> I get  I get  more scared when they ask me questions that you have to quickly think up a a concise yet effective response in a matter of milliseconds</u>
<u n="263" who="S0162">so what have you done when have you been in a situation where you can't answer the question?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I said oh I'd have to do more research about that I couldn't tell you I I couldn't say right now what I would do in that situation</u>
<u n="265" who="S0162">and did you get the job?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0018">well I got offered the assistant position of the job</u>
<u n="267" who="S0162">oh well that's alright</u>
<u n="268" who="S0018">but I think that's because I <trunc>sh</trunc> I was when I was asking them questions I was asking them questions about whether there was a lot of support given to new new intake staff and</u>
<u n="269" who="S0162" trans="overlap">oh right that's why they handed you the assistant</u>
<u n="270" who="S0018">I've <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos I think I didn't pitch myself as very confident <pause dur="short"/> because obviously you know I've always been a teacher and I think you develop a lot of transferable skills as a teacher but when you go into a job that's office based when you're used to having spent you know most of your working life in a classroom interacting with people <pause dur="short"/> and that's your job as opposed to sitting there ploughing through paper work and <trunc>p</trunc> managing projects <pause dur="short"/> then again I mean <trunc>ma</trunc> er classroom teaching is all about managing projects really isn't it</u>
<u n="271" who="S0162">managing people</u>
<u n="272" who="S0018">I can't remember what the question was that they asked me that I couldn't that I didn't know how to answer <pause dur="short"/> oh no it was about assessment procedures</u>
<u n="273" who="S0162">I don't like it already <pause dur="short"/> assessment procedures <pause dur="short"/> ugh <pause dur="short"/> sounds terrible</u>
<u n="274" who="S0018">no I can't remember exactly what the wording was but no when when I didn't have any knowledge of that question because I had no previous experience in the field <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't too much of a faux pas to say I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but it's when they ask you of a</u>
<u n="275" who="S0162" trans="overlap">I think that when you answer as being honest is good</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018">yeah true</u>
<u n="277" who="S0162">it's like actually you know I don't know this but I would  I would  go and research it <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm more likely to try and make up an answer if I didn't know <pause dur="short"/> but that's not necessarily the best technique for an interview <pause dur="short"/> or um answer a different question <pause dur="short"/> you know like you go into an interview you have all these pre prepared answers and then they don't ask you the questions it's really frustrating</u>
<u n="278" who="S0018">I'd say it is the ability to think on your feet isn't it</u>
<u n="279" who="S0162">yeah and then afterwards I always like to ask at least two or three questions cos they always say have you got any questions? And I I don't know I always feel weird if I don't so</u>
<u n="280" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> although it's good to say no I think you've covered everything</u>
<u n="281" who="S0162">yeah that's a good one <pause dur="short"/> I guess you could <pause dur="short"/> you were very thorough</u>
<u n="282" who="S0018">oh I might write that down actually <pause dur="short"/> that's a good one</u>
<u n="283" who="S0162">I really like you</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">I could work with you <pause dur="short"/> could you work with me? Do you wanna give me a job? Go on</u>
<u n="285" who="S0162">what about in Spain? Did you go for interviews in Spain? Or was that a different process?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> I always got the jobs on the basis of sending them a CV and um I guess because not as many people there there aren't many people that have got as much experience as I had and um like a master's level qualification</u>
<u n="287" who="S0162">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018">Cos in Spain it's kind of a teacher training factory isn't it <pause dur="short"/> so most of the teachers going for jobs are people that have been been there for you know have a couple of years' experience and just did a certificate <pause dur="short"/> so I usually just walked into the jobs on the strength of my CV and whenever I they called me in for interview it was never rigorous it was more okay we just wanna check that you haven't got two heads or you haven't got tattoos all over your face</u>
<u n="289" who="S0162" trans="overlap">when can you start and <pause dur="short"/> what about telephone interviews? Telephone interviews I mean they're alright but actually it's a bit strange cos you can't see the response of the people</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0162">I once did one and I they put me on speaker phone <pause dur="short"/> there was like four people on the panel</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="293" who="S0162">and um I just found it really bizarre because I didn't know I <trunc>ju</trunc> couldn't see how they was responding or I couldn't see them or what they looked like and so</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018" trans="overlap">what? What was that for?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0162">it was for I applied for some funding to go to Trinidad</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">ah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0162">and um I got it ironically <pause dur="short"/> but um yeah phone phone <trunc>in</trunc> I mean they're okay but</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">well the only phone interview I've got i he he I think he was so desperate for people that he he just wanted to make sure I could make a coherent sentence and</u>
<u n="299" who="S0162">ah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">but yeah I know I thought it was gonna be interview and it was just basically so when can you start?</u>
</body>
</text>
