<text id="S4VJ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:55</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0247 S0248</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Museums / Imax and 3D cinema / public transport</topics>
		<activity>A Sunday afternoon outing in London</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0247">
				<exactage>61</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Liverpudlian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0248">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Herts</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern/London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired Quantity surveyor</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0247">so do you wanna know where I went today?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0248">yes where did you go today this afternoon?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0247">erm I went basically out to see the People at Work photography exhibition which was advertised as being at the <anon type="place"/> before going on a nationwide tour</u>
<u n="5" who="S0248">okay</u>
<u n="6" who="S0247">and erm it was er nine photographers were asked to take photos of people at work</u>
<u n="7" who="S0248">okay</u>
<u n="8" who="S0247">erm and the purpose behind it seems to be to dispel the idea that industry in Britain is dead <pause dur="short"/> because that's the they all said the same thing you know all you hear is that there's no industry the industry's dead and gone and it's not true apparently there's lots of industry <pause dur="short"/> so they all set out to different parts of the country so you know one one photographer did London somebody else did the North East <pause dur="short"/> somebody did Manchester and so on and they all have different approaches and so on <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so that's in the <anon type="place"/>  and then going on tour and <trunc>i</trunc> actually the <anon type="place"/>  was very busy <pause dur="short"/> but there was hardly anybody in this exhibition</u>
<u n="9" who="S0248">right</u>
<u n="10" who="S0247">and it might've been because nobody could find it <pause dur="short"/> when I went into the <anon type="place"/>  I asked you know where where is this exhibition? and I was told it's on the second floor and given some elaborate erm directions <pause dur="short"/> and when I did go to the second floor which was actually a bit later on I couldn't find it and I asked somebody and he said oh just go down there turn left follow the you know went round no it wasn't there <pause dur="short"/> asked <trunc>some</trunc> you know a museum official who was up there you know where's this People at Work photography exhibition? she said <trunc>n</trunc> don't know what you're talking about <pause dur="short"/> the only exhibitions we've got are these here which were something different <pause dur="short"/> erm so then I wandered around a bit more found another <trunc>a</trunc> official and asked him he said <trunc>als</trunc> sent me back the way I came and I said you know I've got a map of the <anon type="place"/>  so I said you know where on this map is this exhibition? and he was still on the second floor going media space in here it's media space and I said er yeah it says media space but it doesn't say the the name of the exhibition <pause dur="short"/> so he made some excuse about oh well they're printed up you know erm generically and so on <pause dur="short"/> so I said well anyway it isn't there <pause dur="short"/> so I left him and then found somebody else who told me it was on the first floor</u>
<u n="11" who="S0248">okay so you and you believed this person?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0247" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> I well I went to the first floor <pause dur="short"/> I still had trouble finding it</u>
<u n="13" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0247">cos it wasn't terribly well labelled <pause dur="short"/> but I found it in the end <pause dur="short"/> so as I say you know probably nobody there because</u>
<u n="15" who="S0248">wouldn't you have just <trunc>ha</trunc> if you'd been walking around the first floor wouldn't you have just happened upon it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0247">well the <anon type="place"/> is enormous you know?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0248" trans="overlap">well when you</u>
<u n="18" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0248">said that you know aboutthe second floor I was <trunc>e</trunc> I was gonna say how big is this second floor?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0247" trans="overlap">it's very very big and you you know we've been there before there's you know it's big enough to <trunc>h</trunc> to house you know great big aeroplanes and tractors and you <trunc>s</trunc> you know spaceships almost you know so it's</u>
<u n="21" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><trunc>tr</trunc> er yeah okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0247">there's huge er installations in it <pause dur="short"/> erm all you need is a few signs you know but they don't seem to do signs very well</u>
<u n="23" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah it's poor isn't it?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0247">anyway I didn't go straight there because erm I I I went on the three sixty and when I got off the bus I was outside the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and the other thing I wanted to see was an exhibition at the <anon type="place"/> which was all about protests it's like art in protest it was called something like Forbidden Objects <pause dur="short"/> so it featured placards and banners</u>
<u n="25" who="S0248">oh right</u>
<u n="26" who="S0247">and the tin pots do you remember when the Argentinian protest they always took out pots and pans?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah the noise they made coming down the street wow</u>
<u n="28" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so there was there was you know a bit about that</u>
<u n="29" who="S0248" trans="overlap">we used them over here as well did we or not?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0247" trans="overlap">no I don't think so I think they I think they've been erm repeated elsewhere in the world but I don't think they've been used in the UK</u>
<u n="31" who="S0248" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0247">so erm and there was quite a bit to read about that you know sort of <trunc>l</trunc> erm stuff you know mounted with explanations and things so that</u>
<u n="33" who="S0248" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0247">wasn't a very explanation er <trunc>expi</trunc> exhibition but it was erm it was very interesting <pause dur="short"/> and then I had a bit of a wander round the <anon type="place"/> cos it's always there's always plenty to look at there you know so</u>
<u n="35" who="S0248">is that like it's funny the museum I've <trunc>b</trunc>been to them a few times I never really know which one I prefer or</u>
<u n="36" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0248">or which you know?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0247">erm what was interesting was the queue to get in the <anon type="place"/> was massive</u>
<u n="39" who="S0248">oh was it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0247">really big but <trunc>n</trunc>no queue to get in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0248" trans="overlap">they people take their kids there more don't they?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0247">yeah but you'd think people would take their kids to the <anon type="place"/> more you know</u>
<u n="43" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah I thought it was <unclear/> cos you have like things where in the <anon type="place"/> where the kids can actually</u>
<u n="44" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0248">there's things they can <trunc>ex</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> things they can</u>
<u n="46" who="S0247" trans="overlap">interactive displays and yeah there's lots <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>l</trunc> I would've thought there's more for kids in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0248" trans="overlap">displays yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah that it was <unclear/> <unclear>all the time</unclear></u>
<u n="48" who="S0247">but I suppose a lot of children like dinosaurs don't they and <unclear/> that therefore</u>
<u n="49" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah it's got <trunc>s</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0247">erm anyway when I went into the <anon type="place"/> there was an advert for the IMAX 3D cinema <pause dur="short"/> and regular things going on you know so there was a erm something starting about twenty-five minutes later about the universe <pause dur="short"/> so I thought I've never been to an IMAX cinema and I've never seen an 3D film <pause dur="short"/> so I'll get a ticket for that so <unclear>we should do</unclear></u>
<u n="51" who="S0248" trans="overlap">where is that?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0247">it's actually in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0248">on in the <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="54" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's on the second floor <pause dur="short"/> erm so <pause dur="short"/> er it's quite a big erm auditorium and very well attended I mean not packed but</u>
<u n="55" who="S0248">oh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0247">you know lots of people doing the same thing <pause dur="short"/> and you're given a pair of glasses <pause dur="short"/> 3D glasses to put on <pause dur="short"/> and there was a couple of adverts just a advert for a car or you know I was <trunc>b</trunc> dutifully wearing my 3D glasses thinking these don't make any difference at all <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> kept on sort of peeping over the top of them <pause dur="short"/> erm and obviously the adverts <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>w</trunc> obviously weren't 3D so I</u>
<u n="57" who="S0248" trans="overlap">I have some remembrance of doing this as <trunc>i</trunc> very young boy putting some glasses on</u>
<u n="58" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0248">to watch a certain</u>
<u n="60" who="S0247">well when we were kids didn't we have those plastic glasses that would be one red <trunc>w</trunc> erm pane and one blue pane?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0248" trans="overlap">type of thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah probably that but it couldn't've been 3D could it so?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0247" trans="overlap">and that was meant to do something <pause dur="short"/> but anyway erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc> when you do get the the 3D effect it is unbelievable</u>
<u n="63" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0247">I mean really it's it it it makes you jump the</u>
<u n="65" who="S0248" trans="overlap">is it?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0247">the an owl flew out of the screen pretty</u>
<u n="67" who="S0248">mm mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0247">early on and you know and it's you know it really did feel very very close you know erm and erm <pause dur="short"/> so it was a film about er ostrominers astronomers</u>
<u n="69" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0247">and they erm the serious astronomers all work in the desert in Chile <pause dur="short"/> because obviously you know if you you know if you want to look at the stars you need</u>
<u n="71" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0247">a <trunc>zer</trunc></u>
<u n="73" who="S0248">sure</u>
<u n="74" who="S0247">zero light pollution from you know?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0247">and erm so he said <trunc>u</trunc><trunc>u</trunc> you know this this erm guy they featured erm who is also plays the piano so the we had you know followed him sort of arriving in Chile and going to the desert and he's going to the top of a hill erm to work on the VLT <pause dur="short"/> so ask ask me what means?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0248">it's something lettuce and tomato</u>
<u n="78" who="S0247">no V not B</u>
<u n="79" who="S0248">no no I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0247">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> and no it's not lettuce and tomato no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0248">erm the VLT</u>
<u n="82" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0248">er something er the visual land telescope</u>
<u n="84" who="S0247">yeah well you got the telescope bit right the very large telescope <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0248" trans="overlap">very large</u>
<u n="86" who="S0247">and they've got four VLTs in this erm place and erm the pictures were fantastic <trunc>u</trunc><trunc>u</trunc> the they said they are the actual pictures that you're seeing you know it's not it's not some sort of special effects mock up and which is a bit <trunc>di</trunc> because we've seen so much on Star Wars and things like that that you know you weren't sure what you were seeing but you know the</u>
<u n="87" who="S0248">pictures of what?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0247">erm galaxies and you know erm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0248" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="90" who="S0247">erm the I it wasn't</u>
<u n="91" who="S0248" trans="overlap">it must be fantastic that sort of this mustn't it?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah the I mean my only complaint really was that it wasn't very well explained</u>
<u n="93" who="S0248">mm mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0247">it was like you know here's one where the star's exploded and it didn't really tell you</u>
<u n="95" who="S0248" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0247">why or how and you know the <trunc>u</trunc> the it was</u>
<u n="97" who="S0248" trans="overlap">does it matter it's only just?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0247">probably not I mean it was it was more visual impact than explaining</u>
<u n="99" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0247">you know the science behind it but I <trunc>d</trunc> I didn't <trunc>r</trunc> half the time I didn't really know what I was looking at but it was very very erm impressive what they did <pause dur="short"/> and then there was another erm bigger <trunc>telesc</trunc> a VVLT and <vocal desc="laugh"/> they called this one erm ALMA I think this even bigger one erm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0248">big ALMA</u>
<u n="102" who="S0247">because they can't see erm <vocal desc="misc"/> they can only <trunc>s</trunc> they can only penetrate light and so they have learnt from the mosquito who can detect things by erm heat <pause dur="short"/> and movement and stuff like that so they they've got this different approach with this other ALMA telescope it's not just light it's also movement and stuff so you it can penetrate er past the you know where the <trunc>nor</trunc> where the other super duper telescope can see this one can see even further</u>
<u n="103" who="S0248">wasn't that the name of Ray Moore's wife big big Alma?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0247">Ray Moore the radio <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0247">yes and there was an Alma on Coronation Street as well</u>
<u n="107" who="S0248" trans="overlap">he had a <pause dur="short"/> yeah no but I in <trunc>f</trunc> er you you know <unclear>the entire programme</unclear> used to call him er he was always on about big Alma <pause dur="short"/> anyway er yeah sounds great</u>
<u n="108" who="S0247">so I can thoroughly recommend erm a 3D experience</u>
<u n="109" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0247">erm <trunc>th</trunc> you you do sort of see a slight shadow I don't know whether it's cos my eyes are not very good but you know you can sort of <trunc>s</trunc> there's something a little bit fuzzy about the edges of erm figures and so on and I took when the credits went up and it was all writing I took my glasses off to see what that looked like without the glasses and it was all sort of like double you know you</u>
<u n="111" who="S0248">there are 3D actual movies made now aren't there?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0247" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0248">and do people sit with <trunc>gla</trunc> these glasses on do they?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0248">as I say they tried this years and years forty years ago nearly</u>
<u n="116" who="S0247">yeah but I don't think they had the <trunc>f</trunc> the the film technology right forty years ago like you know?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no probably not</u>
<u n="118" who="S0247">erm the the the the techniques would've been very erm basic and crude <pause dur="short"/> they've got completely different filming techniques now for 3D</u>
<u n="119" who="S0248" trans="overlap">mm yeah no it was the way it was pretty underwhelming then quite frankly</u>
<u n="120" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no this is impressive you would you would be impressed with this</u>
<u n="121" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0247">and also the IMAX experience as well is cos <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said that er filming for IMAX is a different technique as well so you could have an IMAX film presumably that wasn't 3D <pause dur="short"/> but the screen's so big it's the height of it is er the height of four double decker buses</u>
<u n="123" who="S0248">the height the screen is</u>
<u n="124" who="S0247" trans="overlap">the height of the screen yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0248">was it?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0247">enormous yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you get this very <pause dur="short"/> you I mean you can't you know can see the edges just but you know it's it's a very overwhelming sort of experience you know you do feel as if z in it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0248">so what room is is you know is it where is it actually?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0247">on the second floor of the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0248" trans="overlap">for but you'd think it you say it's the height of all that</u>
<u n="130" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0248">you know how come it's? er are those <trunc>i</trunc>is it take up does it go beyond the second floor?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0247">well maybe it goes down you know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0247">it it might be like the edge of the building or something like the whole of the erm you know I dunno</u>
<u n="135" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0247">but it's very it's enormous</u>
<u n="137" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0247">but of course there is that one at near Waterloo isn't there at the roundabout the the IMAX one?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah well I thought that was an <trunc>IMA</trunc> that yeah but but er</u>
<u n="140" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah it is yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0248">I knew I'd heard it somewhere</u>
<u n="142" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I don't know what the science of the filming but I know <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said it's very very expensive process to film for IMAX <pause dur="short"/> so presumably as they were showing it off the we would've had the combination of IMAX and 3D in this</u>
<u n="143" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0247">film</u>
<u n="145" who="S0248">mm <pause dur="short"/> sorry so when you went out did you actually know about this IMAX thing?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0247">no no I <trunc>tr</trunc> I mean I kind of did but I'd forgotten really you know I I went out thinking I'll go to that People at Work exhibition and then I thought oh while I'm in the area I might as well go to the <anon type="place"/> as well</u>
<u n="147" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0247">and erm you know <trunc>g</trunc> this other exhibition about forbidden objects you know cos they're both free so</u>
<u n="149" who="S0248">yeah no sure <pause dur="short"/> sure</u>
<u n="150" who="S0247" trans="overlap">I didn't need to book tickets to anything <pause dur="short"/> so but I did it in all the wrong order so I when I got there I went first of all to the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and spent some time there and then when I went to the <anon type="place"/> I went to this erm film <pause dur="short"/> I had a cup of tea in the twenty minutes I had to wait and then after I came out of the IMAX cinema I went to find the People at Work exhibition so the thing I'd gone for I was beginning to think I'm running the risk here of <vocal desc="laugh"/> actually not seeing that you know? erm and then when I came out I thought erm I might walk up to the <anon type="place"/> and book a prom ticket for some time this week</u>
<u n="151" who="S0248">okay</u>
<u n="152" who="S0247">but I looked and I <trunc>di</trunc> I just didn't fancy walking I'd been traipsing around a bit so I didn't really fancy walking up the and then <trunc>u</trunc> much to my annoyance a three sixty</u>
<u n="153" who="S0248"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="154" who="S0247">and I <trunc>d</trunc> I could've caught it cos you know</u>
<u n="155" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0247">and I couldn't wouldn't have been able to get across the road and down to the bus stop so I decided I was gonna race this three sixty to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0248">on the tube</u>
<u n="158" who="S0247">on the tube yeah so I thought if if the three sixty's got to sort of contend with traffic</u>
<u n="159" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0247">you know I thought I could probably beat it if I <trunc>c</trunc>caught the tube to <anon type="place"/> and then just walked around the corner <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="161" who="S0248">but you were not right</u>
<u n="162" who="S0247">mm <pause dur="short"/> I was only just not right I think</u>
<u n="163" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you saw it in disappear into the distance</u>
<u n="164" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah when I came out of <anon type="place"/> station it was just going round the corner</u>
<u n="165" who="S0248"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> dear me</u>
<u n="166" who="S0247">so <pause dur="short"/> so I just walked from there</u>
<u n="167" who="S0248" trans="overlap">thought a bus good bus will always get a good tube will always beat a good bus</u>
<u n="168" who="S0247">yeah but you <trunc>f</trunc> what you forget is how far you have to walk from</u>
<u n="169" who="S0248" trans="overlap">oh sure yeah I mean you were stood to get a a distance to walk to <anon type="place"/> station yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0247" trans="overlap">the museums back to back to <anon type="place"/> station <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you go in that tunnel you know it goes on forever</u>
<u n="171" who="S0248" trans="overlap">I know it's bloody yeah long time I used to go in there years ago</u>
<u n="172" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0248">oh we walked down there didn't we?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0247">yeah we did <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu</u>
<u n="175" who="S0248">cos you were on about some opera or something</u>
<u n="176" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0248">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> a good afternoon was had by all</u>
<u n="178" who="S0247" trans="overlap">so it was yeah it was good yeah and erm I didn't I didn't get my proms ticket I</u>
<u n="179" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0247">didn't go in the <anon type="place"/> but I didn't intend to do that</u>
<u n="181" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you can't do it all</u>
<u n="182" who="S0247">can't do everything can you?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you can't do it all I've always said that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0247" trans="overlap">no</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
