<text id="S4ZT">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:11:16</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house, Cambs</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Career change. differences of career change for men and women. </topics>
		<activity>A couple at home talking about reasons for a career change. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0262">who don't <trunc>ha</trunc> want to go and hang out with a bunch of twenty-year-olds and do an MBA or whatever you know they want to learn</u>
<u n="2" who="S0261">they're they want to change</u>
<u n="3" who="S0262">they want to change</u>
<u n="4" who="S0261" trans="overlap">cos they need to be able to work it out for themselves</u>
<u n="5" who="S0262">find an environment exactly that suits them</u>
<u n="6" who="S0261" trans="overlap">rather than yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">at the age of forty</u>
<u n="8" who="S0261">and their time on their on their terms</u>
<u n="9" who="S0262">yeah your patience levels go fucking out the window basically you know you've got to have what you want you time's too short life's too short to fuck around with people in tutorials who don't fucking do their group work you know that's the point</u>
<u n="10" who="S0261">so I mean one one interesting thing is is we're probably as a as a generation in in the middle of where all the change is yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0262" trans="overlap">we are we're I feel it</u>
<u n="12" who="S0261">and and and</u>
<u n="13" who="S0262">we're right in the middle of it and you're</u>
<u n="14" who="S0261">it's not it's not just what you're talking about it's in a generic sense baby boomers at the top</u>
<u n="15" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0261">going out the door</u>
<u n="17" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="18" who="S0261">then you've got the young ones at the bottom who are actually those two generations are miles apart</u>
<u n="19" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="20" who="S0261">and we're in the middle of it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0261">getting the mix of it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0261">and and sometimes you'll get some of us are of the older generation some of us are younger and a lot of us are actually a mix and so if you look at like education and the way that things have been taught through society now don't expect to be doing the same job for the whole of your life</u>
<u n="25" who="S0262" trans="overlap">fuck no look right okay look when we</u>
<u n="26" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so let me just finish let me just finish</u>
<u n="27" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="28" who="S0261">erm so so the reason why I'm bringing that up is because what I'm doing and that kind of example is in the middle of it it is I'm in the middle of it I'm trying to change so I'm trying to adopt this younger approach but in fact I've probably been brought up in the older world</u>
<u n="29" who="S0262">yeah you have</u>
<u n="30" who="S0261">so trying that's what I mean about the trying to unlearn stuff and disconnect from some of that channelled stuff that you've had in your past that you need to explore things differently and try to learn them differently and and approach things very differently I mean you know there are cases we work on things for bugger all like you've done in your past with your production and stuff like that to try and get places that you offer things for</u>
<u n="31" who="S0262">absolutely</u>
<u n="32" who="S0261">whatever</u>
<u n="33" who="S0262">absolutely</u>
<u n="34" who="S0261">for gratis</u>
<u n="35" who="S0262" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="36" who="S0261">on return for something else some experience some exposure later on</u>
<u n="37" who="S0262">I completely agree with you and I I think that all of those things you've just said is completely valid and I actually think that there are that many nearly forty-year-olds yeah going about it in the way that you're trying to achieve what you're trying to achieve there are two people who stick out in my mind that you know very well one of them is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and the other one is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was some sort of erm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0261">well he was a mechanical</u>
<u n="41" who="S0262">was he mechanical?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0261">no no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a <unclear>hard-core</unclear> engineer</u>
<u n="43" who="S0262">was he?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0262">right okay I didn't know that okay so hard-core engineer</u>
<u n="46" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0262">turned himself into a plumber yeah?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0262">okay career shift <pause dur="short"/> he did it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0261"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="51" who="S0262">yeah he he managed it okay</u>
<u n="52" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0262">did it just in time for his <unclear/> family good idea</u>
<u n="54" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his wife <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0262">they tried to give it a go with the juice bar thing that's tough yeah it's hard they gave they</u>
<u n="58" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and that obviously worked out they didn't wanna work in their nine to five jobs etcetera and do <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0262" trans="overlap">when we were when we were with them in India they wanted to actually open a B and B</u>
<u n="60" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0262">it's actually what they wanted to do they didn't do that though they actually opened a juice bar</u>
<u n="62" who="S0261" trans="overlap">because they worked out it wasn't gonna be a viable business plan or whatever</u>
<u n="63" who="S0262" trans="overlap">whatever but as far as I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone back to something quite similar to what he was doing before</u>
<u n="64" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0262">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has always been a teacher so that's fine you know</u>
<u n="66" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="67" who="S0262">so the point is is that these were people who were in their early thirties thinking like that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> imagine like you don't need to imagine cos you are going through it but imagine other people who are getting to the point now where they haven't done that shift in their early thirties of actually getting into the thing that they want to be in they're actually now going shit if I don't fucking do this now by the age of sometime forty I'm probably going to be doing this job for the rest of my fucking life</u>
<u n="70" who="S0261">well I I think it's fair to say a lot of people leave their their position their current job working for somebody else and and they pick up pick up their own thing and they cramp their own business and they act as consultants that they but they're operating within their own discipline <pause dur="short"/> they <pause dur="short"/> they take</u>
<u n="71" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well that yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0261">expertise and</u>
<u n="73" who="S0262" trans="overlap">like who give us an example of who <unclear/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0261">well just lots of people who just go out on their own being consultants</u>
<u n="75" who="S0262" trans="overlap">like who? like lots of people who?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> they they do that people do that erm an example was at that erm you know er change my career thing there were people who were presenting themselves as career coaches and a lot of those people had come from a variety of backgrounds and they had <trunc>s</trunc>somehow they they had gotten out of working for somebody else and they created their own business working as a career coach using whatever skills they had and that could be simply along the idea that they're experienced in life and therefore they have something better to offer to somebody else they're they're a relative expert there</u>
<u n="77" who="S0262">yeah I mean like</u>
<u n="78" who="S0261">and others would be experts in it you know they they they have HR experience to the ends of the Earth</u>
<u n="79" who="S0262" trans="overlap">alright alright alright alright</u>
<u n="80" who="S0261" trans="overlap">or whatever you know</u>
<u n="81" who="S0262">alright these people are people <unclear/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that's an example</u>
<u n="83" who="S0262">exactly it's an example you've give of ones people I haven't met I'm trying to make it miles more tangible for you of people that you've actually got to know and that you understand some of their psyche you know why does a man choose? okay you're not the only one</u>
<u n="84" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0262">give you two example we could think of more why does a man choose to change his career from what he had in his twenties thirties into something different at a different time in his life okay why does a man choose to do that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? answer me that</u>
<u n="86" who="S0261">erm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and I'm talking about a man not a woman</u>
<u n="88" who="S0261">right er well I I think part of the reason is that erm fortunately from my side of of the coin some of the imperatives aren't there on the context of erm if you have to if you have to graft and you have to earn money and you've got a family to er to to care for then the prerogative is bringing in money day in day out that's just it you know? so erm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0262">but you brought in money day in day out for the majority of your life as working as a civil engineer in England you didn't have a family to think of you did it anyway</u>
<u n="90" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that no that's that's that's right erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and now when we're thinking about having a family in actual fact the money is is not really what you're chasing so I ask you the question why generic okay general question why do you think a man this is where I think I need to understand the male psyche why does a man choose something that's running along quite well yeah in his twenties and thirties choose to shift for whatever reason into a different career? where I'm talking about psyche I'm not talking about oh cos I got made redundant I'm talking about where is that <pause dur="short"/> drive coming from?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0261" trans="overlap">I I think the drive simply is is to to be your own boss</u>
<u n="93" who="S0262"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="94" who="S0261">to to do to do it for yourself</u>
<u n="95" who="S0262">to be your own man</u>
<u n="96" who="S0261"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0261">and and it's it's not about proving anything it's simply a case of that the driver is <pause dur="short"/> I it's freedom related it's simply I want the choice to be able to make decisions that I want and that's what let's say democracy's about people would <unclear>speak</unclear> to be able to make the choice they want and this is another <unclear>adjunct</unclear> to it erm working for somebody else doesn't provide you the environment to do the things that you want to do you can't always do the things you want to do and so quite often you you park or you just dismiss or you hide away those ideas etcetera things that just were never erm feasible you know</u>
<u n="99" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so can I can I add my two pennies worth? okay <pause dur="short"/> with men they clearly I think men are very very good at distinguishing erm what other men are trying to achieve yeah? they're pretty clear I think in the <unclear>cut</unclear> in when you get to be a manager <pause dur="short"/> you start to wield some power yeah <pause dur="short"/> you either like it or you don't hopefully you do like it yeah otherwise you wouldn't do it but from the guys as as you call it you know the types of words you'd use when you were talking about engineers with senior engineers or or management in engineering companies <pause dur="short"/> swing their dicks around suck my cock you know the way you would actually describe these people you were working with you know or in meetings with it sounded horrendous it sounded really like too fucking much in many ways yeah and what I didn't like about it was it was so male dominated it was so much male talk it was so much like I'm an alpha male you're not you're be you're a whatever so you're gonna have to follow me because basically I've got the power shut up fuck off and you'll do what I say yeah? and that male dominated world I'm sorry if you don't fit into it it's shit it's crap it's it's gotta be one of the worst places to be if you're if you wanna be your own man yeah like most men want to be their own men who wants to actually just roll over and go yeah fuck off I just wanna be erm dominated by another man no you don't what what man really wants to be dominated by another man? I mean really I don't want to be fucking dominated by another woman so my idea of this psyche the driver is that actually sometimes it gets to the point where I'm not management I'm fucking off I'm gonna be my own fucking boss because no fucking man is going to fucking talk to me like that</u>
<u n="100" who="S0261">well erm well I mean it's a it's not as simple as that erm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0262">okay well tell me if it's more complicated than that because clearly I'm not a man so I can't get into that psyche but all I'm showing <event desc="recording skips"/> but all I'm showing <event desc="recording skips"/> but all I'm showing</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
