<text id="S59R">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:21:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0251 S0252</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living room in Malton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics> Coffee shop and university </topics>
		<activity> Coffee shop and university </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0251">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>North Ferriby, East Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>GCSE Maths Examiner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0252">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>York</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0251">what was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asking you this morning in the coffee shop?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0252">he was asking whether we liked erm the coffee <unclear/> what was the third one?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0251" trans="overlap">pistachio</u>
<u n="4" who="S0252">pistachio erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0251">no I think it was quite a cheffy sounding combination wasn't it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0252">it was it was</u>
<u n="7" who="S0251">I think the Bake Off's got a lot to answer for don't you?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0252">it has in some ways yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0251">and what did you say <trunc>d</trunc>did you like it?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0252">erm well I I was ah relatively positive with my response</u>
<u n="11" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0252">saying that ah the <unclear/> flavouring does have a little bit in common with the erm the coffee itself</u>
<u n="13" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0252">with the sort of citrus flavour</u>
<u n="15" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm mm I haven't come across that combination before but he said it was quite a popular thing in Scandinavian countries</u>
<u n="16" who="S0252">mm yes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I hadn't heard of it before though</u>
<u n="18" who="S0252">I'm not quite sure why because none of those things would be native to</u>
<u n="19" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="20" who="S0252">Scandinavia</u>
<u n="21" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="22" who="S0252">because obviously usually local specialities tend to be things that come from the area or</u>
<u n="23" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm <unclear/> yeah I suppose the very I imagine they would drink more coffee than we do I don't suppose they drink as much tea</u>
<u n="24" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0251">see I wouldn't have thought of putting <unclear/> with coffee</u>
<u n="26" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="27" who="S0251">I thought to be honest although I wouldn't have said it that he had got it a little bit dry around the edge and it was a little bit more well done around the edge</u>
<u n="28" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0251">because it was quite a big cake</u>
<u n="30" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="31" who="S0251">it would have to be in the oven for quite some time to set in the middle</u>
<u n="32" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it would</u>
<u n="33" who="S0251">so I think if he'd put more greaseproof maybe two or three layers of greaseproof round the edge and maybe some brown paper it would make it bake a bit more evenly</u>
<u n="34" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0251">it was just a little bit on the dry side actually</u>
<u n="36" who="S0252">another thing that <unclear/> depend on what sort of oven he has used</u>
<u n="37" who="S0251">mm I think it actually made it for us in a way because the day before he'd said what was our favourite cake?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="39" who="S0251">and I said coffee</u>
<u n="40" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0251">and then the next day we went in and he'd made that coffee and <unclear/> cake so</u>
<u n="42" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="43" who="S0251">I think he was trying to please us really wasn't he?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0251">but I think it is a very happy coffee shop really isn't it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0252">it is yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0251">friendly</u>
<u n="48" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="49" who="S0251">one of the waitresses there left one time to get a what she thought would be a better job an office type job but after a few months she came back and I thought she'd just come back to maybe fill in for somebody who was ill or something but she said she decided to give the office job up and come back to the coffee shop because she missed it so much and she missed seeing all the people and thought she'd be a lot happier at the coffee shop so</u>
<u n="50" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="51" who="S0251">why not</u>
<u n="52" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0251">it's not always about having what you think's the best job but what's the best job for you isn't it sometimes and what's going to make you the most happy</u>
<u n="54" who="S0252" trans="overlap">indeed and what you can stick at or or working life really</u>
<u n="55" who="S0251">mm mm hm <pause dur="short"/> did you see anybody else today?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0252">erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>was he</unclear> one of our neighbours?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="58" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="59" who="S0251">what did she have to say?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0252">she was erm saying that her son has moved either to the <anon type="place"/> residence</u>
<u n="61" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0252">and erm that she will have to despite her being four children and her husband will be the only one in the house except the cat of course</u>
<u n="63" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yeah just her and the cat left now so I think she'll really feel it don't you?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0252">she will</u>
<u n="65" who="S0251">it's quite sad in some ways when so called empty nest</u>
<u n="66" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no one to speak to really</u>
<u n="67" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="68" who="S0252">and that there'll be a few houses on the estate where only one person lives</u>
<u n="69" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="70" who="S0252"><unclear/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0251">increasing number I think</u>
<u n="72" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="73" who="S0251"><unclear/> she knew somebody else who was also going to university but they were hoping to stay at home live at home and travel in but they've been hoping to pass their driving test in the summer holidays which after all was about three months this time wasn't it?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0252">it was</u>
<u n="75" who="S0251">but unfortunately they hadn't managed to pass</u>
<u n="76" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="77" who="S0251">I don't think three months is really quite long enough</u>
<u n="78" who="S0252">well er I'm aware of companies offering a <trunc>w</trunc> a week course where you <unclear/> you do it for the whole day for a week</u>
<u n="79" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0252">and that is you'd be considered to be er more or less ready for the test after that but</u>
<u n="81" who="S0251" trans="overlap">what's the pass rate on that though? <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0252">it's er erm if you are prepared to do it a bit more gradually</u>
<u n="83" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="84" who="S0252">I think you're just trying to do it one a week it's probably more maybe six to nine months course including maybe a few holidays and that type of thing</u>
<u n="85" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah yes if you just have one lesson yes that's it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0252">but obviously if you do it at the more frequent level then er you can probably expect to pass a bit quicker</u>
<u n="87" who="S0251">mm yeah or if parents can give you a bit of extra practice they can get the car insured</u>
<u n="88" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="89" who="S0251">and get a bit of extra practice that way</u>
<u n="90" who="S0252">yes I think you'd have to choose your routes well <unclear/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0251">yes on quiet roads</u>
<u n="92" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="93" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0252">but whilst quiet roads it's got to be a good mix of roads</u>
<u n="95" who="S0251">mm to get you used to different</u>
<u n="96" who="S0252" trans="overlap">er because in er the test to do real test what <unclear>they'll call</unclear> different road <trunc>con</trunc>conditions</u>
<u n="97" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="98" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="99" who="S0251">so you want some quiet ones and some busy ones</u>
<u n="100" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0251">yeah the trouble with his position is that because he lives in a village he'll have to get a lift into the town centre so that he can catch the either the train or the bus so that he can get himself there so</u>
<u n="102" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="103" who="S0251">he's still going to need a bit of assistance isn't he?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0252">er he is yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0251">and er if you live in a remote area</u>
<u n="106" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0251">you are quite dependent on</u>
<u n="108" who="S0252">cars</u>
<u n="109" who="S0251">cars</u>
<u n="110" who="S0252">yes erm I think another thing that doesn't help is that the er insurance will probably come is most expensive in the first month or so when you pass</u>
<u n="111" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0252">especially if you <unclear/> to be a main driver</u>
<u n="113" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0252">in the time</u>
<u n="115" who="S0251">true</u>
<u n="116" who="S0252">whereas if you just give it five six months</u>
<u n="117" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0252">you can just make it a little bit more of a a reasonable price</u>
<u n="119" who="S0251">yes take the edge off it a bit</u>
<u n="120" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="121" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0252"><unclear/> but it doesn't like they'll have that choice</u>
<u n="123" who="S0251">no not just for now but there again we're doing over more experienced drivers don't we?</u>
<u n="124" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0251">who's had a bit of a <unclear/> how much will that car have cost do you think?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0252"><trunc>w</trunc>which car?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0251"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s car</u>
<u n="128" who="S0252">oh I <trunc>thin</trunc> eh I think that it'd have been at least thirty thousand pounds</u>
<u n="129" who="S0251">ouch he must have only had it what two weeks three weeks</u>
<u n="130" who="S0252">yeah well picked it up on the end of August I think</u>
<u n="131" who="S0251">August so yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0252">over six weeks</u>
<u n="133" who="S0251">mm <pause dur="short"/> and then he gets mixed up between which is the accelerator and which is the brake</u>
<u n="134" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="135" who="S0251">and erm wraps it round the hedge</u>
<u n="136" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="137" who="S0251">and does two and a half thousand pounds worth of damage</u>
<u n="138" who="S0252">yeah I think I don't it must have really got it in the hedge in a bad way to create that amount of damage</u>
<u n="139" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0252">you'd have thought if you just hit the hedge</u>
<u n="141" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0252">might have been eh a little scratch <unclear/> but it must have been it must have more or less knocked the hedge over to create that much damage</u>
<u n="143" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I wonder what's all the damage on it that's cost so much</u>
<u n="144" who="S0252">I don't know</u>
<u n="145" who="S0251">now it could have been worse if he'd have hurt somebody</u>
<u n="146" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0251">or himself</u>
<u n="148" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0251"><unclear>he could've</unclear> banged somebody else's car</u>
<u n="150" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="151" who="S0251">or if his wife had been driving</u>
<u n="152" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0251">yeah so it's a good job it was him that was driving</u>
<u n="154" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="155" who="S0251">I think are the automatics a bit more different and difficult to drive</u>
<u n="156" who="S0252">well if you've been driving a manual car for any length of time then</u>
<u n="157" who="S0251">but have they?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0252">well erm I think they have in the past but due to strange circumstances they've moved to an automatic vehicle</u>
<u n="159" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0252">so I think ah his wife has quite a bit of experience with an automatic a little now but I don't think he has</u>
<u n="161" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes bless her hmm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0252">I think you just get used to the er manual if you drive manual for many years really</u>
<u n="165" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah yes so will he lose his no claims bonus now or will it be protected or</u>
<u n="166" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it's it's a grey area really it's it's sort of depends what's included sometimes the <trunc>lar</trunc> I think it will be covered but I think as long as he's paid the extra to have it covered but I think sometimes in more serious cases it even if you do have that you will still lose it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it's bound to be <pause dur="short"/> mm yes <pause dur="short"/> is it all in the small print?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0252">yes it's not just as simple as just you protect yourself against it or you don't</u>
<u n="169" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0252">it's kind of sort of protect yourself but not fully</u>
<u n="171" who="S0251">in every circumstances</u>
<u n="172" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0251">I don't think small print should be allowed why should some things be in such small print that you can't see them?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0252">well I mean some sort of terms and conditions seem to be about ten pages long in small print</u>
<u n="175" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0252">so if they did it in big print it'd probably be a a small book and no one's going to read it it's ah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0251">but you couldn't read it even if you wanted really when it's so small could you?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0252">but so you're saying if it was in size fourteen to sixteen font you would read it or?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0251">probably not <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think anybody ever reads that kind of thing in detail</u>
<u n="180" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="181" who="S0251">because it's just too painful isn't it?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0252">but you can usually upload them on the computer and then obviously you can magnify it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="184" who="S0252">without a big problem no</u>
<u n="185" who="S0251">yes he does suffer from insomnia doesn't he?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0252">mm hm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0251">god that'd get you off to sleep in no time</u>
<u n="188" who="S0252">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <unclear/> hope I will be alright on my regular commute</u>
<u n="189" who="S0251">yes yes you'll ah have to get used to it won't you and?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0252">yes obviously I will probably be a fairly high mileage driver within the immediate family</u>
<u n="191" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I know you'll be notching up a few miles soon won't you?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="193" who="S0251">mm I think one of the main hazards for you is slow moving traffic</u>
<u n="194" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0251">on the A64</u>
<u n="196" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="197" who="S0251">if that makes you think you're going to be late and then you know start getting a bit anxious about it or something?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0251">what do you think?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0252">I know what you mean I mean I personally just try to not look at the time when I'm driving</u>
<u n="201" who="S0251">yeah you just have to</u>
<u n="202" who="S0252">because it doesn't matter what time it is you've still got to get there safely whether it's what whether it's half one or whether it's midnight you've still got to to get to your destination safely without any damage or anything like that</u>
<u n="203" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah you've got to get there in one piece <pause dur="short"/> mm that's the main thing definitely I just thing that it might be unpredictable you know that you go one time</u>
<u n="204" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="205" who="S0251">and it's completely fine so you think oh I can set off at this time then another occasion you set off at that time and then it makes you late because there never seems to be a reason when you get to the front of the queue oh there'll be an accident or erm something of this sort lorry's slipped its load or something and you'll see what the problem was</u>
<u n="206" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0251">but when you get far up the road then it just disappears there doesn't seem to be any really good reason</u>
<u n="208" who="S0252">I think sometimes it just was too many cars on that road it's a major road</u>
<u n="209" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0252">really links two big cities to the coast</u>
<u n="211" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="212" who="S0252">erm for it to be single carriageway for most of the way</u>
<u n="213" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0252">and obviously where it does change from two to one you get a bit of a bottleneck there</u>
<u n="215" who="S0251">it does</u>
<u n="216" who="S0252">it it really doesn't help</u>
<u n="217" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="218" who="S0252">I think if it was just it was a dual carriageway the whole way I don't think there'd be I think there would rarely be a problem unless there was an actual accident</u>
<u n="219" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0252">but</u>
<u n="221" who="S0251">it <unclear/> when it changes from two lanes to one</u>
<u n="222" who="S0252">yes I think hopefully there will be a bit of a pattern and also hopefully be able to tell before you actually get on</u>
<u n="223" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0252">and <trunc>bef</trunc> have an opportunity to go take a different route</u>
<u n="225" who="S0251">yes yeah but the other way is more of a country way isn't it?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0252">mm it is</u>
<u n="227" who="S0251">and in icy weather that would be a bit dicey wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0252" trans="overlap">you can't do it in icy weather it would only be suitable in normal driving conditions</u>
<u n="229" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah good conditions</u>
<u n="230" who="S0252">just hope there isn't too much ice and snow</u>
<u n="231" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="232" who="S0252">to contend with <unclear/> driving in ice and obviously I think black ice can be a real danger if you are driving at sort of sixty-seventyish on the A64 and black ice and you're you're in a real problem then aren't you?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm definitely mm definitely mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0252">but even if you're doing fifty</u>
<u n="235" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0252">you know it's a tricky thing</u>
<u n="237" who="S0251">but we do have some alternatives because you could go on the train couldn't you?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0252">I could go on the train</u>
<u n="239" who="S0251"><unclear/> thought it was a bit icy</u>
<u n="240" who="S0252">yes obviously it <trunc>do</trunc>does take a bit longer and</u>
<u n="241" who="S0251">you'd more or less have to decide the night before I think so you could plan it more</u>
<u n="242" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes and it's not that frequent really in some ways every hour</u>
<u n="243" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="244" who="S0252">maybe miss one then</u>
<u n="245" who="S0251">yeah you've got a long time to wait for the next one really mm <pause dur="short"/> you just can't tell what kind of winter last winter I think we pretty much got away with it I don't even think we had snow last winter did we?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no we didn't have any snow well other thing is if I don't need to get there until ten or eleven o'clock</u>
<u n="247" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="248" who="S0252">most the worst effects will have probably disappeared</u>
<u n="249" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it should be a lot better by then and probably be gritted and just the temperature will have just lifted a bit</u>
<u n="250" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the sun will have come out won't it?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0251">that will definitely help if you don't need to be in first thing</u>
<u n="252" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="253" who="S0251">but the timetable seems a bit variable doesn't it? there isn't really a set pattern to it I don't think is there?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0252">yeah no well it's just sort of every each component is at a set frequency really</u>
<u n="255" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="256" who="S0252">and it will change at each semester I think</u>
<u n="257" who="S0251">mm so we'll just have to check each day won't we?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0252">yes but in the semester after Easter</u>
<u n="259" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="260" who="S0252">you <unclear/> really any lectures after that it's pretty quiet really</u>
<u n="261" who="S0251" trans="overlap">why not? so what happens at that point?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0252">well it'll be revision I imagine</u>
<u n="263" who="S0251">right</u>
<u n="264" who="S0252">we might get more sort of small group ones I don't know but</u>
<u n="265" who="S0251">I see</u>
<u n="266" who="S0252">there doesn't seem to be that much actual</u>
<u n="267" who="S0251">down for the moment?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="269" who="S0251">well it might fill up a bit more as it gets nearer the time</u>
<u n="270" who="S0252">yes <pause dur="short"/> but in some ways the university is just more or less from October to Easter really isn't it?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm seems to be as far as we can tell up to now anyway I'm glad we've got your parking permit sorted out now</u>
<u n="272" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="273" who="S0251">got that fitted on because I think it'll be very busy in the first few weeks people queuing up trying to get the parking permits trying to get the ID cards and you've got yours collected and there <trunc>wer</trunc> there wasn't any real queues were there?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0252" trans="overlap">sorting themselves out yes <pause dur="long"/> no</u>
<u n="275" who="S0251">pretty quick</u>
<u n="276" who="S0252">yes but obviously if anyone's coming in from any distance they won't really be able to pick up like that</u>
<u n="277" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no that's right they wouldn't</u>
<u n="278" who="S0252">I hope that the car park doesn't fill up too much</u>
<u n="279" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="280" who="S0252">that there are a few spaces</u>
<u n="281" who="S0251">so does that just entitle you to just use one particular car park?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0252">well technically it's two</u>
<u n="283" who="S0251">two?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="285" who="S0251">oh</u>
<u n="286" who="S0252">but that's all the car parks at my part of campus</u>
<u n="287" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="288" who="S0252">but you can't park on other parts of the campus</u>
<u n="289" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="290" who="S0252">but it wouldn't be really convenient for me to anyway because</u>
<u n="291" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no you're too far away</u>
<u n="292" who="S0252">yes really it's one and a half miles from the other part of the campus so</u>
<u n="293" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0252">it's not really handy to park on the other side particularly</u>
<u n="295" who="S0251">so are they pretty extensive car parks? or do you think there's a chance that you might get there and find all the places have gone or?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0252">I think they're just medium-sized car parks really</u>
<u n="297" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0252">they're not they certainly could be a lot bigger</u>
<u n="299" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="300" who="S0252">I went they've done their very best to try and limit car usership</u>
<u n="301" who="S0251" trans="overlap">um hm um hm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0252">like I think ah some of the staff might well have to pay up to four hundred pounds a year to parking permit which</u>
<u n="303" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="304" who="S0252">obviously is quite a lot of money just for a parking space</u>
<u n="305" who="S0251">I know</u>
<u n="306" who="S0252">and they sort of try to discourage it by ah encouraging staff to car share or</u>
<u n="307" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0252">erm if they surrender their pass they get a hundred and fifty pounds to spend on a bike or something like that so</u>
<u n="309" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0252">they're a little bit sort of anti-car really so to what extent that works will depend on how many spaces are there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah mm it's not always practical though in bad weather <unclear/> another thing it depends on how much you've got to carry you've got books and files and laptops and that I think it's a bit dangerous having all that to carry when you're on a bike</u>
<u n="312" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes well their solution to that one is to erm have a permit that allows you to go ten times per semester so you can drive in bad weather and when you carry heavy stuff but use public transport or bike when you don't</u>
<u n="313" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> thought of everything haven't they? mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0252">but erm I don't think it's really particularly possible or convenient in my case really</u>
<u n="315" who="S0251">no oh no <unclear/> it's too far much too far</u>
<u n="316" who="S0252">and also pretty expensive as well really</u>
<u n="317" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0252">without that sort of flexibility</u>
<u n="319" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="320" who="S0252">only good thing is that you can go and leave when you want really</u>
<u n="321" who="S0251">yes it gives you that independence doesn't it?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0252" trans="overlap">there's no yes you don't have to wait half an hour or</u>
<u n="323" who="S0251">for the bus or</u>
<u n="324" who="S0252">the pressure <unclear>have</unclear> to collect something or</u>
<u n="325" who="S0251">no that's it</u>
<u n="326" who="S0252" trans="overlap">the car park's open twenty-four hours so</u>
<u n="327" who="S0251">oh that's good</u>
<u n="328" who="S0252">there's no restriction <unclear/> the only condition is I can't park there for more than twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="329" who="S0251">no mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0252">but I don't think there's any chance of that really unless it's broke or something</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
