<text id="S59W">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:59:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-05-13</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013 S0152</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Freelancer's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Football, application form, problem children, baby birds in nest, cockerel, birthdays, 3D printing, houses, shabby workmanship, not sleeping</topics>
		<activity>Just come round!</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Complaining, Making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0152">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Birmingham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>w_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0152">tonight</u>
<u n="2" who="S0012">yeah Bayern Munich yeah you're right Bayern Munich and Barcelona yeah yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0152">yeah erm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0012">so who do you want to win?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0152">Bayern Munich</u>
<u n="6" who="S0012">yeah Bayern Munich yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0152">but they've got to score four goals</u>
<u n="8" who="S0012">they can do that</u>
<u n="9" who="S0152">cos they're three nil down</u>
<u n="10" who="S0012">yeah they can do that</u>
<u n="11" who="S0152">three nil down</u>
<u n="12" who="S0012">ah that means they're three nil away they they were</u>
<u n="13" who="S0152">no they played at Barcelona so Barcelona</u>
<u n="14" who="S0012">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0152">so if Barcelona get an away get a goal</u>
<u n="16" who="S0012">they've had it haven't they?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0152">then they got to then they got to get four haven't they?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0152">five</u>
<u n="20" who="S0012">five to cancel out the away goal</u>
<u n="21" who="S0152">yeah well then it goes to extra time doesn't it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0012">yeah but an away goal costs more doesn't it?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0152">yeah but if they score three and it's three then it's the same</u>
<u n="24" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0152">if Barcelona score so it's four three</u>
<u n="26" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0152">they've still got to score four because that way</u>
<u n="28" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0152">they got to score five</u>
<u n="30" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0152">cos they got an away goal no yeah they got an away goal they got to score five to win</u>
<u n="32" who="S0012">yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/> you don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0013">are you watching it as well?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="35" who="S0012">why not?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0152">why not? cos I've got some work to do</u>
<u n="37" who="S0013" trans="overlap">work</u>
<u n="38" who="S0152">I've got a letter of application to write</u>
<u n="39" who="S0012">have you?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0012">that'll be interesting have you have you had any advice on what to write?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0152">I'm just going to do the I wish to apply for this job cos it's an application form plus you've got to put a letter of why you want the job</u>
<u n="43" who="S0012">why you want the job?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0012">there's loads of loads of reasons why isn't there?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0152">there's loads of reasons why there's loads of reasons why I don't want the job as well</u>
<u n="48" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0013">couldn't say that</u>
<u n="50" who="S0012">you want more money though</u>
<u n="51" who="S0152">I think there's probably more reasons why I don't want the job than I do want the job</u>
<u n="52" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0012">is it money wise? it is good money?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0152">it'll be an extra seven thousand a year</u>
<u n="55" who="S0012">will it?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0012">well well that's a good reason innit?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well that's go for it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0152">it's more than a good reason at this time</u>
<u n="60" who="S0013">yeah it is</u>
<u n="61" who="S0152">it is more than a good reason at this time but I don't know what's going to happen I mean they interviewed today for erm jobs for a SENCO job</u>
<u n="62" who="S0012">did they?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0152">mm don't know who got it but somebody in the department went for it er</u>
<u n="64" who="S0012">you didn't?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0152">no I don't want a SENCO job not at our place</u>
<u n="66" who="S0012">what does that entail then?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0152">special educational needs</u>
<u n="68" who="S0012">oh I see yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh mm that's quite hard isn't it?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0152" trans="overlap">every <trunc>ev</trunc> every student's got one</u>
<u n="72" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0152">and if they haven't they're trying to get one</u>
<u n="74" who="S0013">oh gosh</u>
<u n="75" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="77" who="S0012">oh dear</u>
<u n="78" who="S0013">so what is special need cases like then?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0012">well they?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0013">really</u>
<u n="81" who="S0152">they can be <trunc>a</trunc> they can be they can be anything they can be from dyslexia all the way from Asperger's</u>
<u n="82" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0152">the whole spectrum</u>
<u n="85" who="S0013">that's hard isn't it?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0152">ADHD er DDD or whatever that is I made that one up</u>
<u n="87" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0152">erm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0012"><trunc>we</trunc> weren't that a bug killer?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0152">oh right</u>
<u n="91" who="S0012">that was DDT</u>
<u n="92" who="S0152">DDT that was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="93" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0152">that's what they need you know I think that's what part of the problem</u>
<u n="95" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0152">they are ah they are just at the moment they're just off the wall</u>
<u n="97" who="S0012">that's weird innit? why is that? what are they being fed on?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0152">I just dunno they're just off the wall this afternoon there was an exam and the exam started at one thirty and it was for an hour I think the I think it was for an hour and a half yeah it was for an hour and a half so one thirty-two thirty not only a hour maybe it was only a hour which meant that they would be ready for their last lesson</u>
<u n="99" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0152">thirty of them this is year eleven decided that they weren't going to go to their last lesson they got out the building</u>
<u n="101" who="S0012">out of the building?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0152">they they left the building</u>
<u n="104" who="S0012">why is that?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0152">because they were being told they could</u>
<u n="106" who="S0012">who on earth told them?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0152">right so you've got one person you've got two people saying you're staying in school until the end of the day</u>
<u n="108" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0152">even though you have an exam because you've still got lessons to go to and then you've got the new head who has kind of said oh if they're <trunc>fi</trunc> if they've done their exam in the afternoon they can go home</u>
<u n="110" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="111" who="S0152">nobody nobody is telling one person or the other person what's what</u>
<u n="112" who="S0012">oh that's a bit bad innit</u>
<u n="113" who="S0152">right? and then of course the students that haven't got exams</u>
<u n="114" who="S0012">they want to go home as well</u>
<u n="115" who="S0152">they want to go home cos it's not fair</u>
<u n="116" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="117" who="S0152">so with my group this afternoon I got laptops and I got I said right you can go on Bitesize this afternoon cos they've got their exam this time next week</u>
<u n="118" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0152">I said you can go on Bitesize and you will do some revision questions now I only had eight but pff two did it two did it no problem at all no real issues but the other six there was issues</u>
<u n="121" who="S0012">was there?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0152">one didn't do anything I'm not doing it it's not fair they've gone home I'm not doing it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0152">you've got an exam next week yeah and so what?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0012">well we never used to be able to talk like that to teacher's did we?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="128" who="S0152">you know I really didn't feel like actually recording it now would I the thing is if I recorded it and then played it back to the senior team would I then get into trouble?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0152">cos cos it's the cos it's then</u>
<u n="131" who="S0012">you're supposed to have permission anyway to record if they give you permission they'd be fine won't they? but then I don't know</u>
<u n="132" who="S0152">it's like should I should I you know should I put a camera on me and show the abuse that you have to put up with from some students</u>
<u n="133" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0012">well there is a case for that</u>
<u n="135" who="S0013" trans="overlap">tempting</u>
<u n="136" who="S0012">because in some er preschools and and not preschools nurseries they used to have the cameras on</u>
<u n="137" who="S0013" trans="overlap">they had to do that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0012">so that the parents could see how they were behaving didn't they?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0013">yeah cos there was a lot of trouble weren't they in some of these nurseries</u>
<u n="141" who="S0012" trans="overlap">cos there was a lot of trouble about it all in the nurseries</u>
<u n="142" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0012">and er you know it was all about abuse and stuff like that wasn't it and things so they had they had the cameras I don't know if they still do it</u>
<u n="144" who="S0152">but but I know you know having been at that higher position I know if you're in a high position even our senior managers the kids don't have any respect for them as such they push it and push it and push it and walk away from them</u>
<u n="145" who="S0012">do they?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0152">so as a classroom teacher you've got no chance</u>
<u n="147" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="148" who="S0152">because they don't see you being a head of school or a vice principal or anything like that they don't see it as the <trunc>p</trunc> they just say oh so what so what? we can still walk away when they do that</u>
<u n="149" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0012">what an attitude</u>
<u n="151" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0012">it's a terrible attitude</u>
<u n="153" who="S0013" trans="overlap">how do you deal with it really?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0012">do they come to school <trunc>d</trunc> do they start that school with that attitude?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0152">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0012">so what happened to the other school the middle school or whatever you call it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0152">same type of thing</u>
<u n="158" who="S0012">so how do they?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0152">it depends it depends on which middle school they came from</u>
<u n="160" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0152">yeah but then what happens is you get the kids who see them getting away with it</u>
<u n="163" who="S0012">well of course you do you get that all the time don't you? but</u>
<u n="164" who="S0013" trans="overlap">the other side mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0012">but you you get decent kids that think oh dear I'm not having anything to do with them you know I'll keep out the way sometimes they get bullied don't they?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0152">yeah I I've my product design groups are year nines apart from one student who just will not do anything</u>
<u n="167" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0152">he'll be negative towards me so I'm feeling</u>
<u n="169" who="S0012">picked upon</u>
<u n="170" who="S0152">picked on</u>
<u n="171" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0013">you'd be so bored wouldn't you if they're not gonna join in and I don't understand that</u>
<u n="173" who="S0152">I don't need it so I'm not going to do it but you're not following the rules you're not doing this you're not doing the other you haven't given me forewarning marks now I don't need to give you forewarning marks because I spoke to my head of department because you're not working that I'm going to move you to an area where you can work yeah but that's creating that's that's putting me down that is isn't it? so I'm I'm feeling I'm getting negative vibes about it so I'm not going to do anything</u>
<u n="174" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="175" who="S0152">and all I want to do really is just laugh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0013">it's their life innit?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0012">that's that's the really weird thing you see it's it's the respect has gone now hasn't it? the respect for anybody in authority is gone you know in in that</u>
<u n="181" who="S0152">yeah ah it we don't we don't have any sanctions</u>
<u n="182" who="S0012">no well you can't touch them for a start can you?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0152" trans="overlap">no you can't do anything like that but we have no it's I've got a lad who shouldn't be at the school alright? he is really severe erm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0012">what's he?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0152">no what's the other one there's Asperger's there's another one</u>
<u n="186" who="S0012">er like a hyperactive</u>
<u n="187" who="S0152">no erm everything is everything has to be explained in unless it's clear it is <trunc>a</trunc> it is a form of Asperger's on the other on the one end of the spectrum</u>
<u n="188" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0152">but he is dangerous he is physically dangerous</u>
<u n="190" who="S0012">ain't that one who had the knife is it?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0152">no no this is a year seven lad he's the one that I had to physically restrain a couple of months ago</u>
<u n="192" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0152">when he got that kid round the neck and was strangling him</u>
<u n="194" who="S0012">yeah that's right yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0152">right he should not be in school</u>
<u n="197" who="S0012">well they used to have special schools for them sort of people didn't they?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0152">yeah he shouldn't be he kicked a lad today he kicked him cos this lad said something</u>
<u n="200" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0152">he then smacked the kid on the on his back because he said something and this lad said well what did you do that for? well you were being mean to me no I was just we were telling you how you were being to us and you didn't like it so you hit out</u>
<u n="202" who="S0012">there's no reasoning with them them sort of people is there?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0152">no reason at all</u>
<u n="204" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you can't reason no</u>
<u n="205" who="S0152">no reason at all and it and it's going all the way <trunc>th</trunc> and you can you can see why some of it is where it is but he is danger he is going to hurt somebody</u>
<u n="206" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0152">now I have sent emails off saying that this person should not be in school</u>
<u n="208" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0012">nothing back</u>
<u n="211" who="S0152">I'm covering myself</u>
<u n="212" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0152">as a head of year as a form tutor as a class teacher this student is not safe to be in school</u>
<u n="214" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0152">yesterday I</u>
<u n="216" who="S0013">wait until something's really serious and then</u>
<u n="217" who="S0152">yeah yeah and it's why isn't something been done about it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's wrong</u>
<u n="219" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0152">why hasn't something been done about it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0012">ah there's some weird weirdy people about</u>
<u n="223" who="S0152">why hasn't there something been done about it</u>
<u n="224" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0012">oh strange strange</u>
<u n="226" who="S0152">and <trunc>yes</trunc> I mean yesterday I was out on the field watching them lunch time on lunch time duty outside this lad got upset because he got hit by the ball by the football</u>
<u n="227" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0152">he was standing behind the goals talking</u>
<u n="229" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="230" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0152">and he got hit three times and the third time he picked the ball and he picked it up and he kicked it in the opposite direction</u>
<u n="232" who="S0012">did he?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0152">so I pulled him over he says he's aiming at me</u>
<u n="234" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="235" who="S0152">and I just went you are standing in the goal area talking you're standing behind the goal area people are playing football they're going to kick and it's going to go in and you're going to get hit he's doing it on purpose doing it on purpose</u>
<u n="236" who="S0012">oh dear</u>
<u n="237" who="S0152">and this was another lad and he couldn't see just couldn't see past that he was on</u>
<u n="238" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0012">ah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0013">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0012">make you wonder where their head is doesn't it? you know what how they're thinking</u>
<u n="242" who="S0152">you know <trunc>o</trunc> other morning other morning all the kids were checked coming into school</u>
<u n="243" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0152">other morning every kid was checked coming into school making certain they've got their planner making certain they've got a pen got a pencil they've got a ruler right? you don't you shouldn't have to do that but that's what happened from the second from the second week in the head says I'm not having that I'm not having that <pause dur="short"/> because she wanted to morning meetings with her SLT cos it was SLT that wanted to do it</u>
<u n="245" who="S0012">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0152">so she said every member of staff had to have a box of equipment in their classroom I never collected my box of equipment cos I always keep pens and pencils</u>
<u n="247" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0152">if a kid hasn't got one never made a song and dance about it there you go</u>
<u n="249" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0152">hand it me back at the end I've <trunc>r</trunc> I've now run out can I have <trunc>mi</trunc> they've all gone <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't but I haven't had my box of pens pencils and rulers I <unclear>had</unclear> my equipment so how come they've all gone? my box should still be there waiting for me</u>
<u n="251" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0152">and it was like well but we've given it to other people because they've run out</u>
<u n="253" who="S0012">well that's great innit?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0152">so yeah so that means that members of staff are not taking ownership of what we're giving out they're not collecting it back in they're not</u>
<u n="255" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0012">I can't remember how we I mean they used to supply the pens and paper and stuff like that they used to keep them in your <trunc>boo</trunc> in your desk</u>
<u n="257" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0152">they don't have desks and things like that at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0012">they don't have flap up desks anymore?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0152" trans="overlap">no dangerous can't have it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0012">no cos people used to crash their fingers in them</u>
<u n="262" who="S0152">and that's what would happen</u>
<u n="263" who="S0013" trans="overlap">and hide behind them</u>
<u n="264" who="S0012">yeah and hide behind them and carve their name in them</u>
<u n="265" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and that's what yeah or <trunc>te</trunc> bang them and things like that</u>
<u n="266" who="S0012">yeah yeah oh dear</u>
<u n="267" who="S0152">so you know and you you you're up against that on a regular basis</u>
<u n="268" who="S0013">yeah soul destroying</u>
<u n="269" who="S0012">that is soul destroying innit?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0152">yeah and when I consider how we you know for <trunc>whate</trunc> we had a really good regime at OBA</u>
<u n="271" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0152">the only person that was wrong with OBA was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0152">right? but every kid was checked as they came into school in the morning their uniform</u>
<u n="275" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0152">and if their uniform wasn't right because they were checked the kids knew there was a consequence they either had to go home and get it or they were put somewhere</u>
<u n="277" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0152">can't do that here if the kids got sent out they had an hour's detention after school that night they were kept we kept them after school doing that? don't believe in it not doing that</u>
<u n="279" who="S0012">oh dear</u>
<u n="280" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0012">need a bit of er discipline though doesn't it? sounds as though the school</u>
<u n="282" who="S0013" trans="overlap">once it start going now that's</u>
<u n="283" who="S0152">once it goes it takes a hell of a long way to get back up to where it should be</u>
<u n="284" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0012">it does yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0013">so and so was able to go home and not do this and</u>
<u n="287" who="S0152" trans="overlap">because yeah the number of lates in the morning pff horrendous amount of lates in the morning</u>
<u n="288" who="S0012">is he?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0012">well that doesn't go well when when the when they come and inspect you does it?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0152">we we need being honest we need we just had that inspection now but we need another inspection a no notice inspection</u>
<u n="292" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah what they give notice do they?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0152">well you some schools give notice some schools don't cos they they're trying it out</u>
<u n="294" who="S0012">I don't think they should give notice at all</u>
<u n="295" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0012">oh dear <pause dur="long"/> the little babies are getting really big</u>
<u n="297" who="S0152">really?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0012">they are ain't they?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0012">you want to see them</u>
<u n="301" who="S0013">some change of <trunc>to</trunc> subject</u>
<u n="302" who="S0012">yeah well I was just thinking</u>
<u n="303" who="S0152">you were just thinking football football</u>
<u n="304" who="S0012">no no no football I go in the other room for football don't I?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0012">I'll show you the babies</u>
<u n="307" who="S0152">footy is on</u>
<u n="308" who="S0012">that's on two innit yeah? there they all are</u>
<u n="309" who="S0152">how many are there?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0012">there is about eight or nine two eggs didn't hatch that made it she had twelve eggs that made it ten</u>
<u n="311" who="S0152">then she took out didn't she?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0012">and she took one out so that's nine and you can't really count</u>
<u n="313" who="S0152">ah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0012">look at that though <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> she's gone round every one hasn't she? two four six eight I can count there're eight babies</u>
<u n="315" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0012">look at how she she goes digging underneath for their sacks</u>
<u n="317" who="S0152">and she's just doing a little poo changing their nappies</u>
<u n="318" who="S0012">yeah look at that</u>
<u n="319" who="S0152">they've grown in three days two days</u>
<u n="320" who="S0013">they have haven't they?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0012">look at her <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0013">amazing</u>
<u n="325" who="S0012">or him he come in as well they both sit on them she's just she's just they look weird <trunc>a</trunc> look at that one mum what are you doing? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0152">it tickles it tickles</u>
<u n="327" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0012">come on I got to make the bed <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's what she's doing innit? she's gone</u>
<u n="329" who="S0152">have you have you got an old video player?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="331" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="332" who="S0152">cos you could feed it into a video player on long play so a four-hour tape in eight hours</u>
<u n="333" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yes you could couldn't you?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0012">you could couldn't you? yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0012">we got a tape player that play tapes but er it's feeding it into that innit?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0152">you just got to plus it into the <trunc>the</trunc> into the er sockets on the back the red yellow and blue sockets well yellow</u>
<u n="338" who="S0012">trouble is we won't be able to record anything will we?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0152">not of you had a separate video</u>
<u n="340" who="S0012">yeah if you had a separate one yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0013">mm mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0012">but look at them though</u>
<u n="343" who="S0013">yeah it won't be long before they're gone will it?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0012">that one has land on the top of the lot of them look he's just he's just land right on top of them all I'm the boss I want feeding first she did start feeding them from the fat balls <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0013">oh that was a quick one</u>
<u n="346" who="S0012" trans="overlap">she only fed one oh she packed in dad that was dad and mum's there</u>
<u n="347" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh oh</u>
<u n="348" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="349" who="S0013">no gone to find food</u>
<u n="350" who="S0012">three four five six seven eight might be nine</u>
<u n="351" who="S0013">they've got to be tiny haven't they? so tiny you forget the size when you keep looking at them like this</u>
<u n="352" who="S0012">yeah but they're getting feathers now look</u>
<u n="353" who="S0152">here he is</u>
<u n="354" who="S0012">oh he's eating them look yeah there he is</u>
<u n="355" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0012">he going back in now? yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0012">there you go have a fat ball <vocal desc="laugh"/> he <unclear/> one of them though <pause dur="short"/> he's having some more oh no <pause dur="short"/> see she's she's gone somewhere you ought to have seen the great big wiggly wormy thing that they they had <trunc>yo</trunc> on there today she was sitting there with this big old worm in her <trunc>fe</trunc> in her hand oh that's a grey tit that one innit?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0152">you know my jar my what's on the wall</u>
<u n="360" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0152">I filled that up yesterday yesterday evening</u>
<u n="362" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0152">with seed it's now empty</u>
<u n="364" who="S0012">is it?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0013">wow</u>
<u n="366" who="S0012">I filled that one up with seed today just this afternoon about four o'clock</u>
<u n="367" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm you're making them lazy</u>
<u n="368" who="S0012">yeah but look how handy it is for the nest</u>
<u n="369" who="S0013">oh I know it's lovely</u>
<u n="370" who="S0152">and they're going to be they're going to be robust then aren't they?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0012">I mean they can get the seed the fat balls and then think I had a great big crow come down and eat half the grub off the I put it on the table on the bird table</u>
<u n="374" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0012">god he comes swooping down it nearly knock that thing over he had a load of</u>
<u n="376" who="S0013">did you did you see our cockerel?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0152">yeah the white one?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0012">yeah I don't know where he's come from</u>
<u n="379" who="S0013">someone must have left it here</u>
<u n="380" who="S0012" trans="overlap">someone someone someone keep dumping chickens</u>
<u n="381" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0012">they dump chickens up the road there they go around <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s or they or they they go with the other chickens then they walk round here and we have several on the field</u>
<u n="383" who="S0152">he's a big cockerel he is</u>
<u n="384" who="S0012">he's a massive isn't he?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0013" trans="overlap">but that cockerel he's got feather legs</u>
<u n="386" who="S0152">yeah he's a massive legs</u>
<u n="387" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0013">I feel really sorry for him cos he just keeps wandering round</u>
<u n="389" who="S0012">them ones over there don't like him you see? and they come over here and there's a little like an Indian fighting cock that is that they've got you know? it's a bantam cock</u>
<u n="390" who="S0013">you saw them fighting did you?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0012">yeah and he come running across the field at him and jumped at him and this one jumps away and then he turns round and he just slowly walk I don't want any trouble</u>
<u n="392" who="S0152" trans="overlap">he's a nice cockerel</u>
<u n="393" who="S0012">I don't want any trouble with those two</u>
<u n="394" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah he's not bad</u>
<u n="395" who="S0152">he is a nice cockerel</u>
<u n="396" who="S0013">don't really want him here though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0012">no cos he sit outside our window</u>
<u n="398" who="S0013">god he was loud this morning wasn't it?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0012" trans="overlap">first thing like four o'clock in the morning going cock-a-doodle-doo god he's loud isn't he?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh he really is loud yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0152">still he he makes some good chicken soup</u>
<u n="402" who="S0013" trans="overlap">we had our window open last night though</u>
<u n="403" who="S0152">he'll make some good soup</u>
<u n="404" who="S0013">mm?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0012">it'd be a bit tough to eat but he'd make good soup wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0013">I wouldn't want it</u>
<u n="407" who="S0012">why not?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0013">last time was bad enough</u>
<u n="409" who="S0012">what?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0013">when you last did one which was a long time ago</u>
<u n="411" who="S0012" trans="overlap">right took a long while there's two in there now look</u>
<u n="412" who="S0013">he can't eat anything</u>
<u n="413" who="S0152">if you cook <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0013">and I bought a load of stock</u>
<u n="415" who="S0152">he's keeping all the grubs down in the garden</u>
<u n="416" who="S0012">it's the thrush do that the thrushes do that they keep them all down I want thrushes rather than him cos there there must have been a magpie that ate two or three birds babies you know</u>
<u n="417" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0013">oh yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0012">took them out the nest just bit their heads off</u>
<u n="420" who="S0013" trans="overlap">just their head</u>
<u n="421" who="S0012">bit their heads off weren't a cat cos a cat would just devoured it or</u>
<u n="422" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0012">or ripped it up</u>
<u n="424" who="S0152">magpie's are like that though</u>
<u n="425" who="S0012">magpies yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0013" trans="overlap">just his head oh awful</u>
<u n="427" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah and and we see him flicking around and he must have just swooped down on them cos they running round round round the green and er when when she bring off her lot I'm going to have to I'm going to have to be up half the time gardening cos they come out he nest little ones the blackbird er the blue tits and they just run along the ground and <trunc>la</trunc> and the year before last we had a a huge storm didn't we? and that killed every one of them they just they just got drowned</u>
<u n="428" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0012">look at that she's feeling them very well</u>
<u n="430" who="S0152" trans="overlap">how's the er thrush</u>
<u n="431" who="S0012">pardon?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0152">how's the thrush in the nest?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0012">she's gone</u>
<u n="434" who="S0013">yeah they that's when we saw a <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="435" who="S0012" trans="overlap">they all gone now and that's when we found two dead magpie got them but the others have gone</u>
<u n="436" who="S0152">what about the robin?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0012">the robin's all gone they all went</u>
<u n="438" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0152">so they fledged?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0012">yeah they all fledged</u>
<u n="441" who="S0013">we got a robin in the erm one of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0012">yes we have yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0013">right yeah don't know where the nest is</u>
<u n="444" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I mean he's in a well the last one was in a flower pot there's still one egg in that flower pot</u>
<u n="445" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well it's not in the flower pot I looked in <unclear>the old one</unclear></u>
<u n="446" who="S0012">yeah that's a there's an egg in there</u>
<u n="447" who="S0013">is there?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0012">there was when I last saw it which was a couple of days ago</u>
<u n="449" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0012">but she's in there somewhere isn't she?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0012">because er when you go in she's she's she's scared of you</u>
<u n="453" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> is she?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0012">she daren't go in that in that shed cos we frightened the poor little old robin <pause dur="long"/> look we're going to have to put football on it's no good</u>
<u n="455" who="S0013">oh no I've got to switch it back sorry <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0012">it ain't on yet <trunc>la</trunc> just let me see if if that's on</u>
<u n="457" who="S0013" trans="overlap">okay I've got to go back haven't I?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0012">yeah <event desc="sound of tv"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0152">that's Roadshow <pause dur="short"/> that's Antiques Roadshow</u>
<u n="460" who="S0012">you got to put it on TV</u>
<u n="461" who="S0013">I'll put it on mute then or do I switch it off?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0012">you can click it off cos I don't I don't think the kick kick off is until eight o'clock</u>
<u n="463" who="S0152">eight o'clock is it?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0012">what are you laughing at</u>
<u n="466" who="S0013">nothing</u>
<u n="467" who="S0012">just cos you're not interested in football <pause dur="short"/> what I have to go through <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hey?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0013">what what to move in the other room? it was your idea</u>
<u n="469" who="S0012">no I will go in the other room when they kick off</u>
<u n="470" who="S0013">it was your idea not mine</u>
<u n="471" who="S0012">yeah well you don't need to sit there moaning about it</u>
<u n="472" who="S0013">well I sometimes let you stay in here don't I?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0012" trans="overlap">or you get out of the way</u>
<u n="474" who="S0152">you need the surround sound on and things like that if you're watching the football</u>
<u n="475" who="S0012">it does yeah have we got surround sound too on this one not on that one</u>
<u n="476" who="S0013">we don't use it really</u>
<u n="477" who="S0012">we got false surround</u>
<u n="478" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I don't think they've got it connected properly</u>
<u n="479" who="S0012">we have</u>
<u n="480" who="S0013">shouldn't it be connected to the bottom one?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0012">it's on cinema sound</u>
<u n="482" who="S0013">shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0013">yeah well we haven't got it connected up</u>
<u n="485" who="S0012">we've got cinema sound on</u>
<u n="486" who="S0013">the area connect or something it should be</u>
<u n="487" who="S0152">it should it should be coming out your bottom one so for your surround sound to work</u>
<u n="488" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0152">your bottom one has to switched on and then you switch that to</u>
<u n="490" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0152">the channel</u>
<u n="492" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well it doesn't it only we have only got it for the videos</u>
<u n="493" who="S0152">oh I see so it's not coming from the TV</u>
<u n="494" who="S0013" trans="overlap">not from the television</u>
<u n="495" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="496" who="S0152">then you <trunc>ne</trunc> then you probably need a optical lead to pull it into the back of it</u>
<u n="497" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0152">so you take your optical lead out the back of your tele into the back of that</u>
<u n="500" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0013">it's a good job the erm aerial man came we got them the wrong way round hadn't we?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0012">I don't know what he did we got a better picture though we got ten and that was six</u>
<u n="503" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he said we'd got the connections the wrong way round or something but it still worked didn't it?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0012">yeah I don't know what he did</u>
<u n="505" who="S0013">yeah but he's having a lot of trouble with it wasn't he? until he realised</u>
<u n="506" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0152">see I I have my Sky box going into my surround sound</u>
<u n="508" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0152">so if it's just using as the DVD player that it's surround sound but I can have my Sky box going in</u>
<u n="510" who="S0012">yeah well that's like the Freesat that'll that's on surround sound but we can't get it on on DVD</u>
<u n="511" who="S0152">well you just need an optical cable then</u>
<u n="512" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0152">I have one</u>
<u n="514" who="S0012">oh ha</u>
<u n="515" who="S0152">I have I have an optical cable I'm sure I have an optical cable</u>
<u n="516" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="517" who="S0152">and you just take it out the back of your TV and you plug it into the surround sound and then you set your surround sound up for your auxiliary coming from your TV</u>
<u n="518" who="S0012">do you? oh</u>
<u n="519" who="S0152">then you can listen to all your sound on your TV coming through that</u>
<u n="520" who="S0012">when it came out of that box down there there's a little there's a little er speaker down there that put the wind up you</u>
<u n="521" who="S0013">no you moved it now</u>
<u n="522" who="S0152">have you?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0013">yes we we moved it over here now didn't we?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0152">what your base?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0012">oh yeah it's down there</u>
<u n="526" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it was down there</u>
<u n="527" who="S0012">it was down there</u>
<u n="528" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0012">but that meant trailing the wire all the way across and down</u>
<u n="530" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0012">what we need is wireless speakers <pause dur="short"/> then you just get stick them anywhere in the house and you get</u>
<u n="532" who="S0152">what you need it a Bose system</u>
<u n="533" who="S0012">a Bose system yeah that's what you need well that their little <trunc>sli</trunc></u>
<u n="534" who="S0152" trans="overlap">sound bar</u>
<u n="535" who="S0012">sound bar wow</u>
<u n="536" who="S0013">they're good aren't they?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0012">they're fantastic yeah but they're very very expensive aren't they?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0152">a good one is yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0012">yeah well I'll have one <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> for my birthday</u>
<u n="540" who="S0152">for your birthday? that's a long way off</u>
<u n="541" who="S0012">oh I'll have one for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday</u>
<u n="542" who="S0152">that's a long way off too</u>
<u n="543" who="S0012">whose birthday have we got next?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0012">I'll have one for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday <pause dur="short"/> twenty-fifth of July that</u>
<u n="546" who="S0152" trans="overlap">that's quite soon that is</u>
<u n="547" who="S0013">yeah not long is it?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0152">that's quite soon</u>
<u n="549" who="S0012">same day as my mum</u>
<u n="550" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0013">fifteen</u>
<u n="553" who="S0152">fifteen</u>
<u n="554" who="S0012">they did a a survey on the television just the other day about birthdays and they reckon that <pause dur="short"/> out of twelve people <pause dur="short"/> two will have the same birthday</u>
<u n="555" who="S0013">out of twelve?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0012">out of only twelve yes that's what they said on there</u>
<u n="557" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0012">but you think</u>
<u n="559" who="S0013">two people you know</u>
<u n="560" who="S0012">no out of twelve people they pick you they pick twelve people out</u>
<u n="561" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0012">and two of them will have the same birthday date they'd be miles apart they could be two and they could be sixty-two</u>
<u n="563" who="S0013">yeah but that's I still that's</u>
<u n="564" who="S0012">well think about it my brother three three people in our family three boys in our family and I'm born on the same day my brother was born on</u>
<u n="565" who="S0013">yeah but that that's not usual</u>
<u n="566" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah but but yeah but if you think logically about it think logically about it</u>
<u n="567" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0012">yeah what's logical about it?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0013">no one in twelve is not</u>
<u n="570" who="S0012">you think about</u>
<u n="571" who="S0013">not logical</u>
<u n="572" who="S0012">when the most most people are born</u>
<u n="573" who="S0013">well there's twelve months for a start off</u>
<u n="574" who="S0012">well this is this is what they did they did research and they tell you and it's on the television and they and they picked they picked twelve people out of the audience and two of them had the same birthday</u>
<u n="575" who="S0013" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="576" who="S0152">er yeah but if you if you I <trunc>ca</trunc> I I I don't think about things like this but sometimes it does cross my mind okay sometimes it crosses my mind okay? a lot of people are born in September October</u>
<u n="577" who="S0012">yeah because there's the spring</u>
<u n="578" who="S0152">alright nine months Christmas New Year</u>
<u n="579" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="S0152">yeah?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0152">erm you can also put it down to around somebody's birthday as well</u>
<u n="583" who="S0012">or the dark nights</u>
<u n="584" who="S0152">or the dark night which is the same type of thing</u>
<u n="585" who="S0013" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="586" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0152">which is the same type of thing so if you know somebody's birthday is in February alright? so February is the second month so you are looking Novemberish time aren't you?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0012">yeah but you you can you're you can do this easier at your school because you've got a load of kids in the school in one class you can do an experiment and find out</u>
<u n="589" who="S0152">in my class I've got nobody that has the same birthday</u>
<u n="590" who="S0012">don't you?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="592" who="S0152">now there's twenty-seven in my class</u>
<u n="593" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="594" who="S0152">but there are there's a couple of people in my year group that is born on the same day as me first of October</u>
<u n="595" who="S0012">oh right yeah well there you go done</u>
<u n="596" who="S0152">alright? but if you take</u>
<u n="597" who="S0013" trans="overlap">alright</u>
<u n="598" who="S0152">see if you take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday that's the same birthday as my sister's</u>
<u n="599" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="601" who="S0152">twelfth of January</u>
<u n="602" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0013" trans="overlap">ah that's unusual innit?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0152">alright? if you take <pause dur="long"/> my cousin which is my nephew's daughter <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her birthday is the same as my other cousin's first of March</u>
<u n="605" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0012">yeah well we got a friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her birthday is the same birthday as me</u>
<u n="607" who="S0013">yeah we know I know <trunc>s</trunc> we know three people who are the same as yours</u>
<u n="608" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah well I mean</u>
<u n="609" who="S0013">I don't know anyone with mine</u>
<u n="610" who="S0012">well you don't mix with anyone</u>
<u n="611" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well you can't say that</u>
<u n="612" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0013">and I don't actually know anyone with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> birthday I don't know anyone</u>
<u n="614" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> sorry</u>
<u n="615" who="S0013">on the first</u>
<u n="616" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="617" who="S0152">I know somebody on the second I know two people on the second</u>
<u n="618" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0152">I went out with a girl whose birthday was on the second</u>
<u n="621" who="S0012">well let's let's admit it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is just a one-off isn't he?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0013">obviously not though because he has <unclear/> on his birthday</u>
<u n="623" who="S0152">I am just a one-off</u>
<u n="624" who="S0013">you are a one-off you are sorry</u>
<u n="625" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0152">I am just a one-off</u>
<u n="627" who="S0012">well aren't we all</u>
<u n="628" who="S0013">nothing to do with other people's birthdays</u>
<u n="629" who="S0152">I am just a one-off</u>
<u n="630" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0152">that's why I'm unique</u>
<u n="632" who="S0012">yeah well everyone's unique</u>
<u n="633" who="S0152">no cos there's three people that you know that's born on your birthday</u>
<u n="634" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no they haven't got the same fingerprint</u>
<u n="635" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0012">they haven't got the same fingerprints as me</u>
<u n="637" who="S0013">and they're both girls</u>
<u n="638" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0012">yeah they haven't got the same fingerprints as me I said</u>
<u n="640" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no they haven't no</u>
<u n="641" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="642" who="S0152">or eye</u>
<u n="643" who="S0012">or eye pupil eyes pupils pupils</u>
<u n="644" who="S0013">no no</u>
<u n="645" who="S0152">or ear pattern</u>
<u n="646" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="647" who="S0152">cos ear pattern is another one they can do I saw something on the on Twitter 3D printing of the ear canal so if people have got a bad ear now and they need to replace the ear canal they can 3D print it and put it in</u>
<u n="648" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="649" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="650" who="S0012">that's pretty brilliant innit?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0013">mm mm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0012">that is pretty brilliant well they can do lots of 3D printing now can't they?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0013">it's going to change a lot of things innit?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0012">well there's these really good 3D printers they are fantastic they printed a plastic gun didn't they?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0152">yeah but that's</u>
<u n="657" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0152">they it failed</u>
<u n="659" who="S0012">it shot a bullet</u>
<u n="660" who="S0152">yeah but it failed exploded</u>
<u n="661" who="S0012">yeah but they could I mean they they've just said they they printed it</u>
<u n="662" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0012">and it it can be not be found in a in a case when they X-ray the only thing that could <trunc>fi</trunc> find in the case was the bullets</u>
<u n="664" who="S0152">yeah cos they were <trunc>thi</trunc> the spring cos the spring has to be metal</u>
<u n="665" who="S0012" trans="overlap">the spring yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0152">although using the right material you can get away with it</u>
<u n="667" who="S0012">well you could yeah yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0152">but you can 3D print almost anything now</u>
<u n="669" who="S0012">you can yeah yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><unclear/> almost if you can get it molten to cool quickly</u>
<u n="671" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0152">cos that's all it is</u>
<u n="673" who="S0012">yeah that that's all it is yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="675" who="S0152">so a lot of jewellery is made 3D printing now</u>
<u n="676" who="S0012">is it?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0152">a lot of gold jewellery</u>
<u n="678" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0013">is it?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0152">so where you used to have to cut with a piercing saw and do all the shaping and whatever</u>
<u n="681" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0152">a 3D printer will print that out now</u>
<u n="683" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="684" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0012">it's fantastic innit?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0152">I watched my favourite programme again twice this week</u>
<u n="690" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0012">what Countryfile?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0152">no the water tower at Settle</u>
<u n="693" who="S0012">oh right did you?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0013" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="695" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0012">oh you're longing to get up there aren't you? huh?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0152">I watched it twice cos the one on the <unclear/> man was fifteen minutes this time so it went from start to finish in fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="698" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0152">but I do have the full version of it which I watched a couple of times</u>
<u n="700" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="702" who="S0152">erm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0012">well you'll just have to win the lottery won't you?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0013">would you want to do up a water tower?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0152">I'd love to live in that water tower I really would love to live in that water tower they paid two hundred and eight thousand pound for it</u>
<u n="706" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0152">and then they spent another two hundred thousand doing it up</u>
<u n="708" who="S0012">I know but look how much it's worth now</u>
<u n="709" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0152">that view they have from the top of it</u>
<u n="712" who="S0012">well there's there's one at er where is it? Easton you could buy that</u>
<u n="713" who="S0152">yeah but sorry that's not the same type of water tower</u>
<u n="714" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="715" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what about the one in <anon type="place"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0152">they finished down the road haven't they?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0012">they have haven't they? yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0152">it's quite neat down there at the moment</u>
<u n="719" who="S0013">it is yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0152">I would like a railway house</u>
<u n="721" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0152">or a railway station</u>
<u n="723" who="S0012">well there's one at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0152">yeah not there though mm</u>
<u n="725" who="S0013">I expect you saw that one didn't you? in Yorkshire <unclear/> and country</u>
<u n="726" who="S0012">yeah that was beautiful we <trunc>co</trunc></u>
<u n="727" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that was nice</u>
<u n="728" who="S0012">yeah we said you'd like that one</u>
<u n="729" who="S0013" trans="overlap">and it was an er accommodation as well wasn't it?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0152">yeah that was at the</u>
<u n="731" who="S0013">ideal</u>
<u n="732" who="S0152">the <trunc>de</trunc> the one at <anon type="place"/> mega expensive thousand pound a week to stay in the <anon type="place"/> accommodation</u>
<u n="733" who="S0012">is it?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0152">yep I'm I just I don't know</u>
<u n="736" who="S0012">you'll have to buy one</u>
<u n="737" who="S0152">I wish <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="738" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0152">well to the <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0013">what was it we saw homes <trunc>h</trunc> <unclear/> what was a lovely house wasn't it? <vocal desc="cough"/> it was only was it thirty-nine?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0012">I don't remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0013">it was thirty-nine thousand I think <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="743" who="S0012">where was it?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0013">and opposite I don't know whereabouts it was was it the Peak district or something? opposite was just fields and woodland and</u>
<u n="745" who="S0012">oh yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0013">you know</u>
<u n="747" who="S0012">beautiful <trunc>thir</trunc> thirty-nine thousand quid</u>
<u n="748" who="S0013">it was only a a semi or something but they did it up beautifully and</u>
<u n="749" who="S0012">they did didn't they? it had a huge garden</u>
<u n="750" who="S0013">yeah and you think what the location was absolutely amazing</u>
<u n="751" who="S0152">yeah I'm sure I'm you know I'm sure that I'll get be able to do something</u>
<u n="752" who="S0013">mm yeah</u>
<u n="753" who="S0152">but you know you just er if I could just pick up things and just move them there so it was same</u>
<u n="754" who="S0013">yeah cos up north there's there's some decent properties isn't there? for</u>
<u n="755" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0152">for certain prices you get some good</u>
<u n="757" who="S0013" trans="overlap">good prices</u>
<u n="758" who="S0012">well you can go and rent out a</u>
<u n="759" who="S0013">especially if you get it at auction</u>
<u n="760" who="S0012">our friend's house at <anon type="place"/> they got they got there annex to rent out now they're renting that out Fair Fairview is it?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0013">it always has been a rent option</u>
<u n="762" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah but they're renting it out under another</u>
<u n="763" who="S0152">I would you know I'd well that's what I'm going to have to do to begin with rent somewhere isn't it? so</u>
<u n="764" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0152">unless things change so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0152">unless things change that's what I'm going to have to do</u>
<u n="768" who="S0012">well now let's hope you have more luck on your next viewing</u>
<u n="769" who="S0013">mm there's got to be someone somewhere</u>
<u n="770" who="S0152">I just think if I paint everywhere I really do think if I paint all the woodwork</u>
<u n="771" who="S0012">and made it look a bit smarter you mean?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0152">yeah just paint all the white woodwork</u>
<u n="773" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0152">get rid of the get rid of the wallpaper just have a plain wall in the dining room</u>
<u n="776" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="777" who="S0152">rather than a wallpaper just paint over it</u>
<u n="778" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0152">the problem I've got then is if I start painting the wallpaper it starts coming off</u>
<u n="780" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0012">that's a problem innit yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0013">that is a problem and then if you're in the middle of it and then you get a viewing that's another problem isn't it?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0012">trouble is when when wallpaper's painted people think ah couldn't he take the wallpaper off? well the plaster come off when you take wallpaper off</u>
<u n="785" who="S0152">yeah it's all those things</u>
<u n="786" who="S0013">they're a problem sometimes aren't they? yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0152">it's like using lining paper and stuff like that</u>
<u n="788" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="789" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0152">no I don't know</u>
<u n="791" who="S0013">I mean we're doing the <trunc>dai</trunc> erm we're doing the dairy up</u>
<u n="792" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0013">but the amount of little holes everywhere and</u>
<u n="794" who="S0012">cracks there's cracks you can get your fists in</u>
<u n="795" who="S0013" trans="overlap">cracks to fill in yeah there were cracks to begin with and then er oh it's just so many little bits</u>
<u n="796" who="S0152">yes</u>
<u n="797" who="S0013">it's amazing it never <trunc>s</trunc> we never saw them before did we?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="799" who="S0013">and the ceiling is bad</u>
<u n="800" who="S0012">ceiling is terrible</u>
<u n="801" who="S0013">I'm not doing that though</u>
<u n="802" who="S0012">that needs scraping all out plastering over</u>
<u n="803" who="S0013" trans="overlap">lots to do</u>
<u n="804" who="S0012">and then putting a skim over the whole lot</u>
<u n="805" who="S0152">well can't you <trunc>ju</trunc> can't you put a skim over the top?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0012">well you could do yeah but we it's got the cracks have got to be mended first because they're too far apart</u>
<u n="807" who="S0152">right</u>
<u n="808" who="S0012">to put skim <trunc>o</trunc> skim over that you're still going to see the the seam where the <trunc>s</trunc> where the cracks are</u>
<u n="809" who="S0013">you taped some of it actually</u>
<u n="810" who="S0012">we did tape some of it</u>
<u n="811" who="S0013" trans="overlap">on a notice yeah mm</u>
<u n="812" who="S0012">it should have been taped in the first place this side</u>
<u n="813" who="S0152" trans="overlap">all the all the things should be taped all the joints should be taped</u>
<u n="814" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it should have been taped he taped them from the top</u>
<u n="815" who="S0013">see because it was just a dairy we think he he did it really roughly we weren't down here then that was the first building</u>
<u n="816" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he just</u>
<u n="817" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0013">that we put on here and he didn't do a very good job</u>
<u n="819" who="S0152">he did a lousy job</u>
<u n="820" who="S0013" trans="overlap">basically because it was just a dairy</u>
<u n="821" who="S0012">he didn't give two monkeys</u>
<u n="822" who="S0013">not <trunc>a</trunc> not supposed to be accommodation</u>
<u n="823" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0012">he only did nine nine-inch footings</u>
<u n="825" who="S0013">mm and we we've put the floor down since and that it's just concrete one the floor wasn't it?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well most building around here are nine-inch footings</u>
<u n="827" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="830" who="S0152">they need to be they got to be a metre now footings</u>
<u n="831" who="S0012">yep</u>
<u n="832" who="S0152">in <trunc>cl</trunc> in this in round here</u>
<u n="833" who="S0012">in clay yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0152">round here cos it just moves</u>
<u n="835" who="S0013">yeah he used an old door for the loft patch <trunc>li</trunc><trunc>li</trunc> odd bits are really bad</u>
<u n="836" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he really made a bodge he really bodged up didn't he?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="838" who="S0012">he he got it done as quick as he could cos he knew that what he charged was too much money and we were getting a grant from the government to to build a a an agricultural place</u>
<u n="839" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0012">you you got grants in and we got three thousand pound grant to build that and he charged us twelve thousand anyway didn't he?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0012">and we had to pay him so much so much every</u>
<u n="843" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0012">every move he made and we just paid up we didn't even inspect it did we?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0013">no we just thought</u>
<u n="846" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we weren't down here</u>
<u n="847" who="S0013">he was the only builder we knew basically</u>
<u n="848" who="S0012" trans="overlap">because he was he's a a local builder</u>
<u n="849" who="S0013">he's er the son of the person who lived next door to us</u>
<u n="850" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0013">or next door but one</u>
<u n="852" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0013">wasn't he? we just thought oh we don't know any other builders</u>
<u n="854" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0013">you know how you do you get someone you know don't you thinking</u>
<u n="856" who="S0012">and we shouldn't have done but then</u>
<u n="857" who="S0013">then we let him use his scaffold the field leave his scaffolding poles and that</u>
<u n="858" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0013">thinking you know</u>
<u n="860" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0012">he wanted a yard</u>
<u n="862" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="S0012">so he left all his all his scaffolding</u>
<u n="864" who="S0013" trans="overlap">didn't do us any favours</u>
<u n="865" who="S0012">gear up here</u>
<u n="866" who="S0013">but there you are it was just a dairy that's all he thought about we had like a <pause dur="short"/> second hand sink and stuff like that in there</u>
<u n="867" who="S0012">it's kick off</u>
<u n="868" who="S0152">kick off work time</u>
<u n="869" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="870" who="S0152">work time</u>
<u n="871" who="S0013">okay</u>
<u n="872" who="S0152">work time</u>
<u n="873" who="S0013">anyway hopefully that'll look nice when it's done up a bit</u>
<u n="874" who="S0012">well it will when it's done won't it?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0013">yeah taken longer than we thought though <pause dur="short"/> I only do it till ten o'clock in the morning and that's it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0152">yeah er</u>
<u n="877" who="S0013">then I'm out in the garden</u>
<u n="878" who="S0012">well she's up at five</u>
<u n="879" who="S0152">thirty minutes <trunc>bef</trunc> I'm up thirty minutes before you</u>
<u n="880" who="S0012">every day?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0152">four thirty</u>
<u n="882" who="S0012">are you? yeah</u>
<u n="883" who="S0013">it's always four thirty?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0152">four thirty</u>
<u n="885" who="S0013">do you know why? just a natural thing</u>
<u n="886" who="S0152">I had some strange dreams last night</u>
<u n="887" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="888" who="S0152">real strange dreams <pause dur="short"/> I dreamt about a piece of metal that needed to be welded that I had to put in my that I had to move in my car to somewhere</u>
<u n="889" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0152">I dreamt somebody phoned me up and says erm <pause dur="short"/> I think I made a mistake I really should still be going out with you dreamt that</u>
<u n="891" who="S0012">oh dear</u>
<u n="892" who="S0152">er</u>
<u n="893" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="894" who="S0152">I dreamt about the house</u>
<u n="895" who="S0013">well it is a bit worrying that is innit? the house</u>
<u n="896" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I dreamt about I dreamt about school I dreamt about things that I hadn't done or thought I'd done or hadn't</u>
<u n="897" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0152">but yeah I'm going to sleep easy I'm going to sleep when I get into bed in the sense that I went to bed at ten o'clock last night and I didn't have any distractions cos I didn't have my Ipad I didn't have anything and I turned the light out and then I fell asleep but then I woke up at half past four so I fell asleep round about eleven o'clock quarter past eleven then woke up at half past four</u>
<u n="899" who="S0013">ah <pause dur="short"/> don't get much sleep at all yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0012">well Maggie Thatcher only got sort of four-hours' sleep and she worked all day and all night so</u>
<u n="901" who="S0152">and then I just and then you then you lie there and you think</u>
<u n="902" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="903" who="S0012">yeah you mustn't lay there thinking you got to get up and do things you mustn't lay there thinking soon as you wake up out of bed now then never mind about</u>
<u n="904" who="S0152">but I don't want to get out of bed and I don't want to get out of bed but I know I have to and then I wake up and I'm quite nervous</u>
<u n="905" who="S0012">nervous? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="906" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0152">mm I know that sounds yeah you know that nervy feeling you have</u>
<u n="908" who="S0012">I know what you mean</u>
<u n="909" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="910" who="S0152">like apprehension or something like that so yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="911" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="912" who="S0012">there's only one cure for it that's the sale of your house to go through</u>
<u n="913" who="S0152">the the the well there's two in there's two really <trunc>three</trunc> or three there is sell the house <pause dur="short"/> do something I really do enjoy doing again cos I'm not enjoying what I'm doing</u>
<u n="914" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0152">and be in a place that I want to be no I I I'd you know I'm not gonna I'm not gonna get to Yorkshire I don't think or the Lakes or anything like that but I need to be able to get there on a regular basis</u>
<u n="917" who="S0012">yeah when you want to go</u>
<u n="918" who="S0152">when when I want to go you know?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="920" who="S0152">you know and it's got to be done in a way that is you know if I can you know if I could find a little spot or something a small caravan park or something like that maybe you know like a</u>
<u n="921" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0152">with not loads of caravans on maybe and get so you can go up like six for a few weeks if I I've got a small house I haven't got to worry about that have I?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="925" who="S0152">then just stay up there</u>
<u n="926" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="927" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="928" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can come and stay could be fun but I don't know I but the house is the the thing</u>
<u n="929" who="S0012">that's the big the big hurdle at the moment innit?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah it is yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0152">and I know I and I know I haven't let the girls down but I do feel I've let the girls down</u>
<u n="932" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0013">no you <trunc>hav</trunc> you haven't you're you're brilliant with them so</u>
<u n="934" who="S0012">yeah but what he mean he hasn't been able to do what he wanted to do with them with them like go places and</u>
<u n="935" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no I must admit that was one thing I regretted we didn't have a holiday really</u>
<u n="936" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no we didn't twenty-three years we went without a holiday</u>
<u n="937" who="S0013">cos of the goats and that</u>
<u n="938" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0013">I took them away for a few days that was it but and they didn't have if they went with the Guides and that Brownies and Guides</u>
<u n="940" who="S0012">yeah they went with the Brownies and Guides</u>
<u n="941" who="S0013">and and the school trips</u>
<u n="942" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="943" who="S0013">they'd have <trunc>be</trunc> really missed out</u>
<u n="944" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0013">but they did get they did get</u>
<u n="946" who="S0012" trans="overlap">they went to ballet too</u>
<u n="947" who="S0013">I'm talking about <trunc>holi</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> like holiday things</u>
<u n="948" who="S0152">experiences</u>
<u n="949" who="S0013">we did have the exchanges and things like that didn't we?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to the Guide trip she went and we went to meet her up the school didn't we?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="952" who="S0012">not Guides cubs</u>
<u n="953" who="S0013">it was Brownies that was</u>
<u n="954" who="S0012">Brownies cubs</u>
<u n="955" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0012">and er</u>
<u n="957" who="S0013">we so missed her</u>
<u n="958" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we so missed her for the whole week</u>
<u n="959" who="S0013">we we did her room all nice cos she was only little then</u>
<u n="960" who="S0012">she come got off the bus and ignored us</u>
<u n="961" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="962" who="S0012">where did you have a lovely <trunc>ti</trunc>? yeah</u>
<u n="963" who="S0013">you know you you always expect that don't you?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0012">you always expect that hello and big cuddles and what have you no nothing like that or</u>
<u n="966" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that was that was a disappointment that was</u>
<u n="967" who="S0012">she must have had a row on the bus with someone I don't know</u>
<u n="968" who="S0013">yeah she said something about she had to sit next to someone she didn't like or something though ah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0012">so she come home in a bad mood</u>
<u n="970" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="971" who="S0012">not out fault was it?</u>
<u n="972" who="S0013">we'd been looking forward to it all week <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="973" who="S0152">no you do you do miss them you know?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0013">ha yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0152">but I you know I I just feel that</u>
<u n="976" who="S0012">well you haven't let them down you</u>
<u n="977" who="S0013">no you haven't</u>
<u n="978" who="S0012">you done all you can for them</u>
<u n="979" who="S0013">you know they don't think that don't you?</u>
<u n="980" who="S0152">yeah I know that but there's still</u>
<u n="981" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yes you do</u>
<u n="982" who="S0152">but it's still</u>
<u n="983" who="S0012">well I think the only thing you're thinking about is you said you were going to take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to Australia when she was fourteen</u>
<u n="984" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah couldn't do it</u>
<u n="985" who="S0012">well course you couldn't you had too many other things going on I mean this is</u>
<u n="986" who="S0013">she she doesn't even remember that does she?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="988" who="S0013">oh she does? oh</u>
<u n="989" who="S0012">does she? what do you tell her?</u>
<u n="990" who="S0152">no she says it</u>
<u n="991" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0152">you know it's like she's learning to drive all her friends have got cars</u>
<u n="993" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but how much is it costing their parents nobody think of that the parents probably got in debt for them</u>
<u n="994" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0152">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has the money to be able to buy a car if she wants to be able to buy a car</u>
<u n="997" who="S0012">oh well that's okay then</u>
<u n="998" who="S0152">she has she has the money to be able to buy a car</u>
<u n="999" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0012">but kids in this day and age I mean a few a few years ago when our kids were going to school they were jealous of everybody's trainers cos the trainers all come out didn't they?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0012">and everybody wanted them and they were getting mugged not our kids but kids were getting mugged for their trainers and then that was phones they get their phones nicked</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0152">that's so bad that's not so bad as it used to be though</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0012">no not as bad as it used to be</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no thank goodness yeah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0012">cos everyone has got one now haven't they?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0013">everybody's got one everybody's either got one type or another type</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0013">so</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0012">and once they got everything on their phone <trunc>th</trunc>that's their god like yours is</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0152">yeah so all my pictures</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0013">oh yeah cool</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0012">fifteen thousand pictures he's got on there</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0152">and they're quite</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0013">I know amazing</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0152">so so there you go right ooh</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0012">okay then I ache like mad</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0152">you've missed four goals now</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0012">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
