<text id="S5AA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:07:14</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0208</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>France</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Sex, boys, uni, work, new house</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting about general stuff</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0208">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0202">how was your shower?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0208">it was good</u>
<u n="3" who="S0202">were you <pause dur="short"/> doing stuff?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0208">no <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="5" who="S0202" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="6" who="S0208">just literally washing</u>
<u n="7" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it just <pause dur="short"/> it just took you a while that's all</u>
<u n="8" who="S0208">I shaved everywhere</u>
<u n="9" who="S0202">ah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0208">felt so good</u>
<u n="11" who="S0202">I don't like shaving down there cos I just get a rash and it's horrible</u>
<u n="12" who="S0208">really? oh wow I did a really good job of that <pause dur="short"/> I can still see all the little <pause dur="short"/> well they're only little blonde hairs but they</u>
<u n="13" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I can't see anything</u>
<u n="14" who="S0208" trans="overlap">never come off easily <pause dur="short"/> have to literally scrape them off <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0202"><vocal desc="sigh"/> it's a beautiful day</u>
<u n="16" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0202">it's gonna be a thunderstorm on Monday <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know what time that's gonna be I'll have a look and see if it'll tell me at <pause dur="long"/> oh it's gonna be cloudy tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="18" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0208">erm he's always erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that erm <pause dur="short"/> the people who like predict the weather are having a hard time this year because the weather's been changing so quick and it's been so unpredictable that they've had a really hard time actually</u>
<u n="20" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0208" trans="overlap">apart from like the past few weeks because it's been back to how it's <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="22" who="S0202">yeah well</u>
<u n="23" who="S0208" trans="overlap">usually like if you say there's gonna be a storm then it is but lately they've been like it's gonna be really really nice and then it's just like been raining and freak hailstorms and stuff</u>
<u n="24" who="S0202">well erm <pause dur="short"/> it says from three o'clock today it's gonna be cloudy</u>
<u n="25" who="S0208">I don't believe that</u>
<u n="26" who="S0202">so</u>
<u n="27" who="S0208">I genuinely don't believe that</u>
<u n="28" who="S0202">it says <pause dur="short"/> er it says <pause dur="short"/> let me just have a look <pause dur="short"/> montreal erm at three o'clock is gonna be clouds</u>
<u n="29" who="S0208">it is Montreal France right and not Canada?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0202">yeah Montreal <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="31" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0202">chance of rain two percent</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="33" who="S0208">Mont Blanc the tallest mountain in France</u>
<u n="34" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0208">so there's been <pause dur="short"/> so like literally <trunc>wi</trunc> a ridiculous amount less of accidents erm <pause dur="short"/> this year <pause dur="short"/> people climbing it but it's because there's been like half the amount of people that usually climb it cos of how bad the weather is like</u>
<u n="36" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0208" trans="overlap">they don't trust it</u>
<u n="38" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0208">so that's why there's been loads less accidents because there's loads less people climbing it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0202">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it says <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>toda</trunc> right from three o'clock today it's gonna be cloudy <pause dur="short"/> and it's gonna be cloudy tomorrow but on Saturday Sunday Monday Tuesday it's gonna be thirty and above</u>
<u n="41" who="S0208">shit</u>
<u n="42" who="S0202">so there's not gonna be a storm on Monday anymore <pause dur="short"/> so if it is cloudy today and tomorrow it don't really matter like <pause dur="short"/> maybe we could do that thing tomorrow you know? if it is going to be cloudy <pause dur="short"/> but still warm we may as well do it tomorrow</u>
<u n="43" who="S0208">yeah why not?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0202" trans="overlap">cos then it's not gonna be as hot</u>
<u n="45" who="S0208">we need to <pause dur="short"/> have a look at I'll talk to dad later when he gets back about when he wants to do cleaning and stuff like that</u>
<u n="46" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0208">then we can plan around that as well</u>
<u n="48" who="S0202">yeah I know he wants us to do Saturday morning <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> I think he said on Saturday we might have to do it</u>
<u n="49" who="S0208">right well as long as if someone like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if he doesn't mind coming and picking me up I can come back and help you guys when I've finished</u>
<u n="50" who="S0202">uhu well I can do that it won't take long to do it</u>
<u n="51" who="S0208">yes it will <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s is massive</u>
<u n="52" who="S0202">oh is it?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0208">yeah it's giant it's a proper house</u>
<u n="54" who="S0202">oh right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0208">so</u>
<u n="56" who="S0202">what do you have to do like like clean the whole thing like?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0208">yeah basically and I think it's <pause dur="short"/> I think my mum said there was something about someone coming in for a long-term stay so</u>
<u n="58" who="S0202">does your mum get paid for that then?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0208">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0202">how much does she get paid?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0208">erm I don't I don't know if it's like in <anon type="place"/> but usually when she's cleaning she charges fifteen euros an hour</u>
<u n="62" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="63" who="S0208">so</u>
<u n="64" who="S0202">so we'd get that?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0208">uhu <pause dur="short"/> and like because she's always like <pause dur="short"/> when I don't want the money or anything if I just go to help she's like yeah but <pause dur="short"/> I'm charging per hour anyway</u>
<u n="66" who="S0202">right is it per person or just per hour?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0208">erm <pause dur="short"/> per person per hour if it's gonna be three of us cleaning there it won't be fifteen split by three it will be fifteen per person per hour</u>
<u n="68" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="69" who="S0208">so it's everyone taking time out of their <pause dur="short"/> lives to do the cleaning</u>
<u n="70" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0208">anyway so he'll <pause dur="short"/> wait for me to finish work at two and then</u>
<u n="72" who="S0202">yeah okay</u>
<u n="73" who="S0208" trans="overlap">we'll go together and then just do it through the afternoon</u>
<u n="74" who="S0202"><vocal desc="cough"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so I'll write Saturday off then for that thing <pause dur="short"/> cos it's gonna take us a while to do that house ain't it?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I think so</u>
<u n="76" who="S0202">so</u>
<u n="77" who="S0208" trans="overlap">well I've I'm gonna be gone from ten till two anyway so</u>
<u n="78" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah we'll write it off then we'll probably go we'll go on a different day</u>
<u n="79" who="S0208">well today is Thursday isn't it?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0202">uhu</u>
<u n="81" who="S0208">we can go tomorrow</u>
<u n="82" who="S0202">yeah we can</u>
<u n="83" who="S0208">tomorrow's Friday</u>
<u n="84" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0208">tomorrow's gonna be cloudy it'll be better to do the gardening that my dad wants done tomorrow</u>
<u n="86" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0208">and we can always do <unclear>aqua branching</unclear> next week some time</u>
<u n="88" who="S0202">okay well I'll leave next week on Wednesday</u>
<u n="89" who="S0208">okay</u>
<u n="90" who="S0202">what date is it today? like <pause dur="short"/> does anyone know the date? er</u>
<u n="91" who="S0208">the fourth I think</u>
<u n="92" who="S0202">I'll leave on the tenth <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but I don't leave until like late afternoon</u>
<u n="93" who="S0208">are you wearing a bra?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="95" who="S0208">shit <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that cleavage though</u>
<u n="96" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> let me just have a look what time I'm flying <pause dur="short"/> fifteen thirty-five I'm flying <pause dur="short"/> and I'll need to be there an hour before because I've got erm hand luggage that's it flight sixteen forty er get there at sixteen forty</u>
<u n="97" who="S0208">that's easy enough</u>
<u n="98" who="S0202">but erm <pause dur="long"/> well if it is cloudy this afternoon when we get back cos it says it's gonna be cloudy from three <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be a bit of sun and a bit of cloud if it is really cloudy do you just want to do the gardening this afternoon?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0202">and then tomorrow we can do that aqua thingy</u>
<u n="101" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0202">or whatever it is</u>
<u n="103" who="S0208" trans="overlap">er <foreign lang="fre"/> be training <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow afternoon</u>
<u n="104" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0208">so</u>
<u n="106" who="S0202" trans="overlap">we've got a bit of morning</u>
<u n="107" who="S0208">I was just saying like if he's up for it</u>
<u n="108" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0208">if it's not gonna make him too tired or anything we can <pause dur="short"/> we'll figure something out</u>
<u n="110" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0208">too dry</u>
<u n="112" who="S0202">have you moisturising?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0208">yeah I've just moisturised all of my legs loads and look they're still really scaly</u>
<u n="114" who="S0202">you're not scaly at all <pause dur="short"/> it's soft <pause dur="long"/> you should try and do it every day though it keeps your skin looking young</u>
<u n="115" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0202">I'm gonna <trunc>se</trunc> I'm gonna send my phone back on when I get back I'm just gonna <pause dur="short"/> say to them look I didn't take it on holiday with me so it's been sat <pause dur="short"/> there's something wrong with the speaker the home button isn't like right and there's no way that I could have done that <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just gonna say look I want it replacing because the battery isn't working the home button's wonky it's not even on straight and like the speakers aren't working</u>
<u n="117" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0202">and I haven't done that <pause dur="short"/> gonna just say I haven't used it at all</u>
<u n="119" who="S0208">yeah do that</u>
<u n="120" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and I'll wipe the phone so it looks like I haven't used it <pause dur="long"/> and I'm just gonna fight it out and say look I've had this phone about for a week</u>
<u n="121" who="S0208">cos it's</u>
<u n="122" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and then I went on holiday</u>
<u n="123" who="S0208">it's true as soon as you got it the battery wasn't working so that's not</u>
<u n="124" who="S0202" trans="overlap">well I rang them straight away so they can't even say that it <pause dur="short"/> they</u>
<u n="125" who="S0208" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="126" who="S0202">they can't say anything <pause dur="short"/> and say look I didn't take I didn't end up taking it on holiday with me I've left it at home so it's been sat in a box at home the whole time <pause dur="short"/> I've not even touched it <pause dur="long"/> I'll just say it must have been damaged in transit</u>
<u n="127" who="S0208">yeah it'll work <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0202">cos I'm not paying fucking a hundred pounds for them to fix my speaker <pause dur="short"/> or the battery <pause dur="short"/> it's just such a rip-off cos it's Apple <pause dur="short"/> it's such a rip off</u>
<u n="129" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0202">it pisses me off so much <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0208">right <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go <pause dur="short"/> get my shit together</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
