<text id="S5B4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:09:32</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Shopping, public relations, music</topics>
		<activity>Chat about the day we’ve had.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0144">okay so it was good there was some stuff left</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">mm I was so late <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was so late I got there literally when there was nobody left there apart from the the <unclear>health</unclear> person a couple of people floating about and they all said ah <unclear/> most of the stuff is gone we don't and I said we here's here's my stuff where shall I put it? and they said well we're gonna get rid of everything that's here now so there's no need for you to leave your stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what are they gonna do with it? chuck it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well the <unclear>IEs</unclear> are getting rid of it so <unclear/> if erm the the nannies and the cleaners</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024">I'm sure it will go to a good home they're erm they'll find some some place for it do you wanna have a look?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> right so you've got this <unclear/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0024">mm yeah was it really really grubby?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0024">I just saw it and I wanted a <unclear>car mat</unclear> I just remember playing on mats and we I never had a car mat I just had to use the lines on the carpet with cars and make my own roads so I just thought</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh I used to do that with pens</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024">mm like that's not for us that's for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0144">okay play mat and</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024">yeah it's nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">yeah that's for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> that's kind of a well</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144">I reckon <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got everything already</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024">yeah well I'm sure he has but you know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> chose that and she loves it I know it looks a bit weird</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144">what is it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024">mm who knows? but she liked the little face her face lit lit up with joy when she saw that</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0024">but she can't hold it yet cos it's a bit fat the ribbon needs to be taken off that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144">don't like <unclear/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0024">don't like it don't don't keep it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144">yeah his legs will come off look its got loads of <unclear/> in there</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024">okay get rid of it throw it away <pause dur="long"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><unclear/> two thousand and eight</u>
<u n="28" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> dropped that in she she told me she said oh you've got my teddy bear</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's a weird one as well</u>
<u n="32" who="S0024">it's a kind of panda</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144">a panda with a <unclear/> on its head <pause dur="short"/> er an empty box? ah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">oh they're for later in life I thought they were quite good</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144">that's quite good</u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0024">keep reminding me of what is it Chinese as well or is it just English or?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">no it's just English</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024">English what are they? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've forgotten</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">erm cabinet bottles it's like little tasks</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0144">and on the back is the answer</u>
<u n="44" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah I like those</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">flash cards</u>
<u n="46" who="S0024">maybe when she's five but you know</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144">there's another panda this house is gonna be full of pandas</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024">yeah they're cute I thought I'd hang that up somewhere</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's that? a <unclear/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0024">I don't know when they said they were throwing everything away I just grabbed all of them really</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144" trans="overlap">Shanghai Airlines</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> come on are you gonna have your dinner sweetheart?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144">oh it's not a <unclear/> it's a plane it looks like a <unclear>whale</unclear></u>
<u n="54" who="S0024">oh I thought it was a whale</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144"><unclear/> it's supposed to be a whale actually</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024">a whale plane</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144">I don't know would you advertise your airlines as a whale?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024">mm no</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0024">heavy</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144"><unclear/> Scooby Dooby Doo</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144">oh Shaggy</u>
<u n="66" who="S0024">Scooby Doo book that's cool isn't it?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">yeah yeah that was good</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024">they said all the books just went so fast</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">there wasn't much left for the books but if that's the case then people would like to get rid of their books quite regularly</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144">Bob the Builder</u>
<u n="72" who="S0024">are you wet?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144">ah you got some DVDs</u>
<u n="74" who="S0024">why is she wet on the outside but not on the inside</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144">probably because I was holding her all the way back home safely</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">oh oh okay</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144" trans="overlap">just just <unclear/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">erm I spy</u>
<u n="80" who="S0024">yeah there's there was three there's three by surprise come on eat your dinner eat your dinner stop listening</u>
<u n="81" who="S0144">oh its got the same as</u>
<u n="82" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well you can keep <unclear>losing</unclear> that one</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144">it's not the same I spy books</u>
<u n="84" who="S0024" trans="overlap">er are they okay?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144">that I used to have</u>
<u n="86" who="S0024">oh no they're not the adventure books they're for</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144">you have to see it in the picture</u>
<u n="88" who="S0024">I don't know what they are I just thought I'd get them what is it?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144">yeah each page has got a picture and things you've got to find in the picture</u>
<u n="90" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144">you've got to find <unclear/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0024">what's that for when she's four? I've bought stuff that when she's four</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144">that's right</u>
<u n="94" who="S0024">she's only six months old <vocal desc="laugh"/> they must have been thinking what a oh earth are you picking up?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thomas the Tank Engine</u>
<u n="96" who="S0024">mm mm that train has a really weird name</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144"><unclear/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0024">I don't know I've never heard of a train in Thomas the Tank Engine with a with a really weird name like that</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">like a Welsh name</u>
<u n="100" who="S0024">that I just picked up at the end cos they were chucking it so I just thought well I'll just have it that I like <pause dur="short"/> like it?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> loves it show can you show me? I didn't really I just well I just thought I could puts some mats on the floor and then I was just gonna put that on the floor</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0024">so</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0024">we haven't really got another mat for</u>
<u n="107" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that's something for her to look at isn't it?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what's that?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0024">oh I just picked it up at the end I thought I'd watch it tonight some romantic comedy I'll watch it when you're out one day</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0024">now we picked up the pig she likes the pig and then somebody said to us oh do you want to take this bear as well? look I hate that bear I don't I don't want that bear</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so we're <unclear/> with the other bear</u>
<u n="114" who="S0024">oh it looks nice though</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144">is that it? is that all <unclear/> underneath?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0024">is that it? no that's all that we all that I got I just I just got the leftovers</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144">oh that's alright <unclear/> I thought you <unclear>might</unclear></u>
<u n="118" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144">that's <unclear/> underneath</u>
<u n="120" who="S0024">nothing</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144">ah ah that's alright</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024">yeah it's alright</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">there's a few good bits there</u>
<u n="124" who="S0024">bet I could have got probably some really cool stuff somebody had erm booked up some stuff you could see it all erm well one of them was a baby bath and stuff but they had other bits and pieces mm mm oh never mind never mind what are you up to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I thought you were gonna go to sleep?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144">well she slept how long did it take to walk back? fifteen minutes?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">she has to sleep the whole way</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024">so it's a fifteen minute nap then alright fair enough that's okay that's fine isn't it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144">what do you want to drink?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024">erm I would love a <pause dur="short"/> camomile tea</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0024">I'm gonna start drinking camomile tea a bit earlier in the day</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144">mm how do you spell camomile?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">I don't know well no just as it's as it's well</u>
<u n="135" who="S0144">I was just putting myself in the transcribers position <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wonder how many Ms its got <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah right well that was a task and a half are we gonna go to IKEA today?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144">well we can do it today or tomorrow</u>
<u n="138" who="S0024">well I thought we we could always have dinner there couldn't we?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0024">I mean I'd like to try it I've forgotten what erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said there's a really nice dish they've loved it every time there'd be smoked salmon salad or something like that or I don't know what it was yeah people really like the food there that's what yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144">we'd have to take her pram</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024">yeah yeah take the pram well yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144">hm?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144">well it's too late to walk around carrying her</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024">yeah yeah agreed okay take the pram one person can have the trolley one person can have the pram yeah that'll work out fine and then</u>
<u n="147" who="S0144">they they must have <unclear/> about it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0024">yeah they do erm right at the end by the plants</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144">at the beginning just near where they've got that weird escalator</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024">oh yeah yeah there must be one there's gotta be unless you have to walk all the way through the front and go up those but then that might be good because we'll be at the plants to start</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144">yeah no it's IKEA <unclear/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144"><unclear/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">so I was thinking if we can get to the plants and then erm text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and say will a plant this big fit in your van will five plants this big fit in your van? <pause dur="long"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0024">why not? and if he says oh the van's in <anon type="place"/> mm well okay try again another day <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> one day we'll get them one day but I think yeah over there with that new cabinet they've put in a nice hanging plant there would look really nice hanging over the side</u>
<u n="159" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0024">and then I've got to get into my routine of looking after the plants again <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0144">what else did we need to get before we go?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s stuff <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thing to go round the cot and some <trunc>cu</trunc> she's ready for cups now she needs a cup</u>
<u n="163" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah she's nearly there isn't she?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0024">she needs a cup for the little bit of water that she's been drinking</u>
<u n="165" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024">so she can practice and yeah and then she then she'll start on water soon as a drink like when it's hot and stuff I don't really know I guess you'll just tell when when she gets to that stage you'll just start realising what she needs she doesn't need a lot of drink until she starts eating because she needs to drink milk from the <unclear/> doesn't she? not crisps not crisps yeah so she doesn't really need a lot of water unless it's very hot her eyes are so erm red <pause dur="short"/> it's like she's got massive bags under them she's been rubbing them doesn't look very good does it? <unclear/> got anything that you can put on eyes</u>
<u n="167" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024"><unclear/> your eyes <pause dur="short"/> yeah so there's an idea that's an idea that's that's dinner sorted too</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0024">that's dinner lovely yeah yeah that'd be nice so that means go soon <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0144">that means go very soon doesn't it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0144">she needs to be back here at half six</u>
<u n="174" who="S0024" trans="overlap">be back at seven yeah about half six seven yeah do you want to go down there? here we go <pause dur="short"/> ah I thought I got more stuff than that but I quite like the blanket I think that that erm if we some more padded floor things and then we can put that blanket on top it would be like a nice rug</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0024">I thought yep <pause dur="short"/> we're getting there we're getting slowly aren't we?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">slowly it's taking a <unclear>while</unclear></u>
<u n="178" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well we <unclear>have</unclear> we've been here over a year and we're still not mm mm mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144">well I think once we've got these big plants</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144">think its come out so</u>
<u n="182" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and the photos that I've been</u>
<u n="183" who="S0144" trans="overlap">saying that for half a year</u>
<u n="184" who="S0024">big plants and photos and then sorted and then it's just little bits like now that you've taken the little bits off that table onto that cabinet</u>
<u n="185" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">it looks really bare and boring you can just see all the wires at the back of the TV</u>
<u n="187" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0024">so</u>
<u n="189" who="S0144">well I was thinking about moving that music stuff into the other room now</u>
<u n="190" who="S0024">what? no we need music here</u>
<u n="191" who="S0144">but we never use it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0024">only because the computer's disappeared where's it gone? I thought</u>
<u n="193" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well cos I've been using it cos I've been using the second sound card well it's useful having two computers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0024">see I thought that you were gonna get your new computer the old computer was gonna stay here for music?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0144">well that's what I thought at first but cos the internet's not working from down <unclear/> I don't know</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="196" who="S0024">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> loved listening to music today</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144">oh right</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024">erm <pause dur="short"/> it was like she missed it you should have seen her eyes so was she just loved it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024">cos when we were travelling she we didn't listen to much music and since we've been back the computer's been in the other room</u>
<u n="201" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I've been playing guitar and stuff to her</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah there's that so loves that but just generally on in the house</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024">I think it I mean when I put the music on she was quiet and happy and yeah she really enjoyed it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">so <pause dur="short"/> I mean I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I like having the option to play music in here whereas it's gonna all be in the other bit is there any kind of programme we can put on the hard drive so that we can make sure I mean all the music is on hard drive yeah? is it all up to date?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">erm no</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">it's just a shame that when you click on the TV you have to just play by the artist</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144">but you can't do that cos there's thousands of folders</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144">well it has to be the jukebox <unclear>it means</unclear> plugging in the computer and</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024"><unclear/> do you really need that computer?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144">I'm using it a lot like in conjunction with the other one</u>
<u n="214" who="S0024">yeah well I'll get jukebox on mine download the music onto mine</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144">er how much space have you got on yours?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">hm don't know</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144">is that eh is it on now?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024">how much space do I need?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144">erm I don't know I guess my music comes to</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024">but then it's annoying because you can't listen to music and do stuff on the computer at the same time <pause dur="short"/> we need another computer</u>
<u n="221" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0144">you'll probably need about fifty-sixty gigs</u>
<u n="223" who="S0024">fifty-sixty gigs</u>
<u n="224" who="S0144">it's a guess</u>
<u n="225" who="S0024">how do I find out?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0144">just go to my computer</u>
<u n="227" who="S0024">well I've got on my local disc on my D drive</u>
<u n="228" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0024">I've got ninety-seven gigabytes free</u>
<u n="230" who="S0144">well you could put it on there but it's gonna take up most of that</u>
<u n="231" who="S0024">I've got look how many I've got loads of drives I've got this on the C drive is the only drive that I've used yeah and okay so that's going down I need to move some stuff across I've got an E drive which has a hundred and twenty-six gigabytes</u>
<u n="232" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0024">an F drive which has a hundred and fifty gigabytes and a D drive ninety-seven point six gigabytes</u>
<u n="234" who="S0144">that's good</u>
<u n="235" who="S0024">hm?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0144">good the C drive you just wanna keep for Windows really how big's your C drive?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0024">mm it's sixty-nine gigs</u>
<u n="238" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0024">but erm I've used quite like about forty</u>
<u n="240" who="S0144">yeah I'd I'd keep that just for like Windows and updates and things like that</u>
<u n="241" who="S0024">you know why? cos I've just been saving everything to the desktop</u>
<u n="242" who="S0144">yeah like photos and music but erm something else</u>
<u n="243" who="S0024">okay and all of my <trunc>doc</trunc> okay yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0144">well documents are tiny but well the <anon type="place"/> videos and stuff like that I'll put on a different one</u>
<u n="245" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay so I need to oh god that's more shorty</u>
<u n="246" who="S0144">nah it's only moving some folders across</u>
<u n="247" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0024">so I have to make</u>
<u n="250" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm so you've got loads of space on there</u>
<u n="251" who="S0024">so I can make a D drive for erm my work my photos or something and an F drive for music hm? <pause dur="short"/> download jukebox</u>
<u n="252" who="S0144">course <unclear/> F drive</u>
<u n="253" who="S0024">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> oh god that starts this week</u>
<u n="254" who="S0144">what?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0024">my <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I think they start this week don't they?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0144">for what?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0024">erm I've forgotten what I signed up to now <vocal desc="laugh"/> shall I tell you? I've signed up to a couple <pause dur="long"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I think I've got some sort of linguistic one or maybe a teaching writing one I don't know why I did that I need to make it to sign me up I'm sick of passwords you know I can't remember all my passwords</u>
<u n="258" who="S0144">yeah I've just I've clicked that box now just remembered my password</u>
<u n="259" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0024">so many times</u>
<u n="262" who="S0144">just got to the stage you know where you've just got too many yeah if someone stole my computer they could have a field day</u>
<u n="263" who="S0024">but they can't get in it without the er first password <unclear/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0144">mm yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0024">so you alright then? oh whoops <pause dur="long"/> I don't really know oh yeah I got the right password second time <pause dur="short"/> you're not it says I'm not enrolled but I am I've enrolled in two courses and they've emailed me about them it says you are not enrolled in any courses upcoming oh upcoming oh okay it's not not starts at tomorrow digital storytelling starts tomorrow</u>
<u n="266" who="S0144">okay what's that about?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0024">erm powerful tools for teaching and learning digital storytelling er course info and next week I've got write rhetorical composing and then I I've got an English composition one cos I wanted to do some writing courses</u>
<u n="268" who="S0144">rhetorical composition?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0144">what's that?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0024">hold on I've got the digital storytelling up</u>
<u n="272" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh sorry</u>
<u n="273" who="S0024">I'll tell you about this one erm <pause dur="short"/> it says for use in a K twelve classroom mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0024">just with still images audio <trunc>narra</trunc>narration and music and text it's for using in a classroom</u>
<u n="276" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0024">but I thought I might get some tips on using some digital stuff anyway</u>
<u n="278" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0024">so so I'll have a look at that <unclear/> yeah it's not really for university <trunc>cours</trunc> teaching university courses erm this one needs rhetorical composing erm <pause dur="short"/> reading research research <unclear>comprising</unclear> activities erm <pause dur="short"/> join us to become more effective writers and better citizens <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0024">erm it's a course where writers exchange words ideas talents and support introduced to rhetorical concepts ideas and techniques to inform and persuade audiences that will help you become a more effective consumer and producer or written visual and <trunc>mul</trunc>multimodal texts</u>
<u n="282" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0024">I think that sounds quite good</u>
<u n="284" who="S0144">it sounds a little bit vague</u>
<u n="285" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="286" who="S0024">don't really say anything else really oh the syllabus is thinking rhetorically oh that's just gonna be responding rhetorically where you do a writing exchange in a peer review</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0024">arguing rhetorically seeing rhetorically <pause dur="short"/> researching rhetorically and then <unclear>reminding</unclear> rhetorically mm <pause dur="short"/> doesn't really sound like I don't know</u>
<u n="289" who="S0144">I don't really understand the focus of that</u>
<u n="290" who="S0024">I don't know but anyway I'll have a look at that</u>
<u n="291" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0024">I've got another one erm starting oh the English composition one <anon type="place"/> university oh that's just for that's for university writing I thought what I'd do is take the course to get a few ideas for my teaching and just like have a look at the materials that they're using for their workshops basically <pause dur="long"/> mm they should be good shouldn't they?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm really getting into my well started that book last night brilliant <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0024">which one?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">the R book</u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">oh yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0144">really good</u>
<u n="298" who="S0024">what's it about?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">well it's like I said it starts with Edward Bernays <pause dur="short"/> erm he set up a meeting with him and he was like ninety-nine or something what it?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024">who?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0144">Edward Bernays</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024">who set up a meeting</u>
<u n="303" who="S0144">this guy who wrote the book</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144">and basically <vocal desc="laugh"/> he said how Bernays <trunc>aft</trunc> it was only after he had done the meeting with him that he realised what a genius he was</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0144">because he basically had manipulated the whole meeting from even before he got there till things happening after the meeting he manipulated the whole thing just to him a lesson <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">what? how?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0144" trans="overlap">like he er <pause dur="short"/> like for example he said oh oh he was saying to him how how to become a er well the <trunc>tech</trunc>techniques of PR <event desc="sound of baby"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is she okay? she's getting a bit frantic</u>
<u n="310" who="S0024">you are you hungry? <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah go on</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144">erm yeah I can't remember what the name of what's the name of the book? the name of the book is erm <pause dur="short"/> the Social History of <unclear>Spin</unclear> oh that's it yeah he did a previous book called All Consuming Images and er in the in the interview Edward Bernays said okay so for example you know if you wanted to become successful if you wanted to become successful you would phone up I would phone up the council on I don't know what it's called council of images or council of advertising or something and say okay what we need to do is focus on the erm consumer images that's about the direction we should go this year erm we should set up at meeting at such and such a place and have a big like kind of workshop get the media involved I don't know he's obviously got a lot a lot more contacts and a lot more detail to that but it's basically what he said and then three months later <vocal desc="laugh"/> this guy gets a phone call for the the council that he mentioned in this interview</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144">just as an example of his power you know cos he was showing his power basically</u>
<u n="314" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144">and they said oh yeah we've we thought it was a good idea this year to a er a big forum on consumer images you know we've got such and such involved and it's exactly what Bernays used in just his like flippant kind of example in the interview <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">yeah so he must have just picked up the phone after the interview and set the balls in motion</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0144">it was just erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it it's just started off saying a few examples like you know the the incubator one in in <unclear/> you know that don't you?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0024">no what one?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0144">erm well you remember all these stories that come out before wars you know been trying to get justification in in their action into a war</u>
<u n="322" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0144">like they did with Syria recently with the chemical weapons</u>
<u n="324" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0144">same thing in Iraq they did a massive thing saying they got this fifteen-year-old girl to say that the erm Saddam Hussein's kind of private army had been going round hospitals and taking babies out of incubators</u>
<u n="326" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="327" who="S0144">leaving them on the cold concrete floors to to die</u>
<u n="328" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0144">you know and this testimony came from a fifteen-year-old girl who got up in front of a it was like a UN panel and you know and stated it erm which after the war was found out that this fifteen-year-old girl was the daughter of the Kuwaiti ambassador <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="331" who="S0144">basically on the payroll of the CIA and er you know fabricated the whole thing but the power's done right? I mean</u>
<u n="332" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0144">and as they're saying you know like now you can see it going on in Syria and <trunc>Ira</trunc> and Iran as well they've all these stories coming up all they're they're bullshit but people don't care about that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0144">cos it's just about shaping people's minds into justifying movement into a certain direction it's just so powerful</u>
<u n="336" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0144">like another one when remember that erm that in the last Gulf War <pause dur="short"/> when they pulled down Saddam Hussein's statue?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0144">that was a</u>
<u n="340" who="S0024">that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that was an image</u>
<u n="342" who="S0024" trans="overlap">major</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144">that needed to happen because it was a shifting point you know it was winning hearts and minds basically</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144">it was like yeah America has or whoever erm has got control we're the is the symbol of winning the war</u>
<u n="346" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144">of take or remove the statue and it had people in the streets like cheering and</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024">mm yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I mean like I read no I read erm <pause dur="short"/> an article one of the journalists that was there who was so disgusted by that he's he's basically become an independent journalist now</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0144">he said that all of the journalists were kind of shepherded into these hotels around that square and basically it was rent a mob you know who came in it was nothing it wasn't you know they were paid people to come in</u>
<u n="352" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that was the one yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0144">and pull down the statue it was all staged</u>
<u n="354" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144">but the way it was shown on the media for days</u>
<u n="356" who="S0024">oh it was on every day for</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024">weeks</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">and that was it was like yes we've won and for the opening <unclear/> that must have been shown in Iraq as well not just for us but for the Iraqi people seeing that</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144">they must have seen that as a a step as well that okay Saddam Hussein's lost <pause dur="short"/> and it's just the things like that it's just so powerful</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">oh yeah that's what the book is all about</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0024">not just images though?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144">no no talking about the history at the moment it's gonna go back to the first world was now I think talk about that because I mean the British were masters of propaganda in the First World War</u>
<u n="366" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144">erm and then you had people like Edward Bernays and <unclear/> Lippman come to prominence like in the twenties they started writing about it how how to control people's minds you know to control society and oh been sick</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024">can you pass me a tissue?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">erm and then the Second World War Joseph Goebbels kind of took their ideas</u>
<u n="370" who="S0024" trans="overlap">who?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144">the Nazi propaganda minister</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024">who?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">Joseph Goebbels</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024">Goebbels</u>
<u n="375" who="S0144">erm and he took like British ideas as well from the First World War <unclear/> a lot of good posters and things didn't they took all those ideas and basically made the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">oh no no no no no</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144">the most successful propaganda campaign in history really</u>
<u n="378" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0144">erm and then it's kind of moved on to er kind of consumer based mind control</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024">mm yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">er which was what Bernays was writing about cos he was the nephew of Freud</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah but it's just yeah it's quite crazy how it must have all</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it was all about the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> it was all about unconscious desires you know and tapping into that</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024">but still <unclear/> now</u>
<u n="385" who="S0144">yeah oh yeah it's still</u>
<u n="386" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but now you've got the internet and the TV where you can just go boom there it is</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144">yeah yeah well it's changing though because people are becoming slightly more savvy about it you know they can see through it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144">so they're constantly having to make it more sophisticated and even more hidden you know erm like remember that erm on GMTV or whatever it is called now remember I got so angry with that guy the doctor who was questioning immunisations with babies</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024">oh yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">and the way that he was took to pieces erm by that other guest they had on and they they did that repeatedly over two weeks on different channels and newspapers and</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144">it it was a systemated er systematic PR campaign basically I would have loved to have investigated that cos I'm sure that was funded by people like Glaxosmithkline</u>
<u n="394" who="S0024" trans="overlap">do you <unclear>think</unclear>?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0144">and Bayer yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024">well if you see it on loads of channels it's a bit suspect isn't it?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144">well look it's the arguments they set up cos they weren't</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah false arguments and</u>
<u n="399" who="S0144" trans="overlap">false arguments it</u>
<u n="400" who="S0024">change direction quite easily</u>
<u n="401" who="S0144">yeah I mean the argument they used very kind of emotive things like <pause dur="short"/> oh you're you're neglecting your child if you're not giving them immunisations</u>
<u n="402" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0144">that was basically the main kind of <unclear/> of the argument</u>
<u n="404" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and you want yeah and that erm what's the other argument? that you say that <trunc>ev</trunc> you know you know if nobody else has everybody else is inoculated yours doesn't need it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0024">and things like that</u>
<u n="407" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0024">and it's just wrong because for the whole community</u>
<u n="409" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0024">it's wrong</u>
<u n="411" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0024">that's the argument</u>
<u n="413" who="S0144">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="414" who="S0024">for the whole community it's wrong not just for your child your neglecting your child and neglecting the community</u>
<u n="415" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0024">you're putting everybody else in danger</u>
<u n="417" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0024">stuff like that</u>
<u n="419" who="S0144">and that's the spin they gave it</u>
<u n="420" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and yeah that's the spin of erm of them that their main argument was probably about the mercury within the injections and</u>
<u n="421" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah no that's not mentioned</u>
<u n="422" who="S0024">no?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0144">ever</u>
<u n="424" who="S0024">no it's a different argument</u>
<u n="425" who="S0144">and and it was very much it wasn't a group of scientists that were saying this it was one person</u>
<u n="426" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0144">one lunatic</u>
<u n="428" who="S0024">oh yeah yeah he got <trunc>out</trunc>outed didn't he?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0144">oh he had to leave the country</u>
<u n="430" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0144">he lives in America now</u>
<u n="432" who="S0024">does he?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0024">I thought he lived in Europe</u>
<u n="435" who="S0144">no he's got quite a successful TV thing I think in America or something</u>
<u n="436" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0144">erm but yeah you can't <vocal desc="laugh"/> you just have to pin it on one person erm but other people aren't gonna you know they're gonna be scared to to research the safety of vaccines because you're just gonna be ousted by the scientific community</u>
<u n="438" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0144">because you have to just pander towards the fucking corporate objectives</u>
<u n="440" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and that's just because yeah and it's not science anymore because you're not allowed to come up with a different hypothesis for something if <unclear>it doesn't</unclear> agree with</u>
<u n="441" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no you have to agree with the consensus</u>
<u n="442" who="S0024">or if you do people just twist the argument and just say something like that</u>
<u n="443" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0024">like they weren't even discussing the what's in the vaccines the vaccines fitting er erm contaminated with HIV or the vaccines getting contaminated with other diseases</u>
<u n="445" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0024">or the mercury content of the nothing like that</u>
<u n="447" who="S0144">no no no and all that</u>
<u n="448" who="S0024">nothing like that that's not the argument for them is it?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> no they'd never touch that</u>
<u n="450" who="S0024">so if you start saying something like that they just bounce it back to you and <trunc>ch</trunc>change the whole</u>
<u n="451" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0024">debate into <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="453" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and it's things like erm swine flu</u>
<u n="454" who="S0024">yeah that's the same as well</u>
<u n="455" who="S0144" trans="overlap">like chicken flu all these things these are all</u>
<u n="456" who="S0024" trans="overlap">chicken flu? bird flu</u>
<u n="457" who="S0144">bird flu whatever <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>the</trunc>these are all driven I'm sure by erm like people like Glaxo</u>
<u n="458" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0144">who pump millions into these PR campaigns stir up a load of fear</u>
<u n="460" who="S0024">oh yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0144">erm just look at the people who've died it's it's miniscule absolutely miniscule</u>
<u n="462" who="S0024">well that</u>
<u n="463" who="S0144">but look at the money they've made they've brought in injections to every single person on this planet now</u>
<u n="464" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah absolutely yep</u>
<u n="465" who="S0144">at birth or they you know flu vaccines and</u>
<u n="466" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they try and put yeah they do pregnant women don't they?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0144">it's you're talking multi-billion probably multi-trillion</u>
<u n="468" who="S0024">yep that the government's pay for and are in on mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="470" who="S0024">it's just weird circulation of money isn't it?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0144">who's got more power? these people making multi-trillion</u>
<u n="472" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0144">pound profits? or some guy with dusty shoulders and a cabinet of?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0024">dusty shoulders?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0144">I dunno</u>
<u n="476" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0024">dusty shoulders? why dusty shoulders? cos he isn't because his suit is so old what do you mean? er</u>
<u n="478" who="S0144" trans="overlap">you know it seemed like quite a good metaphor to use</u>
<u n="479" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0024">he's got dusty shoulders</u>
<u n="481" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0144">but I reckon they're they're gonna do another campaign now on the back of this er Ebola thing</u>
<u n="483" who="S0024">yeah Ebola they're all talking about it</u>
<u n="484" who="S0144">you know they've stirred up fear again in people</u>
<u n="485" who="S0024"><unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0144">people are worried about it we've had bloody emails at work about it</u>
<u n="487" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0144">no I mean this is the kind of thing these PR people do they <trunc>s</trunc> they get on the back of these or they they start it</u>
<u n="489" who="S0024">do you remember when you asked when they had the flu vaccine and you asked for er a poster?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0144">yeah I got like</u>
<u n="491" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they sent it to you?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0144">yeah I've got loads of them</u>
<u n="493" who="S0024">so can't you ask for a poster this time?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0144">what for the Ebola?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0024">Ebola posters</u>
<u n="496" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0024">yeah go on</u>
<u n="498" who="S0144" trans="overlap">the thing is now though you can just get them off erm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0024" trans="overlap">really interesting</u>
<u n="500" who="S0144">tut you can just get them off Google Images</u>
<u n="501" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0144">I mean I didn't get the real posters which is what I wanted but I just got he sent me the er JPEGs</u>
<u n="503" who="S0024">oh did he?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0144">yeah it was some doctor cos I said I was writing a PhD on on the posters of the flu vaccine</u>
<u n="505" who="S0024">I'd like to do that</u>
<u n="506" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0024">oh I'd like to do that</u>
<u n="508" who="S0144">erm yeah I dunno where they are <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0024">didn't you print em out? I thought came back with <trunc>pr</trunc> oh careful now erm with proper posters didn't you?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0144">no no</u>
<u n="511" who="S0024">you got the JPEGs? they'll be on the old hard drive won't they?</u>
<event desc="sound of baby crying"/>
<u n="512" who="S0144">no I think I don't think I've saved them I think they're just in the email</u>
<u n="513" who="S0024">are you alright? it's okay you can play with the box just don't eat it she loves this box</u>
<u n="514" who="S0144">mm yeah I reckon the back of this Ebola thing there erm there's gonna be another kind of swine virus type thing</u>
<u n="515" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah yeah there will be</u>
<u n="516" who="S0144">coming in people have already got that fear</u>
<u n="517" who="S0024"><trunc>di</trunc> no they're already trialling one in the UK cos I've</u>
<u n="518" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0024">tried it erm Ebola thing but</u>
<u n="520" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh I don't know if er I don't think it'd be Ebola it'd be something else</u>
<u n="521" who="S0024">oh careful now erm but they said what? didn't they say at the beginning that they didn't have a vaccine for it and it would take years to get one? and then suddenly they've got one</u>
<u n="522" who="S0144">oh really?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0024">yeah that they want to trial</u>
<u n="524" who="S0144">but people wouldn't take it not unless there was a perceived risk of actually contracting it</u>
<u n="525" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="526" who="S0144">and I don't think that perceived risk is high enough in the UK</u>
<u n="527" who="S0024">yeah we'll they're trying to make it high enough</u>
<u n="528" who="S0144">well I I dunno</u>
<u n="529" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0144">it'd need an outbreak in the UK first or they need at least kind of half a dozen people that'd be enough</u>
<u n="531" who="S0024">half a dozen people with an outbreak?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0144">well it would be for the media</u>
<u n="533" who="S0024">okay <pause dur="short"/> wow she loves this box</u>
<u n="534" who="S0144">I was reading about that it's not even that dangerous Ebola well it is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well it is it it is but erm if you're healthy</u>
<u n="536" who="S0144">but it if erm yeah it said if you get medical good medical attention you'll be fine if you don't have any treatment at all you've got a fifty-fifty chance I've always thought that if you got it in any kind of way shape or form you're screwed</u>
<u n="537" who="S0024">yeah I thought so too well you well look at the outbreak I mean it is</u>
<u n="538" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well it happened look where it happens it's in very poor areas where they've got no medical treatment</u>
<u n="539" who="S0024">I'm really thirsty do you think you can grab me some water or something?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0144">yeah yeah so this book I'm gonna get back into this shit again</u>
<u n="541" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="542" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> cos like</u>
<u n="543" who="S0024">it's really interesting reading like talking to you about it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I needed I needed some time off because it does make you <pause dur="short"/> do you know er I haven't watched TV for two years now really about news</u>
<u n="545" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="546" who="S0144">cos it <trunc>j</trunc> got too much</u>
<u n="547" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no no</u>
<u n="548" who="S0144">it sends you round the twist</u>
<u n="549" who="S0024">don't do that she's eating the cardboard</u>
<u n="550" who="S0144">I'm I'm ready again</u>
<u n="551" who="S0024">that's good cos I missed you teaching me <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I used to rely on you for my information <unclear/> with like stuff like that the propaganda stuff basically you're my you're my tutor in that <pause dur="short"/> oh ow ow <pause dur="short"/> what do you wanna do? er what do you want to go to er what time do you want to go to IKEA? soon?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0144">well we'd have to go what time does it close?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0024">we should go soon because she's gonna</u>
<u n="554" who="S0144">what time does it close?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0024">er it's open all evening</u>
<u n="556" who="S0144">is it?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0024">mm I know people who have been in the evenings after work <unclear/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0144">okay well it must be about five o'clock now</u>
<u n="559" who="S0024">it's twenty past five let's go</u>
<u n="560" who="S0144">well it takes half an hour to get there</u>
<u n="561" who="S0024">yeah and we can have dinner</u>
<u n="562" who="S0144">what we just to have dinner in IKEA? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no pick up the stuff</u>
<u n="564" who="S0144">er we're not get back till half seven eight o'clock</u>
<u n="565" who="S0024" trans="overlap">okay okay okay yeah that's okay okay let's think of something else for dinner then</u>
<u n="566" who="S0144">we can go in tomorrow morning</u>
<u n="567" who="S0024">mm mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0144">is that alright? I don't think I think it'll be too <unclear/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0024">okay mm mm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0144">erm I don't think I'll go to this party tonight</u>
<u n="571" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s party</u>
<u n="572" who="S0144">I need people have been texting me I need to get back to them</u>
<u n="573" who="S0024">okay yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0144">I feel bad because I'm supposed to be playing</u>
<u n="575" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> it depends on cos if you want to become the if you want to be the drummer of the band you're gonna have to go to the gigs to drum you can't skip them can you?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0144">I know but it's not really a gig it's his housewarming party but he wants music so erm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0024">but you know what I mean it's</u>
<u n="578" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's it's a long way</u>
<u n="579" who="S0024">cos if you don't yeah it's a long way</u>
<u n="580" who="S0144">it's a long way to go just for a couple of beers as well if I just wanted to go quickly</u>
<u n="581" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0144">and show my face</u>
<u n="583" who="S0024">yeah mm but it is possible like twenty minute taxi ride and then you can get back in a taxi but it's just that you like to stay late once you're there</u>
<u n="584" who="S0144">yeah well I know that's my problem</u>
<u n="585" who="S0024">how about if I phone you at twelve and say get back home</u>
<u n="586" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="587" who="S0024">I could do if you want me to</u>
<u n="588" who="S0144">yeah but I don't want you to be perceived like that by other people</u>
<u n="589" who="S0024">but if</u>
<u n="590" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s under the thumb <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah well it's not as if I do it often is it?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no well I don't want no I don't want it to be like that</u>
<u n="593" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> would you take her a sec?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0144">oh you <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0024">you don't have no you don't have to tell them that that's what I've done I could just be reminding you that that's what you wanted to do</u>
<u n="596" who="S0144">yeah yeah the trouble is</u>
<u n="597" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but by then you might be so pissed that you'll be like no</u>
<u n="598" who="S0144">well it's difficult people are like oh just have one more or oh just gonna play one more song or say goodbye to people and then people start talking to you</u>
<u n="599" who="S0024" trans="overlap">not if I say that you need to get back cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="600" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I'm just rubbish at leaving</u>
<u n="601" who="S0024">having a bad night</u>
<u n="602" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0024">you know?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0024">mm I'm just saying I'll do that for you if you want but I'm not sure you'll when I phone you</u>
<u n="606" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0024">you'll have had a few drinks by then and been enjoying yourself and you might wanna stay all night then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="609" who="S0024">but I wanna get loads of stuff done tomorrow if you do go out</u>
<u n="610" who="S0144">yeah yeah yeah so I don't wanna get pissed</u>
<u n="611" who="S0024">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="612" who="S0144">and I'm playing tomorrow night <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0144">so well so they're supposed to be playing tomorrow night as well</u>
<u n="615" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0144">and if they get completely hammered then they might not even turn up tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> they should do cos we need to practice it's been three months since we played</u>
<u n="617" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah well they probably want practice tonight and tomorrow</u>
<u n="618" who="S0144">and we've got</u>
<u n="619" who="S0024">all I'm saying is if like</u>
<u n="620" who="S0144" trans="overlap">two gigs coming up so</u>
<u n="621" who="S0024">they're starting yeah if these gigs are coming up and if you start no we're not going to go and play in the band</u>
<u n="622" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0024">then they'll find someone else</u>
<u n="624" who="S0144">yeah the thing is I</u>
<u n="625" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and you'll just be the Sunday night guy</u>
<u n="626" who="S0144">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0024">which is what you were last term and you weren't happy about it</u>
<u n="628" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0024">you wanted to have more didn't you?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0144">yeah I do want more I know I know they want me</u>
<u n="631" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0144">so it's it's difficult with you isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah I know but it won't be all the time will it? it's only cos it's a one-off house party and</u>
<u n="634" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0024">because we've all come back</u>
<u n="636" who="S0144">but I think I could bring quite a lot to the band in terms of expanding them</u>
<u n="637" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0144">with ideas</u>
<u n="639" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0144">erm because we're the only foreign band in this city</u>
<u n="641" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0144">like western foreign band there's Filipino bands and stuff but this what eight million people in this city?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0144">do you know what I mean? that's we're we're playing at a wedding or something erm in a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="645" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that'd be brilliant to do weddings because</u>
<u n="646" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well it's I mean they're not giving us <trunc>mu</trunc> I think it's like er about two hundred and fifty quid it works out</u>
<u n="647" who="S0024">total?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0024">so fifty quid each or something</u>
<u n="650" who="S0144">well yeah about sixty-seventy quid each yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0144">erm <pause dur="short"/> which the agents well I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone through have said they'll pay us more after that but it's only that's only for twenty minutes</u>
<u n="653" who="S0024">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's crazy</u>
<u n="654" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="655" who="S0024">you can't have a band for a wedding for twenty minutes</u>
<u n="656" who="S0144" trans="overlap">if we had like one and a half hour</u>
<u n="657" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="658" who="S0144">slot you know and then we could get probably double that <unclear>now</unclear></u>
<u n="659" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0144">easy <pause dur="short"/> and the amount of you know it's a big city</u>
<u n="661" who="S0024">yeah it's massive everybody will be hiring you for their weddings</u>
<u n="662" who="S0144">and it's not just <unclear/> it's the surrounding areas as well</u>
<u n="663" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0144">there's a lot of money some here in between <anon type="place"/> and here</u>
<u n="665" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0144">that whole kind of belt</u>
<u n="667" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0144"><unclear/> erm there's so much potential there</u>
<u n="669" who="S0024">but all I'm saying is like I know I really need your help tomorrow</u>
<u n="670" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="671" who="S0024">so yeah I don't want you to get pissed either because</u>
<u n="672" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0024">it'll be cos I'm so tired that we're gonna have er yeah we're gonna need you tomorrow</u>
<u n="674" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0024">but I think you need to go to any band practice they've got right now</u>
<u n="676" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0024">I don't mind you going at all I I really don't mind you going but I do need you tomorrow</u>
<u n="678" who="S0144">yeah well maybe I can go just for a few hours</u>
<u n="679" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="680" who="S0144">I need one of those like belt those tags like criminals <unclear/></u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="681" who="S0144">erm what else was I gonna say? er oh yeah and as I think because I play the <unclear> cajón</unclear> and not a drum kit that's another <unclear/> because the Chinese love it</u>
<u n="682" who="S0024">yeah mm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0144">it's such a novelty for them they absolutely love it</u>
<u n="684" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0144">and I think I don't know the best way to publicise ourselves but I was getting ideas from that book I was reading cos Bernays was talking about how it should be a it is a staged event but it should never appear as a staged event as a whole</u>
<u n="686" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0144">it's one of the first points right I was thinking what we could do you know to give a massive impact <unclear/> <event desc="sound of baby"/> yeah? you know to give a massive impact and to bring attention from the media</u>
<u n="688" who="S0024">mm mm</u>
<u n="689" who="S0144">but without making it look appear staged</u>
<u n="690" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="691" who="S0144">but by something we do</u>
<u n="692" who="S0024">erm well it's playing the <unclear/> hotel will be a good start because he he's doing all the advertising for you</u>
<u n="693" who="S0144">yeah he said there's TV radio</u>
<u n="694" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0144">and yeah but I I don't think that'll work just</u>
<u n="696" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah that that's the advertising</u>
<u n="697" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0024">and if you can negotiate not to do it every two weeks to do it to do it every once a month gig</u>
<u n="699" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="700" who="S0024">that will be perfect</u>
<u n="701" who="S0144">yeah <unclear/> time</u>
<u n="702" who="S0024">yeah with the advertising as well it's great</u>
<u n="703" who="S0144">mm yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0024">and then once people how about erm people need to start putting you through reach out basically</u>
<u n="705" who="S0144">well they they do reach out</u>
<u n="706" who="S0024">who?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0144">the band</u>
<u n="708" who="S0024">no no no somebody needs to record you post it on we chat for people to erm to you you know how when you were at uni once one of the lecturers said oh wow you've been on Wechat your face has been on Wechat a lot that was because some students what did they do? they took a picture of you</u>
<u n="709" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0024">passed it on to somebody else who passed it on to somebody else who passed it on to somebody else share a video share a link share a link share a link share a link and it goes round I mean it'll be surprising it'll go round quite rapidly</u>
<u n="711" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so maybe if we could just do yeah a video somewhere</u>
<u n="712" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you need a video and you need someone like me to I'll share it with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> with er I've only got one but we could ask and then get her to watch it probably</u>
<u n="713" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and try and make it go viral</u>
<u n="714" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0144">er locally viral</u>
<u n="716" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah that's what I mean yeah not not like on the internet viral but</u>
<u n="717" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0024">if you do the Wechat then it's all of this community isn't it basically</u>
<u n="719" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0024">everybody who's found it so but you don't want to tell people to repost it so you just make sure you you show it to lots of people</u>
<u n="721" who="S0144">yeah that would get the name recognised but</u>
<u n="722" who="S0024">what's the name of your band? have you got a name?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0144">it's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> which I don't like</u>
<u n="724" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0024" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got this story of this girl he was with basically his story about how this girl ditched him at exit four of the subway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="729" who="S0144">but</u>
<u n="730" who="S0024">and a lot of his songs are about the girl</u>
<u n="731" who="S0144">a lot of his songs are about girls <vocal desc="laugh"/> but <unclear/> I don't like that but that was decided upon before I even knew them so</u>
<u n="732" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that's not yeah that's not too</u>
<u n="733" who="S0144">yeah that's yeah I'm not happy with the name well it depends how big they wanna get</u>
<u n="734" who="S0024">you can always change the name later</u>
<u n="735" who="S0144">cos I think we could get pretty good to be honest <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot of talent in that band</u>
<u n="736" who="S0024">mm yeah there is I agree</u>
<u n="737" who="S0144">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the best lead guitarist I've heard for well apart from listening heard like live</u>
<u n="738" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0144">apart from people who are mega famous <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is very talented is very tight in what he does</u>
<u n="740" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a good bassist although <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might be leaving in December so that's a problem we don't know any other bassists</u>
<u n="742" who="S0024"><unclear>I'll learn</unclear></u>
<u n="743" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0144">erm but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying he wants to start a band with me as well</u>
<u n="746" who="S0024">can't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but he's been saying that for a few months</u>
<u n="748" who="S0024" trans="overlap">can't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> play bass?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="750" who="S0024">can't be that hard can it?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no he sings</u>
<u n="752" who="S0024">if he plays guitar already</u>
<u n="753" who="S0144">no he plays acoustic he's a folk singer</u>
<u n="754" who="S0024">oh you can be in two bands can't you? but that's too much hard work <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you can't you haven't got the time to do that and to make your music on the computer and you're trying to do too much</u>
<u n="755" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0024">and <pause dur="short"/> one thing at a time</u>
<u n="757" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but apart from this one that's where my energy's gonna go</u>
<u n="758" who="S0024">yeah it's</u>
<u n="759" who="S0144">this year</u>
<u n="760" who="S0024"><unclear/></u>
<u n="761" who="S0144">and I wanna yeah I wanna get back on the propaganda stuff as well <pause dur="short"/> cos I</u>
<u n="762" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no more stupid <trunc>vid</trunc> stupid series videos</u>
<u n="763" who="S0144">no no no no no <unclear>they're shit</unclear></u>
<u n="764" who="S0024" trans="overlap">an absolute waste of time</u>
<u n="765" who="S0144">yeah agreed</u>
<u n="766" who="S0024">oh man I can't believe some of the shit we've watched</u>
<u n="767" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0024">lately I know we needed it cos we needed a break and we were always tired and <vocal desc="laugh"/> still tired</u>
<u n="769" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but occasionally <unclear/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0024">yeah but as soon as we start one series thing I don't know then we just sit down at dinner we watch another series and then every dinner time it's the same</u>
<u n="771" who="S0144">yeah yeah it's a waste of time</u>
<u n="772" who="S0024">and then we get tired after dinner and we're like oh shall we watch <unclear/> together</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="773" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="776" who="S0024">do you really?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0144">oh oh oh</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="778" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="779" who="S0144">you're funny aren't you?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0024">ah ah ah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0144">mm sorry I still haven't made this drink do you want to hold it while I get a drink</u>
<u n="782" who="S0024">yeah just <unclear/> erm what are you making camomile tea?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0024">yeah I could do with some camomile tea just</u>
<u n="785" who="S0144" trans="overlap">do you want me to reheat the kettle or</u>
<u n="786" who="S0024">no no no I don't want it too hot</u>
<u n="787" who="S0144">well I'm going to have pineapple juice <event desc="sound of baby"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="788" who="S0024">did you say daddy? daddy daddy look at your big fat tummy <vocal desc="nonsense"/> we could make a drum out of you so are you going tonight now?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0144">erm like you said I don't wanna burn bridges</u>
<u n="790" who="S0024">no I don't I think you have to go but</u>
<u n="791" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I don't want otherwise</u>
<u n="792" who="S0024">but I need you tomorrow though</u>
<u n="793" who="S0144">yeah I know and I wanted <unclear/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0144">otherwise I'm going to be known as the person with a baby that's not reliable</u>
<u n="796" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and not reliable yeah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0144">that aren't they</u>
<u n="798" who="S0024" trans="overlap">who doesn't turn up to half of the stuff</u>
<u n="799" who="S0144" trans="overlap">who's always too tired he can never really come to things</u>
<u n="800" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0144">erm which is the case</u>
<u n="802" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but I don't wanna appear</u>
<u n="804" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it'll be alright once you get there</u>
<u n="805" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0024">bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="807" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I was thinking a lot of this depends on me er becoming a bit more self-disciplined with leaving early rather than being the last one to leave</u>
<u n="808" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0144">that's if I if I'm gonna make this work that's what I need to change</u>
<u n="810" who="S0024">yeah agreed I agree</u>
<u n="811" who="S0144" trans="overlap">cos I can't be having <unclear>it</unclear> both ways</u>
<u n="812" who="S0024">you can't do everything</u>
<u n="813" who="S0144">no I can't I know that cos it would ruin tomorrow as well</u>
<u n="814" who="S0024">and yeah and during the day well she's up isn't she? she's up at six so</u>
<u n="815" who="S0144">where's the camomile tea?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0024">on the left shelf there's only a couple left</u>
<u n="817" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="818" who="S0024">right at the back</u>
<u n="819" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0024">yeah it's gonna be tough <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if you wanna keep this band going</u>
<u n="821" who="S0144">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> but I think there's a there's a possibility that something could happen with this that's why I wanna do it</u>
<u n="822" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0144">cos these guys have got some serious <unclear/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh put it there <pause dur="short"/> oh no <trunc>si</trunc> where's the tissues gone?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0024">I stopped carrying around her cloth because erm because she wasn't sick any more but she's been sick loads today</u>
<u n="827" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><unclear/> which I think's a pretty easy thing to do considering there's no not much competition to be honest</u>
<u n="828" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0144">erm and <anon type="place"/> is only two hours away</u>
<u n="830" who="S0024">yeah well I'm happy for you to focus</u>
<u n="831" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and then you're talking about big money and wouldn't need to teach any more <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0024">yay but we'd still live in <anon type="place"/> wouldn't we?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0144">well yay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0024">but that's alright I don't mind living in <anon type="place"/> like if will I have to teach?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0144">huh?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0024">no I wouldn't I wouldn't want</u>
<u n="837" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><unclear/> erm like carry my stuff</u>
<u n="838" who="S0024">okay erm oh I've forgotten what I was gonna say to you I've forgotten no erm I am really happy for you to do the band I still haven't even come and watched the band</u>
<u n="839" who="S0144">oh really? that's crazy</u>
<u n="840" who="S0024">well we can get babysitters now</u>
<u n="841" who="S0144">yeah and you've never heard me play the <unclear>cajón</unclear> well apart from in here</u>
<u n="842" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="843" who="S0144">while I was practicing that's not the same</u>
<u n="844" who="S0024">I did I heard you play at the beginning when I was pregnant</u>
<u n="845" who="S0144">that's the first time I've ever played it in my life</u>
<u n="846" who="S0024">yeah that's it that's the only time I heard you</u>
<u n="847" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0024">that's why I <unclear>bongos</unclear></u>
<u n="849" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0024">ah you're my bongo man</u>
<u n="851" who="S0144">I'm better on this now than I <unclear>was</unclear> on bongos</u>
<u n="852" who="S0024">you're my bongo bongo man don't change <pause dur="short"/> how are you better? it's still just a drum</u>
<u n="853" who="S0144">no this is more four four <unclear>kind of</unclear> rock beats which I can</u>
<u n="854" who="S0024" trans="overlap">bongo <unclear>congo</unclear></u>
<u n="855" who="S0144">congos bongos are more kind of Latin</u>
<u n="856" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="857" who="S0144">beats which I never learnt properly</u>
<u n="858" who="S0024" trans="overlap">drum <unclear>bay</unclear></u>
<u n="859" who="S0144">drum <unclear>bay</unclear> African beats which I've never learnt the beats properly I always just improvised if I <unclear/> and learnt some beats properly then yeah</u>
<u n="860" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah it doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/> what and you know what the <unclear>cajón</unclear> has certain beats that you have to</u>
<u n="861" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well the cajón has <trunc>bas</trunc> well the music we play is all western music so I can it's all four four rock</u>
<u n="862" who="S0024">yeah yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="863" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so it <unclear>doesn't</unclear> come as easy</u>
<u n="864" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0144">but I can but I still improvise and I I don't I play it differently every time I keep the base</u>
<u n="866" who="S0024" trans="overlap">are you allowed to do that when you're in a band?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0144">no I keep the foundation the same but I change my fills and depending on the sound of the the venue I can put different accents on different things</u>
<u n="868" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well yeah we'll <trunc>cert</trunc> won't quite a few people have said <trunc>we</trunc> they'll babysit and I think they're happier now that she's older and I'm happier now that she's older</u>
<u n="869" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="870" who="S0024">babysit if she sleeps but cos she's not been sleeping can't make anybody do that now at the moment she needs to go back to her routine of seven o'clock go to bed <event desc="sound of baby"/> doesn't wake up till one or two</u>
<u n="871" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="872" who="S0024">that's what she needs to go back to go back to your old routine</u>
<u n="873" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="874" who="S0024"><unclear>how</unclear> are we gonna get back to this routine</u>
<u n="875" who="S0144" trans="overlap">gonna turn this off yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="877" who="S0144">er oh it's an hour exactly</u>
<u n="878" who="S0024">mm er</u>
<u n="879" who="S0144">that's good innit? that's enough money to buy your baby cot thing no</u>
<u n="880" who="S0024">baby cot?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0144">er what are they called? those things that go round the bars of the cot</u>
<u n="882" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what they're called</u>
<u n="883" who="S0144">must have a name</u>
<u n="884" who="S0024">what time is it?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0144" trans="overlap">stop eating your socks</u>
<u n="886" who="S0024">we're gonna have to think of what we're doing for dinner then</u>
<u n="887" who="S0144">okay what are the options?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0024">it depends on the time</u>
<u n="889" who="S0144">erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="890" who="S0024">I might have to oh I've got <unclear/> twenty to six what time are you due out?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0144">twenty to six</u>
<u n="892" who="S0024">mm mm</u>
<u n="893" who="S0144">well the party'll be going on all night</u>
<u n="894" who="S0024">yeah but when are you going?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0144">erm I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it starts at seven officially</u>
<u n="896" who="S0024">so you'll probably go down about nine won't you? seven eight about eight for nine</u>
<u n="897" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah eight nine</u>
<u n="898" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="899" who="S0144">come back twelve</u>
<u n="900" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="901" who="S0144">eleven twelve the latest</u>
<u n="902" who="S0024">yeah sounds good</u>
<u n="903" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0024">mm mm</u>
<u n="905" who="S0144">maybe I can share a taxi with someone</u>
<u n="906" who="S0024" trans="overlap">so that means so I'm just trying to think that means we need to cook dinner now really if you're going out or we need to find some dinner well I quite fancy some pizza</u>
<u n="907" who="S0144">pizza? we could have pizza</u>
<u n="908" who="S0024">do you fancy going down to the pizza place that's it's twenty to six we've got time to go down there eat or will it be busy?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0144">Saturday night</u>
<u n="910" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="911" who="S0144">probably be quite busy people smoking</u>
<u n="912" who="S0024">oh er</u>
<u n="913" who="S0144">we could order a pizza</u>
<u n="914" who="S0024">why can't they we'll walk down there get order a pizza and bring it back</u>
<u n="915" who="S0144">oh I was thinking about ordering a pizza from Papa John's</u>
<u n="916" who="S0024">yeah could order a pizza from Papa John's yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="918" who="S0024">bit naughty we've got all of that stuff in the fridge</u>
<u n="919" who="S0144">erm well what could we make with that?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0024">well I was gonna make erm kedgeree</u>
<u n="921" who="S0144">ah yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0024">but I'm so tired but we could still make kedgeree</u>
<u n="923" who="S0144">would be nice</u>
<u n="924" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but I don't know cos the rice should be colder not you know not freshly cooked really to make it lovely</u>
<u n="925" who="S0144">well shall we have kedgeree tomorrow night then?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0024">could have kedgeree tomorrow yeah</u>
<u n="927" who="S0144">pizza tonight</u>
<u n="928" who="S0024">okay yeah okay do that</u>
<u n="929" who="S0144">well better order it soon then cos it's Saturday night</u>
<u n="930" who="S0024">okay where's <unclear>phone</unclear>?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0144">dunno have we got a menu?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0024">oh erm where did I put my phone? yes there's a menu I've got a menu I'll go and get the menu <pause dur="short"/> oh ah <vocal desc="nonsense"/> would you like to go down here and play? <unclear>tummy</unclear> time do you want to do some <unclear>tummy</unclear> time? has she done any <unclear>tum</unclear> time with you today? she's done a little bit with me oh there's my phone I've got it last time they didn't realise my address from the phone number</u>
<event desc="0024 leaves"/>
<u n="933" who="S0024"><unclear/> on the notice board nobody's put the pizza thing up on the noticeboard</u>
<u n="934" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="935" who="S0024">might be in this drawer because from somebody <unclear/> erm <unclear>moving</unclear> up uh</u>
<u n="936" who="S0144">oh shit</u>
<u n="937" who="S0024">cos that had a special phone number on it didn't it?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0144">oh my god that should have been put somewhere safe</u>
<u n="941" who="S0024">oh here it is</u>
<u n="942" who="S0144">oh thank god for that</u>
<u n="943" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><trunc>wh</trunc>when did we last order pizza? why is this out? have we ordered pizza recently? are we gonna become massive? we're gonna be massive</u>
<u n="944" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="945" who="S0024">can I get pepperoni?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0144">you can get whatever you want</u>
<u n="947" who="S0024">I choose well we don't need two do you want to get two or one?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0144">well if we get two we can save it for tomorrow</u>
<u n="949" who="S0024">okay so we won't bother <unclear/> tomorrow <unclear/> pizza again</u>
<u n="950" who="S0144">well tomorrow lunch or whatever</u>
<u n="951" who="S0024">okay er I choose pepperoni you choose one</u>
<u n="952" who="S0144">you choose pepperoni I choose hm what's John's favourite?</u>
<u n="953" who="S0024">no we had that last time it wasn't that great</u>
<u n="954" who="S0144">it doesn't even say what's in it it says John's favourite</u>
<u n="955" who="S0024">no I just looked at the pictures <unclear>awesome</unclear></u>
<u n="956" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="957" who="S0144">that's so Chinese <pause dur="short"/> super Papa's what's that?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0024">I dunno we had a John's favourite and a super Papa's last time didn't we?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0144">oh did we?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0024">we <unclear/> I think</u>
<u n="961" who="S0144">does it not say?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="963" who="S0144">oh this is silly the pictures all look the same</u>
<u n="964" who="S0024">they are practically the same they've just either got more chillies or not</u>
<u n="965" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well not cos</u>
<u n="966" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah the one we had last time had basically the same meat on it</u>
<u n="967" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but Papa John's is an international</u>
<u n="968" who="S0024">and then then it just had different chillies on more green</u>
<u n="969" who="S0144">er nappy nappy seafood</u>
<u n="970" who="S0024">what? <pause dur="short"/> where?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0144">there</u>
<u n="972" who="S0024">Naples</u>
<u n="973" who="S0144">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0024">oh let me put the light on <pause dur="short"/> you're sitting there squinting</u>
<u n="975" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0024">oh <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="977" who="S0144" trans="overlap">don't want nappy seafood do we?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="979" who="S0144">that doesn't sound very nice</u>
<u n="980" who="S0024">absolutely you must have nappies on the mind</u>
<u n="981" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="982" who="S0024">must have been like one of those <trunc>auto</trunc>automatic that's what it must mean things</u>
<u n="983" who="S0144">I like this pizza all the meats <pause dur="short"/> land and sea oh this is just pot luck isn't it?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0024" trans="overlap">can we just get something normal?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0144">well find something normal</u>
<u n="986" who="S0024">Hawaiian</u>
<u n="987" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> what? barbeque</u>
<u n="988" who="S0024">mushroom</u>
<u n="989" who="S0144">no don't like mushroom</u>
<u n="990" who="S0024">chicken and barbeque</u>
<u n="991" who="S0144">where's that?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0024">there</u>
<u n="993" who="S0144">er er</u>
<u n="994" who="S0024">Italian <unclear>delight</unclear></u>
<u n="995" who="S0144">Italian delight yeah where's that?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0024">there there's no telling what's in it either</u>
<u n="997" who="S0144">oh I don't know as long as its got olives</u>
<u n="998" who="S0024">well I'd get the Italian <unclear>one</unclear> then <pause dur="short"/> do you want to phone?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0144">er yep have they got our phone or address logged on there?</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0024">yeah they should have they did have they did one time and then the next time they didn't and I don't know</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0144">where do we live? I've forgotten <anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0144"><anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="1004" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0024">don't speak Chinese</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0144">oh <pause dur="short"/> our address is <anon type="address"/> no</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0024">you've forgotten where you live? are you serious?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I never give my address I never look</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0024">is that cos I always do the takeaway? <unclear>I'm</unclear> gonna make you do it now</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0144">so it's four we're in block <anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="1012" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0144"><anon type="address"/> or <anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="1014" who="S0024"><anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0144"><anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0144">right okay so we're getting one Italian delight and one what did you want?</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0024">pepperoni <vocal desc="yawn"/> I <unclear/> easy <unclear>me</unclear></u>
<u n="1019" who="S0144">pepperoni</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0024">I'm easy I just have pepperoni every time</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0144">large?</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0024">huh?</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0144">do you want to get a large?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0144">do you want anything else? any side dishes?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0024">oh we haven't got much salad here but I don't know what their salads are like I'd like some salad actually</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0144">salad</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0024">well we've got we've got cucumbers and tomatoes here but we're out lettuce aren't we?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0144">yeah I can't see any salads here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1030" who="S0024">oh really? they must do salad</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> do we get drinks with it?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0024">no oh yeah I think brought they gave a free bottle <unclear>last time</unclear> a bottle of coke</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0144">did they?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0024">but I don't want coke</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0144">I I need some sugar so do I ask for that?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0024">yeah oh</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0024">oh ah <pause dur="short"/> oh dear are you alright?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
