<text id="S5ER">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:13:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-05-07</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0015 S0281</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home, Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Bringing my daughter from abroad to live here</topics>
		<activity>Talking with my sister about my present personal situation</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0015">
				<exactage>68</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Scotland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Brighton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>67 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<event desc="sound of television"/>
<u n="1" who="S0281">paperwork oh that's great thanks</u>
<u n="2" who="S0015">that's er <pause dur="short"/> that's all you needed wasn't it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0281">yeah so presumably I'll just need to fill this in</u>
<u n="4" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0281">and go out to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0015">well you can post it can't you? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is er you can't get in there when you get out to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos I tried before</u>
<u n="7" who="S0281">I can't post <unclear/> got a shared proof identity <pause dur="short"/> I've got to take a passport along</u>
<u n="8" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="9" who="S0281">see I don't know I can't remember how you did it before</u>
<u n="10" who="S0015">I I just took it out and they took it from me at the gate erm maybe you just need a copy of <unclear/> booked here you are sit down you can fill it in</u>
<u n="11" who="S0281">well there's no hurry cos er</u>
<u n="12" who="S0015">no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0281">erm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0015">but that's all I did cos erm I <unclear>didn't</unclear> get out with the checking out</u>
<u n="15" who="S0281">yeah you see it says here erm <pause dur="short"/> er you must have supplied proof of identity <pause dur="short"/> if you want to <unclear/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear>let's have</unclear> a look <pause dur="short"/> you <unclear/> along you <unclear/> half of someone else's and get <unclear/> therefore you must supply proof of identity when your feet get at location access may be <unclear>had</unclear> for instance whether act <unclear/> yeah but presumably that's just a copy of your passport isn't it? you <trunc>ca</trunc> you won't be able to get in there to the place it was they</u>
<u n="17" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0015">collect it at the desk</u>
<u n="19" who="S0281">so before</u>
<u n="20" who="S0015" trans="overlap">how did you do it before? I don't remember</u>
<u n="21" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well you did it for me</u>
<u n="22" who="S0015">well it must have been just a copy then isn't it?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so to say that nobody else can apply on your behalf</u>
<u n="24" who="S0015">yeah but I didn't it was your form I just took it out</u>
<u n="25" who="S0281">you may not apply on behalf of someone <pause dur="short"/> unless you hold a power of attorney</u>
<u n="26" who="S0015">yeah but I didn't apply I just too it out there</u>
<u n="27" who="S0281">oh right</u>
<u n="28" who="S0015">it was your er all of your <unclear>form</unclear></u>
<u n="29" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so I wouldn't actually have to go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do it?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0015">well I don't think so you ring them up and find out I they wouldn't let me in</u>
<u n="31" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0015">I got to the gate</u>
<u n="33" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0015">and they said I'll take that to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously it was addressed to the right person</u>
<u n="35" who="S0281">the thing was the problem I <unclear>just</unclear> remember with money wasn't it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0281">cos they didn't have a a cheque</u>
<u n="38" who="S0015" trans="overlap">a cheque yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0281">so</u>
<u n="40" who="S0015">they won't take cash they have to have cheque</u>
<u n="41" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh they have to have a cheque?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0015">yeah oh I can write you a cheque</u>
<u n="43" who="S0281">okay</u>
<u n="44" who="S0015">postal order or something you know they can't take cash obviously cos it was just a bit</u>
<u n="45" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0015">couldn't <unclear>just appear</unclear></u>
<u n="47" who="S0281">yeah well you can't trust the police <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0015">well did you hear that story about the erm someone that erm there was lots of jewellery <pause dur="short"/> hundreds of thousands of pounds</u>
<u n="49" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0015">that were erm <pause dur="short"/> burgled I think</u>
<u n="51" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0015">and the police found it confiscated it from obviously the thing and it disappeared the whole lot</u>
<u n="53" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0015">yeah and they're still not they've no idea where it went at the police station <pause dur="short"/> so don't believe everything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0281">where where's the er new <unclear/> I bought?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0015">there</u>
<u n="57" who="S0281">you hid it right under my nose</u>
<u n="58" who="S0015">I did <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0281">and scissors please?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0015"><unclear/> there you go</u>
<u n="61" who="S0281">oh thanks</u>
<u n="62" who="S0015">yeah no I don't think they're <unclear>that</unclear> you could ring them say what do I do?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah morning <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0281">morning <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="66" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">breakfast?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0281">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I wouldn't eat it</u>
<u n="69" who="S0015">what?</u>
<u n="70" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I wouldn't eat it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0015">oh what that?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0281">oh manure?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0015">no he's just cleared out the guttering</u>
<u n="74" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="75" who="S0015">we swept the stuff off the roof cos it falls on you know it's erm like moss that grows on the roof</u>
<u n="76" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0015"><unclear/> on the patio and makes it all <trunc>mil</trunc> you know green so we swept the roof off yesterday</u>
<u n="78" who="S0281">ah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0015">scrubbed the patio and <unclear/> the guttering to</u>
<u n="80" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0015">get rid of the rubbish so it doesn't wouldn't go down the drain otherwise it would <unclear/> fat <pause dur="short"/> never ending work I'm afraid</u>
<u n="82" who="S0281">erm I just phoned er the school's er school admissions</u>
<u n="83" who="S0015">school admissions yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0015">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0015">yeah?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0281">checking out the feasibility of maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> coming to school here</u>
<u n="89" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0281">erm I haven't spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0015">no</u>
<u n="92" who="S0281">er because I I thought I'll need to get a bit of information behind me before I do it</u>
<u n="93" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0281">erm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0015">of course</u>
<u n="96" who="S0281">so</u>
<u n="97" who="S0015">what did they say?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0281">well when I <pause dur="short"/> enquired before I <pause dur="short"/> said that er the admissions date</u>
<u n="99" who="S0015">yeah is such and such</u>
<u n="100" who="S0281">er was sort of January</u>
<u n="101" who="S0015" trans="overlap">January mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0281">and March at the latest <pause dur="short"/> you know the guy I just spoke to an Indian guy and <vocal desc="laugh"/> I always I</u>
<u n="103" who="S0015" trans="overlap">you <unclear/> conversation</u>
<u n="104" who="S0281">well I I always have trouble with an Indian accent I find it very difficult to understand them but anyway erm <pause dur="short"/> they're they're it is possible still</u>
<u n="105" who="S0015">I told you you don't believe me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="107" who="S0015">they they have to by law keep a certain number of places available now it might not be your school of choice <pause dur="short"/> erm that's the that that's the thing I mean you know if you know the schools in <anon type="place"/> you choose a good one</u>
<u n="108" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="109" who="S0015">but there's <unclear>you know</unclear> not much chance of getting into the best</u>
<u n="110" who="S0281" trans="overlap">there's erm there's two two aspects of this one is er which would I be applying for primary or junior?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0015">how old is she? eight?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0281">she's eight she's gonna be nine in October</u>
<u n="113" who="S0015">I think that makes her into <trunc>jun</trunc> er junior</u>
<u n="114" who="S0281">but <pause dur="short"/> I said erm <pause dur="short"/> that er you <unclear/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0015" trans="overlap">nine in October?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0281">you you can yeah you can apply for both said it's er it might be a bit harder for junior cos all the places have gone but you might get in on on late admissions</u>
<u n="117" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0281">but also it <trunc>dep</trunc>depends on er where you live and I said well at the moment I'm staying with sister and her family up at erm in <anon type="place"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I I haven't got any accommodation of my own said well they take into consideration erm your application according to where you live and</u>
<u n="119" who="S0015">that's the <trunc>prob</trunc> that's what I said to you you have to decide which area you're gonna go to to be able to put your application that's why that family I'm talking about that moved into our house</u>
<u n="120" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0015">they had to do it by a set you know they had to get choose where they wanted to live they selected the school chose where they wanted to live and searched in that area <pause dur="short"/> for schools</u>
<u n="122" who="S0281">well they said that they said</u>
<u n="123" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0281">yeah but I can't they they said that I need proof of er</u>
<u n="125" who="S0015">accommodation</u>
<u n="126" who="S0281">accommodation right</u>
<u n="127" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah you will</u>
<u n="128" who="S0281">so I can't</u>
<u n="129" who="S0015">apply</u>
<u n="130" who="S0281">I can't do it that way I can only apply giving the only address the the that I've got which is here now</u>
<u n="131" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0281">yeah?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0015">uhu</u>
<u n="134" who="S0281">so</u>
<u n="135" who="S0015" trans="overlap">which would mean you'd know then move to need to move and if you got her into school you'd need to move to that area yeah?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0281">right and then erm I mean how would that fit in with the housing er getting housing</u>
<u n="137" who="S0015">well you just have to look for a flat</u>
<u n="138" who="S0281" trans="overlap">would would I <trunc>ha</trunc> would I have to find er <trunc>w</trunc>would of would er <pause dur="short"/> how does it work? I mean I</u>
<u n="139" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well you then have to look for a flat they if you put our address down then you'd have to look for a flat in this area so that you were in the catchment area from the school</u>
<u n="140" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0015">but I mean</u>
<u n="142" who="S0281">that would be difficult wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0015">well there aren't many flats in this area</u>
<u n="144" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0015">well there are that's not strictly true there's loads of them there's all down where <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> lives all of those flats there</u>
<u n="146" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0015">you know there are available erm you just have to look online <pause dur="short"/> but in the meantime put it down as our address but then you'd have to make sure you otherwise you're stuck with <trunc>try</trunc> travelling <trunc>load</trunc> you know a long way to pick her up and drop her off and you know erm <pause dur="short"/> I know you won't get into <anon type="place"/> school because it is the most popular school in <anon type="place"/> I would think other than the catholic school which they go you can travel all over to go to <trunc>trav</trunc> catholic school but erm <pause dur="short"/> there are flats all down there but erm <pause dur="short"/> the difficulty is they are very popular because they are in the <anon type="place"/> catchment area</u>
<u n="148" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0015">which is where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s at that school just by sheer accident cos we didn't think anything about schooling at that time it just happened to be where the flat was erm but the one the one you would get into would be <anon type="place"/> which is just up the road here</u>
<u n="150" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0015">erm near ASDA now I don't know where the nearest you know flats would be in that area what you'd have to do would be to go to local estate agents such as erm <unclear/> about three or four</u>
<u n="152" who="S0281">yep with I I'm told that it's very difficult to to get accommodation if you're on benefits <pause dur="short"/> now I'm going just I've got a pension <unclear>that</unclear></u>
<u n="153" who="S0015" trans="overlap">it is it is difficult it is erm more difficult because you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> people on benefits quite often have sort of wrecked the joint and they don't look after the place and and you know</u>
<u n="154" who="S0281" trans="overlap">what what if I get erm erm a guarantor as it were</u>
<u n="155" who="S0015">it wouldn't matter whether you've got a guarantor or not the the big the thing well I suppose it may do but that isn't your <unclear>thing</unclear> at the moment you couldn't get any benefits cos you've got too much money that's your problem right now you're not a DHSS case</u>
<u n="156" who="S0281">no well I erm I've seen a house</u>
<u n="157" who="S0015" trans="overlap">you're a private erm individual</u>
<u n="158" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0015">and so there'd be no problem you know they wanna know where you live erm what you know how much you've got in your bank and what you do for a living well you're retired so you know</u>
<u n="160" who="S0281">well I could presumably do do one step at a time</u>
<u n="161" who="S0015">you'd have to and then you'd have to become a DHSS one</u>
<u n="162" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0015">when your <trunc>mon</trunc> as I I was saying to you the other day you couldn't apply they wouldn't help you right now at all</u>
<u n="164" who="S0281">so <trunc>a</trunc>any rent I'll have to pay</u>
<u n="165" who="S0015">you'd have to pay it <trunc>upfron</trunc>front yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0281">well that <unclear>sort</unclear> of money would go very quickly <unclear/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah it would and then you'll become a DHSS <pause dur="short"/> and that's why I said to you she says but buy diamonds or antiques or something because that's money in the bank</u>
<u n="168" who="S0281">yes</u>
<u n="169" who="S0015">but you could sell in the future <pause dur="short"/> and that's you know what some people would do in your situation but of course if you did have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean right now you would only get help if you were DHSS you would only get help as a single person</u>
<u n="170" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0015">which would be a lot less than if you've got two people or three people</u>
<u n="172" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0015">obviously because that's how it's worked you know you only need to look after yourself kind of thing but if it as you person as you are at the current <unclear/> you would erm and you're wanting place for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you need to be looking for a two bedroom</u>
<u n="174" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0015">or you would have to have a large one bedroom where you could sort of use the front room with a put you up or something</u>
<u n="176" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0015">that would work erm as long as that large enough to store all your things and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s things</u>
<u n="178" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0015">erm so that that would be one option and then if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't come you've still only got a one bedroom and you would still be entitled to the same amount now if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did come and you were you know obviously your money that had gone and you were DHSS at that point you erm would have be not a single person any more you have a a dependent a child now if you only had a one bedroom there is a chance not not very good chance in this area that you could be rehoused with the two bedroom if you're in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s area that would be quite quick I mean for instance <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had she had a two-bedroom flat and one child erm November she had the baby was born she registered that you know with the council or housing association in erm December just before Christmas I think or maybe <trunc>a</trunc> I don't know in December and she got a place and she's in it now brand new because in that area there are less people looking for housing in <anon type="place"/> it's the worst possible</u>
<u n="180" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0015">scenarios and and you get families that are homeless they put them in B and B <pause dur="short"/> and certainly single people just don't stand a look in you know? because there's so many families that haven't got</u>
<u n="182" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0015"><trunc>acco</trunc>accommodation because the rents were so high and so it's kind of swings and roundabouts you have to decide what what you do how long you could hang on in with a single bedroom place with a a child you'd have to then look for a a large a very large one which would</u>
<u n="184" who="S0281" trans="overlap">how much would that cost</u>
<u n="185" who="S0015">well they're you know how how I've no no idea they you know I couldn't give you a price cos they're all different prices I know a two bedroom is around about nine hundred to a thousand</u>
<u n="186" who="S0281" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="187" who="S0015">pounds a month</u>
<u n="188" who="S0281">would it would it not be better rather than registering saying my <trunc>ad</trunc>address is here saying it was in er give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s address? <pause dur="short"/> because that'd be easier finding a school and housing</u>
<u n="189" who="S0015">why?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0281">no?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0015">there's no schools around where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is is there?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm are there not? I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0015">no no</u>
<u n="194" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="195" who="S0015">no it would need to well the best thing to do is get on the internet and look at the schools in the area and you'll see I think there is</u>
<u n="196" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well that's that's what <unclear/> I've got to apply anyway erm for an application for a school you this is the website here</u>
<u n="197" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah but <trunc>th</trunc>that's what I'm saying that that's they want to know your erm address currently when you put that application in</u>
<u n="198" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0015">so if you put <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s you'd have to change everything your bank and everything to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="200" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh right okay</u>
<u n="201" who="S0015">erm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah well that's not good and all so he doesn't want because he</u>
<u n="203" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>exact</trunc> yeah there's complications there</u>
<u n="204" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0015">so erm <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>i</trunc>in this area there are three three well four actually if if you count the Catholic school but you'll never get in there without the priests giving you a <vocal desc="laugh"/> the nod erm here there's <anon type="place"/> up here where behind here where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes er but that is one of the most popular schools in <anon type="place"/> and even <unclear>people</unclear> who live in the area struggle to get in there then you've got <anon type="place"/> erm which was just off er <anon type="place"/> which isn't far and you've got <anon type="place"/> up here</u>
<u n="206" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0015">now I know quite a few it's not the most popular because it's right on the edge of a <pause dur="short"/> council estate</u>
<u n="208" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0015">so it's probably the least popular of those three <anon type="place"/> is is always had a good reputation but you need to look on the map and see shall I go and get the the laptop? and look on the</u>
<u n="210" who="S0281">yeah okay</u>
<u n="211" who="S0015">yeah see what the school the okay</u>
<u n="212" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0015">do you want some toast?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0281">no I'm fine thanks</u>
<u n="215" who="S0015">are you sure?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0281">yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> swings and roundabouts <pause dur="short"/> what to do <pause dur="short"/> not gonna be easy <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether it's gonna be possible or not <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0015">age wise I'm sure she'd be in the junior</u>
<u n="218" who="S0281">yeah?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0015">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> why <unclear>so did you</unclear> say she's eight?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0281">nine she's going to be nine end of October</u>
<u n="221" who="S0015" trans="overlap">nine <unclear>ten</unclear> they get they go up <pause dur="short"/> I think at seven and eight <pause dur="short"/> and that sort of erm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0281">I think what about er erm language ability because she</u>
<u n="223" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="224" who="S0281">she's obviously not</u>
<u n="225" who="S0015">no <pause dur="short"/> but you'd be surprised how yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0281" trans="overlap">fluent in in English where well yeah the kids adapt really quickly I know that but er</u>
<u n="227" who="S0015" trans="overlap">they they might prove <unclear/> surrounded by so so quickly but I mean they have got children come from all all over the country <vocal desc="laugh"/> all over the world</u>
<u n="228" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0015">so they all <trunc>ha</trunc> all schools now have quite a lot of mixed erm nationalities so they</u>
<u n="230" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="231" who="S0015">oh phone <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> oh wrong number darling <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm mummy <vocal desc="laugh"/> alright <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> no she's not at uni but she's erm at erm <pause dur="short"/> I think she was taking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s so she can study and I said you know she wanted to bring in <unclear/> in the next few days <unclear/> she can <pause dur="short"/> give her a call okay bye bye <pause dur="short"/> yeah so let me just see what they've got on here <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> where does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> live? <anon type="place"/> area?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="address"/> so actually in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/> schools <pause dur="short"/> mm?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0281"><unclear/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0015">yeah are there any schools in the <anon type="place"/> area <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you know?</u>
<u n="236" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well I'm sure there are</u>
<u n="237" who="S0015">where?</u>
<u n="238" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>kids there</unclear> they have to go to school</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281">yeah I always see lots of</u>
<u n="240" who="S0015" trans="overlap">there's <anon type="place"/> but that's quite a long way isn't it?</u>
<u n="241" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">there's erm er what's it? <anon type="place"/> that <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0281" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="243" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> is it? <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0015">oh no there is one</u>
<u n="245" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0015"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="247" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0015"><anon type="place"/> I think there is one there</u>
<u n="249" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well there is one</u>
<u n="250" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I don't know what age <pause dur="short"/> I presume it's all ages but that is that the only one?</u>
<u n="251" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm trying to think now trying to go through the schools</u>
<u n="252" who="S0015">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I mean <trunc>there</trunc>there'll be some <pause dur="short"/> in the within the</u>
<u n="253" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> there's a nice school there</u>
<u n="254" who="S0015">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't forget we've got the car to the garage today</u>
<u n="255" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">sorry?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0015">gotta take the car</u>
<u n="257" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh if you've got one I'll come and</u>
<u n="258" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well just come up for I'd forgotten about it it's in my laptop</u>
<u n="259" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's what you should be planning around the day</u>
<u n="260" who="S0015">half one</u>
<u n="261" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm going out to get the car back so <unclear>that</unclear> you see it so you go or I go with it</u>
<u n="262" who="S0015">where are you going?</u>
<u n="263" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've gotta go and buy erm <unclear>lawn</unclear> sand</u>
<u n="264" who="S0015">mm okay</u>
<u n="265" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">from <anon type="place"/> and also we've got chairs over from <unclear/> see if she's gonna be in</u>
<u n="266" who="S0015">I don't know that <unclear>have</unclear> to ring her</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0015">right what do we wanna know?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0281">so er</u>
<u n="270" who="S0015">map of school <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0281"><unclear>that there</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> are you on the website? ah there we go mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0015"><anon type="place"/> I think it's a junior but</u>
<u n="273" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello</u>
<u n="274" who="S0015">hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm <unclear/> infants and priming primary</u>
<u n="275" who="S0281"><unclear/> remember yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0015">erm name of schools no that's not what I want is it?</u>
<u n="277" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> my work trousers there</u>
<u n="278" who="S0015"><unclear/> A A B C's</u>
<u n="279" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> my work trousers there</u>
<u n="280" who="S0015">thank you darling what is that dark?</u>
<u n="281" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<u n="282" who="S0015">okay <pause dur="short"/> single catchment area two school catchment area <unclear>for people</unclear> live in on boats and travelling children even they have schools so</u>
<u n="283" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear>ah</unclear> ah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0015">they get places so that's you know</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0015">that's what I'm saying it's not <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> there we go</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0015">so where are we? we're here <pause dur="short"/> no we're not we are here somewhere <unclear/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so what's</u>
<u n="290" who="S0015">that there that's all showing senior schools at the moment</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0015">I think <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is where is he? <anon type="address"/> he's in this area</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0015"><anon type="place"/> that's on <anon type="address"/> near us</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I don't think he wants erm his address er</u>
<u n="296" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no no er</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281">cos he'll he'll have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0015" trans="overlap">but in which <unclear>case</unclear> what I'm saying is you'll if you get her into a school you'd have to move to that area when you get accommodation yourself aren't you?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0015">so</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0015">let's go up here cos this is <unclear/> look they've got erm oh no that well <unclear/> that doesn't say what age groups they are</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0015">one of <pause dur="short"/> the best areas is</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well the guy I spoke to he said erm you have to apply online okay</u>
<u n="306" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281">so erm <pause dur="short"/> then they take into consideration the address you've given so</u>
<u n="308" who="S0015" trans="overlap">right let's see they want proof of a address</u>
<u n="309" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">is this the only cream cheese we've got?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0015">no darling down there look there's quite a bit</u>
<u n="311" who="S0281">okay well <unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh no you can use that anyway</u>
<u n="313" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="314" who="S0281">I can do that cos I got my bank statement</u>
<u n="315" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0015">proof of address for your child</u>
<u n="318" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> that goldfinch now aren't there?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0281">what has it got there? proof of address the different things they accept</u>
<u n="321" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm that</u>
<u n="322" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">can you see it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="323" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0281" trans="overlap">come the</u>
<u n="325" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><trunc>photo</trunc>photocopy of your child benefit statement or child tax credit showing the name of the child <unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh I haven't got that</u>
<u n="327" who="S0015">so can't do any of that at the moment</u>
<u n="328" who="S0281">haven't got a medical card <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got a tenancy agreement</u>
<u n="329" who="S0015">that that's what I'm saying it it you have to get the place to live erm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0281">get a place to live before</u>
<u n="331" who="S0015">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or you put if their address</u>
<u n="332" who="S0281">but I can't I can't apply until I've got a place to live</u>
<u n="333" who="S0015">well that's what I'm saying you'd have to say you're staying here</u>
<u n="334" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0015">and then when you co move you have to move to the area cos the school would be in there</u>
<u n="336" who="S0281">but what do I mean what <pause dur="short"/> how <pause dur="short"/> I I <unclear/> on the situation I mean I haven't even spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yet about joining</u>
<u n="337" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no no exactly</u>
<u n="338" who="S0281">but if I said she <unclear>wanted</unclear> to know about school and accommodation now if I say well</u>
<u n="339" who="S0015" trans="overlap">what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="341" who="S0015">well you don't need to tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what your <pause dur="short"/> exact circumstances are do you?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm no but it seems it</u>
<u n="343" who="S0015" trans="overlap">more than she told you</u>
<u n="344" who="S0281">no erm I I erm I need to get an address</u>
<u n="345" who="S0015">mm mm</u>
<u n="346" who="S0281">but er in if <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's <pause dur="short"/> I'd need to get an address before I can apply for a school essentially</u>
<u n="347" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well you've got an address you've got our address</u>
<u n="348" who="S0281" trans="overlap">because I yeah but I have got any of those documents</u>
<u n="349" who="S0015">no you haven't but if you're staying with family you don't need a</u>
<u n="350" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>ri</trunc> oh really?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0015">a a thingabob</u>
<u n="352" who="S0281">okay</u>
<u n="353" who="S0015">so you know <pause dur="short"/> we we don't have a a or or <unclear/> er most people don't have a tenancy agreement if they own it do they?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0281" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0015">so <trunc>tho</trunc> none of those people will bring that but what your big problem you haven't got anything for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0281">no I haven't given <unclear>up her</unclear> passport at the moment and that's what <unclear>that's</unclear> one</u>
<u n="357" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0281">on the phone said I well I can get her passport over in China</u>
<u n="359" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/> go to the Shanghai British consul</u>
<u n="361" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah that you'd have to do that before you do the application or anything but would she I mean it's it's all <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0281">but other I'd have to <pause dur="short"/> well I can't get the <trunc>p</trunc> I can't get the the passport before I apply</u>
<u n="363" who="S0015">no that's what I'm saying it's complicated <pause dur="short"/> erm oh so it's junior school isn't it we want? junior <pause dur="long"/> yeah <unclear>okay</unclear> that <pause dur="short"/> if we can enlarge that</u>
<u n="364" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0015">right so that's er <pause dur="short"/> erm you can see where erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives down there doesn't he? <pause dur="short"/> and we are <pause dur="short"/> we are <anon type="place"/> here we're in there okay?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0015">now oh they're not showing the schools very well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s school is right up here</u>
<u n="368" who="S0281">mm mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0015">and then <pause dur="short"/> oh here they are oh right it's showing them in <anon type="place"/> by the looks of things <pause dur="short"/> why? where have the schools gone then? <pause dur="short"/> oh it's just showing a map now</u>
<u n="370" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0015">that's strange cos they were there just now let's see if I can go back</u>
<u n="372" who="S0281">I don't know it seems very unlikely trying to juggle everything <unclear/> I haven't got her passport I haven't got an address <unclear>those</unclear></u>
<u n="373" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no that's that oh they had a <unclear>biggest thing</unclear> passport erm and documentation for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you haven't I did say that to you when you came you know make sure you've got a birth certificate and <unclear>things</unclear> like that so that you can erm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but that's all in Chinese isn't it?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0015">ah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0281">and it's on a family book</u>
<u n="377" who="S0015">right <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how that's that works out <pause dur="short"/> let's see <pause dur="short"/> as soon as you take that all the schools go that's weird <pause dur="short"/> look tried to <pause dur="short"/> look they're on there now <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I want</unclear> to get them back <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're the let's move that across</u>
<u n="378" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0015">right so <anon type="place"/> junior school that's the one up by us that's the one I was talking about</u>
<u n="380" who="S0281" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="381" who="S0015">I think that's called <anon type="address"/> it's in <anon type="address"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> there's the <anon type="place"/> which is up by <anon type="place"/> which is you know if you moved up there that wouldn't be too bad <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="place"/> school which is <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> where <anon type="place"/> is <pause dur="short"/> well there's <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/>'s not there <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's <unclear/> out <unclear/> right out <pause dur="short"/> you've got over here you've got <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> that's really weird because erm what's his name's not on that that's erm <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="place"/> isn't on there that's the one in <anon type="place"/> that's easy to get into <pause dur="short"/> that's quite a you know a <pause dur="short"/> you know a possibility er the <anon type="place"/> is a nice school <anon type="place"/> junior school that I can't think where that is <pause dur="short"/> I've actually got the reviews here look what's it say there?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well seeing seeing as I've got nothing no documents for it</u>
<u n="383" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="384" who="S0281">for her at all</u>
<u n="385" who="S0015">no</u>
<u n="386" who="S0281">I haven't even got photos</u>
<u n="387" who="S0015">to be honest you won't get her in for September because there's too much to do</u>
<u n="388" who="S0281">ah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0015">you would have to look at doing it after September you know cos you go over there in June</u>
<u n="390" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0015">and try and er you know get agreement from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you'd need it in writing that you she's prepared to let her come with you</u>
<u n="392" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0015"><unclear>to</unclear> live <pause dur="short"/> you'd need the passport you'd need all of that and once it's over here then you know you can bring that with you and then you know work on it from this end</u>
<u n="394" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0015">so then you'd be back I don't know when you'd be back but when you come back when does your your erm thing erm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0281" trans="overlap">visa expire?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0281">September</u>
<u n="399" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no no not your visa your erm <pause dur="short"/> your your erm Chinese visa expires then?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0281">mid September</u>
<u n="401" who="S0015">right</u>
<u n="402" who="S0281">but I I mean I I intend to apply for a resident's permit actually</u>
<u n="403" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how that how that works what you mean you can go backwards and forward anytime?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0281">well if I got yeah resident's permit I don't need a visa</u>
<u n="405" who="S0015">right okay <pause dur="short"/> so let's assume that you apply for that and but <unclear/> I was thinking more your concessions flight concessions when does that <trunc>e</trunc>end?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0281">oh <unclear/> six months <unclear/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0015">six months so it's when was it?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0281">so that was just before <trunc>ch</trunc> the ninth of December <pause dur="short"/> so that</u>
<u n="409" who="S0015" trans="overlap">so January February March April May June <pause dur="short"/> beginning of June</u>
<u n="410" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0015">that's so then mind you if you're bringing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> over you're gonna have to pay for her flight and</u>
<u n="412" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0015">you would only be on standby so you couldn't be on a standby</u>
<u n="414" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="415" who="S0015">and not get on and she got on</u>
<u n="416" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0015">so that you wouldn't wanna be doing that <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might be able to get you a <trunc>hot</trunc>hotline ticket they call them which is a bit of a reduction this is the erm <anon type="place"/> which shows <unclear/> that's not far from its erm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0281">so to to get this concessions I'll have to go back before the ninth of June</u>
<u n="419" who="S0015">yeah to be for you to yeah back there and be back here or whatever it be on concessions you've got to be back by the ninth of June to still be on</u>
<u n="420" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and be back here oh</u>
<u n="421" who="S0015">otherwise your flight back will get you won't get your flight back</u>
<u n="422" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well <unclear/> I I wouldn't be able to go over there do everything I've got to go over there for an operation</u>
<u n="423" who="S0015">I know</u>
<u n="424" who="S0281">yeah and I've got to apply for a passport and</u>
<u n="425" who="S0015" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0281">I'm not going won't be able to do it</u>
<u n="427" who="S0015">well firstly it depends when you go you know if you went earlier</u>
<u n="428" who="S0281">well yeah but she don't want me to to do that do you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tough innit what she wants</u>
<u n="430" who="S0281">well where am I gonna stay?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0015">mm that's the the problem <pause dur="short"/> well what happens when you go over in June? where are you gonna stay then?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0281">well I'll have to stay initially there but then got to up to <anon type="place"/> to <vocal desc="cough"/> er for <unclear>her</unclear> operation</u>
<u n="433" who="S0015" trans="overlap">to be honest if she came over here she would have her operation done free</u>
<u n="434" who="S0281">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> look at what</u>
<u n="435" who="S0015" trans="overlap">how urgent is that?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0281">yeah well I don't know and also have to <pause dur="short"/> whether it can wait another year</u>
<u n="437" who="S0015">what the operation?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0015">it wouldn't be necessarily be another year you know it just depends what what the problem was some surgery</u>
<u n="440" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0015">some surgery is quick some surgery is not</u>
<u n="442" who="S0281">but if I was gonna bring her over for next year</u>
<u n="443" who="S0015">I don't mean for next year if you didn't make September but came by Christmas or something <unclear/> to I don't mean wait another year I mean you know by Christmas you couldn't fix it all in June and get it all sorted out here by June <pause dur="short"/> but if you went over in June started sorting the paperwork in June <pause dur="short"/> in China came back say in July and then from September you would start sorting everything here <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0015">I know it's I know it's a lot and it seems seems a lot but you'd have to do it step-by-step the most complicated part to me is the Chinese bit cos they don't understand that any of that I understand what happens here what you need to do here and it you know most of it can happen quite quickly here</u>
<u n="446" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0015">once you've got that <unclear/> until you've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s permission passport <pause dur="short"/> and medical even if it is in Chinese</u>
<u n="448" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0015">erm and presumably <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will have her own passport and not a family book</u>
<u n="450" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0015">to do that <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would have to agree that wouldn't she? <pause dur="short"/> to get that done now if you can get past that then I think it's plain sailing this end from my point of view</u>
<u n="452" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0015">cos I understand what'll happen it you know it's it's quite difficult to coordinate it so the time is difficult but you'd be just say you'd apply for a school say with this as your residence and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s residence initially</u>
<u n="454" who="S0281">but it's no in that case <unclear/> the timing's too short to get everything organised to get entry in September <unclear/> she won't</u>
<u n="455" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well I I I don't know whether it is I don't know how long it would take to organise the Chinese end but for me that's the bit it seems insurmountable to me <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't know how it all works and as you say she hasn't got a passport currently she's on a family book you haven't got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s permission <pause dur="short"/> you'd need that in writing <pause dur="short"/> like you know probably signed by a solicitor or something I would imagine which gives permission for her to come <pause dur="short"/> erm and you also need <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to be on board and you know <pause dur="short"/> kind of <trunc>tho</trunc>those are the things I think I find difficult to</u>
<u n="456" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0015">visualise how that would work out if that all works out then and you bring <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> over then it I don't think it's you know you can do you can get accommodation within a week</u>
<u n="458" who="S0281">can you get emergency schooling and what would happen?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0015">well you wouldn't him you might not get in in the first week or two she'd probably <unclear>want</unclear> a week or two to</u>
<u n="460" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="461" who="S0015"><trunc>as</trunc>adjust</u>
<u n="462" who="S0281">no but I mean would it would it be a problem missing the school entry date in September?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0015">it would no why</u>
<u n="464" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no okay</u>
<u n="465" who="S0015"><unclear/> you know cos it'll be it'll be a new entry for her <unclear/> whenever she <unclear>leave</unclear></u>
<u n="466" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah sure</u>
<u n="467" who="S0015">so and to be honest it it could be <unclear>easier</unclear> and <trunc>g</trunc> because erm <pause dur="short"/> she'll be nine she won't be going in with a new cohort of kids that come from infants they go at seven seven plus</u>
<u n="468" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0015">right so she'll have missed that last year Sept last September they they all went up year six <unclear/> in year seven at seven and eight they transfer so she won't be going in with the new cohort of kids she'll be going in new when they go up to the next class</u>
<u n="470" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0015">erm and erm <pause dur="short"/> usually what they would do is they'd give some children the responsibility of being <trunc>hom</trunc> a mentor you know a couple of children just show her round and look after her in school and be her mentor in school so for missing September it's not like it's</u>
<u n="472" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0015">like everyone's gonna be new in September</u>
<u n="474" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0015">they'll be already in their classrooms by by then by the time she's nearly nine erm <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that so much is set whether it's September or Christmas it's gonna be new for her</u>
<u n="476" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0015">and quite quite difficult for for her but at the same time hopefully it'll be quite interesting and <pause dur="short"/> tell you what the air'll be a lot better for her</u>
<u n="478" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0015">and erm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0015">and and you know I <pause dur="short"/> that to me the bit in the in China I don't understand enough about so I can't say yeah that'll work out alright I'll just I don't know how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will react I don't know how long it takes to get a passport I don't know whether she <vocal desc="laugh"/> she was signed for a passport and let me take her or you know I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0281">mm well I've got a <pause dur="short"/> no I'll talk to her this weekend I'll I'll ask her about what she thinks about it cos <unclear/> every time I <pause dur="short"/> nearly every time <unclear>walking</unclear> to something different changing the situation and</u>
<u n="483" who="S0015">that's right cos so what what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> is turmoil</u>
<u n="484" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0015">you know</u>
<u n="486" who="S0281">well it's not it's been pretty <vocal desc="cough"/> steady so far but the plan is now that we can't afford to keep her in this school and so erm <unclear/> that's why she's talking about going back to <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0015">so he's not able to support her?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0281">I've got no idea</u>
<u n="489" who="S0015">I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I I but she strikes me as being the sort who erm money would be</u>
<u n="490" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0015">very important to her</u>
<u n="492" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0015">and she's I think when she stops sinking er stops to think and think well actually do you know what this isn't such a really good arrangement <pause dur="short"/> moving to <anon type="place"/> not</u>
<u n="494" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="495" who="S0015">not not having the school any more and and having to work to support herself really that's what she's saying</u>
<u n="496" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0015">and that's if he goes you know so right now it might be a <pause dur="short"/> you know not a not a erm a lot of a permanent arrangement it might be an idea that she's toying with and trying to struggle with</u>
<u n="498" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0015">and that's why I say to I think you should write an email to her saying I'm really pleased that you think you've found someone you want to be with and that's that's really great erm I hope he's able to support you erm as you've always you know the way you've been used to</u>
<u n="500" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0015">and that erm and you know I'd like to think he could pay for erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s you know to support <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you've selected someone who can look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well <pause dur="short"/> but I'm concerned that if that's the case why are you having to consider going to <anon type="place"/>? which would move you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0015">if he's not able to look after you</u>
<u n="504" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no to put all that in an email her English isn't all that good I don't know if she'd understand all that</u>
<u n="505" who="S0015" trans="overlap">isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> well isn't it all that good? it's not enough to understand that?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0281">well speaking's better than reading</u>
<u n="507" who="S0015">right mm <pause dur="short"/> you should get someone to translate it for her or</u>
<u n="508" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="509" who="S0015">explain it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> in basic words couldn't we?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0015">but that's what I my thing would be is like question what she's doing make her question what she's doing and check whether she is absolutely certain about it <pause dur="short"/> careful that iron's on darling</u>
<u n="512" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I turned it off</u>
<u n="513" who="S0015">that would be my first reaction</u>
<u n="514" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0015">and then you can say if that is the case and you feel you erm what there is a future for you with this chap <pause dur="short"/> erm I would be happy to have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> here and erm you can have your you know opportunity to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whenever you want <pause dur="short"/> and she she'd have a good <trunc>ed</trunc> free education <pause dur="short"/> hm? <pause dur="short"/> free education free erm cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rang didn't she? free education free medical <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="516" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="517" who="S0015">and opportunities that she hasn't might not have in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0015">I don't know what it's like there but you you know I'm just going by what you say it's a country place is it?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0281">mm yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0281"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="523" who="S0015">I I I can't imagine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she's trendy</u>
<u n="524" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0015">she likes nice clothes will she live in a place like that?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0281">well there's <unclear/> always cities and <unclear/> you know just so <anon type="place"/> is a province it isn't all that rich but then there are cities and and cities and towns and all these places to go and and</u>
<u n="527" who="S0015">is there? close by?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0015">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know but you know that she'd be happy for her to is there schools there that look decent I suppose?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0281"><unclear/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0015">erm it's I'm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0015">I <unclear>would</unclear> put questions in her mind about whether it's a permanent arrangement er you know right now she's you know think she's fallen in love with someone but it was very different when you were paying the bills</u>
<u n="534" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0015">and suddenly you're not</u>
<u n="536" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0015">and now she's thinking hang on <pause dur="short"/> so what does she want now? you to come back and eek out an existence and pay the bills?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0281">no I don't think erm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear>or</unclear> look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0281">I don't we haven't even talked about that other than it's I don't think er</u>
<u n="541" who="S0015">what's what's always see I don't know her but I'm just trying to think what her motives are what sort of person she is</u>
<u n="542" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0015">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> looking at it from a different aspect <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> whether she whether it is whether she changes her mind frequently or</u>
<u n="544" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh god yeah like the wind</u>
<u n="545" who="S0015">well there you go so this this idea might just be a</u>
<u n="546" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh sorry</u>
<u n="547" who="S0015">sort of a a threat to you at the moment</u>
<u n="548" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0015">that might be her saying oh you know I <pause dur="short"/> are you gonna see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="550" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yep</u>
<u n="551" who="S0015">well tell her safe journey</u>
<u n="552" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes I will</u>
<u n="553" who="S0015"><unclear/></u>
<u n="554" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0281">pardon?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0015">I said and <unclear>tell her</unclear> hurry home</u>
<u n="557" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yep</u>
<u n="558" who="S0015">not back till Saturday <pause dur="short"/> erm so I don't know that would be my first thing that I would suggest put it in an email sort of some questions to her to make her question herself and and say you know I'm happy for you if that's what you want to do if if you think it's right if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and you think it's right for you and that you can be looked after <unclear>kind of</unclear> like <pause dur="short"/> and then she'll she'll be annoyed by that cos she won't like it she won't like it you saying yeah okay go ahead that's what effectively you're saying <pause dur="short"/> and then you can say alternative if you don't think he's gonna be there forever you don't think he's gonna be a good father erm I erm I can look after him over here</u>
<u n="559" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">did work it well</u>
<u n="560" who="S0015">and that's what you say she can have free school erm and I'll get <unclear/> that <pause dur="short"/> where we can live near a park where she can go to the park and the sea <unclear/> send it to her</u>
<u n="561" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0015">and free free medical <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>manta</trunc><trunc>manta</trunc> fantastic opportunity for someone who can speak <trunc>Mand</trunc> speak and write Mandarin</u>
<u n="563" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0015">the future here everyone want you know all private schools like <anon type="place"/> college they they they're all doing Mandarin</u>
<u n="565" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0015">cos it's the language that is gonna be needed in the future so I don't know that's how I would play it with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="567" who="S0281">yeah okay</u>
<u n="568" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">right I shall return</u>
<u n="569" who="S0015">okay see you in a while darling</u>
<u n="570" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">in a short while</u>
<u n="571" who="S0281" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="572" who="S0015">drive carefully</u>
<u n="573" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<event desc="m leaves"/>
<u n="574" who="S0015">well that's how I'd do it I'd send her an email question it making her question her you know what's going on or think about the future rather than oh what what can I do to get out of this situation? think about where what the reality is she's committing she's committing herself to <pause dur="short"/> so to say then you know if if if it's not if you think there's any doubt in your mind that it might not work <pause dur="short"/> I will have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> while you work you <trunc>wor</trunc>work out your problems</u>
<u n="575" who="S0281">well I don't wanna say that cos <trunc>that</trunc>that'll annoy her erm I I what about saying <pause dur="short"/> erm that er well just ask her about <unclear/> not the the possibility would she be agreeable to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> coming over here now erm rather than later</u>
<u n="576" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0281">er because that way erm I I'll be with her and I can look after her and I can get her into school and erm <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> there was free health and free schools and the the air's much cleaner et cetera et cetera but apart from that because she already well why don't you get a place to live and I said well I already said that I can't get a place to live until I get a job because people will <unclear/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0281">who rent properties so now I'm gonna have to change that</u>
<u n="580" who="S0015">mm <unclear/> say I I now found I can</u>
<u n="581" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well well say that</u>
<u n="582" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><trunc>an</trunc>anyone can</u>
<u n="583" who="S0281">I can if I if I've got a child</u>
<u n="584" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0281">if I've got a child then I can</u>
<u n="586" who="S0015" trans="overlap">because she'll think you only want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for the <unclear/></u>
<u n="587" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's true</u>
<u n="588" who="S0015">you say the situation is that I've not just found that I am eligible and I can rent a place <pause dur="short"/> here</u>
<u n="589" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0015">erm I've now found that I you know some contacts to help me find accommodation <pause dur="short"/> oh thank you erm and and erm see if she will erm <pause dur="short"/> and say and and I but I won't I won't do that unless I know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gonna be able to come</u>
<u n="591" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0015">it's you know I I won't bother with the expense if if I if <unclear/> but if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming if you allow <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to come then I would erm be able to get a place</u>
<u n="593" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0015">why did you say to her you couldn't get a place then without cos you <unclear>know she's</unclear> got a job if that's not</u>
<u n="595" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well she's cos she's pushing me about in</u>
<u n="596" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="597" who="S0281">but er to find somewhere to live</u>
<u n="598" who="S0015">but why was she <trunc>fi</trunc> pushing you? why does she care where you live?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0281">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="600" who="S0015">you say well you should have said well I <unclear>quite</unclear> you know I quite like staying with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="601" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well yeah well <unclear/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0015">he's good company</u>
<u n="603" who="S0281">well yeah and <trunc>ther</trunc>there's</u>
<u n="604" who="S0015" trans="overlap">you know why should she care where you live?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0015">so you you know <trunc>ha</trunc>having spoken to you erm I've decided to start looking for somewhere to live and I can <unclear>find</unclear> I've you know several opportunity</u>
<u n="607" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0015">and send her pictures from the internet <unclear>from</unclear> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know they're all over <pause dur="short"/> so she now thinks you're not able to find <unclear>over</unclear> there good support <unclear/> that's what she's gonna say but you haven't got anywhere to live <pause dur="short"/> gonna be her first thing so maybe you say erm for my part</u>
<u n="609" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and she's gonna ask me about how much money I've got</u>
<u n="610" who="S0015">well say erm going down fast</u>
<u n="611" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="612" who="S0015">but I get</u>
<u n="613" who="S0281">but that's gonna be another bone of contention erm money in the future <unclear/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0015">well her</u>
<u n="615" who="S0281" trans="overlap">cos I I won't be able to get myself my hands on my property cos it's <unclear>all</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> ones in her name solely and the other's in both our names</u>
<u n="616" who="S0015">well you're never going to go back <unclear/> are you now?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="618" who="S0015">and you</u>
<u n="619" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="620" who="S0015">whatever happens you're never going to get that from her</u>
<u n="621" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="622" who="S0015">cos you know <pause dur="short"/> she she's got it and she she <unclear>knew</unclear> that from the beginning</u>
<u n="623" who="S0281">mm yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0015">so <pause dur="short"/> erm I think you should say right no I I erm after talking to you and asking why I haven't got a <unclear>flat</unclear> I decided I ought to really look more you know more closely and I found a can there are lots of properties</u>
<u n="625" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that that yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0015">that I can rent</u>
<u n="627" who="S0281">but there won't until under no</u>
<u n="628" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah there's no point unless I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to come erm I quite staying with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's good company and erm <pause dur="short"/> but if I thought <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was gonna come I erm rent a place and find it all in the locality <pause dur="short"/> a good school for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0015">so <pause dur="short"/> but you ought to ask your questions you know about is this guy gonna look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? is he do you think he's gonna has he got a family <pause dur="short"/> already? you know so many questions you know you know you're thinking about your future with him so that's really good I hope he's going has he got already got a family? is he going to be a good father? <pause dur="short"/> you know is he going to look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well? I would be asking all those questions and she needs to ask herself them <pause dur="short"/> she's probably not thinking about them but she shouldn't</u>
<u n="631" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I think it's better to to put this in an email rather than</u>
<u n="632" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I do because she would take stop and come back to it and backwards and forwards</u>
<u n="633" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="634" who="S0015">if you say it over the phone it's kind of the heat of the moment</u>
<u n="635" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="636" who="S0015">you can't remember everything that's said</u>
<u n="637" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0015">but if by in an email people go back to it and read it again and it will be a a reminder to her that they're you know right now it seemed like a good idea to her but what is the reality? and she may not wanna tell you if he's got a family or not</u>
<u n="639" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0015">what his financial situation but if you ask her she doesn't have to answer but she'll be thinking well it's really bad I can't tell him or it's really good I'll tell him <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but I I think to be honest the only way people <trunc>remain</trunc> you can stop and think about it properly is if it's in writing because it's all in the heat of the moment you remember snippets of conversation but not all of it</u>
<u n="641" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="642" who="S0015">not the fine detail erm and you've you've only remembered the bit that you try to bat off <pause dur="short"/> you know if you say on well you know it's either <unclear/> she'll remember what her retaliation is but later on and she might be angry at it but when she's got an email she can't be angry and retaliate she might be angry about it but she'll go back and look at it <pause dur="short"/> she'll go back and chew it over in her mind and it's all there everything you said so you do have to carefully word it</u>
<u n="643" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0015">so I'd if I was you I'd <trunc>emai</trunc> er er do it in a erm word a word</u>
<u n="645" who="S0281" trans="overlap">draft</u>
<u n="646" who="S0015">yeah <trunc>wo</trunc> and word document until you get it saying exactly what you want to say in a simply form simple form that will make her think deeply about her actions and what where you know where it's leading no just this week this month next year but long term and then once you've done that you can finish it off by saying you might even start it by saying after talking to you about you know renting a place I decided I ought to look into it and I found I can so there are quite a number of places I'm looking at</u>
<u n="647" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0015">erm so end that bit then say I'm happy that you are you know gonna have someone that you're happy with erm I hope he's you know a nice person who'll look after you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> be able to keep you erm <pause dur="short"/> but I don't understand if he is able to why you're moving to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0281">well that's cos the money for the school</u>
<u n="650" who="S0015">I know why</u>
<u n="651" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0015">I know cos he can't afford to pay for the school</u>
<u n="653" who="S0281">mm <unclear/> she would expect me to</u>
<u n="654" who="S0015" trans="overlap">but <unclear/> what I'm saying hm?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0281">she'll expect me to I'm surprised she hadn't asked me already</u>
<u n="656" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well she probably is but you just say like tough innit? you you find someone else</u>
<u n="657" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0015">is he gonna look after you? is he gonna look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I can look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if he doesn't want to but I'm not gonna</u>
<u n="659" who="S0281">well I don't want him to I wanna <unclear>look after her</unclear></u>
<u n="660" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I know but you you that's she she doesn't you don't want her to know that do you? cos you'll go well you're not having <unclear>it</unclear> obviously you can pay and you can whatever but you kind of do it in a much more subtle way as a you know I I'm I'm really pleased you found someone who can look after you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and and you know pay pay to support you but I don't understand why you need to to go to <anon type="place"/> if he's able to look after you <pause dur="short"/> and basically he can't can he? cos she's gotta go to work she's gotta go there for schooling <pause dur="short"/> so then you say if it you know are you sure it's gonna work out is is he gonna be there for the long term I hope so but you know what if all else fails now I'm getting my my life together her and I'm you know I've got I'm gonna rent a flat if that is a problem I would have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to bring her up here where she would have free school free medical fresh air and quite a large family of</u>
<u n="661" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I'd like to <unclear/> here the er erm accent it more on the that I want her rather than the money</u>
<u n="662" who="S0015">well personally</u>
<u n="663" who="S0281" trans="overlap">if he's not gonna pay for it then I the I will take her <unclear/> it's not the way to go about it I think</u>
<u n="664" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I I think it isn't actually <unclear/> I think cos she'll go well you're not having I'm not doing anything to please you</u>
<u n="665" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0015">so it's not about that what you've got to say is kind of like erm make it clear that you're gonna get your life together here you're gonna rent a flat no matter what and if he wants to look after you two but he obviously can't so you point that out in a subtle way</u>
<u n="667" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0015">erm and she start going oh hang on a minute</u>
<u n="669" who="S0281">but then she might question well why do I want to apply for a resident's permit in China</u>
<u n="670" who="S0015">so that you can go backwards and forwards</u>
<u n="671" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0015">to see her</u>
<u n="673" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I can be closer to her</u>
<u n="674" who="S0015">well you you can go regularly to see her</u>
<u n="675" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0015">and because she told you to <pause dur="short"/> I've listened to what you said apply for a resident's erm I'll do that so that I can <trunc>ho</trunc>hopefully go backwards and forwards to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm and I'm renting a flat here because I you're right I do need to set up on my own</u>
<u n="677" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0015">you're right I'm doing what you said now your <pause dur="short"/> let's talk about you kind of attitude this is point out where the shortcomings might be in her plan in a subtle way and then back it up and say however whatever your plans you know if you don't think it's gonna be as easy as that I am happy to bring <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up here where she would have all these positive cos you you don't wanna point out what you want you wanna point out what's good for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos</u>
<u n="679" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="680" who="S0015">she doesn't care what you want</u>
<u n="681" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="682" who="S0015">she cares what hopefully cares with what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will have</u>
<u n="683" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="684" who="S0015">more than what you want you know you wanna be with your child and tough <vocal desc="laugh"/> as far as she's concerned but she should be listening to what's best for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="686" who="S0015">and she's moving to <anon type="place"/> for school</u>
<u n="687" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="688" who="S0015">you know but she still hasn't got free medical she still hasn't got fresh air although is it more better air over there? I don't know</u>
<u n="689" who="S0281">erm yeah it's better than</u>
<u n="690" who="S0015">where they are</u>
<u n="691" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0015">mm <pause dur="short"/> so and then you say when I when I find a place or you know when I'm I'm <unclear/> when you <trunc>doc</trunc> I you know I'm you can send her stuff that you might want to look at I'm gonna look at this today <pause dur="short"/> let her see do it more by email than your phone calls you don't have to wait a week to speak to her</u>
<u n="693" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0015">where it gets all heated and</u>
<u n="695" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="696" who="S0015">difficult you can say what you want to say to her without the retaliation</u>
<u n="697" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0015">though that that'll be how I would play it <pause dur="short"/> very much more subtle saying you're pleased for her <pause dur="short"/> which will annoy her</u>
<u n="699" who="S0281"><unclear/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0015">won't it? cos you're not you know desperate you're giving her permission to go ahead and move to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="701" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="702" who="S0015">aren't you? you know I'm not gonna fight you go go to <anon type="place"/> let him <unclear/> look after you <pause dur="short"/> sound like it I mean either way she's gonna do it</u>
<u n="703" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0015">so better to her think well actually he is happy for me to do that and I'm gonna have to do it he's not coming and he's not gonna pay for everything again <pause dur="short"/> and you can say now you've got your pension details set up and your money tax credits coming in erm and you'll find out <unclear>you</unclear> situations improved a little</u>
<u n="705" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well she's gonna yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's gonna she's gonna ask about the money I said well if you can't find a job where where are you gonna get the money from?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0015">well you say and I get pension credits over here we get benefits if we're not able to work and that's why you know you can survive</u>
<u n="707" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="708" who="S0015"><trunc>we</trunc> it's only on you you get it you can't give it to her</u>
<u n="709" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="710" who="S0015">so she can't have it it's you know I get I get help with whatever I need</u>
<u n="711" who="S0281" trans="overlap">if she'll say you won't you won't have enough money to put pay the flat and if you're not working</u>
<u n="712" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well say I get benefits</u>
<u n="713" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="714" who="S0015">well it's what you do you get benefits if you aren't earning enough then you get help to live everybody does <pause dur="short"/> well <unclear>she'll</unclear> know that I mean you know you you <unclear/> that answer to her <pause dur="short"/> I'll help you do it</u>
<u n="715" who="S0281">okay</u>
<u n="716" who="S0015">you you need to do that quite quickly send that to her to give her something to think about <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s presumably still at school is she?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0281">yeah she was she's on holiday at the moment but erm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but at the end <pause dur="short"/> of that</u>
<u n="719" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> next week she goes back</u>
<u n="720" who="S0015">she send she's happy to send her off week after week to a school where she doesn't you know she doesn't know the teachers <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't know the teachers yeah she's got lots of friends and she's got get to know the teachers but you know it it's not much different except she doesn't see her every week <pause dur="short"/> but she can see her by Skype the same as you do</u>
<u n="721" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0015">can't she? <pause dur="short"/> the only thing I your big problem will be if you get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> over here I think she will take quite a while to settle and I think she'll say I want my mum</u>
<u n="723" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm yeah I'm sure</u>
<u n="724" who="S0015">I wanna go home <pause dur="short"/> that will be the biggest sorting the the the documentation in China</u>
<u n="725" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear>of course</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0015">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> settling in period where with the best will in the world even if she isn't happy <unclear/> there she she'll want to be back to normal</u>
<u n="727" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear/> certain she's always had her mother you see</u>
<u n="728" who="S0015">yeah but she hasn't</u>
<u n="729" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that's that's</u>
<u n="730" who="S0015">she's she's at school all the time</u>
<u n="731" who="S0281">well that's it and</u>
<u n="732" who="S0015">I don't they're not close you seem to say</u>
<u n="733" who="S0281">no <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know so a little girl needs her mother but as I say she she's not been a brilliant mother</u>
<u n="734" who="S0015">oh and what about her grandmother? is she close to them</u>
<u n="735" who="S0281">mm not really</u>
<u n="736" who="S0015">no <pause dur="short"/> not been part of her life</u>
<u n="737" who="S0281">not much no</u>
<u n="738" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no exactly <pause dur="short"/> so you know that's a huge upheaval for her anyway so what she's talking about is a huge upheaval erm and possibly a very uncertain life with this guy <pause dur="short"/> and what happens if this guy isn't around any more <pause dur="short"/> is I dunno what wage is and what erm what erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can do to earn a living is she able to earn enough to support herself and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? would she live with her parents? what would she do?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0281">I don't know</u>
<u n="740" who="S0015">I can't see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> living that kind of life what from what you tell me about her</u>
<u n="741" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="742" who="S0015">and and I bet she can't really and when when you talked about going to <anon type="place"/> no where did you</u>
<u n="743" who="S0281"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0015">no when you talked about going to where your flat is</u>
<u n="745" who="S0281">oh the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0015">yeah she didn't want to go there</u>
<u n="747" who="S0281"><unclear/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0015">why?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0281">well now I know why</u>
<u n="750" who="S0015">why? because of a man</u>
<u n="751" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0015">right so now that man is on the scene but she's going to have to go to <anon type="place"/> isn't that further?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0281">oh it is a lot further</u>
<u n="754" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="755" who="S0281">so I'd I I assume that er she's worked all that out and that he's going</u>
<u n="756" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="757" who="S0281">but er</u>
<u n="758" who="S0015">so he says</u>
<u n="759" who="S0281">I don't know I don't know</u>
<u n="760" who="S0015">but then that's what you say to her you know I presume you've worked it alright you've given consideration for all these things and that you're all going you'll be go there and <unclear>they'll</unclear> look after you you'll both work is what sort of jobs are available in <anon type="place"/> is she able to what is she able to do to earn a living?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0281">yeah I'm gonna have to put all this in very basic terms because <unclear/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0015">no but I'm asking you what sort of job would she do?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0281">I I've got no idea</u>
<u n="764" who="S0015">what she's capable of doing what <unclear>sort of</unclear> what would she turn to?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0281"><unclear>god</unclear> knows</u>
<u n="766" who="S0015">so you know is it is it good pay over there? or <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> all of those things she to be thinking about and if you ask the questions <pause dur="short"/> she'll start thinking more deeply about what she's doing</u>
<u n="767" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0015">and she might then say well actually I can have my cake and eat it if you have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0015">it depends what sort of person she I don't know <unclear>her</unclear></u>
<u n="771" who="S0281">okay <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0015" trans="overlap">all you can do is suss it out to <unclear/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0281" trans="overlap">right well <unclear>draft</unclear> it</u>
<u n="774" who="S0015" trans="overlap">and <unclear/> went up with saw</u>
<u n="775" who="S0281">erm <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="776" who="S0015" trans="overlap">and trying to get some questions together</u>
<u n="777" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="778" who="S0015">and we're you know and then we can phrase it in a way that you think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will understand</u>
<u n="779" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0015">and <pause dur="short"/> go from there that will be my advice <pause dur="short"/> question her <pause dur="short"/> free her up to go and do it cos I don't think she really wants to do that either <pause dur="short"/> and then offer a way out</u>
<u n="781" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="782" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">is it alright this cream?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0281">it's good er</u>
<u n="784" who="S0015" trans="overlap">pardon I yes darling</u>
<u n="785" who="S0281">yeah it's a good strategy</u>
<u n="786" who="S0015">I'm good at strategy <pause dur="short"/> get get your resident's done and tell her you're doing it so that you can come and see it erm <unclear>kids</unclear> see it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whenever you can afford it <pause dur="short"/> you're gonna get a flat here cos you're right I should get my get my life together fortunately my pension now is you know and if I don't have enough money the benefits will kick in and pay my rent <pause dur="short"/> won't pay all of it <unclear>it'll</unclear> pay most of it erm <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna you know start looking forward rather than</u>
<u n="787" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0015">in other words you go forward I'll go forward <pause dur="short"/> but if you want you know I'll have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> offer's always there <pause dur="short"/> so I think that would be my suggestion</u>
<u n="789" who="S0281">okay</u>
<u n="790" who="S0015">and then <pause dur="short"/> if she's</u>
<u n="791" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="792" who="S0015">what darling?</u>
<u n="793" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you've got <unclear>start</unclear></u>
<u n="794" who="S0015">chocolate brownies mm I like my chocolate brownie <pause dur="short"/> getting <unclear/> don't they?</u>
<u n="795" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0015"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then once all that is done if she says <trunc>an</trunc> say well if she says you know okay in which case you can have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> to live with you you you say right okay well in which case erm we'll look at the paperwork when I come <pause dur="short"/> tell her you wanna take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on holiday</u>
<u n="797" who="S0281">if she wants me to she already asked me what are you gonna do with her? <unclear/> ah well I'll take her to the <trunc>cinem</trunc> the the the er seaside</u>
<u n="798" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0281"><unclear/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0015">so you should have probably told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that</u>
<u n="801" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0015">mm <pause dur="short"/> well you could offer <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can come and live at the seaside</u>
<u n="803" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="804" who="S0015">and see the sea every day if you want to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="805" who="S0281">okay well thanks for that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0015">well we'll do it I'll I'll start on it and then if it's any good you can look at it</u>
<u n="807" who="S0281" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="808" who="S0015">and you can chop and change it and write it so in a way that you think she will</u>
<u n="809" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well <unclear>watch this then</unclear></u>
<u n="810" who="S0015">understand</u>
<u n="811" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0015">and erm go from there</u>
<u n="813" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0015">and then once once you get that bar once you get that passport thing sorted then <unclear/> which I think <unclear/> for me the only thing I can't I can't visualise how you would do it or how it would work out for you once you've done that then you worry about schools and accommodation <pause dur="short"/> otherwise you'd be paying for it</u>
<u n="815" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0015">you know</u>
<u n="817" who="S0281">well yeah one slip of the tongue and <unclear/> she's up for it first</u>
<u n="818" who="S0015">yeah she might be and if she's not you've offered and you know the she has the option at any time that if she changes her mind</u>
<u n="819" who="S0281">that's excellent</u>
<u n="820" who="S0015">just leave it on the <unclear>table</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'll <unclear>sort it</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so I think you know I think she might go well that's you know what? that might be better for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="822" who="S0015">and who knows? we'll see won't we?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0015">if I was you I wouldn't bank on anything with her but</u>
<u n="825" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="826" who="S0015">you know you just don't know what her thoughts are sounds like you don't know and I don't know cos I don't know <unclear>her</unclear> cos I don't know</u>
<u n="827" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="828" who="S0015">never met her but</u>
<u n="829" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="830" who="S0015">could be that this bloke could raise her if it's a good idea</u>
<u n="831" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="832" who="S0015">isn't it?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0281">well <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure that er in many ways that she'd prefer me to <pause dur="short"/> for her not to have to have the er</u>
<u n="834" who="S0015">responsibilities</u>
<u n="835" who="S0281" trans="overlap">responsibility and the inconvenience of it all <pause dur="short"/> although she said her mother can look after her in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0015">well</u>
<u n="837" who="S0281">but it's a horrible farm dirty old <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="838" who="S0015">is it?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0281"><trunc>build</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="841" who="S0281">it really is disgusting er</u>
<u n="842" who="S0015">but if you sound as though you're worried about that she'll think that she's got a chance that you'll cough up and stop her that from happening</u>
<u n="843" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="844" who="S0015">but if you say well you know perhaps it is best you know it's the only way you'll be able to do it kind of thing <unclear/> if I'm not helping</u>
<u n="845" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="846" who="S0015">will you you know <pause dur="short"/> your decision you do it I'm not gonna help but if all else fails <pause dur="short"/> you know I'll still have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="847" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="848" who="S0015">but you first of all need to make clear that you erm <pause dur="short"/> are in a position to support her and get a flat so I think your email should start with you're right I've listened to everything you've said I've decided I will go ahead and apply for my residency so that I can see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> regularly and I'm gonna get my act together here my life together and I can get a flat I'm gonna you know do that as soon as I can erm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0281">but I won't do it unless I <unclear>I don't know</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> well I can do it I mean</u>
<u n="850" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no I don't think you just say that you know that but it's only if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes you say I can do this and I'll you know you haven't gotta do it</u>
<u n="851" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0015">just tell her you're going to</u>
<u n="853" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0015">I've looked at several flats and there's some nice places <pause dur="short"/> close to the beach <pause dur="short"/> near parks erm <pause dur="short"/> and so you know I'm I'm gonna do that decided you know she might be going oh hang on a minute he might find someone else and not wanna have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know you don't know what goes on in people's I don't know if I er <unclear/> but you sort of think what <unclear/> think how she's thinking</u>
<u n="855" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> alright well we'll do that later then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I mean if if you were a father that didn't care you could never reply to her again</u>
<u n="857" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="858" who="S0015">she'd never find you</u>
<u n="859" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="860" who="S0015">but it's only that she's got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that that you you know need to keep in contact with her</u>
<u n="861" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0015">and don't forget she's got those flats</u>
<u n="863" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah right <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
