<text id="S5QP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0687 S0688</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Café Venice</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Talking about what they were going to do for the day, What Venice used to be like , Food and drink of Venice</topics>
		<activity>Having coffee talking about what Venice has to offer</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0687">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bolton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- A-level</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0688">
				<exactage>53</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bolton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>53 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Midwife</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0687">what did I think what?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0688">a guy walking in with purpose</u>
<u n="3" who="S0687">yeah he just look looked like he knew where he was going so there's the galleries page twenty-four to twenty-five</u>
<u n="4" who="S0688" trans="overlap">do you think they're saying goodbye? goodbye they say <foreign lang="ita">ciao ciao</foreign></u>
<u n="5" who="S0687">yeah oh yeah maybe maybe it's like bye bye</u>
<u n="6" who="S0688">yeah <foreign lang="ita">ciao ciao</foreign></u>
<u n="7" who="S0687">erm Academia Galleries a dazzling collection of masterpieces spanning the full development of venetian art form Byzantine to Renaissance Baroque and Rococo the Gallery Del Academia is Venice's equivalent of the Uffizi in Florence Giovanni Piazzetta started the collection in seventeen fifty to service models for the art school in in eighteen 0 seven it was boosted by Napoleon with the additions of works from supressed churches basically an art gallery <pause dur="short"/> bothered?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0688">what about the Peggy Guggenheim? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0687">number ten</u>
<u n="10" who="S0688">we did go before it'd be just nice to see the outside again</u>
<u n="11" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0688">but if we get to the Rialto bridge and the market's still on</u>
<u n="13" who="S0687">the delightfully spacious light filled Collezione Peggy Guggenheim is home to works by more than two hundred contemporary artists representing powerful avant-garde movements such as cubism futurism and surrealism I think I've read that already</u>
<u n="14" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0687">it's another art museum isn't it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0688">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0687">admission fourteen euros</u>
<u n="18" who="S0688">okay</u>
<u n="19" who="S0687">erm so we'll do Rialto market and then Campo Santa Marguerite is one of them a wonderful square bustling with life day and night thanks to its market stalls and outdoor cafes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0688">okay that sounds nice</u>
<u n="21" who="S0687">an added bonus is its many architectural styles page thirty-two to thirty-three <pause dur="short"/> this cheery picturesque square in the district of Dorsoduro is a hive of activity day in day out it owes its name to the Christian martyr Saint Margaret of Antioch possibly a fictitious figure but highly popular in medieval times patron saint of expectant mothers she is depicted in a niche in the square's northern wall with her <trunc>e</trunc>emblem the dragon the square's capacious form exploited by local children on bicycles and inline skates is due to ambitious enlargement projects in the eighteen hundreds but it's opened up the south end by filling in canals</u>
<u n="22" who="S0688">how far away is that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0687">just keep you finger on that page would you? <pause dur="long"/> we are somewhere here mum</u>
<u n="24" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0687">can you see? it's over there</u>
<u n="26" who="S0688">so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0687">if we go to Rialto and then back across</u>
<u n="28" who="S0688">okay</u>
<u n="29" who="S0687">that way <pause dur="long"/> and then that's pretty much it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0688">is that this on the map?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0687">yeah that's that and then that's Santa Maria a gothic interior grandiose works of art lies in store behind this church's brick façade is there so that's kind of on the way</u>
<u n="32" who="S0688">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0687">yeah it just seems a bit I don't know exploitative doesn't it?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0688">do you mean the prices?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0687">yeah and the grumpiness it just doesn't feel as relaxed as you know today as yesterday</u>
<u n="36" who="S0688">mm <pause dur="long"/> I suppose some of it's culture</u>
<u n="37" who="S0687">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0688">some of it's they don't need to work very hard some of it's their job I don't know but I I know what you mean</u>
<u n="39" who="S0687">did you feel like that last time you came?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0688">er yeah yeah but it's sweet isn't it?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0687">mm mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0688">and I think I remember in erm touristy areas like erm Lucca and erm what was it called on the hill begins with S? <pause dur="long"/> can't remember what it's called where I was talking about this morning</u>
<u n="43" who="S0687">you were talking about Lucca</u>
<u n="44" who="S0688">yeah no but we were talking about I was telling I was <trunc>to</trunc> I was talking to the lady yesterday</u>
<u n="45" who="S0687">Lake Alta?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0688">no it's Sienna</u>
<u n="47" who="S0687">Sienna</u>
<u n="48" who="S0688">Sienna erm <pause dur="long"/> it's all just a bit touristy really and</u>
<u n="49" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0688">but I do think a lot of it's culture</u>
<u n="51" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0688">you know it's like you're on holiday and you want someone to be nice to you don't you?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0688">the guy was quite nice that first coffee shop this morning where he was explaining to me about Fritz</u>
<u n="55" who="S0687">yeah <pause dur="short"/> our nicest meal was that first night in Mestre wasn't it?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0688">mm <pause dur="long"/> and we can go back there tonight if you like? go back to Mestre</u>
<u n="57" who="S0687">yeah for dinner</u>
<u n="58" who="S0688">if you want</u>
<u n="59" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0688">we just get off the bus</u>
<u n="61" who="S0687">yeah if we stay on the bus until further up</u>
<u n="62" who="S0688">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos we've nothing to go back well there's nothing on your we can't watch anything on your laptop</u>
<u n="63" who="S0687">no</u>
<u n="64" who="S0688">erm <pause dur="short"/> we just need to speak to the boys don't we?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0687">there's not much to pack up really cos we've not really unpacked have we?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0688">mm <pause dur="short"/> let's do that</u>
<u n="67" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0688">unless we see somewhere here that grabs us</u>
<u n="69" who="S0687">yeah or what were those ones?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0688">oh yeah the places that I saw</u>
<u n="71" who="S0687" trans="overlap">shall we have a look? romantic spots we'll give that a miss</u>
<u n="72" who="S0688">not want to be romantic with me?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0687">not particularly mum</u>
<u n="74" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> no that's like medicine</u>
<u n="75" who="S0687">yeah it's horrible isn't it? I won't be trying that again <pause dur="short"/> ten ways to splash out</u>
<u n="76" who="S0688">go on</u>
<u n="77" who="S0687">select a piece of wearable art jewellery from the exquisite Nadi collection on Piazza San Marco listen to the live orchestra while sipping coffee at the extravagant Café Florien choose unique glass creations to take him from L'Isola Carlo Moretti blah de blah de blah de blah de blah cruise the city's waterways in a private taxi or you can get custom made shoes at Giovanna Zanella's</u>
<u n="78" who="S0688">don't think we've got time for that do you?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0687">no don't particularly want to ship my feet out for someone to</u>
<u n="80" who="S0688">measure</u>
<u n="81" who="S0687">measure what was I meant to be looking at? oh where was it the</u>
<u n="82" who="S0688" trans="overlap">places to eat</u>
<u n="83" who="S0687">was it was it in the top ten top ten museums</u>
<u n="84" who="S0688" trans="overlap">it was places to eat</u>
<u n="85" who="S0687">and galleries <pause dur="long"/> churches?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0688">it's a good little book isn't it?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0687">yeah it's good yeah to be fair</u>
<u n="88" who="S0688">I like the way it's organised</u>
<u n="89" who="S0687">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0688">what was that Venice's?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0687">architects I think it was artists and architects <pause dur="short"/> top ten hidden Venice did you read this?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0688">go on</u>
<u n="93" who="S0687">Parco Savorgnan a well hidden haven of chirping birds in towering shaded trees signposted from Campo San <trunc>Ger</trunc>Geremia and Fondamenta Savorgnan <pause dur="short"/> part of the park once belonged to Palazzo Savorgnan now a school which backs on to it and boasted statues citrus trees and roman stone work</u>
<u n="94" who="S0688">where's that? is that near the bus station?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0687" trans="overlap">er map B two where is oh is it this one? oh <pause dur="long"/> there is no B on that one</u>
<u n="96" who="S0688">course there is</u>
<u n="97" who="S0687">no there's not J to R or there's B here what did I say B two?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0687">yeah it's up near the train station actually</u>
<u n="100" who="S0688">yeah I thought that I thought I'd read about that</u>
<u n="101" who="S0687">what erm what does it say? Campo San Geremia from oh it's there look that green bit there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0688">change glasses</u>
<u n="103" who="S0687">it's effort isn't it?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0688">it is an effort <unclear/> it is</u>
<u n="105" who="S0687">oh it says here erm rats are rare thanks to imported Syrian cats in the past replaced by an effective council eradication campaign</u>
<u n="106" who="S0688">good</u>
<u n="107" who="S0687">suits me there you go by law dogs in Venice must be muzzled how many dogs have we seen that haven't been muzzled?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0688">haven't seen one muzzled</u>
<u n="109" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I don't think we've seen one that's been muzzled</u>
<u n="110" who="S0688">they've been hand <trunc>bad</trunc> handbag dogs though</u>
<u n="111" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0688">the Beadle was quite big</u>
<u n="113" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/> obviously no one takes notice</u>
<u n="114" who="S0688">yeah we could pop into this park</u>
<u n="115" who="S0687">yeah and then Rio Terra Rampani this quiet thoroughfare around the corner from Ponte Delle Tette is usually referred to as the Carampane alias the <trunc>re</trunc> the red light district as of fourteen twenty-one</u>
<u n="116" who="S0688">oh we'll skip that</u>
<u n="117" who="S0687">Venice had some eleven thousand six hundred officially registered courtesans in the fifteen hundreds is that the old word for prostitute is courtesans?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0688">no idea</u>
<u n="119" who="S0687">a particularly narrow alley <trunc>Calle</trunc> I don't know what it's telling us to go there</u>
<u n="120" who="S0688">maybe it's not nice</u>
<u n="121" who="S0687">maybe it's not nice</u>
<u n="122" who="S0688">you're supposed to go and have a look</u>
<u n="123" who="S0687">probably</u>
<u n="124" who="S0688">where they used to sell their wares</u>
<u n="125" who="S0687">number three <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0688">see that fella with his white wellies on</u>
<u n="127" who="S0687">it's too late</u>
<u n="128" who="S0688">do you know I was just thinking about go away Mr pigeon <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0687">was the toilet clean?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0688">yeah it was okay</u>
<u n="131" who="S0687">but I was looking for restaurants wasn't I? food wine bars places to eat</u>
<u n="132" who="S0688">to be honest that list can't do it justice there's so many places</u>
<u n="133" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0688">if we'd have stayed on Burano we'd have gone to that nice one that was the Michelin star registered one for dinner</u>
<u n="135" who="S0687">yeah mm mm spaghetti con nero with <trunc>cuttle</trunc>cuttlefish ink sauce <pause dur="long"/> they're all erm very posh</u>
<u n="136" who="S0688">how often they sent that erm there are vegetarian one our must be on a different page <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0687">I think I am but I don't know pubs bars and clubs</u>
<u n="138" who="S0688">there was one that listed a vegetarian</u>
<u n="139" who="S0687">top ten places to eat?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0688">Grand Canal Hotel Monaco</u>
<u n="141" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0688">you probably need to dress up to go we're got going to go back and get changed are we?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0687">no not to come back again I don't know what you were looking at then cos</u>
<u n="144" who="S0688">let me see <pause dur="short"/> drink your medicine</u>
<u n="145" who="S0687">be good for you</u>
<u n="146" who="S0688">it's when it hits the back of your throat</u>
<u n="147" who="S0687">it's awful it tastes like antibiotics <pause dur="long"/> or Skittles <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0688">one of the city's best public sports facilities is located in this series of modest repositories</u>
<u n="149" who="S0687">sports facilities</u>
<u n="150" who="S0688">includes an indoor swimming pool gym and</u>
<u n="151" who="S0687">you're supposed to be looking for grub we're not going to the gym</u>
<u n="152" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I know Yungun's Factory New York style restaurants have been created from this old plot factory</u>
<u n="153" who="S0687">that sounds nice</u>
<u n="154" who="S0688">one of many projects taking place on <trunc>Gode</trunc><unclear>Godettra</unclear></u>
<u n="155" who="S0687">D six where's D six? it is oh it's down here it's on er it's over here look across erm the big canal it's a different island</u>
<u n="156" who="S0688">oh is it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0687">I think yeah it's a different island</u>
<u n="158" who="S0688">after dinner Sgroppino erm a well kept local secret concocted with lemon sorbet</u>
<u n="159" who="S0687">sorry what's this a dessert?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0688" trans="overlap">a drink a drink</u>
<u n="161" who="S0687">oh</u>
<u n="162" who="S0688">top ten drinks spritz</u>
<u n="163" who="S0687">not tried that</u>
<u n="164" who="S0688">unrivalled Venetian favourite of white wine a splash of bitter Peron or</u>
<u n="165" who="S0687">what's a Peron?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0688">or or Select</u>
<u n="167" who="S0687">I don't know what that is</u>
<u n="168" who="S0688">aperitif grand and a shot of mineral water so it's not Prosecco Prosecco excellent natural sparkling dry white wine from the hills that suits us Bellini smooth fresh peach juice with sparkling Prosecco blend</u>
<u n="169" who="S0687" trans="overlap">with Prosecco isn't it? I'd rather just have Prosecco</u>
<u n="170" who="S0688">invented by the Cypriani of <unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0687">that means like Cypriot Cypriani?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0688">I don't know</u>
<u n="173" who="S0687">it says all these things you know like Byzantine but it doesn't explain what it is</u>
<u n="174" who="S0688" trans="overlap">mm Byzantine's an era isn't it?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0687">yeah I understand they're like eras of like architectural design and things but it doesn't kind of give you any more detail than that I don't feel as though I've burnt</u>
<u n="176" who="S0688">well we've had cream on haven't we?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0687">yeah <pause dur="short"/> has your bite stopped itching on your toe?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0688">yeah but this is an after dinner S G how do you pronounce that <trunc>sct</trunc> sgroppino</u>
<u n="179" who="S0687">what is that the word? let's see</u>
<u n="180" who="S0688">S G R O P P I N O</u>
<u n="181" who="S0687">I have no idea</u>
<u n="182" who="S0688">sgroppino</u>
<u n="183" who="S0687">sgroppino yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0688">a well kept local secret concocted with lemon sorbet vodka and Prosecco you'd be on your back wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0687">I know in erm Italian if there's any double letters like double G it means it's like longer so it'll be like sgroppino like that</u>
<u n="186" who="S0688">oh right</u>
<u n="187" who="S0687">like that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0688">sgroppino</u>
<u n="189" who="S0687">I think I think so so like if it's latte so it's like latte</u>
<u n="190" who="S0688">latte</u>
<u n="191" who="S0687">it's like kind of you hold it for a bit longer Prosecco</u>
<u n="192" who="S0688" trans="overlap">Prosecco it's got two Cs</u>
<u n="193" who="S0687">oh has it got two Cs?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0688">yeah one S two Cs</u>
<u n="195" who="S0687">okay Prosecco</u>
<u n="196" who="S0688">Prosecco how do you say coffee?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0687">cafe it's K A F F E isn't it?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0688">no</u>
<u n="199" who="S0687">is it not?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0688">that's Turkish</u>
<u n="201" who="S0687">what do you mean that's Turkish? how do you know what coffee is in Turkish?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0688">K A F F E</u>
<u n="203" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0688">I've been to Turkey</u>
<u n="205" who="S0687">yeah but I'm sure it might be that in Italian as well I'm sure I've seen that on menus</u>
<u n="206" who="S0688">have you?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0688">oh C A F F E</u>
<u n="209" who="S0687">alright close enough</u>
<u n="210" who="S0688"><foreign lang="ita">caffe</foreign> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0687">they must be quite dark these apartments mustn't they?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0688">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I suppose once you've been here</u>
<u n="213" who="S0687">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0688">and you've done this you'd start exploring other areas of it wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0687" trans="overlap">elsewhere yeah I don't think I'd spend a week just doing Venice</u>
<u n="216" who="S0688">no it's a bit like being in London isn't it?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0688">you do the touristy bit but then you start really exploring it like erm erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were doing this like little known walks on London there was a book that her and her friend</u>
<u n="219" who="S0687"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0688">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0687">they're lucky that they've got that apartment that they can go and stay in whenever</u>
<u n="222" who="S0688" trans="overlap">so lucky so lucky <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0687">you never saw it did you? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0688">this sounds nice a wine bar Al Bottegon not far from the Academia bridge</u>
<u n="225" who="S0687">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0688">join the locals at this family run specialist wine cellar that serves excellent Prosecco at a stand up bar</u>
<u n="227" who="S0687">nice</u>
<u n="228" who="S0688">simple nibbles to accompany the wine include tomato della sausage and panini filled with prosciutto or local salami</u>
<u n="229" who="S0687">sounds nice</u>
<u n="230" who="S0688">C five on the map</u>
<u n="231" who="S0687">that is it's near the Academia it's this square here what <trunc>ro</trunc> I can't see roads on here but what road does it say it's on? does it not tell you?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0688">yeah Fondamenta Nani</u>
<u n="233" who="S0687">it'll be on that bigger map that we've got</u>
<u n="234" who="S0688">in Dorsaduro we should try that before we go back</u>
<u n="235" who="S0687">well if we walk we're walking to there anyway</u>
<u n="236" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0687">so if we're not too tired we could go on to it cos it's not well I'm saying it's not that much further on</u>
<u n="238" who="S0688">what is this area?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0687">Dorsaduro well that's not where we are now we're in San Marco still we're somewhere around here</u>
<u n="240" who="S0688">yeah I mean it looks big but I'm sure we can do it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0688">I wonder how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is doing?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0687">shall I see if there's any wi-fi to ring him?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0688">you can call him soon</u>
<u n="245" who="S0687">mm I'll use the toilet before we finish our medicine</u>
<u n="246" who="S0688">it's making me a bit heady actually</u>
<u n="247" who="S0687">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0688">I suppose it's</u>
<u n="249" who="S0687">we <trunc>a</trunc> we ate over three hours ago and we didn't eat a lot did we?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0688">well a sandwich</u>
<u n="251" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0688">it's so much quieter now isn't it?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0687">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0688">I prefer it like this</u>
<u n="255" who="S0687">yeah me too</u>
<u n="256" who="S0688">they don't mind you too much</u>
<u n="257" who="S0687">no that woman did in that clothes shop in Mestre was a bit annoying remember?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0687">she was nice she was just a bit full on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0688">there are lots of Americans here though</u>
<u n="261" who="S0687">yeah loads I suppose it's probably like <pause dur="short"/> if Americans came to England they'd probably go to London if Americans come to Italy they probably come either here or Rome</u>
<u n="262" who="S0688">Venice or Rome yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0687">although that woman we met yesterday travelled around hadn't she?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0688">she'd been around hadn't she? she'd done <trunc>Tusca</trunc> well Florence she said</u>
<u n="265" who="S0687">mm did you think that was her granddaughter that she was with?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0688">I'm not sure probably</u>
<u n="267" who="S0687">probably</u>
<u n="268" who="S0688">although she didn't live in the same place she said she was from South Carolina didn't she?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0687">mm and she said she was well she said she lived in Florida she might not have been from Florida</u>
<u n="270" who="S0688">there's probably a a lot of old people retire</u>
<u n="271" who="S0687">on Florida</u>
<u n="272" who="S0688">yeah whats it was saying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I saw him he was saying maybe I've told you this</u>
<u n="273" who="S0687">oh they've rented a house on in Florida</u>
<u n="274" who="S0688">yeah but his his grandma lives in Albany and he said you know for like five months of the year it was snow and it's cold and she can't even walk to the end of the drive to pick up the mail why would an old person live in those conditions?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0687">yeah when they could be</u>
<u n="276" who="S0688">when they could in Florida</u>
<u n="277" who="S0687">well it's good for arthritis and things like that as well isn't it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0688">well he said there were everyone says it's full of old people Florida but he said I'd rather be with old people who are fit and healthy cos they're out and about doing things</u>
<u n="279" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0688">I don't know</u>
<u n="281" who="S0687">so is that their plan?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0688">he they plan to live in Florida</u>
<u n="283" who="S0687">cos he cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is loads younger than him but he doesn't work does he?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0688">no <pause dur="long"/> who knows don't know who knows?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0687">did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ever find out what the deal was with them splitting up and then they were back together again?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0688">don't know he didn't say he doesn't get involved in that really</u>
<u n="287" who="S0687">no probably does right <pause dur="long"/> making me feel a bit</u>
<u n="288" who="S0688">light headed</u>
<u n="289" who="S0687">yeah squiffy</u>
<u n="290" who="S0688">mm drink the water</u>
<u n="291" who="S0687">I've drunk the water</u>
<u n="292" who="S0688">or get some more water</u>
<u n="293" who="S0687">let's drink it and ask for some more <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0687">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0688">cheers</u>
<u n="297" who="S0687">not cheers over this</u>
<u n="298" who="S0688">leave it darling</u>
<u n="299" who="S0687">no no it's drinkable it's just not I wouldn't order it again</u>
<u n="300" who="S0688" trans="overlap">not enjoyable I wouldn't order it again</u>
<u n="301" who="S0687">for that you may as well just have a glass of Prosecco or a glass of wine</u>
<u n="302" who="S0688">I'd much rather have a glass of Prosecco</u>
<u n="303" who="S0687">this erm soda's not even fizzy is it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0688">well they've put lemon in with it which makes me think it's the bitter erm liquor that they've put in</u>
<u n="305" who="S0687">but it's still quite sweet I think</u>
<u n="306" who="S0688">do you think?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0687">I think it's</u>
<u n="308" who="S0688">I don't think it's sweet at all</u>
<u n="309" who="S0687">I think it's sweet <pause dur="long"/> it's a bit bitter at the back of your throat but it tastes sweet to begin with tastes a bit sugary</u>
<u n="310" who="S0688">it just shows you where your taste buds are on your tongue cos at the front it's a little bit sweet</u>
<u n="311" who="S0687">yeah I remember them doing that at the museum in where what museum was it? where they erm put a cotton bud in coffee and made you rub it on your tongue to see where you tasted different</u>
<u n="312" who="S0688">like salt and sugar and</u>
<u n="313" who="S0687">and salt and sugar and you taste it in different parts of your tongue and your mouth</u>
<u n="314" who="S0688">mm clever isn't it?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0687">yeah I don't understand why that would be like evolutionarily don't know</u>
<u n="316" who="S0688">yeah why would you develop?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0687">why would you develop different parts of your tongue to taste different things? cos it's like if you're taking tablets and you put it on your tongue at the front it tastes really bitter you know like tablets that aren't coated the powdery ones but if you put it to the back of your tongue you can't taste the powderyness it's bizarre <pause dur="short"/> bizarre <pause dur="short"/> this waitress has done so much work she's sat on her Ipad with her headphones in <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0688">I thought that was a customer</u>
<u n="319" who="S0687">did you?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0688">yeah I did yeah I didn't recognise her</u>
<u n="321" who="S0687" trans="overlap">no she was behind the bar</u>
<u n="322" who="S0688">she's the one who served us</u>
<u n="323" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/> what's the matter?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0688">it's an American family I'm just earwigging</u>
<u n="325" who="S0687">being nosy</u>
<u n="326" who="S0688">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think these plants are weird</u>
<u n="327" who="S0687">yeah I don't know <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0688">okay let's take a break and see if we can ring the boys oh it's three o'clock there isn't it?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0687">three it's ten past three there shall I get your phone out and see if there's any wi-fi?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0688">okay</u>
<u n="331" who="S0687">we'll probably have to turn that off if we're</u>
<u n="332" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0687">facetiming</u>
<u n="334" who="S0688"><shift new="singing"/> manic Monday <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0687"><shift new="singing"/> wish it was Sunday <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0688">it's a good song <shift new="singing"/> the wrong day it's just another manic Monday <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0687">I'll have to work out how to get this from here onto the computer</u>
<u n="338" who="S0688">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0687">cos I've done it as a voice memo on my phone so I'm not entirely sure how how I'd get it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0688">convert it</u>
<u n="341" who="S0687">yeah I'm not sure what from it's recording cos there's different types of audio file so I'll work it out <pause dur="long"/> erm where are we? Colanetti looks like there is I'll go and ask the lady on her Ipad</u>
<u n="342" who="S0688">I thought you'd already asked</u>
<u n="343" who="S0687">no no I haven't asked I'll go and ask <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0688">did she set it up for you?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0687">yeah she sorted it you trying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or dad?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0688">I don't now I'll have to have a quick look at messages</u>
<u n="347" who="S0687">we didn't put that photo of us on Facebook either</u>
<u n="348" who="S0688">oh no let's do that</u>
<u n="349" who="S0687">it's on my phone and I've not connected to wi-fi and she typed the password so I don't know what the password is</u>
<u n="350" who="S0688" trans="overlap">okay okay</u>
<u n="351" who="S0687">we can do it at back at the apartment tonight</u>
<u n="352" who="S0688">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't replied to me on Facebook I messaged him twice</u>
<u n="353" who="S0687">what saying?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0688">me?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0688">saying er cos he said are you on the road yet? on Monday I said not yet waiting for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0687">oh to the airport in Boston?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah notifications</u>
<u n="359" who="S0687">try ringing him it'll be what time there? it's four o'clock here and they're six hours it'll be ten o'clock</u>
<u n="360" who="S0688">oh it was yesterday it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum's birthday</u>
<u n="361" who="S0687">oh pooh has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got an Iphone? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0688">she did have</u>
<u n="363" who="S0687">I was just thinking you could send her a message about the budgies and thank and wishing her mum a happy birthday</u>
<u n="364" who="S0688">I can send her mum must have a Ipad oh it's Facebook</u>
<u n="365" who="S0687">it's Facebook</u>
<u n="366" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0687">are you friends with her mum?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0687">oh right send her a message then</u>
<u n="370" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I can send her a <trunc>bi</trunc> a birthday greeting when I find when it winds up</u>
<u n="371" who="S0687">that's nice the waiter's not gone so far for a smoke</u>
<u n="372" who="S0688">it's his second one while we've been here</u>
<u n="373" who="S0687">is it? oh I didn't notice the first time <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0688">it's thinking about it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0687">have you?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0688">and they don't wash their hands before they start</u>
<u n="377" who="S0687">no</u>
<u n="378" who="S0688">look he's going serving food now he's just had a cigarette</u>
<u n="379" who="S0687">yeah it's pleasant did you save the page that had the instructions for that bar the Prosecco bar?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0688">see I</u>
<u n="381" who="S0687">don't forget we've got half a bottle at the apartment to have as well</u>
<u n="382" who="S0688">yeah oh go on I'll have</u>
<u n="383" who="S0687" trans="overlap">you'll have one we're not driving are we?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0688">oh can't connect</u>
<u n="385" who="S0687">is it does it still have the wi-fi symbol at the top?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0688">yeah yeah yeah oh I got it she's seventy-eight</u>
<u n="387" who="S0687">which one was it? <pause dur="long"/> which one was it mam?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0688">the bottom one Bottegon</u>
<u n="389" who="S0687">oh Al Al Bottegon on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0688">happy birthday for <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0687">ah it says what tap water is here</u>
<u n="392" who="S0688">tap water</u>
<u n="393" who="S0687">yeah it says mineral water <trunc>wi</trunc>widely consumed in Italy well I should hope people drink water</u>
<u n="394" who="S0688">shall we get some more water?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0687" trans="overlap">either either sparkling or still tap water is <foreign lang="ita">aqua del rubinetto</foreign></u>
<u n="396" who="S0688">okay <foreign lang="ita">por favor</foreign></u>
<u n="397" who="S0687"><foreign lang="ita">me excusi acqua del rubinetto por favor</foreign></u>
<u n="398" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="ita">si</foreign></u>
<u n="399" who="S0687"><foreign lang="ita">gratie</foreign> that went well</u>
<u n="400" who="S0688">it did it was very good I'm impressed <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0687">right I'll put the bookmark in that page</u>
<u n="402" who="S0688">mm my eyes are burning</u>
<u n="403" who="S0687">are burning?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0687">from wearing my glasses</u>
<u n="406" who="S0688">get hot wearing my glasses I'll put some drops in actually if you get the them out <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0687">hope the house is as nice as we're hoping it to be tomorrow</u>
<u n="408" who="S0688">I hope so too</u>
<u n="409" who="S0687">I'm sure it will be</u>
<u n="410" who="S0688">it looks it</u>
<u n="411" who="S0687">it looks it and she's been so lovely to us that I can't imagine the house wouldn't be</u>
<u n="412" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0687">as you would expect</u>
<u n="414" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0687">erm what am I looking for? is it in your makeup bag your eye drops?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0688">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0687">feel a bit more hydrated now pass us that jug and I'll pour the water</u>
<u n="418" who="S0688">this made her get up off her bum</u>
<u n="419" who="S0687">she's back down now <pause dur="long"/> oh it says that the erm Rialto market is open mornings</u>
<u n="420" who="S0688">oh right</u>
<u n="421" who="S0687">that's rubbish we wanted to buy some fruit didn't we?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0688">we'll have to look at that co-op</u>
<u n="423" who="S0687">yeah that was right back near where we get the bus anyway wasn't it?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0687">it says it's this is ten activities on a budget <pause dur="short"/> erm spend time people watching in Campo Santa Margarita that's what we were just talking about</u>
<u n="426" who="S0688">where's Campo <trunc>S</trunc>?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0687">Santa <trunc>Mar</trunc> that was the one where it said it's erm erm a square</u>
<u n="428" who="S0688">we're heading there aren't we?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0687">you you know that I was telling you about</u>
<u n="430" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah on the way back erm enjoy good value fish or seafood we've not had any seafood yet have we?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0688">no</u>
<u n="433" who="S0687">at Ristorante Al Buon Pesce which is in Chioggia that's erm that's one of the islands Chioggia it's off down here look it's a bit of an effort to get to isn't it?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0688">yeah what's that? eating</u>
<u n="435" who="S0687">erm good <trunc>val</trunc> good value fish and seafood <pause dur="short"/> which is a shame <pause dur="short"/> we can go back to Mestre for our dinner</u>
<u n="436" who="S0688">mm <pause dur="long"/> let's post</u>
<u n="437" who="S0687">what are you posting?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0688">happy birthday for yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hope you had a lovely time we're in Venice so in and out of internet sorry that your birthday greetings are late</u>
<u n="439" who="S0687">are you posting to her timeline or on a message?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0688">timeline</u>
<u n="441" who="S0687">oh back at it now</u>
<u n="442" who="S0688">oh <pause dur="long"/> that's an addiction</u>
<u n="443" who="S0687">mm not good is it?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0688">so I've got two notifications I do not want to look at anything to do with work <pause dur="short"/> I'm right off this Sussex spaniel woman</u>
<u n="445" who="S0687">yeah I don't even want to be friends with her any more she just keeps posting photos and I don't want to see <pause dur="short"/> how did you leave it with the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> woman that you'd get in touch when we were home <pause dur="short"/> and see where she was up to with whether she was keeping?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I don't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s put a DVD out a film she's in Marmaris can you imagine what that's going to be like?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0687" trans="overlap">where's Marmaris?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0688">she's sixty-seven</u>
<u n="449" who="S0687">is it like a?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0688">er Turkey</u>
<u n="451" who="S0687">is it one er is it like a resort like Zante?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0688" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="453" who="S0687">I think it is isn't it hasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> been there?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0687">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> seems quite taken with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend</u>
<u n="456" who="S0688">yeah she wants him to be happy doesn't she?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0688">one beer two raki is it? and wrecked at the <anon type="place"/> Marmaris four AM and home time</u>
<u n="459" who="S0687">nice <pause dur="short"/> how old is she in her forties?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0688">sixty-seven <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0687">sixty-seven oh my god</u>
<u n="462" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've gone off the internet now</u>
<u n="463" who="S0687">let's see her</u>
<u n="464" who="S0688"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <pause dur="short"/> I've lost the internet I think just hold on <pause dur="short"/> do you think this is is interesting enough conversation?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0687">yeah they're not bothered what how interesting it is</u>
<u n="466" who="S0688">okay good</u>
<u n="467" who="S0687">I've audio checked people talking about what's in their dinner salad at work</u>
<u n="468" who="S0688">have you?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0688">right</u>
<u n="471" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I've got carrots <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0687">the other person I've got tuna in mine it's a bit smelly though literally that's it</u>
<u n="474" who="S0688" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0687">yeah so I think we'll be fine</u>
<u n="476" who="S0688">okay</u>
<u n="477" who="S0687">your internet's working fine oh no this is not good she looks like she's in a nightclub</u>
<u n="478" who="S0688">let's have a look she will be let me see</u>
<u n="479" who="S0687" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> that is not a good look for a sixty-seven year old</u>
<u n="480" who="S0688">let me look</u>
<u n="481" who="S0687">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> do you see her?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0688">no</u>
<u n="483" who="S0687">it's quite dark <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="484" who="S0688">has she got her white trousers on?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0687">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the blue top <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0688">what's she like?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0687">has she got children? or are they all grown up?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0688" trans="overlap">in the they're all grown up yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0688">I don't know who she's with oh I think it's her friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0687"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0688"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she's drunk as a skunk</u>
<u n="493" who="S0687">yeah she looks it a bit <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0688">let's see what her comments say <pause dur="short"/> oh god <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0687">I might tip this water in here mum</u>
<u n="496" who="S0688">sure</u>
<u n="497" who="S0687">do you think? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0688">her daughter said really mother?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0687">how old's her daughter?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0688">she's thirties yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0687" trans="overlap">thirties? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0688">what is she like? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0687">need to figure out where we are to come up with a route to Rialto</u>
<u n="504" who="S0688">yeah well when we're finished this er</u>
<u n="505" who="S0687">horribleness if we'd had Prosecco we'd have been finished a bit sooner wouldn't we? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0688" trans="overlap">medicine <pause dur="short"/> I know we would <pause dur="short"/> that's me done</u>
<u n="507" who="S0687">that's you done</u>
<u n="508" who="S0688">not drinking any more <pause dur="long"/> why would you drink medicine just cos you'd paid for it?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0687">cos you've paid for it</u>
<u n="510" who="S0688">it's yacki-doo-da <pause dur="short"/> no more</u>
<u n="511" who="S0687">I thought Italians had taste <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0688">think we're just going to go for <pause dur="short"/> a nice wine bar and a glass of Prosecco we know what we're having then</u>
<u n="513" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0688">he's backwards and forwards him</u>
<u n="515" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I know we could even get <pause dur="short"/> a couple of bottles of that one we got yesterday to take with us to Istria <pause dur="short"/> what do you think?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0688" trans="overlap">it's carrying it though</u>
<u n="517" who="S0687" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>car</trunc> it's weight to carry isn't it yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0688">it's carrying it <pause dur="short"/> we could take a bottle for we need to take something for</u>
<u n="519" who="S0687">yeah we need to take something for erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0688">yeah so if we take a bottle of that and some chocolates or something</u>
<u n="521" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="short"/> were you going to give it her at the start or at the end?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah yeah at the beginning</u>
<u n="523" who="S0687">or if we <trunc>sho</trunc> or or if we see a shop with erm nice biscotti</u>
<u n="524" who="S0688">yeah we haven't seen any have we?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0687">not really maybe that's a regional thing?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0688">maybe it's really different it's like we make lasagne very different than they make it</u>
<u n="527" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0688">and spaghetti bolognaise we'd have had stacks more meat than they have</u>
<u n="529" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah they <trunc>do</trunc> they don't have much sauce with the pasta do they?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0688" trans="overlap">no no I mean I don't mind that</u>
<u n="531" who="S0687">no no no so long as it's flavoursome</u>
<u n="532" who="S0688">yeah as long as you can put olive oil on it or something</u>
<u n="533" who="S0687" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="534" who="S0688">and that was nice yesterday</u>
<u n="535" who="S0687">I've not seen that spaghetti al aglio that you had on any menus</u>
<u n="536" who="S0688" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="537" who="S0687">maybe but that where was that? that was</u>
<u n="538" who="S0688">Tuscany</u>
<u n="539" who="S0687">Tuscany</u>
<u n="540" who="S0688">no it was the lakes</u>
<u n="541" who="S0687">was it the lakes? I'll drink this and then just nip to the bathroom <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0688">okey-dokey <pause dur="long"/> I don't think your dad will be home yet if we ring him</u>
<u n="543" who="S0687">no did you want to try <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0688">we'll try him yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0687">he should be home from his haircut and going seeing nan <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0688">okay shall we take a pause?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0687">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
