<text id="S5YC">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:41:42</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0441</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home –Kitchen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Holiday, great north run, Newcastle, netball, sport, food, friends, catch-up</topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with housemate after holiday</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, inviting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0441">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Mental Health Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439"><unclear/> who got back to me?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0441"><unclear>who do you think</unclear>? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">oh no no not at all</u>
<u n="4" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has not got back to me in the slightest</u>
<u n="6" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">no <event desc="sound of banging"/> I wasn't ever expecting her to I've got got to message her again</u>
<u n="8" who="S0441">do you think that's okay?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">no <unclear>that's fine</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so how was your holiday? tell me all about it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0441">it was amazing it was so good</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439"><unclear>that's nice surely</unclear> you made some erm firm friends as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0441">oh yeah they were really nice actually <unclear/> people <unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0439" trans="overlap">were they? <vocal desc="laugh"/> are you gonna actually meet up with them again?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0441">well oh <pause dur="short"/> they <trunc>w</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> like her one of her dreams in life was just like</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">one of her dreams was what?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0441">one of her dreams in life is to go to England <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">oh where's she from?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0441">she's from Texas</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">oh okay oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they're a really nice couple actually like really down to earth like most of the Americans we met were like like jock Americans</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0441">they're really nice</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">ah <event desc="sound of banging"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0441">so we said if if they come to <anon type="place"/> soon then yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0441">why not? <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0441">but yeah they were lovely</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">so what else did you get up to?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0441">er a lot of lying around which was really good</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">that's what you have to do on a beach holiday though isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0441">yeah we didn't go to the beach much though cos it was so hot by the beach</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439">oh really?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0441">there's a beach obviously like in the resort so you can just walk down to the beach but</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0441">the erm the pool was a bit nicer cos it was sort of</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439">make you a cup of tea</u>
<u n="38" who="S0441">cooler and sort of breezier if that makes sense</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0441">and <vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah which was really nice and we went on er the excursion er to the Caribbean side so we were on the Pacific side</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0441">the Pacific Ocean side we went to like an excursion to the Caribbean side</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">oh cool</u>
<u n="44" who="S0441">the Caribbean Sea is incredible</u>
<u n="45" who="S0439">is it? is it really blue?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0441">yeah it's just like turquoise and just completely clear like</u>
<u n="47" who="S0439">wow</u>
<u n="48" who="S0441">ridiculously clear erm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439">you're looking brown</u>
<u n="50" who="S0441"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really dark <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was ridiculous he literally went black on the first day</u>
<u n="51" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0441">but that was with factor fifty on as well</u>
<u n="53" who="S0439">oh <trunc>s</trunc> god</u>
<u n="54" who="S0441">god knows what would've happened if we didn't have any factor on at all erm <pause dur="short"/> what else? we swam with dolphins</u>
<u n="55" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0441">which was amazing</u>
<u n="57" who="S0439">that's so cool</u>
<u n="58" who="S0441"><unclear/> it was amazing but obviously like they must think it's such a big <unclear>money making scheme</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0439">oh yeah definitely</u>
<u n="60" who="S0441">it was really expensive it wasn't so expensive to do but it was expensive with all the like merchandise that you can buy</u>
<u n="61" who="S0439">oh yeah so <unclear>I assume you can</unclear> have like photos and stuff</u>
<u n="62" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0439"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0441">we did buy photos but only because</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439">did you guys see a dolphin?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0441">we sort of thought</u>
<u n="67" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0441">maybe we'll never <trunc>s</trunc> do it again so</u>
<u n="69" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0441"><unclear>be nice to actually do it once</unclear> erm what else did we do? went on an excursion where we drove our own jeep around which was <unclear>quite good</unclear></u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">oh wow that's cool</u>
<u n="72" who="S0441">that was fun so we saw like er like the proper <unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0441">erm <pause dur="short"/> we er just did a lot of lying around drinking eating it was really nice it was nice to sort of spend a bit of quality time together as well</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0441">we don't really ever spend that that long together</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439">yeah you only spend like weekends er like a few weekends together don't you? so</u>
<u n="78" who="S0441">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">very cool</u>
<u n="80" who="S0441">erm so it was really good erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">back to work today how was it?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0441">oh er it was alright</u>
<u n="83" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0441">the usual</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">for you</u>
<u n="86" who="S0441">a lot of like <pause dur="short"/> one of my <trunc>patien</trunc> in fact two of my patients have gone into hospital <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">oh god okay</u>
<u n="88" who="S0441">one's fine the other's not so fine so that's really annoying</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0441">erm <pause dur="short"/> what else? just I didn't really do a lot today I just sort of like sat there just taking it all in really</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0441">like <unclear/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">what time did you get back? you came back on Monday didn't you?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0441">on Monday at six <trunc>ha</trunc> no we got back about ten in the morning to the flat <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="96" who="S0441">we were in <anon type="place"/> at about eight thirty</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0441">erm <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439">very cool</u>
<u n="100" who="S0441">it was <trunc>u</trunc> really cool where did I put my cucumber? I've lost my cucumber</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">no you put it by the side of the fridge</u>
<u n="102" who="S0441">er there it is er yeah <event desc="sound of banging"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">back to reality</u>
<u n="104" who="S0441">back to reality</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0441">in fact I actually almost forgot about the holiday by lunchtime</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0441"><unclear/> it never changes it's just like I never left</u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">I know I know</u>
<u n="110" who="S0441">people are still moaning</u>
<u n="111" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0441">I didn't see anyone today though so it was fine I just</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">oh you didn't have any <trunc>pa</trunc> you didn't go visit anybody? no</u>
<u n="114" who="S0441">well I had to have a day to catch up on life</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">yeah emails</u>
<u n="116" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439"><unclear>not that</unclear> <unclear/> what er people email <unclear/> about</u>
<u n="118" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">people email you some really boring shit</u>
<u n="120" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">and you're just like you could've solved that problem yourself</u>
<u n="122" who="S0441">we always have like they always send like group emails out to the erm <pause dur="short"/> like people in the in the car park and stuff</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0441">like if if they've double parked so</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">oh yeah I remember you saying</u>
<u n="126" who="S0441">can so and so please move their car mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0441"><unclear/> <unclear>about two weeks ago I don't care now</unclear></u>
<u n="129" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0439">er I wasn't even here fuck off</u>
<u n="131" who="S0441">definitely not me so yeah although <trunc>nor</trunc> they would've normally got my erm <unclear>out of office</unclear> <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="132" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0439">in their faces</u>
<u n="134" who="S0441"><unclear>not that they'd give a shit</unclear></u>
<u n="135" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0441">whoops how was your week?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">erm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">how was my week? last week was really really erm relaxed because erm our division had erm a sales conference and everybody well not everybody but a lot of the bosses were out of the office all week</u>
<u n="140" who="S0441"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="141" who="S0439">so kind of just <unclear/> and stuff and it was <unclear>literally</unclear> like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was ill Monday Tuesday Wednesday with a chest infection managed somehow to go to Bestival on Thursday Friday Saturday Sunday</u>
<u n="142" who="S0441">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">came in halfway through the day on Monday</u>
<u n="144" who="S0441">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> er I don't think people minded too much cos she had booked off her holiday ages ago but it was just a bit like</u>
<u n="146" who="S0441">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">yeah how do you have a chest infection and you're on antibiotics but somehow you can go to a festival on the freezing Isle of Wight and drink?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">and then she came back with a urine infection as well so</u>
<u n="150" who="S0441">all the infections <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">yeah so yeah erm what else? <unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0441"><unclear>have you</unclear> made up yet? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">yeah yeah we had a sort of did I not erm <trunc>d</trunc><trunc>d</trunc> have I not seen you since then?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">so anyway so we had <trunc>breakfa</trunc> like we got to the end of the week and it was a bit weird and I was like we probably should talk about <unclear>this</unclear> and she was like yeah it's been really weird this week and I was like yes yes it has</u>
<u n="156" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">erm so we went to breakfast</u>
<u n="158" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">and you know we had breakfast and then afterwards we were like let's have a quick catch up cos someone else went to breakfast with us so we couldn't really talk about it</u>
<u n="160" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">and I was just like firstly I think you just behaved really poorly this weekend and you you made my weekend very uncomfortable</u>
<u n="162" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439">in a city that I really like</u>
<u n="164" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">and she was like yeah sorry about that and I was like</u>
<u n="166" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">okay I was like you you made it out like you were being ignored or left out of everything when you weren't</u>
<u n="168" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">you behaved like a child like you were in school</u>
<u n="170" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">and I just didn't wanna deal with it and she went yeah I know I'm really sorry like I get really jealous</u>
<u n="172" who="S0441">you get what?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439"><unclear>I just not I think</unclear> I was not expecting her to come out with these answers like she was like yeah when I was at school I always used to get jealous of friends and you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> seem to have all these amazing times together when I'm not there I'm like what? what are you on about? like</u>
<u n="174" who="S0441">oh dear</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">like she was like well you know like just little things that I can't be involved in I was like yeah but you're never gonna be involved in everybody's conversation there's always gonna be a time when you're like left out you know when you're not involved in something cos you don't like like the subject or you're not as like you haven't seen the film or something like that</u>
<u n="176" who="S0441">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439">and you can't get annoyed every time that happens</u>
<u n="178" who="S0441">no just include yourself somehow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">yeah just include yourself or just sit there taking it in and just accept that you are not gonna be able to comment on this conversation</u>
<u n="180" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">and she was like yeah I know I really have to work on it and I'm really sorry and I kept getting more angry and angry because I realised that you were annoyed at me and I was like I wasn't annoyed with you I was just didn't care</u>
<u n="182" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">I didn't I knew what you were doing and I didn't care enough to have a fight with you about it and she was like yeah I'm really sorry I'll try and work on that in the future I was like god that's gonna happen again then erm and then I said and then I said erm I also felt like you were competing with me for the whole holiday on who knew Paris better</u>
<u n="184" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">and I didn't understand it at all and she went yeah I was because it really upset me that you you knew Paris better than me and you're a foreigner</u>
<u n="186" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0439">and I was like</u>
<u n="188" who="S0441">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">yep so <unclear/> she goes well I've always wanted to live in Paris and I haven't been able to and you somehow know it better than I do and I'm French and I was like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0441">so?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">so? like</u>
<u n="192" who="S0441">life goes on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0439">yeah I've been to Paris nearly every single year of my life of course I'm gonna know it well</u>
<u n="194" who="S0441">yeah it's not it's not erm a bad thing</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">it's not even anything to compete over is it? and I was just like I don't understand your behaviour this weekend and you kind of ruined it for me and she went yeah I'm really sorry that's all she</u>
<u n="196" who="S0441"><unclear>well at least</unclear> she's saying something I suppose</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">yeah at least she agreed like er she and she acknowledged</u>
<u n="198" who="S0441"><unclear>at least she agreed that</unclear> she was being difficult</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439">yeah at least she acknowledged that she was being a bitch all weekend and I was just like I do not need like that's just <trunc>f</trunc>from somebody who's twenty-seven twenty-eight years old you're just a bit like</u>
<u n="200" who="S0441">yeah that that makes me think that she's that would suggest to me that she was our age <unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0441"><unclear/> younger than us</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439" trans="overlap">or younger yeah like at school still I was just like I don't need it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so don't do it again or if you do just don't</u>
<u n="204" who="S0441">be quiet about it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0439">don't go don't go grumpy and she <trunc>g</trunc> although she went to Bestival this weekend and I spent quite a few nights just round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s you know just chilling out having tea and stuff</u>
<u n="208" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0439">and she was like oh but you spent time with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this week I was like</u>
<u n="210" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">so you've been at a festival with a group of friends this week like what?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0441">oh dear she sounds <unclear>like</unclear> very jealous</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">very peculiar very strange but that's all sorted now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0439">hopefully it should be fine erm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0441"><unclear/> talk about these things</u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">yeah <unclear>and then what else</unclear>? so yeah last week was quite quiet with the conference and we went to one day and we got like free food and then we had this <trunc>gal</trunc> massive gala dinner on the Thursday night where we got to dress up and everything and</u>
<u n="218" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">look smart and meet everybody and that was quite nice although I was on a table with like my all of the heads of commissioning somebody from <anon type="place"/> and then a sales rep but the problem is they're all at that age where they all have children so</u>
<u n="220" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439">they're all they all talk about their children they're like oh yeah it's weird when your children get to an age and they no longer need your help or advice I was like you're talking about my age <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0441">yeah hello?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">I was like you're talking and bitching about people my age <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">so I couldn't really join in with that but and then obviously I went to <anon type="place"/> this weekend so that was it really</u>
<u n="226" who="S0441">oh yeah how <trunc>w</trunc> how was that? how was that in the end?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">really good</u>
<u n="228" who="S0441">was it?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">it was fine I didn't it wasn't I thought it was gonna be really <unclear>really</unclear> difficult but it wasn't no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0441" trans="overlap">so not as bad as you thought it was <pause dur="short"/> well that's good that that's <unclear/> comforting</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">yeah I did it in two hours fifteen minutes roughly so I'm happy with that although on the Saturday I was just wandering around <anon type="place"/> and I got like er this really creepy text from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0441"><unclear>which is mine</unclear> by the way?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">oh yours is the big one cos I thought you might need more</u>
<u n="234" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0439">er I got this text from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> being like why are you wearing that hoodie? <unclear>and was like</unclear></u>
<u n="236" who="S0441">oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">I was like</u>
<u n="238" who="S0441">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">you know when you're standing in the streets being like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">like what? and I was like where are you? you utter creep like you just made me <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="242" who="S0441">that is really <unclear>weird</unclear></u>
<u n="243" who="S0439">so paranoid cos he always cos I was wearing my <anon type="place"/> hoodie and he's like because that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would never when we were dating he'd be like hated it</u>
<u n="244" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0439">he was like I don't understand why you still have that hoodie it's just like weird <unclear/> <unclear>I was like</unclear></u>
<u n="246" who="S0441">he brought that up?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439">yeah he was <trunc>li</trunc> he was just like it wasn't hi how are you? it was why are you wearing that hoodie?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0441">nice</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439">and I was like where are you you creep? he was like oh we just drove past you</u>
<u n="250" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0439">and I went oh okay weird erm <unclear/> <unclear>you know</unclear> good luck <unclear>for</unclear> the world and everything which <unclear/> was quite quite nice</u>
<u n="252" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>mm quite</unclear> nice that's the word</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like still like he sees his <unclear/> with a hoodie going huh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0439"><unclear>erm like</unclear></u>
<u n="256" who="S0441">hasn't moved on yet <unclear/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's like mm there you go erm but erm well er <anon type="place"/> was really fun the weather was really good on Saturday and we just did the run and then came back home</u>
<u n="258" who="S0441">who were you with?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439">I did it with my running partner <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0441">oh right <unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0439">and her her husband came up so she is I think she is in her fifties and he's sixty-five or something erm and they were <trunc>l</trunc> they were staying in <anon type="place"/> so on the Saturday night I went to <anon type="place"/> and had a wander round and had dinner with them cos <vocal desc="laugh"/> the waiter came over and was like oh so are you erm are you running the Great North Run with your mum? and I was like</u>
<u n="262" who="S0441">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I I knew you were going to say that</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439">I was like no no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I was like she's not my mum</u>
<u n="264" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">right age and stuff but no they were like we're not her parents erm and then er she came back oh my god <unclear/> I was gonna tell you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0441"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">I was gonna tell you on holiday and I was like no no no I've got to wait for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to come back</u>
<u n="268" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0439"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> my head because I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on <trunc>Mond</trunc> well I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> two weeks ago I went home to do this ten K run round <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">and I bumped into him and he was I was like oh my god what are you doing here? and he was like oh hi so we had a little chat like it was only a few minutes before the start and he was just like oh yes you know I broke up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and I was like</u>
<u n="272" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">oh okay are you alright? and he was like mm yeah and then we went on this run and I didn't see him and then because I was I took Monday off erm I said are you around? do you wanna have a catch up?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">and so I went we had like a good two hour catch up actually in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">it was really good erm and so and he talked about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a bit he was just like they'd outgrown each other and you know when like you just you have an argument and you just don't really <trunc>f</trunc> care anymore he was like I was getting to that point where if she stormed off in a mood I just let her go I was like <trunc>s</trunc> fair enough then yeah erm but I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know two weeks ago when you told me that you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had broken up? erm I did a bit of Facebook stalking don't judge me and she hasn't changed her Facebook status <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0439">and she's er she was like still in a relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was like yeah I really have to do something about that it's a bit weird isn't it? I was like erm a little bit you know</u>
<u n="280" who="S0441"><unclear>oh dear</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">and then strangely enough after like on Monday evening her Facebook status had changed</u>
<u n="282" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">so I don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had like sent her a message being like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you really need to change that yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">but erm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0439">yeah he broke up with her</u>
<u n="288" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439">yeah and he and he also cheated on her</u>
<u n="290" who="S0441"><unclear>yeah I know</unclear></u>
<u n="291" who="S0439">I asked him</u>
<u n="292" who="S0441">did you ask him? what? outright?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">yeah outright</u>
<u n="294" who="S0441">what did he say?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">he just he <trunc>la</trunc> well kind of like guiltily laughed and he was like yeah I did he was like how do you know? I was like cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told me he was like how does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> know? I was like cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told her apparently he was like how does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> know? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0441">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">apparently he was on like one of their retreats to Portugal one of their health retreat things</u>
<u n="298" who="S0441">oh okay</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439">she was like the beautician who went along like she did massages and stuff like that for the people <unclear/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> classic</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">she's a bit of a dog though</u>
<u n="302" who="S0441">oh really?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439">I know that sounds really horrible but like I just I Facebook stalked her obviously she's really like chavvy and</u>
<u n="304" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">fake tanned and you know she looks a bit like she looks a bit of a slapper to be honest I'm not gonna lie but erm yeah he is no longer with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and it's er apparently he said the only thing that was really awkward is that he's in a lot of her sister's wedding photos like family wedding photos</u>
<u n="306" who="S0441">that is awkward <pause dur="short"/> that is really awkward</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">yeah like they've been together for like he said about seven years and he's in all pretty much of all of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s family wedding photos and had a suit bought for him and everything and they only got married like two or three weeks ago</u>
<u n="308" who="S0441">that was not long ago was it? oh my god that is awkward</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0441">oh god poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">I was gonna say I don't I didn't think I'd ever hear poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come out of your mouth <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah so that happened</u>
<u n="312" who="S0441">I can just I can just I can just feel what she's going through you know when you just sort of like <pause dur="short"/> put your heart and soul into something and think it's never gonna end?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0441">hence why you've put your boyfriend in sister's wedding photos</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439" trans="overlap">also when you've been together for seven years</u>
<u n="316" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">you kind of like like what was it? I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what? a few months ago maybe in May and I was like we were in the car home I was like do you think you're gonna marry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? he was like mm yeah probably and then what? now he's just broke up with her? it was just like he just said they went to <pause dur="short"/> did they go to Majorca? or they went on holiday and he was just like it just didn't feel the same I was like well at least you dumped her you know at least you</u>
<u n="318" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">like made the er the the decision to do it cos you had been together for a very long time and stuff but</u>
<u n="320" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't dealing with it too well to begin with but he thinks er cos they handed <trunc>th</trunc>they exchanged stuff last week or something and he said she was doing a bit better but</u>
<u n="322" who="S0441">how gallant of him</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">yeah but it's the same as like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though like they broke up after years together didn't they? so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">I just don't think there's any couple left from school now</u>
<u n="326" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">well from our group anyway</u>
<u n="328" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="330" who="S0441">wow</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">yeah it completely slipped I was gonna text you like the moment that I found out and I was like no no no I've got to wait until she gets back from holiday she just</u>
<u n="332" who="S0441">you just need to see my face</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">yeah and she doesn't wanna really like this this <trunc>j</trunc> this isn't that important enough to like tell her on holiday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0441">no and if I had told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he'd've been like great <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">yeah you would've been like you <trunc>w</trunc> you wouldn't've been able to share with me kind of like</u>
<u n="336" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I couldn't've shared with him</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">the understanding of what just happened</u>
<u n="338" who="S0441"><unclear>you know that</unclear></u>
<u n="339" who="S0439">of what went down</u>
<u n="340" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">so yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0441">wow</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">but you see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seems to be okay</u>
<u n="344" who="S0441">that's good</u>
<u n="345" who="S0439">he seems fine actually</u>
<u n="346" who="S0441">that's good I suppose he's probably seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go through it so <unclear/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0439">yeah cos obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> broke up but he said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s was a lot more mutual but</u>
<u n="348" who="S0441"><unclear>oh okay</unclear> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <trunc>w</trunc> er wasn't mutual</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">he didn't say I don't he didn't like imply that they had a massive argument or that she hated him I think she was just</u>
<u n="350" who="S0441">really upset</u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">really hurt by it yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then like he made it sound also that they had a lot of problems for a long time but people just never saw that like</u>
<u n="352" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439">he was like we used to argue all the time about stupid stuff</u>
<u n="354" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">and she used to storm off in a mood and</u>
<u n="356" who="S0441">I can imagine her being really hard to argue with <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0439">oh yeah I can imagine her just being like if she doesn't get her own way she would stomp off until she does</u>
<u n="358" who="S0441">yeah and he'd always have to go to her <unclear>and not</unclear></u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">yeah mm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0441">oh well she'll find someone else I'm sure</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">probably quite soon <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0441">probably I bet he will as well to be honest</u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">mm yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0441">he's in that right sort of erm <pause dur="long"/> what's the word? <pause dur="long"/> what's the word?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">I don't know I'm not sure what you're trying to imply</u>
<u n="366" who="S0441"><unclear>I think</unclear> he's always with people isn't he? it's not like he's</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0441">he's in a job where he always meets people</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0441"><unclear/> so I'm sure he'll meet people</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439">and he said he's er he's been going on a few dates with this girl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so</u>
<u n="372" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is her name apparently she didn't go to our school though she went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0441"><unclear>is she on Facebook</unclear>?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">yeah she's on Facebook seriously she looks like a right tramp</u>
<u n="376" who="S0441">oh this is the person that he?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">he cheated on her with yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0441">that he's <trunc>g</trunc> now going on dates with her?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0441">that was probably the the beginning of the end then wasn't it?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0441">when he cheated on her</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439">he also said that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like cos obviously the <trunc>c</trunc> the whole <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> commute was a bit of a pain he was like when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> suggested moving to like <anon type="place"/> and commuting and I was like well I don't wanna drag her out if we broke up in six months <unclear>it's</unclear> like so you <trunc>y</trunc>you were already thinking that you might break up and he was like yeah I was like well then that just says it all doesn't it?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439">like if you don't wanna move in with your girlfriend of seven years</u>
<u n="388" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439">because you're worried it might not work</u>
<u n="390" who="S0441">that's the time</u>
<u n="391" who="S0439">that's the yeah you should be like enthusiastic about moving in with your girlfriend not <trunc>t</trunc> saying oh well it might not work you should be like oh it's gonna work it's gonna be amazing I'm so excited about this</u>
<u n="392" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439">he was like yep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0441"><unclear>oh dear</unclear></u>
<u n="395" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like obviously no I I do I <trunc>d</trunc> I was gonna message <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I was like I don't think I'm a person she would ever want to hear from so</u>
<u n="396" who="S0441">probably not</u>
<u n="397" who="S0439">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> we've never been bosom pals have we?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0439">yeah she's completely different</u>
<u n="400" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>completely different</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I've also got three mutual friends <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">oh god apparently she went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0441">is er <unclear/> is that near us?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0439">it's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0441">yes I've got two mutual friends <unclear/> Facebook</u>
<u n="405" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0441">and she works at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0439">yeah at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439">so this is gonna sound really horrible of me but she's probably not the brightest bunny in the forest but</u>
<u n="410" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0439">but then no offence but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't the brightest</u>
<u n="412" who="S0441">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't either</u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">yeah he wasn't the brightest bunny in the forest <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0441">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is</u>
<u n="415" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0441"><trunc>n</trunc>not that not that that makes any difference at all but</u>
<u n="417" who="S0439" trans="overlap">not yeah obviously not that yeah yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0441">wow big news <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think there is anyone else that's still together is there?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0441">even at all like I'm trying to think of like people that were at school <trunc>toge</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">I genuinely can't think of anybody from school who's still together</u>
<u n="422" who="S0441">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is still going out oh but I don't think they went out anyway in school</u>
<u n="423" who="S0439">who was that? who is she with now?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0441"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0439">can't think of him</u>
<u n="426" who="S0441">they were in art in <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0439"><unclear>I know who <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was but I don't know who he is like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a right weirdo</unclear></u>
<u n="428" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure you did</u>
<u n="429" who="S0439">oh well I obviously blanked him from my memory <vocal desc="laugh"/> he obviously didn't fill my life with any joy but erm <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah no one else I can really think of is still in a relationship with somebody else from school</u>
<u n="430" who="S0441">just them two <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0441">flying the flag</u>
<u n="433" who="S0439">they're done and dusted now</u>
<u n="434" who="S0441"><unclear/> <unclear>the flag</unclear></u>
<u n="435" who="S0439">I did say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> whether he think they'd get back together in the in like in the future he was like mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0441" trans="overlap">but then again I <trunc>g</trunc> I guess <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would've said probably no wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">mm well no I think people always get back together</u>
<u n="438" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439">I think people break up then get back together and then</u>
<u n="440" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0439">either yeah er either they're gonna get married and stay together forever or they're gonna break up <trunc>s</trunc> you know again</u>
<u n="442" who="S0441"><unclear>that's enough</unclear></u>
<u n="443" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> because they're like no</u>
<u n="444" who="S0441">like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0439">exactly like you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bless him</u>
<u n="446" who="S0441">don't bless him</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439">okay sorry I will not bless <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="448" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0439"><unclear/> I think he's still with erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though</u>
<u n="450" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0441">lucky <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="452" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0439"><unclear/> other women he probably slept with in the time</u>
<u n="454" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I keep thinking er that it obviously says play seven thirty but I keep thinking it says pay seven thirty</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439">oh no play yeah we've got erm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0441"><unclear/> like why are you paying so much money on the seventeenth? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0439">somebody somebody in my office who left he was head of marketing he was part time what he does part time is like do create er create write plays and produce plays and erm our team are going out as like a team outing</u>
<u n="458" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439">to go and see him on his opening night</u>
<u n="460" who="S0441"><unclear>nice</unclear></u>
<u n="461" who="S0439">I don't know if he knows that we're going but we are</u>
<u n="462" who="S0441">he's not he's he's not acting in it though? he's</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0441">oh he is?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">he is he's acting directing <trunc>produc</trunc> I'm not entirely sure the difference between the director and the producer are but he's doing all of it</u>
<u n="466" who="S0441">is it a monologue?</u>
<u n="467" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0439">just him a one man band</u>
<u n="469" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0439">bless him</u>
<u n="471" who="S0441">oh that's good</u>
<u n="472" who="S0439"><unclear>but yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="473" who="S0441">can you imagine? that'd be <unclear>the fact that you can go to where you work</unclear></u>
<u n="474" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="475" who="S0441">I've produced directed and starring in my own play</u>
<u n="476" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's called</u>
<u n="477" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0439">it's called the man who stars produces and directs his own play <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0441">and also do all the music</u>
<u n="480" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">if I hop off for a moment it's cos I've got to change the CD</u>
<u n="482" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0441"><unclear>oh god</unclear></u>
<u n="484" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="485" who="S0441">have you got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> coming as well? <unclear>or is she</unclear> <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0439">she's well I'm supposed to be catching up er catching up with her in the afternoon but we haven't really planned anything and <unclear><trunc>w</trunc>er well</unclear></u>
<u n="487" who="S0441"><unclear/> there</u>
<u n="488" who="S0439">pardon?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0441"><unclear/> there</u>
<u n="490" who="S0439">the problem with <anon type="place"/> it's <trunc>k</trunc> it's kind of inbetween</u>
<u n="491" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0439">cos it's really difficult for some reason to get to <anon type="place"/> from <trunc>t</trunc> from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> or vice versa and she doesn't drive and I can't be bothered to drive all the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0439">but she er so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the biggest hypochondriac I've ever met in my entire life so she was gonna come to <anon type="place"/> with me and she goes well I woke up in the middle of the night and my knee really hurts so I can't go I was like oh okay that's fine don't worry</u>
<u n="495" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0439">and then she messaged me <unclear>she was saying being like</unclear> oh I really had the flu this weekend and I'm really recovering from that I was like okay <unclear/> okay <unclear>but but like should you actually be</unclear> going anywhere if you have a dodgy knee and the flu and she was like I don't know <unclear>I was like</unclear> okay just let me know <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I've got a netball <trunc>ma</trunc> netball match on in the morning</u>
<u n="497" who="S0441">what? with the team?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0439">yeah I had my first netball match two weeks ago</u>
<u n="499" who="S0441">how did it go?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0439">it went really well really well played centre for three quarters</u>
<u n="501" who="S0441">oh cool</u>
<u n="502" who="S0439">oh good god I couldn't get my piercing out</u>
<u n="503" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0439">one woman tried to help didn't realise it was a screw and tried to like yank it and I was like ow you are actually like pulling my tragus and she went well oh er are you <trunc>s</trunc> not supposed to? I'm like no you're supposed to twist the ball at the end and she was like oh erm sorry about that I was like <unclear>yeah could you stop it</unclear>? so</u>
<u n="505" who="S0441"><unclear>get off me</unclear></u>
<u n="506" who="S0439">I couldn't so I didn't play for the first quarter because you're not allowed to play with any piercings in</u>
<u n="507" who="S0441"><unclear>oh gosh</unclear></u>
<u n="508" who="S0439">but luckily we had enough people though and then I managed to get it out but I had to go to the there's like a tattoo piercing shop in <anon type="place"/> which is new well newish and they put a different one in for me which is easier to take out</u>
<u n="509" who="S0441">is it a hoop?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0439">yeah I don't like it very much I prefer just a plain stud but I need it I need one that can come out easily but erm but yeah no I played really well and I got an email from the captain being like you played really well for your first match I'm really impressed and you're</u>
<u n="511" who="S0441">woo</u>
<u n="512" who="S0439">you're an asset to the team apparently so</u>
<u n="513" who="S0441">oh wow</u>
<u n="514" who="S0439">I was like yay</u>
<u n="515" who="S0441">all that school netball paid off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0439">yep school netball but erm but no yeah apart from that it's been a bit just been chilled had a little <unclear>strop</unclear> last week <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0441">good</u>
<u n="518" who="S0439">so yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0441">I might go home this weekend I don't know cos my <trunc>unc</trunc> my uncle's had a bit of a funny turn again so <unclear>he's coming</unclear> to stay for the week on Saturday</u>
<u n="520" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0441">but <unclear>I don't even know whether</unclear> to go back I'm either going back to be there just for my mum cos <unclear/> <unclear>find it</unclear> really heavy going</u>
<u n="522" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0441">cos <unclear/> or I don't go back cos I don't wanna be there I don't really wanna be around him</u>
<u n="524" who="S0439">what's wrong with him?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0441">he's just an alcoholic <unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0439">I thought yeah I thought he was but I was like is that the <unclear/> <trunc>confu</trunc> am I confusing him with somebody else or is he the alcoholic?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0441">no <pause dur="short"/> he's the alcoholic one it's just really sad really he's just had such a shitty life</u>
<u n="528" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah obviously it is like it is a disease isn't it? so</u>
<u n="529" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0439">it's not his fault but</u>
<u n="531" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> not his fault I mean he's just had he can't cope socially or emotionally he can't he's really like he really it's really odd he's really like fragile it's very strange</u>
<u n="532" who="S0439">oh it's one of those things where it's like you don't really wanna be there but you probably should go back and support your mum</u>
<u n="533" who="S0441">I know cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't</u>
<u n="534" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0441">cos he can't be bothered with it he's very black and white you know he doesn't get things like that</u>
<u n="536" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0441">he will just sort of he'll probably go out <vocal desc="laugh"/> but <unclear>I think I should be there</unclear></u>
<u n="538" who="S0439">mm like my mum's like do you wanna come to <anon type="place"/> with me? I'm like mm no I'm fine and I normally go not because obviously I do wanna see my grandad but it's just <trunc>lo</trunc> such a long way but normally I'd go for her</u>
<u n="539" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0439">cos I know that she struggles with it like</u>
<u n="541" who="S0441">yeah and er</u>
<u n="542" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0441">I suppose if I can be helpful maybe <unclear>any</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0439">well if not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming here on <trunc>S</trunc> on Sunday if you wanna be there</u>
<u n="545" who="S0441">okay I'm definitely going</u>
<u n="546" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I knew you were gonna say that</u>
<u n="547" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's nice why's she coming here? just <unclear/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0439">well I sent her a message a few weeks ago just being like haven't heard from you in a while how's it going? and she sent me a message being like oh I'm on holiday <trunc>s</trunc> I'm sorry but I will message you when I get back</u>
<u n="549" who="S0441">yeah I saw her holiday pictures</u>
<u n="550" who="S0439">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has put on so much weight again hasn't he?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0441">I didn't see him I just saw her <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0439">okay I'm <unclear/> like a massive bitch right then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0441">no I haven't seen him I I might agree with you</u>
<u n="554" who="S0439">erm and so and then she sent me a message she was like oh hi I'm back from holiday it's <trunc>s</trunc> been so long do you wanna do something? and I was like yeah okay and obviously because she lives in <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="555" who="S0441"><unclear>it's</unclear> so close</u>
<u n="556" who="S0439">it's so close she's gonna come here and then I'm gonna drive us into town and do that and we're just gonna do some shopping</u>
<u n="557" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's erm it takes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like under half an hour to <unclear/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0441">it's really close <unclear/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0439">but yeah she's just gonna come here for the day and we're gonna go into town and do some shopping and just have a catch up really she needs to get some work clothes so</u>
<u n="561" who="S0441"><unclear>mm a riding holiday</unclear></u>
<u n="562" who="S0439">did she?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0441"><unclear>no she just video of her riding</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0439">oh no she just likes riding I think <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0441">oh I see it is it is in <anon type="place"/> that's <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0441"><unclear/> <unclear>holiday</unclear></u>
<u n="568" who="S0439">yeah so she's got like</u>
<u n="569" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0439">he kind of was really heavy then he lost a bit of weight and then he just put it all back on <pause dur="short"/> as horrible as I sound I'm such a horrible person</u>
<u n="571" who="S0441">she's not looking too bad though</u>
<u n="572" who="S0439">no she's looking <trunc>sh</trunc> er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s always been quite pretty though I think</u>
<u n="573" who="S0441">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0439">not like erm <pause dur="short"/> not like erm oh I'm trying to think like you know American Hollywood sweetheart pretty</u>
<u n="575" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="576" who="S0439">but she's always been quite <pause dur="short"/> erm she is yeah she's quite a pretty girl I think <unclear>but</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0441">with a large boyfriend <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0439">yeah I actually I I was really <trunc>horrib</trunc> well no not horrible it was just funny I showed erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a picture of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then a picture of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she was just like what is wrong with your friend's like taste in men?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>but she's got got</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0439">yeah I was like I know it's hilarious isn't it? I was like they both look like Mr Bean</u>
<u n="581" who="S0441">what does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> look like <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually I think oh don't don't quote me on this and don't mock me but I think he's actually got a bit better looking with age but that doesn't mean I think he's good looking</u>
<u n="583" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0439">but he's just a bit better <trunc>l</trunc> he's not as like sickly looking or just like pointy looking or just like ill looking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0441"><unclear>yeah</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> he looks a little bit more healthy</u>
<u n="586" who="S0439">he genuinely just used to look ill though didn't he? <unclear>he</unclear> was just like odd looking no you see I <trunc>w</trunc> he's never gonna be sexy but he's not as unattractive as he used to be</u>
<u n="587" who="S0441">I'm gonna try and find a before and after</u>
<u n="588" who="S0439">oh er I I definitely did find <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> before and after <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she was just like why why does your friend like these men? I'm like well I hoped she was blind but but but she isn't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0439">she just has really bad taste <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="591" who="S0439">oh my god that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0441">yeah I know but er</u>
<u n="593" who="S0439">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was just so bad when erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> he turned round and told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm like before they even started going out he was like oh yeah I fancied <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I never fancied you</u>
<u n="594" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0441">what is it <trunc>w</trunc>? seriously guys like seriously</u>
<u n="596" who="S0439">I mean I me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> look nothing like each other</u>
<u n="597" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="598" who="S0439">like it'd be it'd be weird you know it would be more likely that he'd fancy me then fancy <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are probably more similar but to fancy <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and me and not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is a bit bizarre cos <unclear>we are</unclear> completely different looking</u>
<u n="599" who="S0441" trans="overlap">maybe he likes maybe he really likes personality maybe <unclear/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0439">cos I have an amazing personality <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="601" who="S0441">maybe he maybe he saw something in your personality that he liked</u>
<u n="602" who="S0439">true maybe <pause dur="short"/> mm god that was a weird picture of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0439">a bit shaggy wasn't he?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0439"><unclear>with his hairy hair going on</unclear></u>
<u n="607" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0439">he's bulked up now he's really muscly</u>
<u n="609" who="S0441">I haven't got him on Facebook though</u>
<u n="610" who="S0439">you're not Facebook friends?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0441">I haven't had my Facebook for ages</u>
<u n="612" who="S0439">have you not?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0441">like <unclear/> years</u>
<u n="614" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0441"><unclear/> Facebook <unclear/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I love Facebook stalking people it's like the only way you're <trunc>legitima</trunc>  <trunc>y</trunc>you're legitimately allowed to stalk somebody without anybody like caring although me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were doing that on Monday night and she accidentally like nearly tagged her ex boyfriend in one of his own profile pictures</u>
<u n="617" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="618" who="S0439">she was like look at him he wasn't he wasn't very good looking was he? shit <vocal desc="laugh"/> and er she nearly we wasn't sure we weren't sure whether she actually did it</u>
<u n="619" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0439">and then we had to go back and double check</u>
<u n="621" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0439">and she was like oh my god oh my god</u>
<u n="623" who="S0441">that's so embarrassing</u>
<u n="624" who="S0439">cos what do you do? like it's gonna <trunc>c</trunc> it'd come up on his news feed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have tagged you in your own Facebook profile</u>
<u n="625" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0441">from fifteen years ago</u>
<u n="627" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0439">erm were you Facebook stalking me by any chance?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0441">it's like Instagram when you scroll down <unclear/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0441">and you get to like eighty-three weeks in and you like something that's really obviously that you've obviously been</u>
<u n="633" who="S0439">stalking</u>
<u n="634" who="S0441">stalking I've only got him erm <pause dur="short"/> from this time last year <unclear/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0439">I yeah is it him looking up at you?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="637" who="S0439">yeah I think that's the same I don't really know I don't really look at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s profile very often it's only cos he put a photo recently up and he had like a massive like bulging bicep I was like you clearly have nothing else to do in Australia apart from go to the gym apparently <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0441"><unclear>life</unclear></u>
<u n="639" who="S0439">mm looking very brown though</u>
<u n="640" who="S0441">yeah he always looked really brown though</u>
<u n="641" who="S0439">I've also got some other news which is not as good</u>
<u n="642" who="S0441">what?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0439">er my mum might be made redundant</u>
<u n="644" who="S0441">oh god</u>
<u n="645" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0441">why?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0439">cos erm you know they're being made into an academy?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0439">they literally all came in on Monday so they had a week back came in on Monday and the head teacher was like pretty much all your jobs are at risk</u>
<u n="650" who="S0441">as in the whole staff <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0439">yeah well er all the admin</u>
<u n="652" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="653" who="S0439">I'm not sure about <trunc>teachi</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was made redundant <pause dur="short"/> like I think his is er he has officially been made redundant</u>
<u n="654" who="S0441">shit</u>
<u n="655" who="S0439">all the heads of houses have been not heads of houses that's a Harry Potter reference</u>
<u n="656" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0439">all the heads of year have been made redundant but don't tell anybody cos I don't know like mum's job is up is one of the candidates for redundancy</u>
<u n="658" who="S0441">so like are heads of year teachers as well? they've been made redundant anyway?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0439">I don't think they're teachers I think heads of year are just people who are like who look after the year group</u>
<u n="660" who="S0441">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was head of year wasn't she <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0439">possibly yeah I think they actually created roles specifically</u>
<u n="662" who="S0441">oh okay so <unclear/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0439">for people who are head of year erm but I think because mum's probably one of the highest paid admin staff she is at risk</u>
<u n="664" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is at risk erm and they're gonna release some jobs because obviously what are they gonna do without mum?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0441">I hate these things cos they all like obviously they've gotta cut money don't they? so they're just like oh get rid of her</u>
<u n="667" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0441">because she's really expensive but then shit happens down the line</u>
<u n="669" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0441">because you're not <unclear/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0439">cos you don't have an exams officer</u>
<u n="672" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0439">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been made redundant like I think she has officially been er made redundant</u>
<u n="676" who="S0441">is that your mum's friend?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0439">er the one <trunc>m</trunc>mum's assistant person</u>
<u n="678" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0439">so yeah they're literally hacking hacking <unclear/> back</u>
<u n="680" who="S0441">can't they just hack people back that aren't as important? that sounds really horrible but</u>
<u n="681" who="S0439">like teachers? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0441">well people that are sort of less lower like less paid</u>
<u n="683" who="S0439">mm?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0441">and hack back more</u>
<u n="685" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0441">and then <trunc>ha</trunc> it'll be the equivalent because</u>
<u n="687" who="S0439">apparently all four deputy heads are keeping all four PAs though</u>
<u n="688" who="S0441">oh great</u>
<u n="689" who="S0439">yeah so you might not have an exams officer but at least you have a secretary to write up all the notes when parents complain about the fact that you don't have an exams officer</u>
<u n="690" who="S0441">yeah and write all the reports for you</u>
<u n="691" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0441"><unclear/> four deputy heads?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0439">apparently so with four PAs well one no one head teacher and four deputy heads sorry and all four of them have PAs</u>
<u n="694" who="S0441"><unclear>why have they got so many deputy heads</unclear>?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0439">I don't know how many <unclear/>? well because they were probably cos their school is now like sixteen hundred people</u>
<u n="696" who="S0441">true</u>
<u n="697" who="S0439">cos they've just taken on the the year</u>
<u n="698" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0439">eights and sevens haven't they? but yeah so I'm not entirely I'm just not sure what they're thinking because no offence but mum's job is really important</u>
<u n="700" who="S0441">what are they gonna do <unclear>when er</unclear> without her?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0439">I don't know</u>
<u n="702" who="S0441">are they gonna <trunc>ha</trunc> like get somebody else? <unclear/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0439">I er genuinely don't know like no one else <unclear/></u>
<u n="704" who="S0441">do it differently?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0439">like how else can you organise exams?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0441">cos you've got like a lot of experience going <unclear/></u>
<u n="707" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0441">she knows what she's doing <unclear/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0439"><unclear/> like she is the only person who can use SIMS she's the only person who does data she is the only person who knows how to organise an exam and do like all the data entry sheets for the grades so I'm not entirely sure what they're thinking of doing</u>
<u n="710" who="S0441"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="711" who="S0439">but like mum's worried that they'll make them both redundant and then get them to like get her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to like apply for the same job but then mum's like I don't want to go up against <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in a job</u>
<u n="712" who="S0441"><unclear>no</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="713" who="S0439">I'm like well you're gonna have to aren't you?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0441">yeah I suppose I suppose you have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0439">so yeah <trunc>sca</trunc> well not scary times but</u>
<u n="718" who="S0441">not very nice</u>
<u n="719" who="S0439">sad times it's just so stupid to bring them back one week after <trunc>t</trunc> like term starts to then threaten them with redundancy</u>
<u n="720" who="S0441">should've done it before term even started <unclear/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0439">yeah cos then it gives them the chance to find a new job like</u>
<u n="722" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0439">all the postings for schools would've come up during the summer holidays</u>
<u n="724" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0439">so now all of these people who work in the school won't be able to get jobs really until next year</u>
<u n="726" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="727" who="S0439">if they want to go back into education</u>
<u n="728" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="730" who="S0441"><unclear>does your mum do anything else</unclear>? <unclear/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0439">yeah she could work for like <anon type="place"/> or you know one of the exam boards and stuff like that</u>
<u n="732" who="S0441"><unclear>oh okay</unclear></u>
<u n="733" who="S0439">but I don't know she literally found out on Monday and that was dad's sixtieth birthday so</u>
<u n="734" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="735" who="S0439">cos we were gonna drive over to <anon type="place"/> and take her out for lunch cos dad had the day off as well so erm yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0441">I remember you saying</u>
<u n="737" who="S0439">and then so she rang up and was like don't come like I can't really go out for lunch and celebrate when all these people are at risk of losing their job and then she rang back an hour later and was like actually I might be at risk of losing my job it was like oh fuck <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>but erm</unclear> luckily dad's salary is okay to er cos they don't have to pay their mortgage off anymore so I think they have like they've got enough</u>
<u n="738" who="S0441">but still</u>
<u n="739" who="S0439">but it's still like just the mental side of just <trunc>si</trunc> you can't just retire at fifty-eight years old</u>
<u n="740" who="S0441">oh my goodness your mum will literally become addicted to online poker</u>
<u n="741" who="S0439"><unclear/> yeah yeah she'll just sit there on the Ipad all day</u>
<u n="742" who="S0441">she will</u>
<u n="743" who="S0439">and do nothing for like the next</u>
<u n="744" who="S0441">this can't happen <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="745" who="S0439">the next thirty years of her life</u>
<u n="746" who="S0441">this can't happen</u>
<u n="747" who="S0439">no dad's like you have to do something</u>
<u n="748" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh or she'll just continuously watch box sets over and over and over and over again</u>
<u n="749" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0439">she'll know er know Buffy inside out she already knows Buffy inside out</u>
<u n="752" who="S0441">she can't do that</u>
<u n="753" who="S0439">no Buffy what else would she start watching? she'd start <trunc>w</trunc> just watching like everything</u>
<u n="754" who="S0441">she wouldn't even care anymore she'd just start watching it</u>
<u n="755" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no she she <pause dur="short"/> it'd just be awful so</u>
<u n="756" who="S0441">or she'd just go wild with the credit card</u>
<u n="757" who="S0439">she can't go wild with the credit card she hasn't got any money</u>
<u n="758" who="S0441">but just imagine the temptation</u>
<u n="759" who="S0439"><unclear>true</unclear> but then dad would have all control over the money</u>
<u n="760" who="S0441">true</u>
<u n="761" who="S0439">she wouldn't</u>
<u n="762" who="S0441"><unclear/> <trunc>would</trunc>wouldn't be any of hers would it?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0439">no it'd all be his</u>
<u n="764" who="S0441">I can imagine her strolling around the kitchen thinking oh I really need a</u>
<u n="765" who="S0439">new mixer</u>
<u n="766" who="S0441">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0439">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will you give me the money? no</u>
<u n="768" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I really need an apple corer</u>
<u n="769" who="S0439">no you don't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0439">she'd have to ask him for money</u>
<u n="772" who="S0441">oh no oh no she'd hate that</u>
<u n="773" who="S0439">she would hate that so much she still has <trunc>acce</trunc>access to all his credit cards and everything but still</u>
<u n="774" who="S0441"><unclear>she'd just hate that</unclear></u>
<u n="775" who="S0439">I I don't know what she does with her money</u>
<u n="776" who="S0441">we've <trunc>alr</trunc> we've already had this discussion</u>
<u n="777" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="778" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="779" who="S0439">like I think she gets paid something like twenty-six thousand pounds which is about say hypothetically it's fifteen hundred a month what does she do with it?</u>
<u n="780" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0439">she doesn't have any bills to pay cos dad pays them all she doesn't have a mortgage to pay cos it's done</u>
<u n="782" who="S0441">she buys shit <vocal desc="laugh"/> we've already said this <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0439">what the fuck? <vocal desc="laugh"/> mum what the fuck are you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0441">gambles it all away on <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0439">she probably does and buys bloody cook books</u>
<u n="786" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0441">cook books and box sets</u>
<u n="788" who="S0439"><unclear>too much</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0441"><unclear/> games for her Ipad</u>
<u n="790" who="S0439">clothes</u>
<u n="791" who="S0441">woolly jumpers</u>
<u n="792" who="S0439">yeah woolly jumpers her and her woolly jumpers haircuts I <trunc>suppo</trunc> I suppose she goes to the <trunc>hai</trunc></u>
<u n="793" who="S0441">glasses</u>
<u n="794" who="S0439">glasses oh my god glasses <vocal desc="laugh"/> shoes shoes are her new thing the Doc Martens shop is just round the corner so she now like</u>
<u n="795" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0439">goes like every other week and buys a pair of shoes</u>
<u n="797" who="S0441">round the corner from where?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0439">it's just past <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0441">oh okay</u>
<u n="800" who="S0439">so not literally round the corner</u>
<u n="801" who="S0441">oh right I was gonna say</u>
<u n="802" who="S0439">but figuratively twenty minutes down the road</u>
<u n="803" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="804" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="805" who="S0441">oh I can see her in Doc Martens</u>
<u n="806" who="S0439">yeah she does love them I always find them a bit clumpy and a bit thick</u>
<u n="807" who="S0441"><unclear/> <unclear>I would be like</unclear> be a Doc Marten kinda person</u>
<u n="808" who="S0439">no you have to have like have a very like specific outfit I think to pull them off you'd have to plan the outfit</u>
<u n="809" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0439">and I can't do it</u>
<u n="811" who="S0441">too much hassle</u>
<u n="812" who="S0439">yep <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> people'd just be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what the fuck are you wearing on your feet? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="814" who="S0439">erm yeah no I think apart from so what have we gone through? we've gone through the Great North Run netball match <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mum what <unclear>else do I have to tick</unclear> off my list? I think that's everything that's happened don't think you've missed anything apart from that</u>
<u n="815" who="S0441">good</u>
<u n="816" who="S0439">apart from a man died doing the Great North Run</u>
<u n="817" who="S0441">really?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0439">yeah of natural causes fifty-eight years old</u>
<u n="819" who="S0441">oh that's <unclear/> sad</u>
<u n="820" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="821" who="S0441">were all his family were there as well?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0441">that's really sad</u>
<u n="824" who="S0439">and he was apparently he'd run it loads of times before</u>
<u n="825" who="S0441">was it his heart?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0439">I should think it was a heart attack or something yeah</u>
<u n="827" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="828" who="S0439">mm it's like oh yeah thirteen miles isn't going to kill you well maybe maybe speak again yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0441">it's okay the world's gonna end next week so it's fine</u>
<u n="830" who="S0439">why's the world gonna end next week?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0441">apparently people are saying the world's gonna end cos there's an <trunc>astero</trunc><trunc>ast</trunc>asteroid?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0439">yeah asteroid or</u>
<u n="833" who="S0441">heading towards the earth</u>
<u n="834" who="S0439">fabulous</u>
<u n="835" who="S0441">but NASA have already established that that is not happening</u>
<u n="836" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="837" who="S0441">but people are still <unclear/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0439">carrying on yeah but people were sort of like it was gonna be the end of the world like a few years ago wasn't it?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0441"><unclear/> every five years it happens</u>
<u n="840" who="S0439">mm every five years people are gonna and then one day it will come and they'll be like in your face we told you so we'll be like</u>
<u n="841" who="S0441">exactly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0439">yeah okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0441">sorry</u>
<u n="844" who="S0439">sorry we didn't believe you this time you nut job</u>
<u n="845" who="S0441">there's gonna be earthquakes tsunamis and just terror <unclear>I think</unclear></u>
<u n="846" who="S0439">I look forward to that tsunami <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="847" who="S0441"><unclear>me too</unclear></u>
<u n="848" who="S0439">as we live in the slap bang in the middle of the country</u>
<u n="849" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0441">to be fair <unclear>maybe</unclear> a big enough tsunami'd probably take us out</u>
<u n="851" who="S0439">it would have to be <trunc>hu</trunc> like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="852" who="S0441">yeah quite big</u>
<u n="853" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a massive one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0441">if it's the end of the world though you'd expect it</u>
<u n="855" who="S0439">I think this house is sturdy enough I'm sure it is fine <unclear/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0441"><unclear/> the cellar that'd be good</u>
<u n="857" who="S0439">hide in the cupboard <vocal desc="laugh"/> <event desc="sound of phone"/> oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? is he alright? is it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0441">no it's his mum</u>
<u n="859" who="S0439">mum? what's she saying?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0441"><unclear/> she's saying that I should cos I was saying that I'm getting stressed at work and she just <unclear/> stressed <unclear/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0439">are you besties with his mum?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0441"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="863" who="S0439">BFFs for life?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0439">is she gonna be your maid of honour now? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0441">no she's the mother of the groom</u>
<u n="867" who="S0439">oh yeah true <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> so when's he gonna pop the question?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0441">not yet</u>
<u n="869" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0441">not just yet it's happening so quickly you know er like time sort flies over you it's like oh shit</u>
<u n="871" who="S0439">yep</u>
<u n="872" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0439">I can't believe it's mid September already to be honest</u>
<u n="874" who="S0441">I know <vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0439">oh I booked two holidays as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0441">oh what? Lapland and where else?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0439">oh no that er Lapland was ages ago because I er</u>
<u n="878" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0439">I booked because Lapland I'm going from the twenty-second to the twenty-eighth of December <unclear>before I go</unclear> on the the on the seventh to ninth of November which is a Saturday to a Monday I'm going to Bratislava we've got a ninety-<trunc>ni</trunc> er both <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm both this one and the next holiday were ninety-nine pounds on Secret Escapes</u>
<u n="880" who="S0441">oh good</u>
<u n="881" who="S0439">so Bratislava from Saturday to the Monday and that's from the <trunc>secon</trunc> no second weekend in November and then I'm going to Naples for four days Friday to the Monday all inclusive flights breakfast hotel ninety-nine pounds as well</u>
<u n="882" who="S0441">when's that?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0439">last weekend in November</u>
<u n="884" who="S0441">so you're going the first week and last week?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0439">second week and last week</u>
<u n="886" who="S0441">cool</u>
<u n="887" who="S0439">so yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0441">nice who's that with?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="891" who="S0439">from <anon type="place"/> from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0441">that is cheap isn't it?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0439">I know we just saw</u>
<u n="894" who="S0441">Secret Escapes is so good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="895" who="S0439">I know I love Secret Escapes</u>
<u n="896" who="S0441">that was our holiday Secret Escapes</u>
<u n="897" who="S0439">mm I don't I don't no <trunc>th</trunc>they're fine people say isn't that really expensive? I was like</u>
<u n="898" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="899" who="S0439">actually no it's like it's fine</u>
<u n="900" who="S0441">and it's yeah it's cos you can guarantee that it's a nice place as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0439">yeah like they have like saver the ones we bought were called saver holidays they were like right go on the cheap but they're still really nice hotels</u>
<u n="902" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0439">and like we get like a welcome cocktail when we arrive and everything and when we went to Berlin it was perfect</u>
<u n="904" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="905" who="S0439">we had no problems so</u>
<u n="906" who="S0441"><unclear>same with</unclear> our Brussels one that was really good</u>
<u n="907" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0441">and that was really really nice hotel actually</u>
<u n="909" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I I like Secret Escapes it's a <unclear>good old</unclear> secret</u>
<u n="910" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="911" who="S0441"><unclear/> though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="912" who="S0439"><unclear/> everbody knows <unclear/> now <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="913" who="S0441">even though everyone knows about it it's not changed</u>
<u n="914" who="S0439">no still amazing <unclear>but no</unclear> I desperately need the loo</u>
<u n="915" who="S0441"><unclear>well you go</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0439">I will I will indeed oh <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0439">what are you gonna have?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0441"><unclear>er well I was gonna have gnocchi but</unclear> <unclear/> effort</u>
<u n="920" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0439">so much effort okay</u>
<u n="922" who="S0441">don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="923" who="S0439">well I'm gonna go upstairs while you decide <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0441"><unclear>you have fun</unclear></u>
<u n="925" who="S0439">will do</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
