<text id="S63K">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The countryside, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>art exhibition, home repairs, dresses, auctions</topics>
		<activity>Couple go for a walk in the countryside.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T14</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0144">so what was that exhibition like?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">yeah it was really good <pause dur="short"/> em loads of dragonfly stuff <pause dur="short"/> never thought that loads of people would do <trunc>dragon</trunc> like specifically don't applied art works just for that <pause dur="short"/> they'd done em glass mosaic eh big massive massive eh glass mosaic dragonfly which <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> walked over to and went I can do that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0024">it's easy <pause dur="short"/> Which it is in theory but you've got to have the patience and you've got to have the time and you've got you know and then you've got to be meticulous about every part you do <pause dur="short"/> you've got to find all the materials and the glass and the this and the that <pause dur="short"/> I mean it might be in theory yeah smash a mirror and put put all the pieces in but <vocal desc="laugh"/> in theory yeah but time wise and dedication wise it's just not going to happen for me I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> mhm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> what and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that to the person who had made it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024">no we were just walking along looking</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0024">and then ah  and then eh  there were some really good photos close up photos <pause dur="short"/> don't know how they got such clear photos it's amazing</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0024">really clear close up photos of dragonflies <pause dur="short"/> beautiful <pause dur="short"/> eh then <trunc>so</trunc> there's some pottery like lovely</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what dragonfly pottery?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024">well no lovely made em bowls and plates</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144">with dragonflies on it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024">all this specific decoration <pause dur="short"/> yeah well it just had some painted a painted pattern with a dragonfly and a flower <pause dur="short"/> eh it was quite tastefully done like just one little a little tiny dragonfly on a white background <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was quite tastefully done <pause dur="short"/> was nice <pause dur="short"/> and then there was paintings and just every single I mean a quilt with like dragonfly made out of stitching <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">it was everybody kinda tweaked their own stuff to gear towards the theme <pause dur="short"/> was nice</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but there was some somebody had put up these kids' <trunc>pictu</trunc> they were like kids' pictures they were just like crayon drawings and that to me isn't art because I could seriously I could sit down and do that you know?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024">and not even put that much effort in you know those kind of drawings that you look at and somebody</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0024">and they're always the highest priced ones as well</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0024">it's kinda like a weird style of art but really it's just <pause dur="short"/> maybe they spent ages doing it but it does just the end result looks like a kid has drawn with some crayons <pause dur="short"/> so it's a shame</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144">so why why was it all about dragonflies?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024">em the gallery is called Dragonfly Gallery and like this woman oh we spoke to the owner cos we spoke to the people doing it <pause dur="short"/> asked to be put back on the list and uh they uh what she say <pause dur="short"/> oh she <vocal desc="laugh"/> she came out to <trunc>se</trunc> to visit us cos they went in and said oh yes there's an artistic family here cos of me and dad selling it up a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/> and ah talking to the other to the person who does the exhibition</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0024">and so the owner came out she's got these dragonfly pins and everything she just loves dragonflies and she said the exhibition was supposed to be for her collection of dragonfly items <pause dur="short"/> and she was just going to put on this little tiny um she in the gallery she was going to put all of the items that she'd got over the years she's like this nice old lady over the years of all the dragonfly things she'd ever got</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0024">so pins and paintings and all of this <pause dur="short"/> and then uh she advertised it for all the other artists to for some other artists to come in and do some dragonfly stuff and uh she got too much so much stuff come in that there wasn't room for her little collection anymore</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144">aww</u>
<u n="32" who="S0024">so she didn't have any of her stuff on</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">but she couldn't sacrifice the artists' space kinda thing she was like well you know there were some some beautiful stuff there so it was like she didn't want to say sorry you can't have your dragonfly stuff</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> how much stuff was there? Was it a big place?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">no it's only little place <pause dur="short"/> but enough <pause dur="short"/> enough to let me see <pause dur="short"/> well it's split into two so I guess you've got one wall two walls two and a half walls and then the other side the half of the other two walls and then bits in between and tables with people had made little dragonfly earrings and jewels and you know necklaces and stuff</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0024">yeah so it was all a whole range of materials <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> should have come</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah well I was doing my work</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but then I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> anyway and like <pause dur="short"/> we met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the gallery and then I went with off with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> straight away and mum and dad came home so</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024">did the chimney man come?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0144">no he didn't phone</u>
<u n="44" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> although are we only doing the chimney cos we said</u>
<u n="46" who="S0024">no they they knew</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144" trans="overlap">or are they going to do it anyway?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024">the knew that it was a problem for ages <pause dur="short"/> they knew that it was a problem and they <vocal desc="gasp"/> I think we're gonna get rained on</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">yeah it's not looking too good is it?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0024">no shall we turn back?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144">ah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144">why well we're almost half way anyway <pause dur="short"/> if we go this way</u>
<u n="54" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144">so we'll carry on</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024">not really <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">so what does the chimney <pause dur="short"/> what is it chimney sweep or just chimney man?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> they had it swept but <trunc>so</trunc> it's leaking <pause dur="short"/> that's why their whole <vocal desc="cough"/> side of the chimney on the outside looks bad</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024">it's all stained black isn't it?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">it shouldn't be going through to the brick work but it has</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144">so what can he do to fix it?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0024">got to get the whole chimney done again haven't you? Whole new chimney <pause dur="short"/> that's a big job</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">yeah sounds like a big job</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024">and they've been looking at the other stuff and I'm wonder whether that's cos we said</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">no but it's good they need</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144">yeah well</u>
<u n="72" who="S0024">my dad said needs maintenance and you've got to keep on top of that otherwise you lose</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144" trans="overlap">to point out the pointing</u>
<u n="74" who="S0024">mm yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144">it does need doing</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144">it's the kinda thing I think if you are living in somewhere</u>
<u n="78" who="S0024">Don't notice</u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">you don't notice it yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it just gradually creeps up don't it?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but even as we left today they were looking it all the details of the house going Oh look at that</u>
<u n="81" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0024">yeah so I think they've really started to have a look and ah yeah they wanna get everything done but that's gonna cost a fortune</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144">yeah it's not cheap is it?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0024">I mean <pause dur="short"/> the only thing they were gonna have done this year was to have their windows painted <pause dur="short"/> and that costs enough</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0024">that costs enough and ah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144">they can do the ground floor ones can't they?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or we can do it couldn't we?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it's just the ones above like the conservatory and stuff</u>
<u n="90" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> it's not just the painting they've got all sanded down</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0024">properly <pause dur="short"/> and then a base coat cos they're all wooden <pause dur="short"/> base coat put on and then painted on top <pause dur="short"/> it's not just oh slap a bit of you know I can paint nice and neatly I'll do that window <pause dur="short"/> you've got to do all of the preparation</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0024">which I can't <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind doing the painting bit but to sand it all down and everything <pause dur="short"/> imagine</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot to do <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot to do <pause dur="short"/> like it's better if we're gonna go away there's still a lot wanted to do before we go</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0024">and then this rain doesn't help</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="100" who="S0024">we're walking directly into the black cloud</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144">needed the rain though</u>
<u n="102" who="S0024">eh</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144">still got a hosepipe ban though <vocal desc="laugh"/> Take some time to fill up the water level</u>
<u n="104" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah well it's not <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I mean it's not that much <unclear/> is it? That hail did you have hail here?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0024">that was a shocker <pause dur="short"/> where did that come from? And then it stopped and it was sunny</u>
<u n="107" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0024">S'like proper big hailstones</u>
<u n="109" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0024">quite massive</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144">April showers wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> it's good for the <trunc>gra</trunc> grass though look <pause dur="short"/> it's just sprouted everywhere <pause dur="short"/> rain and then sun rain sun <pause dur="short"/> plants love it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says it's good because then by August em cos they <trunc>sa</trunc> she said they had a rubbish August last year and that's cos it was sunny all of April <vocal desc="laugh"/> All all of the time it was fairly sunny <pause dur="short"/> quack quack</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0024">and eh em she reckons that cos they've had some rotten weather now then August is going to be beautiful ready for our party</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I hope she's right</u>
<u n="116" who="S0024">they've gone  they've gone  crazy picking their dresses</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0024">they're calling themselves bridesmaids and I never even said that</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0024">they're going oh we're yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> phoned up and then</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144">they're going to be the only ones in dresses won't they?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on the phone going oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we're just picking the bridesmaids' dresses</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0024">I didn't say bridesmaids I said they could be matrons or something like that matrons and they said they'd stand if they were matrons they'd stand at the a gate and say hello to people or something I don't know</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144">oh so if we've got bridesmaids what are they gonna do?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">they're gonna meet and greet</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024">meet great and I don't know <pause dur="short"/> dunno</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144">so <pause dur="short"/> are we</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024" trans="overlap">help out I dunno <pause dur="short"/> they're so <pause dur="short"/> they're unbelievably excited <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0144" trans="overlap">are we gonna <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0024">like I just sat there <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just sat there and they're like  they're like  going away oh what do you think about this design oh and <trunc>sha</trunc> and shall I book in nail to go and get our nails done we could all get our nails done and have a bit of pampering beforehand</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144" trans="overlap">bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">I said if I gets my nails done on the Tuesday they're going to be ruined by the Saturday <pause dur="short"/> I'm not exactly the most delicate person in the world <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Could you imagine I've had my nails painted before they just chip <pause dur="short"/> they just chip <pause dur="short"/> I'll go outside and do some gardening or dunno</u>
<u n="135" who="S0144">so I better get my haircut done then</u>
<u n="136" who="S0024">I think so I think the girls are going to rollick you if you don't cut your hair</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0024">actually I might do as well</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144">what cut my hair?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I might rollick you if you don't do your hair <pause dur="short"/> for the party</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024">yeah they're going  they're going  all out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> all out</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144">hm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024">they say all what flowers are you having for the pinholes no pin <pause dur="short"/> I don't know breast pocket I don't know <pause dur="short"/> pins something</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024">and I said I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> whatever flower I can pick in the garden <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't even going to plan to have <pause dur="short"/> I was just going to say pick a flower</u>
<u n="147" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there will be plenty flowers about <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0024">I mean does it have to be all the same?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="150" who="S0024">I don't care if people have different flowers they can pick their favourite <pause dur="short"/> it there is  there is  some kind of nice thing about uniformity though <pause dur="short"/> with the colour code or colour scheme something like that <pause dur="short"/> isn't there?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024" trans="overlap">like I am gonna buy all of the all like the best men <pause dur="short"/> your two best men <pause dur="short"/> a red tie</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0024" trans="overlap">is it just two? Is it just two</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144">oh Dave and Rick</u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">Dave and Rick is that? Cos I was <trunc>think</trunc> oh and you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh and me yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0024">and you yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but yeah deep <pause dur="short"/> the deep red wine like like that kinda uniformity is <unclear/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0144">yeah it's okay to coordinate something that but I I think it's nice not coordinating as well because</u>
<u n="162" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well maybe you should <unclear/> them</u>
<u n="163" who="S0144">specially cos it's gonna be a lot of nature like entwined with the wedding <pause dur="short"/> it's nice having the variety <pause dur="short"/> of the nature</u>
<u n="164" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well maybe</u>
<u n="165" who="S0144">if you conform too much to a certain look then it it makes it too human</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah well I think <pause dur="short"/> cos she thinks of things too human? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0144">well too yeah <pause dur="short"/> like you've influenced it <pause dur="short"/> too much <pause dur="short"/> don't wanna <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> quite like it wild</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024">and well <pause dur="short"/> ivo little Ivo he's in <unclear/> he was like I'm gonna wear my spongebob t-shirt to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding can I can I?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0024">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went No you can't <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>fe</trunc> I almost said aww course you can</u>
<u n="171" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0024">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like you've gotta wear something a bit smarter than that I was thinking I don't mind him wearing his spongebob t-shirt</u>
<u n="173" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0024">I watched Spongebob with him today</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144">did you?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> it was weird <pause dur="short"/> and freaky</u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">was it?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0024">and Spongebob is angry <pause dur="short"/> I always thought he would be a happy character but I've never seen it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144">I've never seen it either</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024">he's an angry character</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0024">and he was smashing things up <pause dur="short"/> he was smashing alarm clocks up</u>
<u n="183" who="S0144">was that just today or was he like that every?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0024" trans="overlap">because he didn't  he didn't  want his friend to get up for the competition <pause dur="short"/> so so he snuck in his room hid under his pillow or in his pillow scared him half to death and then smashed all of his alarm clocks up</u>
<u n="185" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">kind of thing is that?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0024">I was going to the kids God I'd be really scared if someone hid in my pillow <pause dur="short"/> then and then like he started smashing up this room and I was like oh dude I thought Spongebob was supposed to be nice <pause dur="short"/> I was trying to get them to see that he's being he was being a horrible idiot the character on the television cos they all look up to him</u>
<u n="189" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0024">not look up to him but they all see him as you know haha oh he's a cool character <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0144">I remember when I hid under my brother's bed <vocal desc="laugh"/> Actually <trunc>fel</trunc></u>
<u n="192" who="S0024">see you would have got that idea from the cartoon</u>
<u n="193" who="S0144">actually fell asleep under his bed for a good couple of hours <pause dur="short"/> then I woke up I don't know what time it must have been about twelve or something and he was only seven</u>
<u n="194" who="S0024">aww</u>
<u n="195" who="S0144">I just remember poking him under the bed <pause dur="short"/> like poking the mattress and then I <vocal desc="laugh"/> started making some growling noises</u>
<u n="196" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that is funny <pause dur="short"/> did he realise it was you or did he?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024">was he just petrified and better not able to even look underneath</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144" trans="overlap">he was terrified <pause dur="short"/> no I just heard him start whining and then he just leapt out</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0144">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> I was quite a mean brother really</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024">no that's quite funny though</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">and I hid in a I had like this monkey arm as well <pause dur="short"/> and I hid in his cupboard one night <vocal desc="laugh"/> and slowly opened the cupboard with this monkey arm out</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0144">so a similar effect <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah that's what older brothers are for though isn't it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's alright <pause dur="short"/> does Ricky even remember? I think he's talked about you hiding under the bed before actually</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">I think he has <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> God it's cold</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Bit cold</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144">so what are you doing tonight?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024">I was gonna do some work <pause dur="short"/> but I'm I'm very tired so I think I might play dad at table tennis</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144">it's eight o'clock now nearly</u>
<u n="214" who="S0024">yeah see</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">sss aw I really haven't done enough work this week <pause dur="short"/> crazy <pause dur="short"/> don't know where the time is <trunc>fly</trunc> is flying by and I'm not it's not like I'm dong loads of art work cos something like that <pause dur="short"/> lovely</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah well I'm just <pause dur="short"/> if I'm not working I'm just bored <pause dur="short"/> I've got nothing else to do</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024">well make your film <pause dur="short"/> you were gonna make that film that scary film with all of the hidey holes in the garden</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024">there you go wait for it to get like dusky <pause dur="short"/> dusk is quite the best time <pause dur="short"/> go out in the garden with your video camera</u>
<u n="221" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I need to make a storyboard a little bit and think of the scenes <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0024">you need the tripod <pause dur="short"/> just do it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0024">you could stick th microphone outside and try and get some some um animal noises</u>
<u n="225" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0024">couldn't you?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0024">I might play a game with mum ugh</u>
<u n="229" who="S0144">that house is beautiful isn't it?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0144">I do like that</u>
<u n="232" who="S0024"><unclear/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0144">not sure about those window frames though</u>
<u n="234" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0144">does look like an old barn doesn't it? I quite like the way they they get those big windows put in</u>
<u n="236" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> from the top yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0024">all the way down</u>
<u n="239" who="S0144">let's in <pause dur="short"/> cos the trouble with those old buildings is that they're so dark <pause dur="short"/> so you need big windows like that don't you</u>
<u n="240" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0144">surprised they're allowed planning permission to be honest</u>
<u n="242" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this is what I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> why aren't her and Ray buying land with a barn on it? Or with a shed on it even <pause dur="short"/> you know some sort of thing that then <pause dur="short"/> I'm lost</u>
<u n="243" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we only walk this way every day</u>
<u n="244" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="245" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> surely it would make much more sense to buy something with even if it was just a tiny shed <pause dur="short"/> like built on it already wouldn't that increase the chances of planning permission later? You know it's got a shed on it so you know</u>
<u n="247" who="S0144">I've no idea how it works</u>
<u n="248" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> meadowland</u>
<u n="249" who="S0144">I think so though if it's got some kind of structure on it already</u>
<u n="250" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0144">yeah well I hope it goes alright for them</u>
<u n="252" who="S0024">yeah me too</u>
<u n="253" who="S0144">do seem to be putting all their eggs in one basket though don't they?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go down though are you coming?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0144">oh are we invited are we?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I want to go and watch it <pause dur="short"/> but it's <unclear/> It's <unclear/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I don't know I might get <pause dur="short"/> oh is it?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0024">I was just gonna walk down</u>
<u n="259" who="S0144">oh right could do</u>
<u n="260" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0144">I might get twitchy though I might <pause dur="short"/> put my hand up or something</u>
<u n="262" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they said afterwards they might fancy going to the pub so we could take them to there</u>
<u n="263" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> which pub oh the pub</u>
<u n="264" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you know you get twitchy and put your arm <pause dur="short"/> I'll tape your hands down to your sides</u>
<u n="265" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0024">no problem <pause dur="short"/> we haven't even viewed any of the lands so it's not like you're gonna make any bids on it blindly <pause dur="short"/> would ya?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Dunno</u>
<u n="268" who="S0024">well we wouldn't have any deposit <pause dur="short"/> let's not even take a deposit with like this not take any any money or anything <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="269" who="S0144">is it just land? Is that?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0024">ah it's all sorts <pause dur="short"/> it's no it's one of the <pause dur="short"/> uh property auctions so it's land and property <pause dur="short"/> I've had a look at a couple that they're selling there</u>
<u n="271" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> on the website we could have a look <pause dur="short"/> if you want <pause dur="short"/> but we're not buying <pause dur="short"/> just looking</u>
<u n="273" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know we're not buying God <pause dur="short"/> don't worry I won't buy a house without telling you</u>
<u n="274" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'm surprised they haven't gone to view some more land but they just fell in love with this one <pause dur="short"/> haven't they? We still need to find dad that water table <pause dur="short"/> thing</u>
<u n="275" who="S0144"><unclear/> plane</u>
<u n="276" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="277" who="S0144">well don't they need to know that before they buy it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they will</u>
<u n="279" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0024">yeah they will</u>
<u n="281" who="S0144">how are they gonna find that out?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0024">there's supposed to be a big package coming through their door with all of the information about the land</u>
<u n="283" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="284" who="S0024">the the legal pack</u>
<u n="285" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="286" who="S0024">Cos you have to read the legal pack before you buy it don't you <pause dur="short"/> or you should</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">or you should do</u>
<u n="288" who="S0024" trans="overlap">the whole <pause dur="short"/> it's quite big I think these legal packs</u>
<u n="289" who="S0144">yeah do they have to pay for it?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0024">ah don't think so</u>
<u n="291" who="S0144">really? What you can just get any property and get a legal pack for it <pause dur="short"/> if it's up for sale?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> well how can they charge you for it? That's that won't be very fair</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144">well can't see how they can just give it out <pause dur="short"/> quite expensive wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0024">yeah I suppose <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> dunno <pause dur="short"/> maybe the auction pays for it for the legal packs cos they get their commission <pause dur="short"/> maybe it just comes off of off the auction fees</u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">well I think if anyone has to pay for it it would be the seller</u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0144">is that a sparrow</u>
<u n="298" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go I think it's next Thursday</u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">next Thursday</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024">I thought it's in the afternoon so I thought I'd just wander down to <unclear/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0144">oh next Thursday we might know if we're going or not</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024">yeah? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> might do <pause dur="short"/> that would be a shocker wouldn't it <pause dur="short"/> I think I'll be I'd be shocked and surprised and go oh no now I haven't got enough time to do all this stuff that I said I was gonna do</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024">well if it's not a positive answer by next week I'm gonna really lose heart <pause dur="short"/> and <vocal desc="laugh"/> although chip in on their land and go and live over there</u>
<u n="307" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">we'll chip in <pause dur="short"/> em they always  they always  kinda land on their feet in the end I just hope they make this <pause dur="short"/> this is a big decision <pause dur="short"/> massive <pause dur="short"/> massive</u>
<u n="309" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah once they have got his they won't be able to leave the country again</u>
<u n="310" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> this is what they want though</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's getting serious <pause dur="short"/> getting to the serious stage aren't we</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144">no more pissing about</u>
<u n="316" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> she she has this dream of having a little house just like at home <pause dur="short"/> you know somewhere you love to be <pause dur="short"/> somewhere you can have a few animals and do a bit of gardening and potter about and somewhere where you really love to be</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">but with with this building a house lark it's not gonna happen for</u>
<u n="319" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="320" who="S0024">ten years</u>
<u n="321" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> at least</u>
<u n="322" who="S0024">I mean I don't get it <pause dur="short"/> I I say slowly slowly</u>
<u n="323" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I can see where they're coming from like I mean first of all they want an investment that's gonna store it's wealth which land is a great way to do that</u>
<u n="324" who="S0024">mhm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0144">Don't think houses are necessarily good at the moment because they are so inflated</u>
<u n="326" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="327" who="S0144">but land is</u>
<u n="328" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0144">like what they're looking at to see the idea</u>
<u n="330" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and it could really work out <pause dur="short"/> it could like <pause dur="short"/> just like the laws could change or the land <pause dur="short"/> suddenly they're allowed to build on it</u>
<u n="331" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's a  it's a  long term investment</u>
<u n="332" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0144">and it's not somewhere where you'd be able to call home for a good ten years</u>
<u n="334" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0144">at least <pause dur="short"/> and I shouldn't think they'd be able to re-sell it</u>
<u n="336" who="S0024">see that's the thing I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is ready to move onto the land</u>
<u n="337" who="S0144">is he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0024">well he they've moved to <trunc>hat</trunc> their flat and they're in a flat staying with friends until they get the land</u>
<u n="339" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so are they  are they  gonna live in tents?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0024">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> reckons they can live on the land for forty days of the year <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="341" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0024">but what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were saying you can't  you can't  go and just start camping straight away cos the neighbours are gonna be like oh my God what's happened?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">there's a</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144" trans="overlap">specially if there's a what? How many of them? Four?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> four</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144">yeah so that's gonna be a couple of tents like big tents</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0144">like straight off <pause dur="short"/> soon as  soon as  it's been sold <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna raise some eyebrows isn't it?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and if the five of them are cooking their tea and stuff like that</u>
<u n="351" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean the neighbours will think a couple of gypsies will have move in</u>
<u n="352" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it will until <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> they're gonna be like oh they sold the land and suddenly there's these people camping on there</u>
<u n="353" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0024">um <pause dur="short"/> They where where are the owners? They won't immediately think that they're the owners</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> so I mean they'll tell the police</u>
<u n="356" who="S0024">mm they could do</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144">and then that'll be a record of them being on the land and then they've got forty days from that moment haven't they? So</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if you can scatter your time <pause dur="short"/> there <pause dur="short"/> and back</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">oh what leave for a day and then come back again?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024">huh?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144">like doing a visa run or something?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as long as you've got another address eh oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying if like they have kids they can't live on the land while they have kids cos you're not allowed <pause dur="short"/> an address</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but I mean <pause dur="short"/> you need a residents</u>
<u n="366" who="S0024">you won't have an address until you've built a house</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024">so you can't <pause dur="short"/> kids can't live in a caravan anymore unless you're on a caravan site with an address because otherwise they can't go to school</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="370" who="S0024">Cos you you have to have an address to go to school</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144">oh dear</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024">but I don't know  I don't know</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">aw I admire their bravery</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024">yeah I just hope it all works out as like a  like a  dream</u>
<u n="375" who="S0144">it'll be interesting to see what happens</u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0024">but I've told em what I think <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've told them what to be careful of and what I think to be careful of <pause dur="short"/> maybe I haven't mentioned the water thing again <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s told them what they what she thinks they need to be careful of and we said now we're just gonna leave it because they want to make their decision and they want it to be a happy one not one full of doubt and dread</u>
<u n="379" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024">and we don't want to keep feeding them oh you gotta think about this and think about that <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> even said to me the other day oh I want to stop thinking about the bad things that could possibly go wrong</u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">yeah well as long as they're aware of them then it is up to them isn't it?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144">I mean and you have voiced</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ooo I hope it works out with them <pause dur="short"/> we when we come back next time we can go live there as well</u>
<u n="385" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0024">we can go and stay there</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144">I mean how long were they realistically gonna want to live in a tent for? Seriously?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah with Ray working so hard I mean he works all the hours under the sun</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just gonna be sitting there in a tent</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">what are they doing for heating and stuff like that?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">yeah eh</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144">I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0144">I just don't know if they've <pause dur="short"/> they must have thought about these things</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'll quiz em <pause dur="short"/> quiz em in a positive</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144">although they are very spontaneous though aren't they so?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we can quiz them on Saturday when we go see them</u>
<u n="399" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0024">just asking little <pause dur="short"/> little questions <pause dur="short"/> don't ask too much but</u>
<u n="401" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I don't want to ask them before they buy it</u>
<u n="402" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> what completely change their mind?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0144">yeah no</u>
<u n="404" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah well I hope it works out in the end</u>
<u n="405" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0024">and knowing them it will work out perfectly <pause dur="short"/> cos they've got Lady Luck on their side <pause dur="short"/> if you believe in such things <pause dur="short"/> they yeah <pause dur="short"/> they really do have someone smiling at them most of the time I think</u>
<u n="407" who="S0144">well I dunno</u>
<u n="408" who="S0024">well with that they <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> they always seem to land on their feet <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="409" who="S0144">didn't have much luck in Spain</u>
<u n="410" who="S0024">well no but they did to begin with and then like <pause dur="short"/> the whole economy crashed really hard there <pause dur="short"/> really hard <pause dur="short"/> I'm surprised Spain aren't even lower than they are</u>
<u n="411" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well they are <pause dur="short"/> just hiding it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> such a shame <pause dur="short"/> he had that whole business <pause dur="short"/> everything <pause dur="short"/> he had loads of employees</u>
<u n="413" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0024">he helped them all out <pause dur="short"/> he's too nice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> He helped them all out and then crash <pause dur="short"/> no money <pause dur="short"/> well we're just gonna make it I think</u>
<u n="415" who="S0144">yep</u>
<u n="416" who="S0024">you gonna make it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0144">I can't wait to get back actually my hand is frozen holding this thing</u>
<u n="418" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're welcome <pause dur="short"/> well that's enough <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> might as well let it go another minute then we've got thirty minutes</u>
<u n="420" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0144">nice round number</u>
<u n="422" who="S0024">that's it I might play one quick game with dad dad wants me to play and then  and then  I'm gonna stay in the warm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0144">yeah he was happy he beat me earlier</u>
<u n="424" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0024">well yeah you've been on a run of winning</u>
<u n="427" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I don't think I've lost this year <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="429" who="S0144">I was trying out a few new moves</u>
<u n="430" who="S0024">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> you have to do don't you? Everybody tries out a few new moves you can't use that as an excuse to lose can you?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0144">no</u>
</body>
</text>
