<text id="S63L">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:02:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>House-sitting in Australia</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Changing careers, and personal life goals and interests. </topics>
		<activity>A couple talking about future plans for a career change and how to set up a small business. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0261">okay if you wanna put it that way</u>
<u n="2" who="S0262">can I ask you a question please? I don't understand <trunc>w</trunc> I do understand what you're <trunc>g</trunc> where's you're going but I'd really like to know what is it that you wanna do with your life? cos this is all about you changing career you know <trunc>w</trunc> you know when you said I don't wanna do engineering any more which is fine have you now figured out what it is <vocal desc="laugh"/> apart from just growing a business but what what's what are you passionate about? what what is gonna get you up in the morning and go great <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm gonna do this and I'm gonna do that what is it that you like?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><trunc>o</trunc><trunc>o</trunc>okay well er well er well well part part of this goes back to the discussion I had with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0262">yes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0261">okay?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0261"><unclear>because that</unclear> I'm gonna ask the same question and and it's a case of what can be aligned in such a way that you and I work together doing things that we are interested in that provides us the lifestyle that we're interested in? that's what I</u>
<u n="8" who="S0262">but I don't know what you like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know what I'm like you know I love <trunc>passio</trunc> I am passionate about education</u>
<u n="9" who="S0261">I I know you er you're making a point but you're actually cutting me off</u>
<u n="10" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but I don't know what you're</u>
<u n="11" who="S0261">you're you're cutting me off so you're not hearing me out</u>
<u n="12" who="S0262">I've heard it twice</u>
<u n="13" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0262">I we're aligning with each other</u>
<u n="15" who="S0261">yeah that's right okay so what can we do? right? that we have skills in that we're interested in I'm a visual person I like photography I'm interested in video stuff it's feasible that we do erm some kind of element of erm er not film-based but documentary-based information that could be delivery of whatever product in that media digitally online to whatever audience okay?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0262">so what's that called then? as a as an overarching word</u>
<u n="17" who="S0261">as a er er well you could say a documentary maker or er a digital product maker producer</u>
<u n="18" who="S0262">mm digital producer</u>
<u n="19" who="S0261">a digital producer</u>
<u n="20" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0261">so erm you you've got er</u>
<u n="22" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0261"><trunc>y</trunc>you could you could call it media</u>
<u n="24" who="S0262" trans="overlap">is is that what you're doing now? digital producer?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0261">well er well er</u>
<u n="26" who="S0262" trans="overlap">is that an example of digital production?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0261">that that that is an example of of producing digital content which is called web design and web development</u>
<u n="28" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="29" who="S0261">okay? so that's creating a <trunc>w</trunc> an a a web page that <trunc>f</trunc> that also combines erm er online retail business yeah? erm and er <trunc>a</trunc>and an element of also erm bringing together existing systems and creating new systems</u>
<u n="30" who="S0262">so is that still digital producer? if you're creating new systems?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0261">it it's in the context of a digital producer</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262" trans="overlap">or are you a systems engineer?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0261">you're not forget er forget systems engineer forget the systems stuff</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="35" who="S0261">I'm I'm creating digital products which are being presented online and the digital through digital media in a digital way yeah? it's all digital okay?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262">right okay so let's just say</u>
<u n="37" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so I'm thinking I've er I'm <trunc>g</trunc> I'm learning new skills that one should be building on yes?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay I I you see I need I need I need definitions and I need I need titles</u>
<u n="39" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262">I can't I can't work without knowing who you are and what you do yeah?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes that's right</u>
<u n="42" who="S0262">cos that's so much easier that's why we say teacher teacher what does a teacher do?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0262">definition right okay got you so let's just say you're a digital producer right now okay? what does a digital producer do? can you summarise it for me? and I'll take notes and try and summarise it yeah?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0261">erm I don't know whether there's such a thing I just I just come off the tongue I don't know whether there's a er that's the normal way somebody <trunc>pr</trunc> calls it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">but this is your definition</u>
<u n="47" who="S0261">my my definition</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">yeah is</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">of of that is erm <vocal desc="misc"/> er <unclear>alright</unclear> it's er a producer of digital content</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261">er that digital content can be broken down into images visual digital images <pause dur="short"/> and that can be erm film video <pause dur="short"/> photography <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0262"><unclear>text</unclear> et cetera et cetera right okay</u>
<u n="53" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah we've got er web page web design web development so graphic design <pause dur="long"/> erm there's the project management</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261">as part of it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">right <pause dur="short"/> I was hoping you were just gonna stick on the definition of digital producer</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261">well I think that is part of it</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262"><unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0261">okay?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">erm <vocal desc="misc"/> er so erm there there is erm er social media social media erm internet marketing <pause dur="long"/> erm we can call a subset is is search engine optimisation SEO <pause dur="long"/> that'll do for the moment</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261">okay</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">so what I would do is I would take that write it</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261">I'd probably refine that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262"><trunc>w</trunc> yes</u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">work on it and send it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and get his review on what you think it is a digital producer does <pause dur="short"/> cos when you go out into the market place</u>
<u n="71" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you need to be clear about what you're called</u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">and then you call yourself a digital producer and everybody else is like this isn't what a digital producer does or yeah yeah that's exactly what a digital producer does so when you are creating <unclear>your title you wanna know exactly right</unclear> what that actually means cos there might be such a thing as digital producer existing already in the world I like the name of it I think it's fantastic but I think you need a second opinion whether that's actually mm accurate</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261">well I've just put together the skillset that I'm starting to learn that's all</u>
<u n="74" who="S0262">exactly</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0262">but we know from what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s work is is that he already told us there are people like this and they've got job titles and they might be freelancers <unclear/> he works with freelancers quite a lot if you looked in his Linkedin you'll see all the creative titles that people give themselves as freelancers</u>
<u n="77" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262">so I was just saying <pause dur="short"/> if he's got some time and you write it up nicely and get you get some words going in there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might give you some better words to choose to describe it yeah? so that it's really accurate in terms of what a digital producer does and then you can pick and choose whether that's what you want inside your own definition</u>
<u n="79" who="S0261">so I see that er as as part of a tool to er lead into this</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262">yeah yeah yeah fine</u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">yeah fine</u>
<u n="83" who="S0261" trans="overlap">it's a tool</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">it's basically a series a set of skills that you can use as a as a tool to to get to to to do something that's related to that</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">right okay and then I'll tell you what bits I quite like the idea of as well okay?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="long"/> but you see I don't actually think that in the bigger picture that fits that</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262">well you don't you don't know yet</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262">cos you don't actually know what this is</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">it fits what I want that to be</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262">ah well this is what I've been asking you what do you want to do? rather than what <unclear>we</unclear> want to do</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261">right yeah well that's what I'm doing at the moment yeah?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262">so this is</u>
<u n="95" who="S0261">at the moment I haven't got a real tangible vision of what I want to do but I can see there are things there that interest me on the <trunc>con</trunc> in the context of as long as I manage it I don't do it yeah?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>right</unclear> okay <unclear>right</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">so it's the where the <trunc>produ</trunc> the <unclear/> the producer is</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261">so what I'm saying is I'm trying it out at the moment get a certain basic skillset and then manage others to bring together a project</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">only if you had some project of some size if you didn't have a project of some size you wouldn't need somebody else to do it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">mm well if you have a quantity of projects of of of X size you would have somebody else do that work</u>
<u n="102" who="S0262" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">I would suggest though that you're gonna be doing a lot of this on your own to start with as you're growing the business</u>
<u n="105" who="S0261">yes I know that</u>
<u n="106" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah but er but I'm of the point of view that er that as long as I know a bit about how that works then I can outsource that and get others to do it and simply</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm okay</u>
<u n="109" who="S0261">you're dealing with the margin while you're allowing yourself to build your time to build other things yeah? <pause dur="short"/> because other people have a lot more skill than I do <unclear>in</unclear> that stuff there's no point in me spending X amount of time trying to skill up on that to a level where I could operate like they would</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262">okay er <trunc>tha</trunc>that's something I don't know anything about and you I think you'll need to really take <unclear/> advice on that at the beginning point of <unclear>your</unclear> business you really do need to find out whether that's you know viable cos you have to pay someone <unclear>at least</unclear> you can pay yourself</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah but I mean you wouldn't enter into that unless you <trunc>kn</trunc>you knew you know A plus B equals C you know?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right it's quite hard to get A and B together sometimes you know to get C but anyway what I think is that if if we work within this context I can see what you do and I can see and I can see that you know you can you can grow this whichever way you want to grow it but I can see why you would be a digital producer in this day and age</u>
<u n="113" who="S0261">right okay</u>
<u n="114" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0261">so what what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> mentioned was in in context of my interest in that your interest in education he simply said the idea might be that you could make go and make documentaries as an example of whatever erm and they're products that you would then sell as content to educational bodies to support any of their educational needs right?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0262">there you go</u>
<u n="117" who="S0261">educational what?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0262">consultant</u>
<u n="119" who="S0261">yes mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0262">and what I do best is I go in to the client me myself and I I find out what the brief is okay? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I put the brief together <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then I give it to you</u>
<u n="121" who="S0261">er yeah yeah fuck that</u>
<u n="122" who="S0262">and then you go and design it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah I don't</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262">and then I go back and deliver it</u>
<u n="125" who="S0261">mm yeah I <trunc>d</trunc> er I I I understand that but I I want to work at that top level as well</u>
<u n="126" who="S0262">well you see that's the thing</u>
<u n="127" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0262">it's not obvious that we're gonna be able to work together on that top level <trunc>some</trunc><trunc>s</trunc>someone's gonna have to</u>
<u n="129" who="S0261">yeah but there's no</u>
<u n="130" who="S0262" trans="overlap">play second fiddle</u>
<u n="131" who="S0261">there's no reason why you can't treat it as two different streams yeah?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0262"><unclear>not really</unclear> cos you always need to go and talk to a client and who's the person who's gonna go and talk to the client?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0261">well if it's er if it's if it's er er projects or or products to to be produced in a certain way that both of you can do that <pause dur="long"/> because what what you've done by presenting it like that effectively is is is that erm you're at the top level and I er so so <trunc>y</trunc>you're operating at the the top managerial level I'm the delivery guy <pause dur="short"/> and what I want to learn as a part of this process is how to own and operate business that's one of my main drivers yeah?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah so maybe we leave me out of it until you've learnt that and then we work together cos er that's what your driver is is that you want to be at that level and that's when you will be able to work with me cos we'll then be at the same level</u>
<u n="135" who="S0261">yeah I understand it in the context of if you were starting out and there was that disparity that's fine but I expect to learn out of that</u>
<u n="136" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0261"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="138" who="S0262">but you'll be learning from me</u>
<u n="139" who="S0261">which is absolutely fine as long as it's quick <trunc>lear</trunc>learning and then you're on the same level you see</u>
<u n="140" who="S0262">yeah well that's the thing is that if you</u>
<u n="141" who="S0261" trans="overlap">cos you don't wanna take ages to do it</u>
<u n="142" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's it's</u>
<u n="143" who="S0261">this is I'm I'm very much about shortcutting things to to try and get somewhere fast</u>
<u n="144" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I know it's <trunc>w</trunc>it's whether it's whether you can really catch up and learn really quickly</u>
<u n="145" who="S0261">yeah well that's part of what this is about this is where I was going from and to yeah?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0262">well we're not starting from the same point so you can't possibly catch up <unclear>from</unclear> me</u>
<u n="147" who="S0261" trans="overlap">no well no that's what I've presented here yeah?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah so your logic doesn't work <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0261">no no what I'm saying is over time that that is where the meeting happens yeah?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0262">oh I see</u>
<u n="151" who="S0261">er yeah over time that's where the meeting happens so at the moment I'm doing this learning whatever skills such that when you meet there you're actually operating in the same business as partners rather than a differentiator and what would be better is that you're both working at that level and you have others that are working at the other level yeah?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0262">so when I originally asked you the question why did you put me somewhere around about here then?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0261">erm because <pause dur="long"/> because in context of that I could deliver that right?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0262">well that's all I thought I'd simplified for you by giving you that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0261">no yeah but that <trunc>y</trunc> er I don't this this to me was a different conversation this was this was about something specific and I didn't really <trunc>s</trunc> tangibly see where it was going</u>
<u n="156" who="S0262">no you didn't you didn't see it</u>
<u n="157" who="S0261" trans="overlap">or what the purpose for it was</u>
<u n="158" who="S0262">but you still gave me the answer that I was looking for which is how your mind works</u>
<u n="159" who="S0261">that was in context of that right? okay?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah so draw me</u>
<u n="161" who="S0261">but this was a whole different thing this is forget that forget that</u>
<u n="162" who="S0262">er no no I'm not forgetting it</u>
<u n="163" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0262">because I thought it was worthwhile</u>
<u n="165" who="S0261">right okay in context of this they're not the same</u>
<u n="166" who="S0262">well I beg to differ I think they're very much the same thing cos it's a project it's a project</u>
<u n="167" who="S0261"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah but we're not talking about operating a project we're talking about running a business</u>
<u n="168" who="S0262">well I think yeah er the the</u>
<u n="169" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0262">the thing is is that normally you get a client first you go great <vocal desc="laugh"/> we've got a fucking client</u>
<u n="171" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0262">and then it becomes what I'm calling a business is that it starts to actually earn some money over a period of time and that's what I call business but first project and then you grow business gotta get a project first</u>
<u n="173" who="S0261">yes that's right and you've gotta deliver a project and</u>
<u n="174" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0261">you've gotta prove that you're of X and you've got certain experience and then you can market yourself et cetera et cetera et cetera</u>
<u n="176" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>? so erm er er a part of this is you you know <trunc>th</trunc>there's a lot of learning together along that timeline yeah? to get to the point where actually things are in place such that this can exist</u>
<u n="178" who="S0262">I know I I just <trunc>th</trunc>I just think that because we're not both we're not really both educators I can't I I don't I can't really see how er you know</u>
<u n="179" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you're an educator <unclear>though</unclear></u>
<u n="180" who="S0262">yeah but we're not both educators meaning</u>
<u n="181" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="182" who="S0262">you know <trunc>y</trunc> er it's not necessarily erm you know an industry that interests you I don't quite know why you'd</u>
<u n="183" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0262">come into that industry unless you'd actually be sort of vaguely interested in it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0261">okay so if you've got if you've got <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0262">cos a digital producer is you could go and work for a company like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0261">yeah but what I'm trying to connect together are the two things that we are interested in right? <pause dur="short"/> like that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0262">but what are the two things we're interested in? I don't are you interested in education?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0261">yes I am</u>
<u n="190" who="S0262">what sort of part of it?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0261">well <pause dur="short"/> one thing I'm starting to realise is that I do quite like teaching things to people</u>
<u n="192" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="193" who="S0261">you know? and I think people have told me in the past that I'm I'm alright at explaining stuff to people on a step-by-step type thing you know?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0261">which is what I just produced today</u>
<u n="196" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0261">for somebody who has no real experience in something</u>
<u n="198" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0261">and for me that's very straightforward to explain that to teach somebody like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> something I can adapt to a variety of different people to teach them stuff okay?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0261">erm and it was through talking with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about some of the stuff that I've done in the past as part of my engineering thing</u>
<u n="202" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0261">is that as a manager you're teaching others other stuff</u>
<u n="204" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0261">yeah? so and I'm and I quite like sitting down and taking <trunc>peop</trunc> this is how it works and da da da da da</u>
<u n="206" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0261">so if if you consider the idea of erm education being er the product you are producing an education-based product that helps people learn something and that you need to deliver that product and that you're gonna deliver it in a digital medium and that let's say you have an understanding of what the educational product needs to be and the tools that are needed to be produced to help somebody to learn</u>
<u n="208" who="S0262">potentially yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0261">yeah and that in the context of the way that erm the modern world is heading a lot of that is the visually-based output</u>
<u n="210" who="S0262"><unclear>that's</unclear> true</u>
<u n="211" who="S0261">and so if you have the digital skills being that you can make the film you can make the text you can make the imagery whatever the audio to put all of that stuff together that you can create that and you can publish it and you publish it through digital output and so the stuff I've been talking about as the digital producer is that you know?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0262">okay I'm gonna <pause dur="long"/> this is my theory and when I started teaching I was here</u>
<u n="213" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0262">from about early nineteen nineties okay?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="216" who="S0262">then I learnt how to create <trunc>doc</trunc> erm resources for learners in Word document</u>
<u n="217" who="S0261" trans="overlap">is there any more of that?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0262">yeah then okay start started like maybe playing around with tape cassettes and and and and recording my voice so that others could learn from my voice for pronunciation</u>
<u n="219" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0262">then er images and I became more interested in photographs and teaching students to describe photographs and get their own photographs and then I'm moving into this area now of well I've always loved using film</u>
<u n="221" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0262">as an audio visual tool</u>
<u n="223" who="S0261">exactly</u>
<u n="224" who="S0262">erm and er I'm thinking that by the time I'm <unclear/> by I'm pretty sure maybe about fifty-five</u>
<u n="225" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0262">I'll be back here again</u>
<u n="227" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0262">but I'll probably will be hanging around this area for quite some time possibly might be something slightly different going on here between forty and fifty-five</u>
<u n="229" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0262">but I don't see what that could possibly be now</u>
<u n="231" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="232" who="S0262">I just can't think <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0262">what else there is in the world that's gonna be any different from these things yeah?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0261">yes mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0262">if you can that's where you're gonna make a lot of money but I think I'm gonna be sitting there at the age of fifty-five and I'm gonna be sitting down with students and I'm gonna be</u>
<u n="237" who="S0261" trans="overlap">going back to square one</u>
<u n="238" who="S0262">yep</u>
<u n="239" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and I'll be</u>
<u n="241" who="S0261">because it becomes the social interaction that's important not the technical interaction</u>
<u n="242" who="S0262">we're gonna be so bored of seeing people like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> everyone talking on audio visual on the internet and never really getting to meet them and we'll just get we'll just run out of er enthusiasm for it yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc>interest <unclear>in it</unclear> yeah erm well it'll just become it'll become a tool that is actually only used when er when there's a focused output for it</u>
<u n="244" who="S0262">and this is why I'm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0261"><unclear>mm</unclear>?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0262">so interested in <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s research because what he's suggesting is it doesn't matter what <trunc>te</trunc> er technology is doing at any point in time the patterns <unclear>are about</unclear> social pattern</u>
<u n="247" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="248" who="S0262">and there is a language connected to that I'm I'm not talking about languages in a er French or German or English</u>
<u n="249" who="S0261">mm?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0262">there's a there's a there's a something else language</u>
<u n="251" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="252" who="S0262">it's kind of like a design language</u>
<u n="253" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="254" who="S0262">so designers when they talk to each other they have some sort of way of communicating you know</u>
<u n="255" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0262">or maybe when you design software you have another slightly different language <unclear/> whatever</u>
<u n="257" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="258" who="S0262">and I'm not talking just you know something going on <unclear>should</unclear> be going on people creating this at the moment and they're just pulling this in <pause dur="short"/> but the people who are gonna actually have power will be the <unclear/> the ones who'd actually thoroughly understand how this works and can just basically create like you say a template I think it's not quite the right word but let's call it a template for the moment and basically can reproduce that template again and again and again and again in many many many many many many social contexts</u>
<u n="259" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="260" who="S0262">around the world</u>
<u n="261" who="S0261">er I mean you I er I and <trunc>s</trunc>so I'm I'm interested in what you tell me about this stuff yeah? er I'm I'm I I have a interest in listening to what that is about okay? so my point of view is is that erm whether it's a case of I'm an operator of the visual device that creates stuff or whether I manage that to be done to the the output that we want it to be yeah? and and still <trunc>opera</trunc> be a part of operating a business and that's just part of it right? that's where I want to kind of connect with some of that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="262" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="263" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>? so that's kind of the digital producer stuff but also you're running the business part that goes with it alright?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0262">yeah and and yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and er part of that is boring</u>
<u n="266" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0261">but I mean it is er there is er a fundamental need to know how that works</u>
<u n="268" who="S0262">the <pause dur="long"/> to me my definition of running a business is simply the ongoing activities of a business mean <trunc>o</trunc>of a day-to-day going concern that means one day you'll have to do your accounts the next day you'll have to pay your contract erm your erm you know for your for your internet connection</u>
<u n="269" who="S0261">your costs and all that kind of stuff so</u>
<u n="270" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right that's just business for me</u>
<u n="271" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="272" who="S0262">that's that's all it means okay</u>
<u n="273" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0262">the stuff in your heart is the stuff that you're actually trying to reach out to a customer or er or a</u>
<u n="275" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that's <trunc>r</trunc><trunc>ri</trunc> <trunc>ab</trunc>absolutely</u>
<u n="276" who="S0262">and most of the time you're you're providing a product or a service</u>
<u n="277" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0262">so the stuff in your heart is the product or the service</u>
<u n="279" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes that's right</u>
<u n="280" who="S0262">the business is just how you keep that all going</u>
<u n="281" who="S0261">yes that's right mm mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0262">so for me</u>
<u n="283" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so the thread is the business</u>
<u n="284" who="S0262">the thread is the business yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="286" who="S0262">but but the stuff in my heart where I wanna be</u>
<u n="287" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0262">is I wanna be in that area</u>
<u n="289" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="290" who="S0262">okay? because I've explored these different areas and I like them all</u>
<u n="291" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0262">and I've got some knowledge of them</u>
<u n="293" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="294" who="S0262">but I'm not gonna be somebody's fucking audio visual bitch and just keep making fucking films for people or whatever there's plenty of fucking people out there to do that I don't mind <trunc>s</trunc> outsourcing these people</u>
<u n="295" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0262">I have no problem with that when we find talented people</u>
<u n="297" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="298" who="S0262">but this is the mastermind stuff this is the stuff that most people who aren't clever enough to fucking think about it and how to grow it won't be able to do it and that's why they stay here</u>
<u n="299" who="S0261">yes that's fine</u>
<u n="300" who="S0262">okay?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0261">that's good and er it's exactly what er one would hope to achieve and and have as a direction</u>
<u n="302" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did when he did social media</u>
<u n="303" who="S0261">he <trunc>w</trunc> he found that core</u>
<u n="304" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0261">right yes mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0262">so I feel like I've found a core</u>
<u n="307" who="S0261">right that's fine so that's good so</u>
<u n="308" who="S0262">yeah but is that a core that interests you? if we er er if we unravel it together and find out what it means is there something maybe potentially you could go I'm open-minded enough to unravel this a little bit more and then I'll see if something about it grabs my attention enough to pursue it for ten years or eight years?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0261">however it goes yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0262">well you've gotta commit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0261" trans="overlap">of course of <trunc>c</trunc> of no of of course</u>
<u n="312" who="S0262">you er <trunc>s</trunc> you <trunc>g</trunc> you <trunc>g</trunc> you <trunc>c</trunc>you can't swap and change your products and services or you know you've gotta</u>
<u n="313" who="S0261">er er er er er absolutely so what I'm trying to identify is a core path that both of us can <trunc>bu</trunc>buy into and operate on</u>
<u n="314" who="S0262">I know and that's what I'm trying to do but I've told you what my core is and I'm not gonna change it</u>
<u n="315" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's great it's good to hear</u>
<u n="316" who="S0262">but do you have a core that you can add to my core? or are you gonna go with my core first and then change it into something else?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><trunc>wha</trunc><trunc>wha</trunc>what what what what kind of products do you?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0262">no there aren't products</u>
<u n="319" who="S0261">there aren't?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0262">at the moment this is all totally theoretical</u>
<u n="321" who="S0261">righto so so if you point point the fact that these different things exist as a part of that</u>
<u n="322" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0261">right? they're a subset</u>
<u n="324" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0261">that that you do create things on the basis of this</u>
<u n="326" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0261">and they're a start when this comes on board that's when you you change your attention to all of that so it's that you're producing something that makes money</u>
<u n="328" who="S0262">oh yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0262">and what you're telling em will tell em <unclear/> what you do normally with these two <unclear>things</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> with er this type of thing is er <trunc>w</trunc> er where the top dollar is always gonna be is on selling know-how <pause dur="short"/> that's top dollar money yeah? content is not top dollar yeah? because the content is a product it's an output</u>
<u n="331" who="S0261">so er it has a finite lifetime</u>
<u n="332" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0261">yeah so you're saying selling knowledge?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0262">no cos knowledge and know-how are not the same thing <pause dur="short"/> know-how in business is a very specific term</u>
<u n="335" who="S0261">yeah so you're you you you're demonstrating a mechanism by er er erm er <trunc>some</trunc>something that somebody can learn to do</u>
<u n="336" who="S0262">yeah but not too much</u>
<u n="337" who="S0261"><unclear>you</unclear></u>
<u n="338" who="S0262">so that they don't get it for themselves and then just go away and reproduce it and then you've lost your core <unclear>competency</unclear></u>
<u n="339" who="S0261" trans="overlap">but that's exactly how like some of these relationships working that I'm a part of now that that Location Rebel is effectively an old product and the guy who owns and operates it has already moved on to start his other stuff which he's interested in</u>
<u n="340" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="341" who="S0261">but this still works as a as a <trunc>f</trunc> as a as an income-earning stream of business</u>
<u n="342" who="S0262">yeah cos</u>
<u n="343" who="S0261">but his input into it is different because he's put somebody in between him and it who is now the person who's doing the day-to-day operation of it</u>
<u n="344" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0261">yeah? he still owns it</u>
<u n="346" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he's grown he's he he he's grown as an individual</u>
<u n="347" who="S0261">yes that's right</u>
<u n="348" who="S0262">but so has the world grown so he's grown with it</u>
<u n="349" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0262">and that's what I'm telling you is that what I kept picking up on from my research from somebody who's apparently apparently one of the most erm visionary people in terms of erm learning at the moment</u>
<u n="351" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="352" who="S0262">is <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="354" who="S0262">okay?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0262">and there'll be others around like him in the world</u>
<u n="357" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0262">but <pause dur="short"/> they're onto something and it's gonna be really really really big</u>
<u n="359" who="S0261">so have you got a a context of how that might be realised in the real world</u>
<u n="360" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well yes because there's two things that you that you and I absolutely love <pause dur="short"/> we love design</u>
<u n="361" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="362" who="S0262">so <pause dur="short"/> I've never studied architecture in my life <pause dur="short"/> but if I put this in front of the word architecture</u>
<u n="363" who="S0261">learning?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0262">architecture meaning not learning about architecture <vocal desc="laugh"/> meaning er okay er <unclear>all</unclear></u>
<u n="365" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the the learning architecture</u>
<u n="366" who="S0262">the architecture of learning</u>
<u n="367" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the architecture of learning yes that's so that's the structure of how does one go about learning yes?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0262">and what <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is <trunc>g</trunc> eventually gonna come out with maybe in a couple of years time is he's gonna come out with some really good clues for the rest of us to pick up on about what what <pause dur="short"/> okay what this actually is this is a new theory being born right now</u>
<u n="369" who="S0261">okay so er <trunc>tha</trunc>that as you've explained might be the context of of individual learning plans such that people can as <trunc>inde</trunc>independents of of a system find a mechanism to learn what they want the way they want to do it and so it becomes highly individualised and hints erm of <unclear>great</unclear> benefit to everybody who wants to be involved in that system</u>
<u n="370" who="S0262">it's an evolution</u>
<u n="371" who="S0261">but but er so er do you see that evolving in the context of our the existing way that education needs to be</u>
<u n="372" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="373" who="S0261">delivered? not delivered what I mean is the the the fundamental value that education is provided to everybody</u>
<u n="374" who="S0262">oh fuck yeah yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0261">yeah so so so</u>
<u n="376" who="S0262" trans="overlap">education for everyone</u>
<u n="377" who="S0261">it becomes an alternative mechanism to deliver that</u>
<u n="378" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0261">education</u>
<u n="380" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0261">but do you think that the context of the way that education is delivered and the way that governments control that stuff the budgets and the money that this type of learning would become day-to-day normality?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0262">yeah but it <trunc>w</trunc><trunc>w</trunc> er it will be about</u>
<u n="383" who="S0261">twenty years</u>
<u n="384" who="S0262">seventy when that happens</u>
<u n="385" who="S0261">yeah it's a long time where it becomes the norm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0262"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0261">however your example in Sydney of somebody who is is of some outfit that is actually trying to operate on this basis now</u>
<u n="388" who="S0262">oh researching yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0261">they're they're carrying out research</u>
<u n="390" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0261">but at a at a at a er at a place where real people are learning real things in the way that they want to learn them for themselves</u>
<u n="392" who="S0262">no they haven't got to that stage yet they're using people like us who are the er who are the the collaborators and they're trying to learn how we use language and how we create in terms of learning architecture so er we had <trunc>lear</trunc> we had educational designers we had learning advisors we have erm you know a number of <trunc>c</trunc>of cool people who he perceives to be the people of the future as soon as these people understand how to efficiently collaborate with each other so that creativity is becoming efficient they will get much better at getting blueprints or templates together and those people will be passing on the templates to the people who need it the most I E the individual learner</u>
<u n="393" who="S0261">right so</u>
<u n="394" who="S0262">and by the way there are lots of things in between <trunc>s</trunc><trunc>s</trunc>schools primary schools secondary schools universities</u>
<u n="395" who="S0261">er er all of that</u>
<u n="396" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0261">at different levels so <pause dur="short"/> er <trunc>i</trunc>is it feasible in a way I mean in is it er feasible in a way to provide somebody with that service in advance of a lot of research? <pause dur="short"/> in your own mechanism</u>
<u n="398" who="S0262"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0261">if you're thinking about people who operate at a certain level</u>
<u n="400" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah you could give it you could give it a go you could <trunc>g</trunc> yes yes if you if you could give it a go as a bit of an experiment</u>
<u n="401" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0262">not necessarily as a business yeah? cos <unclear>the business idea is like you've gotta have money coming in</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0261"><unclear/> no but er <trunc>y</trunc>you you your own R and D would be</u>
<u n="404" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0261">take ten people</u>
<u n="406" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0261">over a period of six months</u>
<u n="408" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0261">and that you operate with them</u>
<u n="410" who="S0262">yes</u>
<u n="411" who="S0261">on such a level that you try and learn this together with these people</u>
<u n="412" who="S0262">and I document it yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0261">and you document it</u>
<u n="414" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0261">and then you actually</u>
<u n="416" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0261">try to run it as a business where you <unclear/> two people</u>
<u n="418" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0261">the context of if you've got enough money</u>
<u n="420" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0261">you can pay us</u>
<u n="422" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0261">yeah if you've got enough you can pay us</u>
<u n="424" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0261">like an individual tutor</u>
<u n="426" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0261">however we will teach and we can demonstrate that the learning will be a lot more individual-focused now you've got to have people with the freedom of mind to connect with that idea</u>
<u n="428" who="S0262">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0261">and that's part of the problem because</u>
<u n="430" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0261">they've been institutionalised throughout generations and over lifetimes</u>
<u n="432" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well no you just find a whole lot of different people who haven't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she'd be brilliant as er as one of them you know erm but remember when you're selling er literally when you're selling top dollar okay? as an architect as a as a traditional architect the thing that costs the most amount of money <pause dur="short"/> is</u>
<u n="433" who="S0261">the way that it's done the blueprint</u>
<u n="434" who="S0262" trans="overlap">er er er aren't they cool blueprints? you spread them out and you look and</u>
<u n="435" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah of course of course yeah it's the tools and</u>
<u n="436" who="S0262" trans="overlap">think how fucking how much work has gone into a blueprint <pause dur="short"/> that's why it costs so much</u>
<u n="437" who="S0261">yes because somebody has to develop it right? and if you're in it for the real business of it</u>
<u n="438" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0261">you would develop your own and you would hold that tool</u>
<u n="440" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0261">and you would use that tool to your advantage</u>
<u n="442" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0261">erm and that's when you start working with er business other providers to to use your blueprint to demonstrate something <unclear>to work with that</unclear></u>
<u n="444" who="S0262">you'd be working with some very clever people</u>
<u n="445" who="S0261">yes and but there's I mean as an outsider effectively I don't see the context of of unless you're on the inside of all of that why anybody else would want to work with you because they'd go well I can do that myself</u>
<u n="446" who="S0262">no they can't how the fuck can they do that on their own?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0261">no I'm talking about the people who are in on it</u>
<u n="448" who="S0262">oh yeah but then not everyone's got the same reasons to be in on it</u>
<u n="449" who="S0261">yeah yeah okay</u>
<u n="450" who="S0262">not everyone wants to be an entrepreneur</u>
<u n="451" who="S0261">no that's right but er what I see there is is er is a long period of time</u>
<u n="452" who="S0262">yes</u>
<u n="453" who="S0261">right? so if if you say that's kind of at some point in the future <pause dur="short"/> in order to be able to do some things that build towards that you have to have a variety of steps</u>
<u n="454" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0261">a strategic kind of direction and</u>
<u n="456" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah and the <trunc>s</trunc> research and development takes a long time</u>
<u n="457" who="S0261">that's right so if you say that that needs to happen you need to be doing something else that's still allowing you to operate and bring an income et cetera</u>
<u n="458" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0261">which could be going back to the bread and butter <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0262">well yeah exactly</u>
<u n="461" who="S0261">you know that kind of thing</u>
<u n="462" who="S0262">well that's not bread and butter that that's not bread and butter this bit is the bread and butter it's whatever you choose to do for the next you know how many however long it takes to be a research and developer this is you here say this is the er the point where we go to the market with a blueprint <pause dur="short"/> we've got <unclear>a whole</unclear> we've gotta bring on board people at the right time we've gotta get the right people on board we've gotta get the right developers in on time I mean we're talking about some big stuff here <pause dur="short"/> this is what you're good at doing this is why you've got to go out and find people</u>
<u n="463" who="S0261">yes that's right and that's true about building a team and bringing the right people on board et cetera</u>
<u n="464" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0261">so I appreciate I appreciate that erm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0262">do you really know enough about software and how it's developed though? this is the thing</u>
<u n="467" who="S0261">well the you see the thing is er I don't I'm not convinced you need to know how it's done</u>
<u n="468" who="S0262">no you don't but you need you need to <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="469" who="S0261" trans="overlap">but I I think you need to</u>
<u n="470" who="S0262">you need to defend or attack software at the right time</u>
<u n="471" who="S0261">er when you say defend or attack what do you mean?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0262">so if you have a blueprint and erm you used some tools</u>
<u n="473" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="474" who="S0262">to develop the the blueprint</u>
<u n="475" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="476" who="S0262">and somebody asked you why did you use those tools to develop the blueprint?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0262">you could actually argue your case why you used these tools and not those tools</u>
<u n="479" who="S0261">well and and part of that is being aware of</u>
<u n="480" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you need to know about software</u>
<u n="481" who="S0261">er well it's about being aware of of the technology er software development of software where things are shifting to in context of tech yeah? so erm if I use an example I talked to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about what he's doing with his brother</u>
<u n="482" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0261">neither of them really are computer people</u>
<u n="484" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0261">his brother just sells shit in IT</u>
<u n="486" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0261">that's <trunc>f</trunc> it's it's it's er he sells telephony services</u>
<u n="488" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="489" who="S0261">you know so he's not an IT guy</u>
<u n="490" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0261">he doesn't make stuff</u>
<u n="492" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he's a salesman yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0261">yeah but they have erm they have an idea and as long as you can bring together the idea with the right people erm and you pay for the right people to produce the products that you need produced like an app like er er a web app erm whatever you're just hiring certain people with certain skills to do that</u>
<u n="494" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0261">so you don't need necessarily need to know that you just need to know that I'm gonna hire X person of X quality to produce X yeah?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay okay but but but but sorry to cut you off but <pause dur="long"/> <unclear>I'm</unclear> guessing that a project manager has a fair bit of knowledge about all of these things <unclear/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0261">er over time yes</u>
<u n="498" who="S0262">that's why you get experience and get good ones in so they actually know what the fuck these fuckers are doing</u>
<u n="499" who="S0261">yes that's right</u>
<u n="500" who="S0262">and they can <trunc>g</trunc>give em a fucking kick up the arse</u>
<u n="501" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear>that er</unclear> that is right so you need er I mean er you know one way to manage it is by by by erm hiring outfits that can demonstrate they have the <trunc>cr</trunc>the credibility so you pay top dollar for that or you you you you come across people who who have worked for those outfits but no longer want to</u>
<u n="502" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0261">who offer who are actually trying to do their own thing starting out</u>
<u n="504" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0261">and <unclear>hint</unclear> that they don't cost so much because they they've gotta kind of but they have the skills and the quality et cetera and the awareness of how it does work</u>
<u n="506" who="S0262">like a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sort of thing he used to work for Saab or whoever and he did something <trunc>wro</trunc> you know guy next door to us in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah <trunc>exa</trunc>exactly</u>
<u n="508" who="S0262"><unclear>you know</unclear></u>
<u n="509" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0262">and and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0262">when he went out on his own and became and he became a plumber but you know</u>
<u n="513" who="S0261" trans="overlap">of of course and they're people with very good skills</u>
<u n="514" who="S0262">yeah <unclear>who leave</unclear></u>
<u n="515" who="S0261" trans="overlap">who you can rely on who</u>
<u n="516" who="S0262">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0261">mm yes mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0261">yes exactly of course</u>
<u n="520" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so yeah there there are loads of em knocking around</u>
<u n="521" who="S0261">yes of course so they're the people that you would try and work with</u>
<u n="522" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and they'll be about the same age like you</u>
<u n="523" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="524" who="S0262">mid mid change of career <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0261">yes but <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="526" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0261">but they're they're the kind of people that you would try and bring on board</u>
<u n="528" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0261">but they're they're you you're just getting them in at the right part of the process</u>
<u n="530" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0261">to provide you a certain part</u>
<u n="532" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but do you agree with my assumption that to be an effective project manager you would need to know a fair bit about these things?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0261">well that yes and that and that is what makes the difference between a top notch and whatever blah blah blah blah however the good one is somebody who is continuously learning and and hence there will be things where they need to learn different things within these things or that the rules have changed and all of that</u>
<u n="534" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0261">and they pick that up as they go and over time grow with that</u>
<u n="536" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well this that that well then that's you that's perfectly you</u>
<u n="537" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>? yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0262">yeah? that's why you can do that job</u>
<u n="539" who="S0261" trans="overlap">I mean it's not it's er <trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc>yeah of of course because you can pick it up and learn it as you go</u>
<u n="540" who="S0262">yeah but you're managing</u>
<u n="541" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="542" who="S0262">so you're doing the people work as well</u>
<u n="543" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0262">not just quality and lifelong learning <unclear>and sort of</unclear> like taking an interest in their work</u>
<u n="545" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0262">but you're actually going mm I don't think he's really put as much effort into that as I think he should've done</u>
<u n="547" who="S0261">yes of course and and and</u>
<u n="548" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and I won't get him to do more for me for the same</u>
<u n="549" who="S0261" trans="overlap">look I'm very able</u>
<u n="550" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0261">to be able to find out put two and two together and say well does that equal what I want it to equal? because it doesn't take much to find out enough yourself very quickly and it doesn't take much to connect with people who do know what the story is yeah?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well fuck then that's good because you've got a bit of a talent for it then from what you're saying</u>
<u n="553" who="S0261">so you <trunc>j</trunc> you yeah you just go well look I'm being delivered to the this is it right? if er if you don't feel in your gut that it is right then you go to somebody else and you say would you mind having a look at this? or can I ask you some questions about this? and you'll get a a an appropriate and I can usually pick up something look at it and go dunno about that you know I'll ask a few questions you go back to the person you ask a few questions</u>
<u n="554" who="S0262">yeah but <unclear>there's no</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0261">all of that</u>
<u n="556" who="S0262">remember you put <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>you have some</unclear> experience in that area</u>
<u n="557" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="558" who="S0262"><unclear/> starting a whole new subject from scratch <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's like you've been put back at the age of whatever age it was you started in</u>
<u n="559" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="560" who="S0262"><unclear/> university ah just think how long it took you to be able to do that in your subject area you think you're gonna be able to do the same in a new subject?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0261">yes of course</u>
<u n="562" who="S0262">but what's the accelerator? what's actually going to speed you up so it doesn't take as long as it took to <unclear/> in engineering?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0261" trans="overlap">I am er no er the well the your point erm goes back to the core of what a project manager is</u>
<u n="564" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0261">yeah? and that er er er the the PRINCE two side of project manager is somebody who generically has skills who can work in a variety of different things regardless of their background their <trunc>s</trunc> their their core skill</u>
<u n="566" who="S0262">mm okay</u>
<u n="567" who="S0261">and <trunc>th</trunc>they can operate in these different levels in these different <unclear>outlets</unclear> doing different projects right? so what they were trying to present was the idea that project managers that's a skill in itself er being a project manager the argument in certain outfits with <unclear/> <unclear>certain</unclear> things is that as a professional as a professional project manager in engineering you need to be an engineer and you need to know how things are built right? that makes common sense whereas if you were working as a project manager you could go along and you could work with people in the services people who who do er electrical infrastructure and you could probably operate that to a certain level by employing certain people with certain skill to ensure that they carry that yeah?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="569" who="S0261">but</u>
<u n="570" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0261">IT's another one</u>
<u n="572" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0261">right? IT</u>
<u n="574" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0261">right? I don't know how to put together er a <trunc>com</trunc>a computer system but I know how to I'll <trunc>pr</trunc>probably be able to procure the right people to do it and make sure that they do what I want them to do to a certain amount and that's exactly what these people in the Highway's Agency were doing they were certainly saying we don't know how it's supposed to work we know what we want but we hire somebody to tell us what we want er</u>
<u n="576" who="S0262" trans="overlap">was it efficient?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0261">and then</u>
<u n="578" who="S0262">did they run over budget?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0261">well erm in some cases of course you do because er er <trunc>s</trunc>some things are unknown however a well-run operation does not go over budget</u>
<u n="580" who="S0262">okay so as a as a project manager erm this would be equivalent in the film industry would be a producer and this would be er called a production manager</u>
<u n="581" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0262">and erm working as both erm <vocal desc="misc"/> you know you can imagine that's sound and that's you know wardrobe and that's you know you whoever and that's catering or whatever and like yeah fair enough I don't need to know a fuck of a lot about it but yeah I er I'm running with your argument a bit er that you you you you know in principle how it's meant to work yeah? you've got er enough quality assurance control to be able to go you haven't done it right go back and do it again yeah? and er you erm you are really a people person you know you are able to get the right type of contribution from the people at the right time</u>
<u n="583" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0262">when you need it</u>
<u n="585" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="586" who="S0262">and you can kick arse when it's not fucking happening right</u>
<u n="587" who="S0261">of course</u>
<u n="588" who="S0262">and you have to er but I still do think that going to film school and having worked in these departments with people</u>
<u n="589" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you're you're ahead of the game</u>
<u n="590" who="S0262">helped me a hell of a lot to know what it feels like to be one of them</u>
<u n="591" who="S0261">yes <trunc>th</trunc>that that's true</u>
<u n="592" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so I know what it's like to be a caterer</u>
<u n="593" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="594" who="S0262">I know what it's like to <trunc>ha</trunc> er hold that fucking boom thing I know what it's like to be hanging around with camera people and fucking cables and shit</u>
<u n="595" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0262">I know what it's like</u>
<u n="597" who="S0261">yeah so you've got a good gut feel of it</u>
<u n="598" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0261">yeah that's that's fine exactly</u>
<u n="600" who="S0262">I'm not a specialist</u>
<u n="601" who="S0261">and so if you were <trunc>t</trunc>trying to do this for new what you would do is you would put yourself in situations where you could ask the right questions and learn about the stuff pretty quickly right? so let's say that you bring together a team of people that you've never met before and you've asked them to do something right? and you've given yourself a week to say these people will do what they do you're saying they're the right group of people to work collaboratively together and you say you need to do this simple whatever get the right team of people together and you are there working with them to do that stuff in that one week and you will learn a huge amount in that one week by putting your time into that having that all together in the same place <unclear>right</unclear>?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0262">okay okay and for a new era that's not a bad way of doing it</u>
<u n="603" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="604" who="S0262">because we are talking about things that have been professionally been done for years and years and years</u>
<u n="605" who="S0261">er er <trunc>e</trunc>exactly</u>
<u n="606" who="S0262">but if you are in a new area of design I say era sorry era</u>
<u n="607" who="S0261" trans="overlap">era mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0262">of design then potentially yes you are actually even the blueprint is not just the actual thing that you sell the know-how</u>
<u n="609" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="610" who="S0262">it's the getting together of the right creators and contributors</u>
<u n="611" who="S0261">and <trunc>c</trunc> er exactly so</u>
<u n="612" who="S0262">but these are new people</u>
<u n="613" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0262">on the block</u>
<u n="615" who="S0261">so if you consider what I'm trying to do at the moment and I have this idea in my head that I want to have a certain amount of things done I want to outsource them one thing I need to know is how <trunc>f</trunc> how the fuck do you do outsourcing? alright? I don't know but what I can do when I'm away is I can meet up with two or three different people who actually do it and talk to them and find out in a short period of time a gut feel for how it works right?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0262">okay what I like about what you've just said before that and I agree with you for <trunc>outsour</trunc> the at the <trunc>w</trunc> er what you said was ask questions sorry ask people questions at the right time to get the most accurate</u>
<u n="617" who="S0261">presentation?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0262">impression of what's really going on and what needs to be done</u>
<u n="619" who="S0261">yes of course</u>
<u n="620" who="S0262">and by when</u>
<u n="621" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="622" who="S0262">so that's a project manager's remit</u>
<u n="623" who="S0261">yes of course</u>
<u n="624" who="S0262">okay now er er outsourcing to me it's just still like finding your team yeah? you're creating a team</u>
<u n="625" who="S0261">er <trunc>a</trunc>absolutely of course all all I'm talking er I I don't like the word I'm going to call it remote working I don't like that either but it's</u>
<u n="626" who="S0262">can't we just call it creating a team?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0261">yes okay yes alright</u>
<u n="628" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay so when you go to er when you go to <unclear>your</unclear> countries you select to go and have a look</u>
<u n="629" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0262">there are the cultural things and observing business and all those sort of things that's great but another <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="631" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the foundational things you need to understand</u>
<u n="632" who="S0262">okay foundation is culture yeah you're right</u>
<u n="633" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="634" who="S0262"><unclear>culture and</unclear> <unclear/> cultural way of doing business you know all the way to how they shake hands and everything you try and soak it all up</u>
<u n="635" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="636" who="S0262">and erm but then on the other levels you were thinking right shit if I was a project manager and I had to create a team <pause dur="short"/> er what are the steps that are required to do that?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="638" who="S0262">that's I think what you should do</u>
<u n="639" who="S0261">exactly of course</u>
<u n="640" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="641" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="642" who="S0262">good</u>
<u n="643" who="S0261">so you asked that simple question and and over over dinner you can find out the answers to stuff</u>
<u n="644" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0261">it's <trunc>v</trunc> it's straightforward</u>
<u n="646" who="S0262">yeah you need to get a thingy on</u>
<u n="647" who="S0261">okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but yeah if <trunc>y</trunc>if you do that in Asia but also definitely talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0261">who sorry?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0261">yes yes er erm to ask <unclear>our</unclear> questions</u>
<u n="652" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and also talk to erm <vocal desc="misc"/> er anybody else we can think of</u>
<u n="653" who="S0261"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah and I think that what we wanna do now is actually write down who we think those people are</u>
<u n="654" who="S0262">yeah okay</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="655" who="S0261">we were erm talking about creating a team and having a understanding a cultural foundation so when we consider <unclear>that</unclear> in the future you want to create a team and if you look at the bigger wider context of you want to be trying to create a business where you have the flexibility to live where you need to live or where you want to live and operate that business with freedom of moving around from location to location right? so then you can maximise erm things like if you wanted to go and hang with your dad for three months you could go and do that wherever or and then you could say well I want to go and hang here with somebody else for a period of time or you could just go to a certain location because that's where you want to go right? so you create a team which can still work with your business and they can be located wherever they want to be so they're a remote team</u>
<u n="656" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="657" who="S0261">yeah? so part of what I'm thinking about is this the the context of the outsourcing that I'm talking about is that if I create er some kind of business stream that er that brings in some money which I'm working in an outsourcing context and putting together all the threads that you need to work with to be able to operate that future business on that <trunc>m</trunc> on that way</u>
<u n="658" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="659" who="S0261">right? so you're saying you you're doing all of the the nasty things that you have to deal with which is finding the right people making sure they can do what you want trying some stuff out and then <trunc>p</trunc> getting people on board creating a reliable relationship such that they erm continually deliver things for you to the quality that you want and the time that you want yeah? erm and the more that you get to do that you're learning how to do that and also you're learning the skills to be able to sell that as a product to other people so that you bring business in from other people which you then outsource so you're providing you're the conduit to allow them to be outsourcing and you take a middleman's fee on it</u>
<u n="660" who="S0262">and you run run that all past <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> see what he makes of what you're saying</u>
<u n="661" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0262">cos I actually have got no clue what you're talking about not er not because I don't understand the English just that I <trunc>d</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc><trunc>n</trunc>none of this I've ever done I I've not read anything about it I'm not</u>
<u n="663" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="664" who="S0262">aware of how it could operate I don't know how the money comes in and how you get capital to pay people and how you pay people and er you know that's the things that I don't I wouldn't know how to do you know</u>
<u n="665" who="S0261" trans="overlap">right okay yeah well there is some guys out of these outfits that I was being listening erm listening to who operate businesses solely providing outsourcing services in the Philippines for instance yeah? and that they make good business out of that so they go and live in these places they make the right connections they get quality people to work with them and then they sell that as a product to people who need that particular skill set</u>
<u n="666" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no no I get that I get that</u>
<u n="667" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0262">it's just that</u>
<u n="669" who="S0261" trans="overlap">all of that</u>
<u n="670" who="S0262">for for your reality</u>
<u n="671" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0262">of how you put that all together erm and I think the biggest thing you've got to be thinking about now is money how do you finance that?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0261">yes exactly so if if I simply take what I'm what I'm just doing now which is web design and development yeah? if I'm if I can see that it's a worthwhile exercise <trunc>t</trunc>to to to compartmentalise some of the things I've been doing and ship those out and get clients first er you've gotta make the things fit together nicely in a box but if you can get clients' work in ship that stuff out get it back and you're allowing yourself enough time to make sure that you're providing them exactly what they want how they want it to be done so you're probably doing some work yourself but not all of it</u>
<u n="674" who="S0262">I think I think I think I think erm I think for the first crack at this I think you're on er quite a complicated level and I think you need to seek business advice before embarking on this a proper businessman who would understand how how do you deal with creditors? how do you deal with debtors? how do you you know what currency are we talking?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0261">well there are there's international stuff that you need to deal with</u>
<u n="676" who="S0262">yeah so er</u>
<u n="677" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0262">so <trunc>w</trunc> talking to</u>
<u n="679" who="S0261" trans="overlap">contractual et cetera</u>
<u n="680" who="S0262">er I'd say yes but get a lot of advice before you start running that yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah and and and the first thing I do I'm just gonna go on the Location Rebel community and ask them a bunch of questions and say I want to talk to anybody who's got experience in doing this stuff in Asia and I want to hear the different stories and try and cherry-pick out the key points that I can put together as these are a bunch of questions I'm gonna ask some bigger points about <unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0262">absolutely you see if you just go into your remit for the next you know if you set yourself a course about about always always always getting that what you want</u>
<u n="683" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="684" who="S0262">getting these answers yeah?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="686" who="S0262">and if you can actually go I've got eighty-seven percent success</u>
<u n="687" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="688" who="S0262">yeah? on getting answers that I think on your hunch or gut or whatever it is that you've used in the past</u>
<u n="689" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="690" who="S0262">if you can actually rate yourself and rate the answers</u>
<u n="691" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="692" who="S0262">then yeah you're you are finding out how to create a team</u>
<u n="693" who="S0261">mm that's right</u>
<u n="694" who="S0262" trans="overlap">absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0261">so as an er example what I was thinking er of the other day which is slightly towards that but erm I was thinking I've gotta create a video out of the the stuff that I got for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="697" who="S0261">from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0261">I've got to create that so I went on on on to Fiverr dot com</u>
<u n="700" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0261">cost five dollars</u>
<u n="702" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0261">look for video editors</u>
<u n="704" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0261">see what they can do</u>
<u n="706" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0261">for fifteen dollars I can get three different editors to do three different things you've got three different creative products for fifteen bucks</u>
<u n="708" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0261">and you go okay for fifteen dollars I've tested who I want to go with</u>
<u n="710" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0261">right? and then you go back to the other person you say okay well I can see what you can do for five bucks I'll pay you fifty dollars to produce something for me</u>
<u n="712" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0261">I want something that's two minutes long out of this content and erm we want to have er something at the start and something at the end and some of these guys do animation and stuff like that so</u>
<u n="714" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0261"><unclear>just</unclear> mix and mix and match it and make it something fun this is the brief</u>
<u n="716" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0261">and these are the threads that I wanna see in it put it together</u>
<u n="718" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0261">and</u>
<u n="720" who="S0262">but <trunc>th</trunc>the I the the thing about this is this is all really good and all the stuff you've just said but again er I I really would like to know how you're gonna finance it <pause dur="short"/> when you pay somebody fifteen dollars or fifty dollars that's not not not necessarily obvious to me where this money is coming from</u>
<u n="721" who="S0261">no no that's right so so in in in that context the money er is coming in in that I'm being paid to do this job right?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0262">er yeah this is doesn't</u>
<u n="723" who="S0261">so it's an expense</u>
<u n="724" who="S0262">yeah it doesn't work like that</u>
<u n="725" who="S0261">it's an expense right?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0262">you need capital <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to before you get paid <pause dur="short"/> that capital</u>
<u n="727" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well <trunc>w</trunc><trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="728" who="S0262">will see you through until you actually get paid</u>
<u n="729" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes that's right</u>
<u n="730" who="S0262"><unclear>you don't work it the other way round you're fucked if you do it the other way round</unclear></u>
<u n="731" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I know that and I've got capital cos I've been paid two thirds of the job I've got that sitting in a bank account</u>
<u n="732" who="S0262">oh I see</u>
<u n="733" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="735" who="S0261">I've already got that I've already been through part of the process to get to the point where I'm trying to finish something off</u>
<u n="736" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay so</u>
<u n="737" who="S0261">I decide based upon my effort and time that rather than me do it I get somebody else to do it</u>
<u n="738" who="S0262">okay <trunc>tha</trunc>that's fine</u>
<u n="739" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0262">er that's fine I didn't understand that so what you're saying is is that the money that you got from <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="741" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="742" who="S0262">is what you're calling seed money</u>
<u n="743" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="744" who="S0262">to give this a go</u>
<u n="745" who="S0261">well I'm calling it in context of just what I talked about the bigger picture stuff erm yes I could call that that sorry I <trunc>d</trunc> er I think we've gone two different directions slightly</u>
<u n="746" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay alright here's er here the thing is is that erm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0261">in the context of what we've just talked about I could argue you use the money that's sitting there fifteen dollars goes out of that pot I've already got yeah? and then I and then I choose somebody and I pay them fifty dollars and so I've created an expense yeah?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0262" trans="overlap">er I think</u>
<u n="749" who="S0261">which I can then claim back in the final invoice</u>
<u n="750" who="S0262">I think you really need to go and do a a a a business er just a little short <trunc>s</trunc>short cos</u>
<u n="751" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear>alright</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0262">what you're saying really doesn't work like that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't you really need to know how it works before you start playing around with this with your own money but you need to ask <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that cos you won't believe me but ask a businessman <vocal desc="laugh"/> and see if he understands what you're talking about</u>
<u n="753" who="S0261">well what are you? look the some of the stuff's very obvious to me right? you need capital up front to fund something to be able to get it going right? you need that money from somewhere okay? and <pause dur="short"/> and you need to plan out with that pot of money what you expect it to cost to get to somewhere right? trying to meet a certain end before the income comes in cos you need to provide yourself that er that float before you get into getting income in</u>
<u n="754" who="S0262">I think you need to break it up into manageable chunks</u>
<u n="755" who="S0261">yes I <trunc>kn</trunc> yeah yeah yeah mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0262">yeah I think you just need to go to Asia</u>
<u n="757" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0262">and fucking don't worry about revenue for the moment okay? don't even worry about capital just just break it up into <trunc>s</trunc> er one small thing</u>
<u n="759" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0262">then come back</u>
<u n="761" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="762" who="S0262">and then just think about the next step er this is not gonna happen overnight</u>
<u n="763" who="S0261">no I know that</u>
<u n="764" who="S0262">capital needs to come from somewhere</u>
<u n="765" who="S0261">yes that's right</u>
<u n="766" who="S0262">yeah?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0262">and you while you're going to Asia and you're doing what you're doing you will start thinking how the fuck am I gonna get the money together to start doing all this?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0262">and that that'll be you solving that problem</u>
<u n="771" who="S0261">yes that's right mm</u>
<u n="772" who="S0262">but you don't have the answer to it yet</u>
<u n="773" who="S0261">well once you put together a coherent plan in theory you can go to the bank and go er give us some money if you wanted to yeah? or we can say we're gonna get this money from somewhere which pot of are we going to come bring this from? if we see that there's value in it</u>
<u n="774" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0261">or then you can do what's called bootstrapping and you can go and find a small job get some income in set set some of that aside as you receive money to go into your capital pot and do several of those till you build up your capital pot and then you carry on with what you do and that's what I suggested that before this this kind of get on the right thread do a series of things first to try and put that kind of mechanism in place so you're getting an income stream that is helping to then provide the seed to carry on with the bigger plan</u>
<u n="776" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0261">yeah? so if you can come up with two or three income streams for different things that aren't large amounts of money but they don't require a lot of your work online and there are things that you can do that don't require a lot of input but you don't get a lot of financial input either that's something that's quick and easy to do and you get paid five hundred to a thousand dollars to do it</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
