<text id="S66E">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:26:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0405 S0555</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Footpath, Slough</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>School project, poverty, life, friends, politics, scientific research, consumerism, comics, </topics>
		<activity>Friends walking home discussing schoolwork and friendships</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0405">
				<exactage>17</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Slough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Slough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years and 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0555">
				<exactage>17</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wembley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Slough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0405">I was meant to have a session with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday say that we were handing it in but <pause dur="short"/> but I don't I said oh there's no point having a session until I've finished it so handed it in she's like that's cool okay</u>
<u n="2" who="S0555">how long is your EPQ going to be? like your essay</u>
<u n="3" who="S0405">apparently it's only like five thousand words which is like I could write that in a day</u>
<u n="4" who="S0555">really? <pause dur="short"/> five thousand words I <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="5" who="S0405" trans="overlap">like a whole day right if if I dedicated a whole day to it five thousand words is like <pause dur="short"/> that's not ridiculous</u>
<u n="6" who="S0555">I I struggle with like writing like coursework and stuff like that</u>
<u n="7" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0555">I can't do it</u>
<u n="9" who="S0405">but that would be like fluff that would be like <pause dur="short"/> me chatting bullshit I <trunc>wa</trunc> I want to make it decent</u>
<u n="10" who="S0555">mate what is er your title?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0405">er erm so it's now What Should Humanity Do About Poverty in the West <unclear>Balkans</unclear>? <pause dur="short"/> erm because I wanna include erm you know political responses as well as you know human responses such as biological and religious responses</u>
<u n="12" who="S0555">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0405">but I think the EU thing is really interesting and that relates to when we're going to Montenegro so <pause dur="short"/> well like it's it's it's going to be so easy to just make it really broad and just <pause dur="short"/> literally just chat about the Balkans <pause dur="short"/> but I should like I need to have a focus title and I need to <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you know have an aim and analyse some data and all that so</u>
<u n="14" who="S0555">why did you choose the Balkans?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0405">erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> suggested it and <pause dur="short"/> basically it was gonna be on poverty in general</u>
<u n="16" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0405">then <pause dur="short"/> it made sense to choose a specific areas cos poverty's so massive and <pause dur="short"/> there's likely to be more data and there there is data on poverty in the Western Balkans so I should focus on just that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> yeah and then she suggested it and I'm kind of doing it in history so and then then we're going to Montenegro so I was like yeah why not? <pause dur="short"/> plus I've been to Turkey which you know European poverty is like more related to erm situations in <pause dur="short"/> er Africa or something you know you know that erm <pause dur="short"/> what was I <unclear>gonna</unclear> say? you know the I don't know if I did give it to you in the end there was booklets on like the stuff we got in the Helsinki group</u>
<u n="18" who="S0555">oh yeah yeah I still I still have I have them I still have them I need to give them back</u>
<u n="19" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah I mean <unclear/> I didn't read them can I yeah can I have them back just for the EPQ? <unclear/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0555">yeah yeah yeah you can have them they're yours anyway</u>
<u n="21" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah cos erm <pause dur="short"/> might be useful <trunc>w</trunc>was it? <pause dur="short"/> it was overcoming <pause dur="short"/> oppression or <trunc>eco</trunc>economic erm <pause dur="short"/> problems in it was either Turkey or it was like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0555">it was Turkey</u>
<u n="23" who="S0405">it was Turkey okay but it's cool in erm in history now we're doing <pause dur="short"/> well I'm doing the Armenian genocide and stuff and like</u>
<u n="24" who="S0555">your what do you mean you're only doing it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0405">erm we were all assigned a country</u>
<u n="26" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0405">and then we had to research its change from eighteen fifteen to nineteen fifteen to the outbreak of war</u>
<u n="28" who="S0555" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0405">and obviously how that contributed so you know stuff like <pause dur="short"/> countries becoming more nationalistic encouraged further or a country becoming more <pause dur="short"/> liberal against you know autocracies if you look at countries in eighteen fifteen kings were so important or or or tsars or erm <pause dur="short"/> whatever Germany had</u>
<u n="30" who="S0555">er Kaiser</u>
<u n="31" who="S0405">Kaisers and then <pause dur="short"/> later well if you look at nineteen fifteen you could argue it had much less influence just because of the growth of modernism and liberalism</u>
<u n="32" who="S0555"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="33" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that was <unclear/> er so <unclear/></u>
<u n="35" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0405">ah <pause dur="short"/> you're <trunc>ma</trunc> no no that's gross</u>
<u n="37" who="S0555">my grandma does that it's disgusting</u>
<u n="38" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah? what in in the house?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0555">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0405">no that's like like grandma okay but when you hear like thirty year olds who have like that's what I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be like when he's twenty-five <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0555" trans="overlap">I seriously don't get this mentality about like if <pause dur="short"/> cos he's basically just like a nihilist</u>
<u n="42" who="S0405">yeah is he?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's like</u>
<u n="44" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0555">nothing nothing really matters so we should all be so we should be hedonists</u>
<u n="46" who="S0405">does he <trunc>rea</trunc>? <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="47" who="S0555">so if nothing matters the only thing you should pursue is pleasure</u>
<u n="48" who="S0405">I think</u>
<u n="49" who="S0555">and he thinks that it's good to pursue things which are</u>
<u n="50" who="S0405" trans="overlap">just short term</u>
<u n="51" who="S0555" trans="overlap">ultimately yeah self destructive</u>
<u n="52" who="S0405">right</u>
<u n="53" who="S0555">he thinks it's equal to pursue things which aren't</u>
<u n="54" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> shit <pause dur="short"/> you need to think of the rest of your life</u>
<u n="55" who="S0555">and it's just like yeah I know exactly like if you're gonna say yolo like you only live once</u>
<u n="56" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0555">your point is if you only live once then make sure it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0405" trans="overlap">then you should make it more precious right?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0405">not</u>
<u n="61" who="S0555">not like try and make yourself die at fucking forty</u>
<u n="62" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's that's what's wrong about yolo because that's how it's interpreted <pause dur="short"/> by like everyone</u>
<u n="63" who="S0555" trans="overlap">oh there's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0405">where?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0555">in there Starbucks</u>
<u n="66" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh right oh <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it's like how can you not know how even occasional smoking how much it's <unclear>doing to you</unclear>?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0555" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't get him</u>
<u n="68" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> argue it</u>
<u n="69" who="S0555">I think he's like <pause dur="short"/> he was like oh yeah or cos like apparently <trunc>lo</trunc>loads of people in his family smoke <unclear/> family</u>
<u n="70" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0555">like even though like <pause dur="short"/> really old people and he's like oh yeah they've smoked for so many years and they're still fine <pause dur="short"/> like maybe I've got good genes or something</u>
<u n="72" who="S0405" trans="overlap">no way fucking <pause dur="short"/> shittiest argument</u>
<u n="73" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0405">ah <pause dur="short"/> my garage roof is made of asbestos and I got really worried about it <pause dur="short"/> cos er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and someone I don't know</u>
<u n="75" who="S0555">oh it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I lived under it for a year before finding that out and then then I researched it and it's only when it's like used in building work and it's inhaling the dust that does the damage but it's really scary cos you don't find out that you've got erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>asbos</trunc>asbestosis erm lung cancer twenty or thirty years afterwards</u>
<u n="77" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0405">and like you like you not that you'd want it immediately but like the thought that you could just die from or you could</u>
<u n="79" who="S0555" trans="overlap">cos the thing is then it could advance in later stages and then you're left with like stage four cancer</u>
<u n="80" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah you don't know about it and you're like shit</u>
<u n="81" who="S0555">cos I I did lung cancer for my er issue report last year</u>
<u n="82" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0555">and like it it's you're so fucked basically that's what it is</u>
<u n="84" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's awful</u>
<u n="85" who="S0555">if if you get lung cancer you're so fucked</u>
<u n="86" who="S0405">really?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0405">I thought I did I did childhood leukaemia and the like survival rates now are like ninety percent</u>
<u n="89" who="S0555">yeah yeah that's the thing like oh if all all for things like leukaemia they're really high</u>
<u n="90" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0555">but for things like lung cancer it erm <pause dur="short"/> smoking-based lung cancer</u>
<u n="92" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0555">is really er really high er death rate because it's really high hard to notice</u>
<u n="94" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0555">so because it develops in different cells than normal</u>
<u n="96" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> does it relapse after with some people do find a way to <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0555">yeah yeah also yeah and also it's really hard to get shit out of your lungs cos</u>
<u n="98" who="S0405">oh right</u>
<u n="99" who="S0555">you know you need to breathe air but you also need to like extract everything</u>
<u n="100" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0555">and make sure you don't do do enough damage while you're extracting stuff</u>
<u n="102" who="S0405">right</u>
<u n="103" who="S0555">like you can burn skin off like to take cancer cells off and stuff</u>
<u n="104" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0555">if you burn your lungs and they're damaged you can't really breathe properly</u>
<u n="106" who="S0405">yeah of course</u>
<u n="107" who="S0555">but yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0405">feel so precious <pause dur="short"/> hey erm erm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0555">feel like I'm interviewing you</u>
<u n="110" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is what yeah I know it makes it so much formal more formal erm <pause dur="short"/> when I I was cleaning my garage and like <pause dur="short"/> it's just always been dusty as shit</u>
<u n="111" who="S0555">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0405">so I've like wiped everything but like for two days it it was last weekend the two days where I was cleaning it</u>
<u n="113" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0405">it was just like ah like <pause dur="short"/> you know your throat gets really wheezy I don't know if you ever have that and like <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> just coughing up so much phlegm and like mucus and like but like it's completely clean now so <pause dur="short"/> there's no fucking dust in there <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0555" trans="overlap">it's horrible</u>
<u n="116" who="S0405">I checked whether that does anything bad and it's fine</u>
<u n="117" who="S0555">I I went to the airport on Saturday <pause dur="short"/> because my er</u>
<u n="118" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0555">er no no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos my uncle was going erm to Pakistan to get my grandmother</u>
<u n="120" who="S0405">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0555">cos she's she's like ninety she lives by herself and she's ninety</u>
<u n="122" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0555">and like <pause dur="short"/> she got a bit sick recently</u>
<u n="124" who="S0405">uhu</u>
<u n="125" who="S0555">so my gran er so my gran er my uncle's taking her back here <pause dur="short"/> so like <pause dur="short"/> she's</u>
<u n="126" who="S0405" trans="overlap">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0555">no just for like cos like she might need more help because and the medical care is much better here</u>
<u n="128" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0555">so like he was there and like while we were there erm <pause dur="short"/> we saw like these Sikh people</u>
<u n="130" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0555">and <pause dur="short"/> because they were in the part where erm like where they were like Pakistan airlines and shit they were obviously going to Pakistan</u>
<u n="132" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0555">which is you know er yeah okay that's a bit unusual cos they usually go</u>
<u n="134" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0555">but like the first er the first good rah is in Pakistan</u>
<u n="136" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0555">so I was like it's not that odd</u>
<u n="138" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0555">cos they do go</u>
<u n="140" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0555">but then erm <pause dur="short"/> he got he was getting interviewed</u>
<u n="142" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0555">by by <pause dur="short"/> this thing I don't what it was called <pause dur="short"/> he was being interviewed and I was like oh that's really weird so of course er my dad</u>
<u n="144" who="S0405">uhu</u>
<u n="145" who="S0555">and me went like snuck up next to him <vocal desc="laugh"/> so we could try and hear what he was saying</u>
<u n="146" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0555">and erm he was speaking really loudly as well he was like <pause dur="short"/> he wasn't speaking English so I didn't understand it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0555">but basically <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> in <pause dur="short"/> in Indian Punjab</u>
<u n="150" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0555">they're like <pause dur="short"/> the government's treating Sikhs really really really badly</u>
<u n="152" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0555">and so they've gone they've gone to these people are going like members of the Sikh community from the UK</u>
<u n="154" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0555">or India I don't know where they're from <pause dur="short"/> are going to Pakistan</u>
<u n="156" who="S0405">right</u>
<u n="157" who="S0555">Pakistan Punjab</u>
<u n="158" who="S0405">I see</u>
<u n="159" who="S0555" trans="overlap">to to try and</u>
<u n="160" who="S0405">escape</u>
<u n="161" who="S0555">not escape but like help relations like</u>
<u n="162" who="S0405">oh I see</u>
<u n="163" who="S0555">see if they can do anything <pause dur="short"/> it was like so weird</u>
<u n="164" who="S0405">so what he was being er they were going because of cos of that do you think?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0555">yeah yeah they said he said they were</u>
<u n="166" who="S0405">oh right okay</u>
<u n="167" who="S0555">that's why he was going</u>
<u n="168" who="S0405">did you see the guy on TV who were <pause dur="short"/> he was like on some some chat show BBC chat show and he was just like yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah no one's talking about this on the media?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0405" trans="overlap">and that's like I obviously haven't heard of it before like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0405">like is that a <unclear/>? I don't know it over there a fancy car outside a golf club <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> erm but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's the only time I've heard about it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0555">yeah apparently people are like dying a lot</u>
<u n="174" who="S0405">really?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0555">I don't know what I don't really know what's happening</u>
<u n="176" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0555">I should know but I don't know</u>
<u n="178" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right so many so much stuff like <pause dur="short"/> I wanna research like so I can actually have some authority to say stuff</u>
<u n="179" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0405">cos I hate people that they talk about <pause dur="short"/> like I don't it in general like I'm not obsessed about it but like people who <pause dur="short"/> they're gonna make really rash statements about like ISIS or <pause dur="short"/> the situation in Syria and they know nothing about it like</u>
<u n="181" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah that's why <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't <pause dur="short"/> that's why like I don't <pause dur="short"/> talk about when you talked about ISIS and stuff in RS cos I don't know anything</u>
<u n="182" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right right I see <pause dur="short"/> I see I see</u>
<u n="183" who="S0555">but like</u>
<u n="184" who="S0405">you do know a lot about <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>loads of</unclear> things</u>
<u n="185" who="S0555" trans="overlap">I don't <pause dur="short"/> no but it's like it's I don't get why people like feel the need to always add their opinion</u>
<u n="186" who="S0405">just have their opinion out there I know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0555">like some people</u>
<u n="188" who="S0405">like no one we're gonna reference <unclear/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0555" trans="overlap">no one we're gonna reference <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="190" who="S0405">there is puke on the floor</u>
<u n="191" who="S0555">I know I just noticed</u>
<u n="192" who="S0405">I I wasn't saying that to you</u>
<u n="193" who="S0555">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0405">I was just clarifying <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0555" trans="overlap">just clarifying</u>
<u n="196" who="S0405">we were just like er</u>
<u n="197" who="S0555">we we said er so many times</u>
<u n="198" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know or like ah or like er <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0555">ah <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0405">but yeah he does that he just <unclear/> like I don't I I'm not hitting on him but lots of people do it but as an example you know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0405">they just have to have their <pause dur="short"/> say like the most <pause dur="short"/> er did you see like today how pissed off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was getting? cos literally his hand <pause dur="short"/> went er like he usually puts his hand up a lot</u>
<u n="203" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0405">but today he <trunc>ju</trunc> he wouldn't shut up like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> er anyway I'm done with that done</u>
<u n="205" who="S0555">I was just it's so weird how like <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0405">uhu</u>
<u n="207" who="S0555">just talks like every lesson and then it's hardly like anyone else other than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0405">see like the whole <vocal desc="laugh"/> lesson like the dialogue between him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0405">like no but no he he's like way better than <pause dur="short"/> year twelve</u>
<u n="211" who="S0555" trans="overlap">he he says interesting things</u>
<u n="212" who="S0405">yeah I know now like I I respect much more of what he says</u>
<u n="213" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0405">than</u>
<u n="215" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0405">year twelve I think</u>
<u n="217" who="S0555" trans="overlap">he's actually had like a visible change like even when he was in year twelve it was it was still interesting but sometimes it was less</u>
<u n="218" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0555">it was just a bit like <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="220" who="S0405">shouting random</u>
<u n="221" who="S0555">and like yeah kind of like I don't know and also like less</u>
<u n="222" who="S0405">irrelevant</u>
<u n="223" who="S0555">yeah less relevant and less</u>
<u n="224" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0555">so invested in the topic more like doing mental gymnastics</u>
<u n="226" who="S0405">right <vocal desc="laugh"/> so what do you think about what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said about <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> social <trunc>just</trunc> health care and justice across the world?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0555">I don't know</u>
<u n="228" who="S0405" trans="overlap">do you think it's like?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0555">erm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0405">I did this I did this as part of my erm <pause dur="short"/> history report as well er like <pause dur="short"/> you know we had to do an ethics section I talked about <pause dur="short"/> cos the world health organisation was talking about it a lot and like erm <pause dur="short"/> er the survival rates of cancer like way lower obviously than erm in some parts of the third world than they are in <pause dur="short"/> western countries or <pause dur="short"/> more economic <trunc>de</trunc> economically developed countries <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I just felt like in RS they were just like hating on the science community and</u>
<u n="231" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah I <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's <trunc>al</trunc> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of odd to say like <pause dur="short"/> how do you justify prioritising research?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0405">yeah I know</u>
<u n="233" who="S0555">because people we haven't even got to where we are just by following what we need</u>
<u n="234" who="S0405">exactly <pause dur="short"/> we don't know <pause dur="short"/> where the next <pause dur="short"/> scientific discovery or where where research is heading or you know we don't know that we're gonna find <pause dur="short"/> you know er respective cures for erm <pause dur="short"/> cancers and and erm <pause dur="short"/> other deadly illnesses but we research it anyway because that's what's important now but</u>
<u n="235" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah and stuff like stuff that isn't always related or sometimes you know does <pause dur="short"/> help</u>
<u n="236" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is often</u>
<event desc="sound of cars"/>
<u n="237" who="S0555">like I don't know about cloning cloning I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how it can help</u>
<u n="238" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know my opinion of cloning</u>
<u n="239" who="S0555" trans="overlap">maybe <pause dur="short"/> I don't know maybe within like developmental psychology or shit like or nature versus nurture that would be</u>
<u n="240" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0555">but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know stuff like the <trunc>hun</trunc> human genome project</u>
<u n="242" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0555">they don't have any direct like application to medicine but indirectly it had has helped so much</u>
<u n="244" who="S0405">yeah I guess that is useful in erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah as you say nature versus nurture is really important in <pause dur="short"/> criminal law and you know justifying actions</u>
<u n="245" who="S0555">but also stuff like finding out like things with different developmental diseases like</u>
<u n="246" who="S0405">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but do you think that it it should be a natural er aspiration of humanity to just research things in general?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0555">I don't know</u>
<u n="248" who="S0405" trans="overlap">it's science science is knowing</u>
<u n="249" who="S0555" trans="overlap">I mean like technically <pause dur="short"/> technically we can mate with chimps but erm <pause dur="short"/> we don't</u>
<u n="250" who="S0405">shall we do it? <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't that like</u>
<u n="251" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0405">I mean yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0555">so we we could technically but it's so people can deem it so unethical that we don't but should it be? I mean like</u>
<u n="254" who="S0405">why do you think it is unethical?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0555">I don't know I don't</u>
<u n="256" who="S0405">what wait what what would be the point? just to see what happens?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0555">I guess kind of <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="258" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> like cos they're not <pause dur="short"/> they're not evolved <unclear/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0555" trans="overlap">I mean that's just something <pause dur="short"/> I I know that's that's just the thing that's just something we could do for science</u>
<u n="260" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right right oh I see right</u>
<u n="261" who="S0555">but like it doesn't really have any direct benefit</u>
<u n="262" who="S0405">right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0555">you could do loads of random shit</u>
<u n="264" who="S0405">yeah I know</u>
<u n="265" who="S0555">but we don't</u>
<u n="266" who="S0405">yeah <pause dur="short"/> at least <pause dur="short"/> most scientific research it has a <pause dur="short"/> it has a context now and like from doing my <pause dur="short"/> er placement thing in the summer like <pause dur="short"/> they have to have a context and they have to explain why it's relevant to either local community or or the scientific community <pause dur="short"/> even though some things obviously seem pointless but most of the time you know you can justify why it's important and <pause dur="short"/> keeping contexts informed yes but <pause dur="short"/> but just knowing stuff is an aspiration in itself I think</u>
<u n="267" who="S0555">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0405">I don't think you can hate on someone for that <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think you should hate on like materialism before you hate on scientific research I mean</u>
<u n="269" who="S0555">there's a <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he <unclear/> brought this picture of like <pause dur="short"/> erm a erm <pause dur="short"/> of like your basically just like this thing like condemning the fact you like people prefer brand things over normal other non branded things</u>
<u n="270" who="S0405">right</u>
<u n="271" who="S0555">because the difference in price is not necessarily the difference in quality</u>
<u n="272" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0555">and like that's so fucking ironic <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is such a</u>
<u n="274" who="S0405" trans="overlap">isn't he the most sort of like <unclear/>? but like yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah he loves brands so much</u>
<u n="276" who="S0405">yeah I know like</u>
<u n="277" who="S0555">and the</u>
<u n="278" who="S0405">he's not obsessive about it but he always talks about like yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0555">the thing he he's like such he's very materialistic cos</u>
<u n="280" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0555">he was like <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I'd be happy if I couldn't afford things that I want</u>
<u n="282" who="S0405">I see</u>
<u n="283" who="S0555">like if I couldn't go out to get <pause dur="short"/> really fancy dinners or buy really expensive clothes I wouldn't be happy</u>
<u n="284" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0555">I just find that so strange that he's like</u>
<u n="286" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="287" who="S0555">er heading for like materialistic hedonist nihilist</u>
<u n="288" who="S0405">so yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> the nihilism</u>
<u n="289" who="S0555" trans="overlap">I can understand I I can understand the nihilism kind of</u>
<u n="290" who="S0405">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then if you're nihilistic you should really not give a shit about what you own other than unless it brings <unclear/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0555" trans="overlap">kind of yeah you should but if you're not er usually if you're nihilistic you replace the set of values that you would get from religion from another set of values</u>
<u n="292" who="S0405" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0555">rather than becoming just hedonistic</u>
<u n="294" who="S0405">or just hate society and choose <pause dur="short"/> to conform to your own laws because you believe that <pause dur="short"/> society is pointless and and erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was talking about erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah people who go outside of the conforming conforming can can can</u>
<u n="295" who="S0555">conformity <pause dur="short"/> convention</u>
<u n="296" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><trunc>conform</trunc>conformity <pause dur="short"/> conventions probably yeah conventions of society are more free <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> that's why there is such an argument that <pause dur="short"/> erm the Joker was <pause dur="short"/> erm a nihilist because he <pause dur="short"/> because he didn't he didn't obey society's laws but <pause dur="short"/> then you you think that he wasn't a nihilist because he did believe in things like anarchy and <pause dur="short"/> creating chaos for a purpose not just for the sake of it but <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> comic book</u>
<u n="297" who="S0555" trans="overlap">there was this book on the psychology of either the Joker or Batman</u>
<u n="298" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0555">one of them</u>
<u n="300" who="S0405" trans="overlap">there's there's a oh what's it called? there's like a really famous erm <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> er er let's see like a cultural anthropologist or something he just analyses Batman and <pause dur="short"/> erm Star Wars and Game of Thrones now</u>
<u n="301" who="S0555" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> like popular fiction and popular culture</u>
<u n="302" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah really famous stuff erm and that's his life and like he's like consulted on <pause dur="short"/> I was watching some erm <pause dur="short"/> not a documentary but news things on Batman it was like they had him as a consultant brought on and it's like it's his full time job I was like no way and you know erm <pause dur="short"/> you know you're talking about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0405">did you say that he was like he wrote the original <pause dur="short"/> what Star Wars was based on?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0555">did he?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0405">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc>I was watching a cinema <unclear/> of erm the honest trailer for Star Wars and it was like</u>
<u n="307" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0405">the last thing they did was Joseph Campbell's star wars I was like what the fuck? and then I googled it and George Lucas admitted that he based Star Wars on one of Joseph Campbell's stories</u>
<u n="309" who="S0555">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0405">I need to look up which one it was one of his mythological <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0555" trans="overlap">he <trunc>wro</trunc> I don't <pause dur="short"/> no he he <pause dur="short"/> he developed the idea of like a mono myth which is the idea that</u>
<u n="312" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="313" who="S0555">all myths are inherently the same cos they contain the same er features and then he can outline all the features that they contain into one story</u>
<u n="314" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right okay <pause dur="short"/> I guess that's why</u>
<u n="315" who="S0555" trans="overlap">not one story he made like it's not like he was a writer he's like more of a</u>
<u n="316" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know I I knew he didn't write it</u>
<u n="317" who="S0555" trans="overlap">an analyst <pause dur="short"/> like yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0405">but like erm <pause dur="short"/> no I I think it was I think it was a specific story that was referred to <pause dur="short"/> but I was thinking why he wouldn't er I don't think he sued you know Lucas <unclear/> or anything <pause dur="short"/> but yeah what you're saying if if he believed that everything was just the same story repeated then yeah I guess so but yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I was George Lucas got a lot of crap for it</u>
<u n="319" who="S0555">I still haven't finished the trilogy</u>
<u n="320" who="S0405">what are you on?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0555">I've still I've only watched the first movie</u>
<u n="322" who="S0405">oh okay okay</u>
<u n="323" who="S0555">I haven't</u>
<u n="324" who="S0405">Empire Strikes Back is like one of those films that they say is just as good as the first like <pause dur="short"/> cos sequels don't usually do that</u>
<u n="325" who="S0555"><trunc>appar</trunc> is Jar Jar Binks only in the prequels?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah he's only in the prequels <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0555">is he why do people hate him so much?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0405">because he's just the most annoying <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> like character like just imagine</u>
<u n="329" who="S0555"><vocal desc="laugh"/> if you're gonna not know you mean he's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0405" trans="overlap">not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not religious but we have a friend called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is really annoying</u>
<u n="331" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0405">erm he's er <pause dur="short"/> erm okay so he he he he he was there to put as like to attract a younger audience</u>
<u n="333" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0405">and like a really wacky says stupid stuff erm <pause dur="short"/> but not in the Yoda way</u>
<u n="335" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0405">like in the original trilogy Yoda was like wacky but he was cool in that way</u>
<u n="337" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0405">because he was a Jedi master and he was this weird guy that lived out in Dagobar</u>
<u n="339" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0405">Jar Jar Binks is literally just there as an attention seeking hey look at me kids laugh at me and obviously that really annoyed pretty much all everyone <pause dur="short"/> like any of the fight scenes with him like he he he did really stupid stuff like erm <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> that made it just you know Star Wars is like hard to engross yourself in as it is but it made it more unbelievable because it was just this stupid guy just flailing around so <pause dur="short"/> but yeah he's annoying that's that's the main thing <pause dur="short"/> hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0555">hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="342" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hey</u>
<u n="343" who="S0405">you know what happened <unclear/> today? you know I said we're doing this presentation right?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0405">you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? they're two they're two people</u>
<u n="346" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0405">they went in to do their presentation in front of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0405">they were sitting down and they literally wouldn't stop laughing for a good two minutes <pause dur="short"/> they would just get like like they'd try to say er er er a line</u>
<u n="350" who="S0555">yeah?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0405">and then they'd just keep laughing <pause dur="short"/> and then erm <pause dur="short"/> and then erm so like thirty seconds er I'll walk around that way</u>
<u n="352" who="S0555" trans="overlap">are you doing <pause dur="short"/> are you sure?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0405">yeah then like yeah and then thirty seconds <pause dur="short"/> later <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh come on girls <pause dur="short"/> then like they just kept on laughing I was like oh fuck like literally any other teacher would just be like what the fuck? like in front of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then</u>
<u n="354" who="S0555">did he explode?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0405" trans="overlap">and then he <trunc>lit</trunc> he like came very close to it but he handled it so well he was just like girls just go outside for two minutes get in the right frame of mind but then he went into like <pause dur="short"/> you're gonna have to do presentations in your working life and if you just do shits and giggles you're gonna lose your job and all this shit like I don't know it was like really weird like you know you know how we lose it when <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0555" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0405">when like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says something that but in front of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's just like what? <pause dur="short"/> it's like really weird experience</u>
<u n="358" who="S0555">I've never had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> except for like in year eight</u>
<u n="359" who="S0405">oh yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0555">and nine</u>
<u n="361" who="S0405" trans="overlap">he was cool he was cool yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0555">I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah he was so nice to me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0405">oh really?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0405">in what way?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0555">cos like I <pause dur="short"/> we had this like big end of year project and I forgot to do it</u>
<u n="367" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah oh really</u>
<u n="368" who="S0555">and I was like I forgot it at home and he was like oh okay that's fine give it in to me tomorrow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0405">oh okay that's <unclear>cool</unclear> for what history?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0555">yeah and then I did it and then he gave me a prize</u>
<u n="371" who="S0405">no way ah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0405">what was it about do you remember?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0555">he probably gave me like a gift card or something for for <unclear/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0405" trans="overlap">no do you remember the project?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0555">oh the project was about erm <pause dur="short"/> independence of India</u>
<u n="377" who="S0405">oh that's <unclear>right</unclear> yeah I remember that <unclear/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0555">yeah I made pictures <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0405">made pictures?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0555">I <trunc>dre</trunc> I made pictures on the computer <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0405" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> that is <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with like?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0555"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> projects were so good</u>
<u n="383" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but she'd be fucking ah my god</u>
<u n="384" who="S0555">she is actually the</u>
<u n="385" who="S0405">she'd go OT on it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0555">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear>holy shit</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="388" who="S0555">her hers were like it's it it's like</u>
<u n="389" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0555">it's like you didn't get a person to do this you got someone someone has published a book and you've just bought that in</u>
<u n="391" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0555">it was so good they were so amazing</u>
<u n="393" who="S0405" trans="overlap">it was like do you think she got her mum's help or something?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0555">I don't know</u>
<u n="395" who="S0405" trans="overlap">they were like immense like oh</u>
<u n="396" who="S0555">I felt that she could of been that good cos she just I think she's just like</u>
<u n="397" who="S0405" trans="overlap">she <unclear>couldn't have</unclear> or could of?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0555" trans="overlap">no she could have been that good</u>
<u n="399" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="400" who="S0555">cos she's like I don't know <pause dur="short"/> she could have been I don't know</u>
<u n="401" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> her mum's smart</u>
<u n="402" who="S0555">her mum's smart? <vocal desc="laugh"/> what does that mean?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0405">I don't know you <vocal desc="laugh"/> have opinions about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0555">oh she's just an odd teacher I I'm it's</u>
<u n="405" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> how she is as a person? do you think she's like a knowledgable person like I see as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0555">er I don't know</u>
<u n="407" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0555">I don't I don't talk to her like</u>
<u n="409" who="S0405">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0555">I don't like ask her things <pause dur="short"/> the only thing I'd ask her is during lesson I wouldn't like ask her <pause dur="short"/> about anything else other than</u>
<u n="411" who="S0405" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="412" who="S0555">what we're doing right at that moment</u>
<u n="413" who="S0405">right right right so not like <pause dur="short"/> delve into her personal life</u>
<u n="414" who="S0555">no</u>
<u n="415" who="S0405"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will</u>
<u n="416" who="S0555">I mean no no</u>
<u n="417" who="S0405">I see I see</u>
<u n="418" who="S0555" trans="overlap">I don't think she wants she must I think she kind of sort of hinted at that she might of been in an abusive relationship before</u>
<u n="419" who="S0405">wow</u>
<u n="420" who="S0555">because we were talking about that in one of our books but</u>
<u n="421" who="S0405">jeez</u>
<u n="422" who="S0555">that wasn't really <pause dur="short"/> like proper</u>
<u n="423" who="S0405">right right</u>
<u n="424" who="S0555">and afterwards she took so long to remember my name <pause dur="short"/> she took forever</u>
<u n="425" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you don't joke about that with her you're just pissed off about <unclear/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0555">yeah I'm <pause dur="short"/> like how</u>
<u n="427" who="S0405">oh</u>
<u n="428" who="S0555">so annoying</u>
<u n="429" who="S0405">it's kinda funny <pause dur="short"/> there are a lot of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in our year you know <pause dur="short"/> in our</u>
<u n="430" who="S0555" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the only one you have to she knew everyone's name</u>
<u n="431" who="S0405">wow just like you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0555">yeah yeah that one</u>
<u n="433" who="S0405">oh man oh jeez <pause dur="short"/> that's awkward <pause dur="short"/> that's really awkward</u>
<u n="434" who="S0555">and also like this book I'm doing</u>
<u n="435" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0555">she mispronounces she says er main character's name wrong</u>
<u n="437" who="S0405">really?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0555">that I'm reading for my coursework and I was like oh maybe it's just her accent cos <unclear/> different</u>
<u n="439" who="S0405" trans="overlap">really? <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> right right right</u>
<u n="440" who="S0555">but then she wrote it down once and she doesn't fucking know his name <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0405">what? <pause dur="short"/> in what way? did she write it down the spelling wrong?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0555">yeah she spelt his name wrong</u>
<u n="443" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh what? <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="444" who="S0555">she's <trunc>wei</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but no <unclear/> is shit it's so bad it's so shit</u>
<u n="445" who="S0405">yeah not that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he was good</u>
<u n="446" who="S0555">he was interesting</u>
<u n="447" who="S0405">yeah and I just liked his debate he had strong opinions that he voiced</u>
<u n="448" who="S0555">oh yeah I remember debating <pause dur="short"/> very very very <pause dur="short"/> faintly</u>
<u n="449" who="S0405">he was like so good and so good at just getting people fired up</u>
<u n="450" who="S0555">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0405">and like er you know <pause dur="short"/> excited <pause dur="short"/> how how long's it been? <pause dur="short"/> as long as we've made twenty minutes</u>
<u n="452" who="S0555">er</u>
<u n="453" who="S0405">do do <pause dur="short"/> twenty-six nice</u>
<u n="454" who="S0555">yes</u>
<u n="455" who="S0405">perfect <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'll I'll I endeavour to send this off tonight so <pause dur="short"/> anyway bye <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0555" trans="overlap">bye</u>
<u n="457" who="S0405">bye bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
