<text id="S66F">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0251 S0252</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living room in Malton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cars and car insurance</topics>
		<activity>Cars</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0251">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>North Ferriby, East Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>GCSE Maths Examiner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0252">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>York</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0251">I think we need to get this car insurance sorted out soon <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and need to get another quote</u>
<u n="2" who="S0252">we do ah one thing that we need to do from ah change it to is erm put me as the main driver and increase the mileage up to erm nine thousand miles a year given that I will be doing a erm daily commute during most of the year</u>
<u n="3" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes that's going to be significantly more than it's been doing in the past</u>
<u n="4" who="S0252">yes it will a little bit of a shock <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0251">it will the car won't know what's happened</u>
<u n="6" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="7" who="S0251">so we'll have to try and give them a ring tomorrow</u>
<u n="8" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="9" who="S0251">and let them know that circumstances are going to change so</u>
<u n="10" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0251">I expect it's going to be quite a bit dearer this time</u>
<u n="12" who="S0252">well technically it will be the same price as last year but erm because we started erm at erm without not the full twelve months</u>
<u n="13" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0252">but this time you <unclear/> full amount</u>
<u n="15" who="S0251" trans="overlap">for the full year yes yes and a few extra miles won't it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0252">yes so technically you are getting a bit more for your money this time</u>
<u n="17" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="18" who="S0252">but obviously it's not as good as a a decrease in the price</u>
<u n="19" who="S0251">no it isn't how are you finding driving the Polo?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0252">it is a little bit different from what I was erm originally used to</u>
<u n="21" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="22" who="S0252">a learner car erm I think I've got used to it it does require a different style of driving</u>
<u n="23" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="24" who="S0252">I think you've got to remember you don't have as much power under your foot</u>
<u n="25" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="26" who="S0252">and the steering is doesn't produce as much feedback and a little bit lighter</u>
<u n="27" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="28" who="S0252">the gears are approximately the same</u>
<u n="29" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0252">although the <trunc>i</trunc>if you were driving the A three erm you'd probably find that the eh gear stick is a little stiffer</u>
<u n="31" who="S0251">oh right is it? yes</u>
<u n="32" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it's they think it's more feedback but</u>
<u n="33" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I see</u>
<u n="34" who="S0252">I think <unclear/> some ways designing cars for it to feel good to the driver as well as a a practical point of view</u>
<u n="35" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yes yes do you think that you're more likely to buy the car that you learned to drive in in the future?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0252">certainly that are similar</u>
<u n="37" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="38" who="S0252">ah I I was a a very good car really</u>
<u n="39" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0252">I think it was built to have very high standards</u>
<u n="41" who="S0251">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0252">and erm nice easy erm pleasurable to drive</u>
<u n="43" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="44" who="S0252">very sharp brakes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0252">erm quite a lot feedback on the steering and the gearbox</u>
<u n="47" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="48" who="S0252">I like the automatic handbrake</u>
<u n="49" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="50" who="S0252">I like that you don't have to take it off when you start erm the car</u>
<u n="51" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm I think I might find that a bit difficult to get used to actually</u>
<u n="52" who="S0252">well you'd if once you got used to it</u>
<u n="53" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="54" who="S0252">you would certainly miss it</u>
<u n="55" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="56" who="S0252">because for things like hill starts and when you're stopped at the traffic lights</u>
<u n="57" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="58" who="S0252">it definitely does make it a lot easier that you can just focus on putting it in gear one rather than having to release the handbrake from that type of thing</u>
<u n="59" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes the handbrake yes</u>
<u n="60" who="S0252">and also you know it's on it's either on or off you can't have partially have it on and then it rolls down a hill or something</u>
<u n="61" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes no no no I think once you've got used to using a handbrake that it comes pretty automatically when you're driving you just do it without too much thought really</u>
<u n="62" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes I think you find that I put the handbrake on a bit too stiff</u>
<u n="63" who="S0251">yes I can't pull it <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> can't release it when you put it on</u>
<u n="64" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0251">do you think more cars will have automatic handbrakes in the future?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0252">yes it is definitely something that is coming into <unclear/> you notice that with the erm Golf hire car</u>
<u n="67" who="S0251" trans="overlap">is that the way it's going? did that have it too?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="69" who="S0251">yes is it something that Audi have pioneered?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0252">I think Vauxhall had it before Audi but I think each car company designed its own slightly different variation</u>
<u n="71" who="S0251" trans="overlap">did they really? yes</u>
<u n="72" who="S0252">for example whilst Audi and VW are in the same group</u>
<u n="73" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0252">the VW erm automatic handbrake works differently to that of the Audi</u>
<u n="75" who="S0251">oh I see</u>
<u n="76" who="S0252">and that can be said a bit about different car manufacturers</u>
<u n="77" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="78" who="S0252">so all work slightly differently</u>
<u n="79" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0252">which is not such a good thing because the handbrake in a normal car it was really universal</u>
<u n="81" who="S0251">yes it was</u>
<u n="82" who="S0252" trans="overlap">but obviously if you're fitting these automatic button handbrakes that slightly different</u>
<u n="83" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="84" who="S0252">it's not going to help it when people have to borrow a car or hire a car or change a car</u>
<u n="85" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes that's right yeah that's true anyway we're going to have to have a little erm practice drive I think that the about the time that you would normally be leaving</u>
<u n="86" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="87" who="S0251">so that we get an idea of how long it's going to take you to get there</u>
<u n="88" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="89" who="S0251">bearing in mind that it could be very heavy traffic conditions</u>
<u n="90" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="91" who="S0251">which will probably take more time than we imagine</u>
<u n="92" who="S0252">I think if the traffic is generally bad</u>
<u n="93" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0252"><unclear/> I don't know how many trials we're going to do</u>
<u n="95" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="96" who="S0252">it might be worth considering the back route</u>
<u n="97" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="98" who="S0252">definitely when the weather is reasonable</u>
<u n="99" who="S0251">in good weather that'll probably be quicker</u>
<u n="100" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0251">if it's icy though you'll have to stick to the main road I think</u>
<u n="102" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="103" who="S0251">cos that will be sure to be gritted I think</u>
<u n="104" who="S0252">yes the that back road is unlikely to be</u>
<u n="105" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="106" who="S0252">well gritted</u>
<u n="107" who="S0251">it would be too dicey wouldn't it? <trunc>i</trunc>in this weather</u>
<u n="108" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><unclear/> be alright if you've got a four-by-four but</u>
<u n="109" who="S0251">mm but we haven't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0252">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0251">yeah and then there's the question of whether it's better to get the parking permit or to park at the park-and-ride and get the shuttle bus for the last little bit</u>
<u n="112" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes yes there's for and against with both really I think one good thing about the park-and-ride is there should be an abundance of space</u>
<u n="113" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="114" who="S0252">whereas I doubt that'll be guaranteed in the site parking</u>
<u n="115" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no that's it might get the parking permit get there and then find that all the spaces have gone and then you've got to go park it somewhere else anyway which might make you late</u>
<u n="116" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I know I know yes another thing about the er park-and-ride is there's usually so many spaces that it's really easy to get into them</u>
<u n="117" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yes yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0252">whereas er if there's only one space left at the university and the person's parked slightly over or something that's going to be a bit hard to get in</u>
<u n="119" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes I know sometimes it can be a bit tight that might be why it's left because it's a slightly narrower one</u>
<u n="120" who="S0252">yeah whilst I think the Polo is capable of getting in narrower <vocal desc="laugh"/> spaces it does make it more challenging to reverse it in and that sort of thing</u>
<u n="121" who="S0251">yeah we don't want to put it to the test <vocal desc="laugh"/> it sure does yeah mm if you could buy any car which car do you think you would like to choose? er which would you like the best?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0252">if it was any car?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0252">erm I I think it would be a a high spec A three saloon</u>
<u n="125" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="126" who="S0252">yes I think the saloon does provide a bit more space than the the A three hatchback</u>
<u n="127" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0252">but erm I think the saloons will be generally more expensive to buy</u>
<u n="129" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0252">which I'm not really looking for any additional expenditure</u>
<u n="131" who="S0251">mm was the headroom quite good? because with you being quite tall you need quite a deep cabin to fit in comfortably don't you?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it was reasonable</u>
<u n="133" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0252"><unclear/> the A three saloon might be more a bit more generous than the hatchback <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0252">yes but also I think erm a car that was smaller <unclear/> you'd struggle to have a fourth person in because the person behind the driver wouldn't have much legroom if I was using it</u>
<u n="137" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes that's right because you have your seat pushed as far back as it can</u>
<u n="138" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="139" who="S0251">to get yourself in don't you?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0252">because I can't reach the pedals with comfort if I'm not sat right</u>
<u n="141" who="S0251">no that's right you've got long legs <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0252" trans="overlap">my knees are hitting the</u>
<u n="143" who="S0251">steering wheel?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="145" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0252">one disadvantage of that is that if you are to just conceal the <unclear/> it doesn't mean you have to really bend forward a bit</u>
<u n="147" who="S0251" trans="overlap">lean forward yes you can see any traffic coming</u>
<u n="148" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="149" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0252">but it's amazing what opportunities we're getting I mean some cars do erm side by side parking spaces automatically</u>
<u n="151" who="S0251">really?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0252">they take control of the steering wheel and do it themselves</u>
<u n="153" who="S0251">that would be fantastic because that's one of the difficult manoeuvres isn't it?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="155" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="156" who="S0252">yes and erm some of them have got erm cameras at the back and the front to help you <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0251">yes that would be good as well</u>
<u n="158" who="S0252">that comes up on the erm it's off the entertainment system</u>
<u n="159" who="S0251">oh I see yes</u>
<u n="160" who="S0252">of course most medium to high-spec cars now come equipped with satnavs</u>
<u n="161" who="S0251">yes already built in</u>
<u n="162" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="163" who="S0251">yes that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0252">erm most have telephones integrated as well</u>
<u n="165" who="S0251">do they?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="167" who="S0251">like a mobile?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="169" who="S0251" trans="overlap">sort of</u>
<u n="170" who="S0252">so you don't have to install the hands-free equipment</u>
<u n="171" who="S0251">no oh right amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0252">yes what's erm do you think we should try and erm get a a further potentially a further discount by trying to compete insurance companies with one another or do you think that we're going to struggle to achieve that considering that there's not that much difference between our current insurer and the cheapest?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0251" trans="overlap">erm no have you checked on the comparison websites?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0252">yes the I think erm there's not going to be very much difference</u>
<u n="175" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no so you think we've more or less found the best deal that we can for the circumstances?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes but also I think it's with a good insurer as well it's it's got quite good erm which recommended provider status well it's just lost it but it was very close</u>
<u n="177" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes reviews? yes right yes</u>
<u n="178" who="S0252">yes so it's sort of in the top four or five insurers</u>
<u n="179" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes about yeah that's reassuring isn't it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0252">it is and also it's got the Yougov survey most erm assured <unclear/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah reliable yeah why is it that some of the insurance companies are not on the comparison websites then and you've got to look up those separately</u>
<u n="182" who="S0252">well they're trying their best not to have to lower their premiums as a result of erm comparison websites or they'll claim they're the cheapest so people will just think oh there's no point looking at comparison sites I'll just get a quote from there <unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh I see the competition yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm I see</u>
<u n="184" who="S0252">but generally some of them have been relatively competitive but not as good as the one <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes no</u>
<u n="186" who="S0252">so having a union discount also helps</u>
<u n="187" who="S0251">mm yeah it also makes it harder work for erm somebody who's looking for insurance that you've got to go on several different comparison websites and then these two or three other providers that you have to look up separately as well</u>
<u n="188" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it does yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0251">so it makes it a bit more long-winded</u>
<u n="190" who="S0252" trans="overlap">well to be honest the ah <anon type="place"/> don't seem to <unclear>be</unclear> on comparison sites either</u>
<u n="191" who="S0251">oh are they not on there?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0252">I think they are but I think I do suspect sometimes with comparison sites is one way that they make their money is to try and erm sort of do it by a ranking of which insurer has paid them the most to try and sort of broker a bargain like that</u>
<u n="193" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes really? bit convoluted isn't it?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="195" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0252">but I think with the best providers or the ones that are top on the Which list I think if you get a quote from them it just gives you a different idea of what it costs to get some reasonable cover because I don't think you would want to go for one that is quite far down the list with maybe only forty percent quality score and customer service I just want somewhere that's nearer seventy-eightyish <unclear/> what the best ones are</u>
<u n="197" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yes no no satisfied yeah mm and it probably be best to pay it all in one lump is it rather than doing these <unclear/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes well they treat it more like a mortgage agreement rather than a erm like a <unclear/> if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="199" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0252">I think from your point of view you're seen as a pay-as-you-go <unclear/> pay one month then pay the next month but they seem to think it's a way to make another twenty percent eh margin by sort of dressing it up as a loan</u>
<u n="201" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes oh right so you've got to pay for the of paying monthly yeah so we'll just do it all in one go and get it over with</u>
<u n="202" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm yes some do offer it without additional charge but I don't think that is one of them</u>
<u n="203" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes that is one of them no</u>
<u n="204" who="S0252">eh I think that we should really just focus on getting the best price within the year I don't think it's worth paying extra just for the privilege of paying each month</u>
<u n="205" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no yes mm and something that's going to be different this time I mean I think when I get the tax renewal which happens near Christmas</u>
<u n="206" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="207" who="S0251">it's eh not going to have a tax disc any more is it?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0252">I know I know</u>
<u n="209" who="S0251">I'm surprised that's happened</u>
<u n="210" who="S0252">it is it is it's it sort of marks the end of an era really</u>
<u n="211" who="S0251">it does yeah they'll be collector's pieces now</u>
<u n="212" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="213" who="S0251">those tax discs</u>
<u n="214" who="S0252">I've got some in my old toy post office</u>
<u n="215" who="S0251">I know I used to give you them to play with in your post office so it was a good way though police for instance telling immediately whether or not your tax disc was in date</u>
<u n="216" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="217" who="S0251">but now presumably they'll have to look something up won't they? on their database?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm well maybe with a like a scanner or something</u>
<u n="219" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0252">you know like just tap the registration plate and having said that I have noticed that on some of the roads we've been on there have been DVLA vans with cameras</u>
<u n="221" who="S0251">right</u>
<u n="222" who="S0252">erm obviously they must be checking for whether people have paid their tax or not so if they're using a camera I imagine they are using a database rather than the disc</u>
<u n="223" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="224" who="S0252">but I think in terms of something like an accident or erm what if erm a policeman's walking round on his duties it'll be easier to detect whether it's in date and whether it's been paid or not</u>
<u n="225" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm well the last time I bought the tax disc at the post office I took my insurance and MOT certificate but the girl didn't look at them because once she'd put in my car registration number she could already tell whether the insurance was paid and up to date and whether the MOT was</u>
<u n="226" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="227" who="S0251">so that's already a step towards doing that</u>
<u n="228" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it is yes but also you can buy it online as well</u>
<u n="229" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="230" who="S0252">so that would be erm using that same technology</u>
<u n="231" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="232" who="S0252">I don't know whether they expect people buy tax discs online new digital ones or whether you can still buy them at the post office or what the arrangement is exactly</u>
<u n="233" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yeah I don't know we'll have to see when we get the renewal won't we? that's exactly what's going to happen</u>
<u n="234" who="S0252">erm I don't know whether erm it will have its downsides I think it will possibly could be a little bit more bureaucratic in some ways because I don't think you know having these massive databases is perhaps not as simple as issuing the discs</u>
<u n="235" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0252">what do you think?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0251">I have to say there's usually a downside isn't there?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0252">yes or do you think people might think that they can get away with paying because there isn't any physical evidence of whether they've got it or not</u>
<u n="239" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I think that would be a bit dangerous really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0251">yes <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0252">do you how much more time do you think I will need before I get a car of my own do you think? it will probably be at the next renewal or?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0251">I don't know it's just finding the right car that you're interested in isn't it?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes and crucially at the right price</u>
<u n="245" who="S0251">at the right price definitely yeah will have to be quite a good value model car won't it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0252">yes I am personally hoping to get a an A three hatchback</u>
<u n="247" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="248" who="S0252">erm but the new model only came out two years ago</u>
<u n="249" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="250" who="S0252">so <unclear/> sort of this time next year we should start to see some reasonable ones on the second-hand markets</u>
<u n="251" who="S0251">yes that people have had for a couple of years and are then going to buy another new one</u>
<u n="252" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes yes but ah I think I would prefer to get the new model because I think it will age less</u>
<u n="253" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="254" who="S0252">because obviously the new model should be on the go for another well the old model was on the go for in excess of ten years</u>
<u n="255" who="S0251">oh right</u>
<u n="256" who="S0252">hopefully the new model will be so therefore it makes the car look newer which is they're still being produced</u>
<u n="257" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0252">but ah in some ways that is what you did with the Polo because erm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0252">you were one of their first new generation Polo owners</u>
<u n="261" who="S0251">oh I was I was a real trailblazer <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0252">indeed</u>
<u n="263" who="S0251">yeah I've liked it I've enjoyed driving it</u>
<u n="264" who="S0252">yes still have made some use of it</u>
<u n="265" who="S0251"><unclear/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0252">and erm I'll be bumping up the mileage significantly</u>
<u n="267" who="S0251">not literally I hope</u>
<u n="268" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0251">yeah I'm sure you'll be a very safe driver</u>
<u n="270" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0252">I personally find driving on A roads a bit easier than B roads</u>
<u n="273" who="S0251">mm yes</u>
<u n="274" who="S0252">there's a I think one thing about B roads is you do worry about <unclear/> enough space for a big lorry to come and pass <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah so tractors and things</u>
<u n="276" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes but obviously you don't need to worry about that quite as much on an A road because the dual carriageway</u>
<u n="277" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes it's more spacious isn't it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0252">yes obviously they are quite expensive to install and erm maintain if you <unclear/> a dual carriageway</u>
<u n="279" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah that's right</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
