<text id="S6A5">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:21:46</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013 S0152</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>no info</topics>
		<activity>talking about Liverpool over a cup of tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0152">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Birmingham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>w_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0013">okay</u>
<u n="2" who="S0152">is it working?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0012">yep</u>
<u n="4" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0152">so we goes on this and it's like first revolution round trying to get my bearings where it's so I swapped over seats in the in this eye type thing and it's <unclear/> second revolution round <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0152">oh I said oh we'll be getting off soon third revolution weren't stopping</u>
<u n="8" who="S0012">didn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0152">we had we went around six times</u>
<u n="10" who="S0013">six?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0152">and I went well that's pretty that's pretty good</u>
<u n="13" who="S0012">yeah that is that's brilliant</u>
<u n="14" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I said that's that's really good so he stops because you have your picture taken as you get on and they expect you to buy maybe buy that</u>
<u n="15" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0152">it was not a bad picture but I weren't paying</u>
<u n="17" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="18" who="S0152">I weren't paying ten pound for my picture</u>
<u n="19" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0152">and then I said like I said I think we're and it was getting probably round about</u>
<u n="21" who="S0012">was that a <trunc>polar</trunc>polaroid was it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0152">no it was a digital camera then printed out</u>
<u n="23" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="24" who="S0152">so it was a proper picture in a pack and everything and for fifteen pound you could have a fridge magnet and stuff like that</u>
<u n="25" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0152">yeah all the <unclear/> seen it before now never done it with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so I ain't gonna do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0012">cool</u>
<u n="28" who="S0152">yeah so I said no I think we need to get something to eat and it was like well we'll go to this place this jazz this steakhouse and jazz place I says well to be honest I said I don't know where it I don't know where it is I said and I am feeling a bit a bit peckish now I've had my breakfast at seven thirty this morning it is now like</u>
<u n="29" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="30" who="S0152">seven thirty quarter to eight of an evening I said I am a little bit hungry and I would like something I didn't <unclear/> I'd had crisps and something and a</u>
<u n="31" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no that's not good though is it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0152">cup of tea but I wanted I wanted something to eat and I remember last time and I says so we need to go somewhere and I said look there's plenty of restaurants by the docks I says and I don't <trunc>real</trunc> I said I don't really care tonight where we go so I do fancy steak I said but I'm quite happy they were well I fancy all you can eat Chinese and I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> okay I don't drink that often</u>
<u n="33" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0152">if I have steak I know that I can have a drink and it won't affect me</u>
<u n="35" who="S0012">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="36" who="S0152">where if I had all</u>
<u n="37" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0152">Chinese stuff it's gonna bloat me out in any case and I'm not gonna I'm not gonna wanna have a drink and I really I felt like I'm gonna have a drink type of thing that's what I felt like</u>
<u n="39" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0152">so we there was this steak house and we went in really really buzzing really busy and the guy came and said oh can I help you etcetera? yeah got a table for two? and he went yeah no problem looked at looked at the menu and it was a bit expensive it was a bit expensive but I I thought no I'm this is it this is if this is the only meal I have out this week <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's that's</u>
<u n="41" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this week</u>
<u n="42" who="S0152">that's that's what I'm doing cos I</u>
<u n="43" who="S0013" trans="overlap">go out yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0152">cos I cos I know from experience that's what it that's what it would be <vocal desc="laugh"/> so he went gotta tell you he said we haven't got this and we haven't got that and we haven't got the other he said we've had a we've had a run on steaks today</u>
<u n="45" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right</u>
<u n="46" who="S0152"><unclear/> all the time okay not a problem you know thanks for honest because some places would have just got you in sat down had a drink then you would have then felt</u>
<u n="47" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0152">that you had to have something because of that I said no it's alright no problem <pause dur="short"/> so er she says well what shall we do now? I said well we'll find somewhere else we'll head back to where the hotel is I said we've got all those places to eat round by the hotel I said they're all reasonable I said they're not expensive I says but we'll find some <unclear/> and as we're walking I spotted Bill's and I went in Bill's in <anon type="place"/> the other week for a cup of coffee it's a new it's a new restaurant chain that's open but it's starting to appear so I said well we'll go in here <pause dur="short"/> oh okay so <unclear/> look at the menu and it was <pause dur="short"/> it was it's cheap you know in in the sense of</u>
<u n="50" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0152">price of food went in I can't remember what oh we had a starter I can't remember what I had we had a starter and then we had a main meal with chips or <trunc>somet</trunc> I had a burger that's what I had burger and that was alright and I had a bottle of Bill's beer</u>
<u n="52" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="53" who="S0152">Bill's beer and that was alright and then we walked back to the hotel <pause dur="short"/> and she said we'll we've got <trunc>co</trunc> we've got we've in our package we've got complimentary drinks</u>
<u n="54" who="S0012">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0152">and I thought okay got complimentary drinks that's that's alright okay gets to the bar er one is <unclear>packaged</unclear> etcetera etcetera yeah you can have any drink you want bottles or on draught and I I was full so I didn't really want anything mega</u>
<u n="56" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="57" who="S0152">I didn't want anything mega from that from that point so I went oh I'll have a bottle I had a bottle of Peranoni or something like that and then it was like well I'll have a ginger beer an alcoholic ginger beer a ginger ale and I went do you want a ginger ale or a ginger beer? cos they're totally different</u>
<u n="58" who="S0012">yes</u>
<u n="59" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0152">no they're not <pause dur="short"/> canadian Dry</u>
<u n="61" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0152">is ginger ale</u>
<u n="63" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0152">a ginger beer is ginger beer that is alcoholic ginger ale isn't alcoholic oh in the end she had this bottle of ginger ale ginger beer with something in that was that was alright drank it <pause dur="short"/> felt a bit intimidated inside the bar cos there was this guy almost breathing down my neck but standing at the bar there was like there's that close and I'm thinking</u>
<u n="65" who="S0012">oh he's in his space and</u>
<u n="66" who="S0152" trans="overlap">mm you're in my space here I want you to get I want you to move away from me</u>
<u n="67" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0152">and he he was getting closer and closer and I I just thought no don't need this in the end he he went gets goes to bed gets up on the morning for breakfast goes down for breakfast great big room help yourself breakfast <pause dur="short"/> so I had you know cereal to begin with</u>
<u n="69" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0152">fried English breakfast but I had to wait for my sausages <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh cos they were not there was not enough there so they had to bring some more out there was a chef on the on the table who cooked what you wanted fresh so if you wanted <trunc>scram</trunc> if you wanted erm poached egg he'd do you a poached egg</u>
<u n="73" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0152">if you wanted fried egg do you fried egg if you wanted an omelette he'll do you an omelette and he just stood at this station cooking fresh stuff and while I was waiting for these sausages I got chatting to him and he you know the first thing in Liverpool you talk about is football that's</u>
<u n="75" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0152">the first thing I went okay then are you a red or are you a blue? oh I'm a blue he says I say oh not happy this morning then? cos there was like loads of people in Liverpool shirts <unclear/> time he says get it all the time he says we have people from Norway Finland Sweden who come down for for a game or something to watch the football they stay here they have their night out or whatever all Liverpool supporters and I went oh he says so you just you get used to it I said you had a good couple of results type thing and he says where are you from? and I says <anon type="place"/> and he said my cousin used to play for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0012">oh wow</u>
<u n="78" who="S0152">I went your cousin? he went yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0152">he says er he said it was a nice city and all the bits and pieces yeah I said it is I said he says what's he says what's the local derby there? I said well it's fifty miles it's Ipswich and I says what what really gets me I said you your two grounds are quite close to each other there's hardly any <trunc>troub</trunc> well hardly any trouble he says no he says but it's beginning to happen again like in the eighties</u>
<u n="81" who="S0012">is it? oh dear well there there's Liverpool Everton and Manchester that round that area</u>
<u n="82" who="S0152">all very close Manchester's only about twenty-four miles away</u>
<u n="83" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0152">but you've got Tranmere Rovers</u>
<u n="85" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0152">which is one part of Liverpool</u>
<u n="87" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="88" who="S0152">Stockport is another another part he says yeah I said well I said there's always been trouble between Ipswich and <anon type="place"/> supporters even though there's fifty miles difference</u>
<u n="89" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0152">I said it's a bit like in Birmingham with</u>
<u n="91" who="S0012">Aston Villa</u>
<u n="92" who="S0152" trans="overlap">Aston Aston Villa and Birmingham I said it's horrendous I said you know you wouldn't go and sit next to each other if you were a Birmingham fan and a Villa fan where at least in Liverpool they can still just about do that and they</u>
<u n="93" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0152">so anyway so then we went off for the day so that was it we had breakfast get in the hotel went off for the day and it was well what shall we do? and I said well we'll walk to the Albert Albert Docks I says and we'll go and do the <pause dur="short"/> maritime Museum and the Slave Museum all in one</u>
<u n="95" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0152">all in one and er I think we must have been in there around about four hours</u>
<u n="97" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="98" who="S0152">it was really it was <trunc>in</trunc> it was really interesting and er we had some conversations about the ships and and people didn't realise how how many people went from Liverpool and as you walk in to the Maritime Museum there's all about children hundred thousand children were moved to different countries like Canada Australia</u>
<u n="99" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0152">Barbados because the parents didn't want them any more</u>
<u n="101" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="102" who="S0013">awful <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0152">you know and the and the <trunc>gov</trunc> and the government's way of doing it was</u>
<u n="104" who="S0012">that was in the sixties wasn't it?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0152">er yeah early sixties it was just after the war as well yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0152">not that long ago in when you put it into a time frame</u>
<u n="109" who="S0012">I remember them all going from from Liverpool to Australia and and they had queues of little kids going</u>
<u n="110" who="S0152">yeah and it was like oh and that kind of made you think and some of the buildings on the on the front of Liverpool on the docks Cunard building type thing Cunard building they were one of the biggest people transporting they had children to other countries and you kind of think okay did they make their money out of that?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0152">you know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0152">you know so that was interesting and then we went through the Maritime and stuff and there was <pause dur="short"/> really good displays and then there was this display and it was about we could be who we wanted to be when we were on the on the merchant ships etcetera and it was about and it it's it did say hello sailor</u>
<u n="115" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh did it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0152">and when you read it it was about homosexuals and things</u>
<u n="117" who="S0012">oh was it? yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0152">and how they felt out at sea they could do what they wanted they wasn't under the jurisdiction of anything and could be free and they <unclear>were</unclear> prosecuted and</u>
<u n="119" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that's where you got me over a barrel come from innit</u>
<u n="120" who="S0152">yeah things like that</u>
<u n="121" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0152">and that was like and it like why have they put that up here? I said because that's what happened out at sea that that's telling you about how and they've got this special language that they used <unclear/> being with a P I can't remember poyet or something like that where certain words mean certain things</u>
<u n="123" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0152">and if you used them people knew that you were that way inclined</u>
<u n="125" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="126" who="S0152">but you were and you were safe well they shouldn't have that here pardon? did you really say that?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0152">am I you know that's part of the history of the maritime and everything that goes with it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0152">and then it was like oh and then we got into another bit of a conversation and I <trunc>th</trunc> I'm thinking are you trying to wind me up here or are you just being a Norfolk girl as I put it</u>
<u n="131" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0152">are you trying to be a Norfolk girl are you in the sense that you're gonna make comments which you know you shouldn't really be making type thing</u>
<u n="133" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0152">which are not really appropriate if you are a human being at the end of the day you may you know whatever you think so we gets up onto the slavery floor and I think that really hit home in in some respects just how these big concerns were actually making them money by trading in slavery</u>
<u n="135" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0152">for the spices and gold and stuff like that</u>
<u n="137" who="S0012" trans="overlap">the East India Company and the they did all that too didn't they?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0152">yeah places like and that was like what? I said yeah I said <pause dur="short"/> and they've got this map Belgium <pause dur="short"/> big one of the biggest slavery countries <unclear/> in slaves Netherlands Netherlands?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0012" trans="overlap">Netherlands was massive yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0152">France</u>
<u n="142" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0152">Portugal</u>
<u n="144" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0152">Great Britain</u>
<u n="146" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0152">and it was like <pause dur="short"/> yeah I said all those countries because they'd invaded other <trunc>co</trunc> other countries</u>
<u n="148" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0152">that's what they that's what they <unclear>do</unclear></u>
<u n="150" who="S0012" trans="overlap">what they did yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0152">and that was that was really</u>
<u n="152" who="S0012" trans="overlap">anything about Wilberforce cos he he</u>
<u n="153" who="S0152">yeah there was lots of things about the anti-slave people and how they came about</u>
<u n="154" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0152">and how they they had problems</u>
<u n="156" who="S0012">cos it was Wilberforce that stopped the trade the slave trade weren't it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0152">yeah but Liverpool's links with the American civil war as well</u>
<u n="158" who="S0012">I expect it is yeah yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0152"><trunc>co</trunc> because of a lot of me a lot of people from Liverpool went to America</u>
<u n="160" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0152">that way links to links to Ireland and stuff so it was really fascinating</u>
<u n="162" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0152">so we so we comes out and it was like well what we what we gonna do now? well I think we go and do the Beatles tour now</u>
<u n="164" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh gosh</u>
<u n="165" who="S0152">oh well what are we gonna do tomorrow? I says well we can do the other half of the Beatles tour and we can do this and it was like oh but I wanna go shopping</u>
<u n="166" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right</u>
<u n="167" who="S0152">and I went okay well we can go shopping I said but the shops close at six o'clock no they don't close at eight o'clock do they? I said that's a surprise really? all the shops in that part of Liverpool stay open till eight o'clock</u>
<u n="168" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0152">every night so she said I've seen this jumper that I want in Debenhams but they hadn't got my size in <anon type="place"/> but she'd got a picture of it on her phone</u>
<u n="170" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right</u>
<u n="171" who="S0152">and I went oh okay alright I said well we can do that on the way back to the hotel then no problem I said so we'll well what we'll do is we'll walk so we walked to the just round from the Slavery Museum Maritime was one of the Beatles museums</u>
<u n="172" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0152">gets there and read what it says <unclear/> fourteen pound fifty gets you in both the Beatles museums</u>
<u n="174" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="175" who="S0152">so one here and one and while half a mile further down</u>
<u n="176" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0152">the <unclear>coast</unclear> but if you have a ticket you can do the two Beatles museums and go on the ferry</u>
<u n="178" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right that's pretty good</u>
<u n="179" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so you had so you had a three you had a three thing and the ferry's an hour in length</u>
<u n="180" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0152">an hour in length and that and that was it so I said well we'll do that said oh I don't really want to do that <unclear>to</unclear> now I said <pause dur="short"/> well what are we gonna do then?</u>
<u n="182" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0152">I and it was like well let's walk to the other one <unclear>pier</unclear> head and find out what's what's there so I said okay so we walked to pier head <pause dur="short"/> and went in and looked at the price and you could buy the ticket for the two Beatles museums and the ferry on that day and it was twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="184" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="185" who="S0152">so it gave you twenty-four hours and the one ticket actually gave you forty-eight hours</u>
<u n="186" who="S0012">oh great</u>
<u n="187" who="S0152">if you use it in forty-eight hours so I said okay I said well let's as we got there there was a ferry coming in at four o'clock so I said well let's do the ferry now</u>
<u n="188" who="S0012">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0152">said let's do the ferry now so we get said so okay so we get on the lines which go on the ferry and it was like as you get on and just as they're pulling away the Ferry Across The Mersey starts to sing</u>
<u n="190" who="S0012">does it? yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0152">and that's quite nice cos that <unclear/> cos you automatically think then</u>
<u n="192" who="S0012" trans="overlap">Gerry and the Pacemakers yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0152" trans="overlap">Gerry and the Pacemakers yeah and that was really that was really nice and then it tells you a little bit of history as you're going down</u>
<u n="195" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0152">and it had three stops well yeah back to where it came from and the the biggest brick built building in the country at the standing warehouse which was part of the tobacco</u>
<u n="197" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0152">industry be great big <unclear/> and that was still there so</u>
<u n="199" who="S0012" trans="overlap">was it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0152">they must be doing stuff on there erm New Brighton how that came about on the Wirral and stuff so it was so that was really good so we get off <vocal desc="laugh"/> we get off and it was like that was really good I enjoyed that don't feel very well</u>
<u n="201" who="S0012">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0152">I said it wasn't rough <unclear>she</unclear> said <unclear/> I feel I suffer with sea sickness well you wanted to go on a canal cos wanted to go on a canal trip barge type thing</u>
<u n="203" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="204" who="S0152">I thought you no okay so we then walked back towards the hotel I said what are we doing for <trunc>foo</trunc> what are we doing to eat tonight? and again not eaten since breakfast as such apart from like a a cup of tea and a bag</u>
<u n="205" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0152">erm don't know don't know <pause dur="short"/> oh okay well we've got the choice of da da da da again all the all the restaurants round by the hotel etcetera so I said er wanna go are you getting changed? and I went well no not really I said I might just freshen up but I'm not getting changed to go back out again there's no point</u>
<u n="207" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0152">I'm I'm I don't smell I'm fine oh I don't feel like I'm going out if I don't get dressed up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0152">so we walked so we walked to Debenhams we get this top from Debenhams and I I made a comment about it it was a nice top and then er we get back to the hotel and er she said we've got to get our complimentary drinks I went I don't think we get complimentary drinks tonight yeah we get them every night</u>
<u n="211" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="213" who="S0152">no I don't think we do but okay you know you you booked it I didn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> so er get <unclear>she</unclear> comes out she's well where are we gonna go? I says I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I said we'll have a walk so I found that one restaurant which she said about about the voucher but it was closed on a Monday</u>
<u n="214" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="215" who="S0152">okay</u>
<u n="216" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0152">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> and we</u>
<u n="218" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that's typical innit?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0152">and er and it was kind I thought we were gonna go and get <trunc>s</trunc>steak that night but we didn't and then we were walking down this road couple of Chinese places turned up oh we'll go in here two for the price of one I went no it's half past seven now they finish at seven o'clock</u>
<u n="220" who="S0012">oh god</u>
<u n="221" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="222" who="S0152">and it was like oh oh okay and we were walking down and I and I knew where we were gonna we were heading towards the <unclear>Cavern</unclear> Club so I said er as we started we're walking down and I went oh we'll go in here which was like a pub pub food and I went okay I said I said to be honest I said I don't really fancy what's on the menu there <vocal desc="laugh"/> but we can go in not a problem and as I turned away there I saw the Cavern Club</u>
<u n="223" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right</u>
<u n="224" who="S0152">and I'd not had anything to eat or anything since you know so I said we'll go in there goes in gets a drink <pause dur="short"/> well I <trunc>th</trunc> I had a pint of Guinness</u>
<u n="225" who="S0012">oh yeah lovely</u>
<u n="226" who="S0152">and it was ice cold Guinness and it was and it was really really nice</u>
<u n="227" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I bet it was gorgeous it's my favourite drink</u>
<u n="228" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it just went down so nice I had another one and then we left there around about ten o'clock</u>
<u n="229" who="S0012">you had two pints?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0152">I had two pints</u>
<u n="231" who="S0012">I'd I'd have been down flat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0152">I had two pints and then I had and I ah I thought I'm hungry I'm hungry at midnight and I knew it would happen I knew full well that it would happen and I said er I'm hungry as we came I said I'm hungry I need something have something to eat said oh I don't want anything now</u>
<u n="233" who="S0012" whoConfidence="low">what? oh dear</u>
<u n="234" who="S0152">and I went well I do so I think I'm gonna get some chips <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I went and got some chips</u>
<u n="235" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0152"><unclear/> like a big portion of chips a large portion of chips and two forks I don't want any in the end</u>
<u n="237" who="S0012">she had some?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0152">she had some of the chips with me we went back to the hotel went and I said I don't want another drink</u>
<u n="239" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0152">I said I I know but we're gonna have it because it's our complimentary drink</u>
<u n="241" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0152">just because it's your complimentary drink it doesn't mean you've gotta have it you know you can not have it you know yeah but we paid for it ah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0013">she could have had yours</u>
<u n="245" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it was <unclear>like</unclear> said okay so she goes to the bar says oh can I have two bottles of in the end two bottles of water</u>
<u n="246" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="247" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0152">just so that you've got something for your complimentary drink what room are you? <anon type="address"/> okay and as we're waiting by the lift they phone through to reception <anon type="address"/> and I heard that lady just said our number just said our number room and it was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> which it's alright you've just said our number oh just checking who it was that's all the name because you signed for it and everything</u>
<u n="249" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0152">okay no problem <unclear/> up to the room didn't undo the <unclear>water</unclear> and went to bed that that was it and there was a couple in the Cavern Club before who said this isn't the this isn't the real Cavern Club the real Cavern Club is over there <pause dur="short"/> okay and there was a picture on the wall and she says and that's not real</u>
<u n="251" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0152">but that's in here and I looked at the picture <unclear/> I looked at it and I thought no that is the Cavern Club cos no matter how you try and get <trunc>s</trunc> an old fashioned picture old fashioned you can tell the people in the picture</u>
<u n="253" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0152">on how they look and the dress I know you can put dress on</u>
<u n="255" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0152">but the dress now is different to the dress then even though it's the same style and the women in those days were a lot thinner and just the way the way they held their hands</u>
<u n="257" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0152">you know when they were dancing and stuff like that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0012">well in the sixties they were <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0152" trans="overlap">you can you can tell and if it had been in there I said well okay I said if that was cos this couple had gone if that picture is now then they must have took taken all this ducting out</u>
<u n="261" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0152">cos it was all ducting across the roof for ventilation that's</u>
<u n="263" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0152">so you're telling me take this picture here they've taken all the ducting out so they can get a <trunc>re</trunc></u>
<u n="265" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0152">constitute I said no if that's an original picture just a print of an original picture and the guy says that the Cavern Club was like it was over there around about ten metres over there and what they what they've done to because the capacity wasn't large enough they excavated it</u>
<u n="267" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0152">so the it became larger</u>
<u n="269" who="S0012">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0152">underneath so it was it was still in the same place still the same doorway going down</u>
<u n="271" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0152">from what I from what I read but they've excavated it out underneath the buildings more</u>
<u n="273" who="S0012">so yeah so to accommodate more people</u>
<u n="274" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so they've they've got a rather than just being one room they've now got a like a little mini theatre where groups go and perform in there</u>
<u n="275" who="S0012">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0152">which you can go and see and stuff like that so there was kind of that was that was fine it was good you know</u>
<u n="277" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you enjoyed yourself all together then?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0013" trans="overlap">you did didn't you?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0152">so that so I I enjoyed</u>
<u n="280" who="S0012" trans="overlap">apart from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was quite contrary <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0152">ah so I was like I <trunc>enjoy</trunc> you know nice I drink and I was singing and whatever not a problem that was alright I know all the Beatles songs so</u>
<u n="282" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0152">you know if you know them I don't know this one well tough I know all the Beatles songs most of them you know</u>
<u n="284" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0152">so on the on the Tuesday we went and did the two Beatle bits</u>
<u n="286" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0152">and that was that was good and you know picked up things that I didn't know and stuff and</u>
<u n="288" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0152">no it was it was really good in the end I'm just <trunc>watch</trunc><trunc>w</trunc>watching the time cos I've <unclear>gotta meet</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="291" who="S0152">and I'll tell you more about er the Tuesday night next time cos I've gotta I've gotta pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up at twelve so</u>
<u n="292" who="S0012" trans="overlap">have you? oh oh crikey that's five to</u>
<u n="293" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0012">is that right?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> eight minutes to</u>
<u n="296" who="S0012">yeah eight minutes to</u>
<u n="297" who="S0152">it's yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0013">so where are you picking her up from?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0152"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0152">I'll get there it's not a problem it's only it's only ten to that clock's five minutes fast</u>
<u n="302" who="S0012">is it? oh right</u>
<u n="303" who="S0152">yeah so so <vocal desc="laugh"/> so that was it really and then well I'll tell you more about the the Tuesday night <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> was it good?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0152">yeah it was alright yeah I enjoyed <unclear>the</unclear> Tuesday night</u>
<u n="306" who="S0012">can you give us a trailer?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0152">a trailer a bit of a trailer yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> went out went went back to the Cavern Club</u>
<u n="308" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="309" who="S0152">but didn't leave until around about quarter past eleven</u>
<u n="310" who="S0012">oh very good time then</u>
<u n="311" who="S0152">I had a good time erm singing dancing</u>
<u n="312" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0152">dancing</u>
<u n="315" who="S0012">dancing? what you dancing? what with your gamby leg? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0152">dancing yeah I took some tablets so I was alright</u>
<u n="317" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're not supposed to have tablets with a drink</u>
<u n="318" who="S0152">I'd <unclear/> earlier in the day so it was alright</u>
<u n="319" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="320" who="S0152">so it wasn't a problem <pause dur="short"/> but er no but there was a couple of people from Belfast and they were absolutely blottoed</u>
<u n="321" who="S0012">were they?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0152">and I thought this could be this could be really</u>
<u n="323" who="S0012">yes</u>
<u n="324" who="S0152">he was loud he was like don't rate the Beatles you're in the Cavern and you don't rate the Beatles</u>
<u n="325" who="S0012">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you don't say that too loud <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> thing</u>
<u n="327" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="328" who="S0012">well he was either looking for trouble or</u>
<u n="329" who="S0152">you know and then he got into this pink then he went through all these bands he went Pink Floyd yeah Pink Floyd are good said they have some good music the only the only Beatles album that was any good was Sergeant Pepper's and I went pardon?</u>
<u n="330" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0152">said yeah then he was looking I'm sure he was either looking for an argument or something</u>
<u n="332" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0152">he weren't he weren't gonna get an argument out of me like that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0152">and then his partner she was like absolutely blottoed</u>
<u n="336" who="S0013">was she?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0152">absolutely blottoed and when we got in there he'd been doing selfies with this group of women type thing he was like giving it all the you know from Belfast kind of thing</u>
<u n="338" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0152">I don't think he could hardly this this could be embarrassing and then she sat down and then I like I was I was sitting on a bench here if one was behind me she was sitting like here and I my feet were facing out that way she was <trunc>sit</trunc>sitting here with her back to me he was sitting there and every so often she would fall on my leg at the back</u>
<u n="340" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="341" who="S0152">oh she'd be like way and I'm thinking oh god here we go so I just kept still as I could he went off to the toilet comes back and she and he goes I want another drink so she goes to the bar and buys four shots of whatever it was I have no idea what it was</u>
<u n="342" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0152">four shots <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking oh okay that looks a bit obvious it's <unclear/> he gets up I then want one of those in his Belfast <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0012">accent</u>
<u n="345" who="S0152">something ah and er he goes back to the bar and she turns to say I was only trying to be loving and do something really nice I think</u>
<u n="346" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0152">I'm thinking yeah yeah yeah you have it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0012">so he gave it to you? and she</u>
<u n="349" who="S0152">I'm like no it's alright no I'm okay I don't I don't want it and she'd knocked one back I says no I'm I'm not really into those not really <trunc>in</trunc> well if it was Sambuca then I might have had it but I had had no idea what was in it</u>
<u n="350" who="S0012">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0152">you have it no I don't want it you have it no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't want it well sip it then try it no <unclear/> one's going try it and I'm going <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't wanna try it</u>
<u n="352" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0152">have it ah so I had a little sip it was alright it wasn't it was a bit like cough stuff it was alright don't be a wuss don't be a wuss just knock it back</u>
<u n="354" who="S0012" trans="overlap">knock it back <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god there's people that get everywhere</u>
<u n="355" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and it's like oh come on do you do I really need to knock this back? no I don't I do want to sip it cos it is quite nice but I'm not gonna take that type thing and it's like and I got this impression like well you can't knock it back can you?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0152">and I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like you can't knock it back can you?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="359" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and I thought oh we're not gonna play this game I will knock it back and there's not not a problem so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> and he comes back from the bar with his drink and whatever and she drinks the other one and he drinks the other one and that is it and then she's really going <trunc>wa</trunc></u>
<u n="360" who="S0013">oh no</u>
<u n="361" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="362" who="S0152">and then this girl comes in with a fella must have been round about twenty-eight twenty-nine really happy going to each of the tables getting people up to dance</u>
<u n="363" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0152">just pulling come on come and dance you know type thing and I thought please don't come onto this table please don't please you know don't come to this table</u>
<u n="365" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0152">please don't come</u>
<u n="367" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0152">well she comes to the table and <unclear/> hitting the <unclear/> cos I'm sitting like this at the table like this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> behind me so you got got this Irish couple up and they were dancing she pulls me up <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah very nice of you yeah yeah it's nice yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I'm dancing and her partner then said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you come and get up I'm not dancing I'm not dancing and I'm thinking to myself but you like dancing you go to dance classes you go to dance classes why aren't you gonna dance? opportunity other people are dancing why aren't you gonna dance? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0152">so there I am dancing and she's still sitting down and I'm thinking well this is going down doing well somehow</u>
<u n="371" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0152">and it's <unclear/> well and then in the end she gets up in to dance and then we go round like round handbag type thing dancing as I call it</u>
<u n="373" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0152">and then it was like mm mm mm mm and then she says and this she leaves she says she she was <unclear/> she'd had a little bit to drink as well <unclear/> she said ladies she says you ain't gonna keep these men if you don't get your boobies out</u>
<u n="375" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0013">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="377" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> she saying</u>
<u n="378" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="379" who="S0152">like this the girl's like she's going</u>
<u n="380" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="382" who="S0152">I was just going oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0152">I just go oh okay yep</u>
<u n="386" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="387" who="S0152">and I'm like and I just thought mm only one <unclear/> with <pause dur="short"/> it's funny how you men get up and dance with younger women isn't it?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="389" who="S0152">and I went I was dragged up I wasn't gonna get up I'd fought I said but didn't see you getting up to dance and you like dancing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0152">she's like oh okay and that was it really</u>
<u n="392" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0152">so that was so that was alright</u>
<u n="394" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0152">but this this couple from Belfast were like oh my god</u>
<u n="396" who="S0012">oh dear</u>
<u n="397" who="S0152"><unclear/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I think there's fights every night in Liverpool somewhere around aren't they?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0152">security so really high round there</u>
<u n="401" who="S0012">is it?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0152">yeah it's all to be honest there wasn't that much trouble</u>
<u n="403" who="S0012">no?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0152">to be honest but the beer the drink is so cheap</u>
<u n="405" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0152">this one this one bar as we're walking out from the Cavern this is at eleven o'clock you could have two shots two Budweiser fiver</u>
<u n="407" who="S0012">what? <pause dur="short"/> well I see <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's good innit</u>
<u n="408" who="S0152">two bottles of Bud</u>
<u n="409" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0152">two shots a fiver</u>
<u n="411" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="413" who="S0152">now whether that's a fiver to get you in and then when you're in</u>
<u n="414" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0152">you know</u>
<u n="418" who="S0012">cos once you've had a few drinks like that to</u>
<u n="419" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0012">two and then two and then two shots you start getting a bit dehydrated and you need some more drink and that's how it go on</u>
<u n="421" who="S0013">mm that's why the the happy hours are <unclear/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well yeah that's why they have I dunno if they still have happy hours do they?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0152">yeah they still yeah so and we so that was it and but prior to that we'd gone prior to that we'd gone in the hotel gone for our complimentary drinks</u>
<u n="424" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="425" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0152">and the girl behind the thing says <vocal desc="laugh"/> I shouldn't have served you last night really because you only get one complimentary drink on the night you arrive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="428" who="S0012">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0152">and I thought and I thought to myself well that's what I thought but I weren't gonna say anything cos I'd been accused of you know or so</u>
<u n="430" who="S0012">yeah oh well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0152">oh and what do you <trunc>wa</trunc> what do you wanna do? we'll do this oh why do we have to do everything <trunc>y</trunc>? so it was a case of</u>
<u n="432" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0152">what are you gonna do? what do you wanna do? I'll do what you want so</u>
<u n="434" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0152">that was it really but er I'd go back to Liverpool it <trunc>w</trunc>it was good <trunc>tr</trunc> a good couple of days</u>
<u n="436" who="S0012">was it?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0152">and I'd spend more <trunc>t</trunc> I'd wanna spend more time in the places</u>
<u n="439" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0012">cos there's a lot of interesting things <unclear>ain't there</unclear></u>
<u n="442" who="S0152" trans="overlap">lots of interesting things</u>
<u n="443" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0152">not just skim it and not</u>
<u n="445" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0152">get the time there's Liverpool Museum would've been good to go into a trip up to the Anglican Cathedral</u>
<u n="447" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0152">big one</u>
<u n="449" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0152">that would've been good</u>
<u n="451" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it's a lovely big one yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0152">and <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="453" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0152">and even the Catholic one which is a strange shape with the wigwam things <unclear>on the side of</unclear></u>
<u n="455" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="456" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0152">that would've been good</u>
<u n="458" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0152"><trunc>b</trunc>but no so and it's knowing knowing how easy it is to get about</u>
<u n="461" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0152">although</u>
<u n="463" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0152">some places like <anon type="place"/> is twelve twelve minutes away by car</u>
<u n="465" who="S0012" trans="overlap">is it? yeah by car oh right</u>
<u n="466" who="S0152">China cos China they've got the biggest China Town outside China in Liverpool</u>
<u n="467" who="S0012" trans="overlap">have they? oh right sound good</u>
<u n="468" who="S0152">because China was</u>
<u n="469" who="S0012">yeah that's where they come in weren't it?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><trunc>b</trunc>big big <trunc>f</trunc> big influx of Chinese people there</u>
<u n="472" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0152">so but that was too far out and on the <trunc>Tue</trunc> I think it was the <trunc>Tue</trunc> I think it was the Monday night just picked up a brochure of things to do cos she wanted to wanted to go and do something</u>
<u n="475" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0152">and I'd looked at the one I says well that that's five thirty start we're too late for that one I said and the other one that is on on tonight I said is the other side of Liverpool because I <trunc>che</trunc>checked it out cos they've got 4G</u>
<u n="477" who="S0012">yeah well</u>
<u n="478" who="S0152">er <trunc>f</trunc> so it was just like having internet on your phone instant 4G</u>
<u n="479" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="480" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0152">er you <trunc>cou</trunc> I I put put my map on I put my map on and away I went</u>
<u n="482" who="S0012">brilliant</u>
<u n="483" who="S0152">and I could phone <pause dur="short"/> I don't have to go yet</u>
<u n="484" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0152">so I can <unclear>take</unclear> more</u>
<u n="486" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't wanna be met until one fifteen</u>
<u n="488" who="S0012">don't she?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0152">no no I think it's just <trunc>t</trunc>taking a little bit longer than she would've done it so yeah so erm <pause dur="short"/> so we just <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I I just got to the point where if I was gonna do something I was gonna do it</u>
<u n="490" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0152">you know?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0152">we'd gone into this we'd gone into this patisserie place and it was on the afternoon and I didn't mean anything by it but <pause dur="short"/> we walked in and there was tables and there was really low chairs</u>
<u n="495" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0152">so when you're sat at so when you're sat in the chair your head</u>
<u n="497" who="S0012">was level with the table?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0152" trans="overlap">was almost level with the table</u>
<u n="499" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="500" who="S0152">and I thought I don't really wanna</u>
<u n="501" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0152">sit here er and it was like shall we er shall we sit here? yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> oh I suppose you wanted to sit over there no I'm quite happy sitting here <vocal desc="laugh"/> so like this like</u>
<u n="503" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0152">so ordered the ordered the cakes and whatever and it was like and er this tart came</u>
<u n="505" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0012">was she nice? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0152">she <unclear/> it was only it was only round about that size and I'd have picked it up I wouldn't have bothered cutting it I'd have just picked it up</u>
<u n="508" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0152">you know it's like a tart and joke I said oh I said don't worry about <trunc>c</trunc> you don't have to be posh just pick it up and eat it like you would do at home type thing I'm fed up of people telling me what to do and whatever erm I haven't told you what to do</u>
<u n="510" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0152">I've just like <vocal desc="misc"/> tut</u>
<u n="512" who="S0012">oh dear</u>
<u n="513" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="514" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="516" who="S0152">and it was like you know <pause dur="short"/> just just <unclear>get on with it</unclear></u>
<u n="517" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0152">just <unclear>get on</unclear></u>
<u n="519" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0152">and er and it I felt that <trunc>s</trunc>sometimes it was shall we try and make er try and cause an argument about something?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0012">yeah that's weird ain't it yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0152">mm no well I'm not gonna argue about it</u>
<u n="523" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="524" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="525" who="S0152">you don't say much</u>
<u n="526" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="527" who="S0152">well I'll say what I have to say erm but I don't say <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't say much</u>
<u n="528" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="529" who="S0152">you know?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0012">so do you think that'll last?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0152">don't know don't know I <trunc>d</trunc> I you know had a nice had a nice time erm doesn't give <trunc>d</trunc>doesn't give much away but I suppose I'm not giving much away so</u>
<u n="532" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="533" who="S0152">you know I've not said anything about</u>
<u n="534" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0152">what's going on about the house or anything like that</u>
<u n="536" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="537" who="S0152">erm I'd I'd thought that she would probably would be staying last night but as soon as I got back here it was she went</u>
<u n="538" who="S0012">did she?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0152">and it was like oh okay I've got some I've got some things to do well you're on holiday for the week</u>
<u n="540" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0152">type thing and it was well what you well what are you doing? what are you doing tomorrow? meaning today erm I'm going round to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at half past nine okay well she must have arranged it</u>
<u n="542" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0152">she says I'm staying there for my tea and everything having a day with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="545" who="S0152">alright okay</u>
<u n="546" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0152">that's that's alright and then erm Friday I thought she was going to the beer festival <anon type="place"/> beer festival and she'd said about the beer festival and hadn't said anything so I hadn't I hadn't assumed anything or anything and then she says er have you got to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up on Friday from erm work? and I went well I'm picking her up tonight cos she worked yesterday I said I'm not too certain whether she's working on Friday so if she is working on Friday then yeah I'll have to I'll have to pick her up from from work oh she says that means you won't be able to have a drink then I <unclear>want</unclear> a drink? she said yeah the beer festival I said well what time are you going to the beer festival then? she says I might go in the afternoon and then go and have something to eat afterwards and I went well I said to be honest I said I'm not really too fussed about going to the beer festival I says you know I er you hadn't said anything about it about</u>
<u n="548" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="549" who="S0152">going or whatever I said you you'd mentioned it back in in September time when somebody had asked you whether you <trunc>w</trunc>wanted to go and you said about getting tickets I says but you hadn't said anything</u>
<u n="550" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="551" who="S0152">about er</u>
<u n="552" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0152">going I said and to be honest you know <vocal desc="sigh"/> how do I how do I get home? because a taxi from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> is round about twenty-five pound</u>
<u n="554" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0012">that is that is yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0152">you know sorry but I'm not paying twenty-five pound because I've had three halves of beer to get I'm I'm not doing that</u>
<u n="557" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="558" who="S0152">I'll I'll go without</u>
<u n="559" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0152">I'll go without I said and if you I said and if you wanna go then you can go I says and if you if you wanna come come to mine afterwards I'll come and pick you up <pause dur="short"/> I'll come and pick you up from <anon type="place"/> type thing</u>
<u n="561" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0152">and then I'll drop you off on Saturday morning back at back at yours when I take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> riding on</u>
<u n="563" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0152">Saturday morning I haven't said anything about erm <pause dur="short"/> saturday evening the <trunc>bon</trunc> the fireworks over at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="565" who="S0012">oh no</u>
<u n="566" who="S0152">because she has she hasn't said anything about Saturday and the last number of Saturdays she's she's done something on a Saturday</u>
<u n="567" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0152">it's like Fridays is I'll come to you but Saturdays I'm gonna be at home type thing so I'm not you know and if she says anything about the Saturday well I'll turn around and say well you didn't say anything the Friday or the</u>
<u n="570" who="S0012">well that's true you know</u>
<u n="571" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah don't know what don't know what you're doing so</u>
<u n="572" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0152">you know and</u>
<u n="575" who="S0012">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a bit more er civil lately? or is she</u>
<u n="576" who="S0152">well I had a little chat with her when I picked her up last night</u>
<u n="577" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0152">I had a little chat</u>
<u n="579" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you said you were going to</u>
<u n="580" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I had a little chat with her last night when I and and said to her I'm a little bit worried about you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I says because you're having a go at people for for no reason you you're upsetting people you're having a go at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said no you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can says things I says but you get upset with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> quite quickly you you're not thinking straight I says I'm just a little bit <trunc>conc</trunc> I'm concerned about you I'm worried about you I said I know that you're not enjoying the sixth form as such</u>
<u n="581" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0152">because of erm the work load and it is totally different I says but you're doing really well I said and as long as you continue to to try your hardest I don't have a I don't have problem with it I says but I don't like you not being happy er I said and some of the things that you say or I see you say does concern me I said it does concern me I said so you know I really would like to get to the bottom of it you know</u>
<u n="583" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0152">I want you know I want you to be I said you know we all grow up we all have we all have problems and everybody's problems are different I says but you know if there was a <trunc>pro</trunc> if you had something wrong you need to talk to me about it</u>
<u n="585" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0152">and she says well I'm alright I said no you need to talk to me about it and er I said you know we've gotta do certain things I said but you know everything will everything will be alright everything will be alright and er she got back to a t-shirt I got her a t-shirt for the Beatles</u>
<u n="587" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="588" who="S0152">er she'd gotten one Beatles t-shirt which she loves that she'd got got this one and it'd got like a pop art image of the Beatles</u>
<u n="589" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0152" trans="overlap">then I got her some badges as well and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says well what you giving what you giving <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I said I'm not getting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> anything</u>
<u n="591" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0152">and she said well why not? I said because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has her her riding</u>
<u n="593" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't get that much I try and balance it the best that I can but there's nothing here for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="596" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0152">that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would want you know I could go into H and M and buy her something from there or I could just give her some money and she can go and pick it herself</u>
<u n="598" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0152">these Beatles t-shirts and Beatles badges</u>
<u n="600" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0152">will mean more to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because it is from where the Beatles come from</u>
<u n="603" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0152">and I've I've got got it from Liverpool type thing</u>
<u n="605" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0152">and she was <unclear/> she's got it on today she's wearing it today</u>
<u n="608" who="S0012">she's wearing it?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0152" trans="overlap">she's <unclear/> top <unclear/> she's <unclear/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0012">ah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0013">lovely</u>
<u n="612" who="S0152">I think he jobs her job is alright now as well</u>
<u n="613" who="S0012">she has <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0152">she's getting a bit happy with her job as well</u>
<u n="615" who="S0013">it does take time doesn't it getting into these things</u>
<u n="616" who="S0012">I mean when you <trunc>wer</trunc></u>
<u n="617" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0012">when you have to go for a <trunc>wo</trunc> to work from school or whatever or</u>
<u n="619" who="S0152">if you're not</u>
<u n="620" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it's a bit difficult</u>
<u n="621" who="S0152">if you're not used to doing it</u>
<u n="622" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0152">then it is difficult you know I was I suppose I was lucky just like yourselves in some respects that my parents had a shop and I was <trunc>ins</trunc> expected to work or help out in the shop</u>
<u n="624" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah that's true yeah yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0152">stack the shelves and stuff like that from a from a very early age</u>
<u n="626" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0152">you know and then when <pause dur="short"/> dad died and then mum just had the shop by herself I used to have to go to the cash and carry with somebody because mum couldn't drive to pick the stuff off the shelves and whatever</u>
<u n="628" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0152">so that independence that helped me to get things get things right as always as always <unclear/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah it's weird innit? yeah we we've all been brought up with parents self employed and working</u>
<u n="631" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0012">and helping them out haven't we?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0152">yeah you know and <trunc>it</trunc>it's what you it's what you do and I I I got into another another conversation that we started to have was about youngsters today why do youngsters today need to go to university?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0012">oh that's a bit weird</u>
<u n="635" who="S0152">why why do youngsters today need to go to university? when they don't do the jobs with the degrees that they come out with because it shows people shows employers that they can work</u>
<u n="636" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well that's true yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0152">to a higher level than other people</u>
<u n="638" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0013">we actually talked to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about this</u>
<u n="640" who="S0012">yes we did didn't we?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0013">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0012">we had a</u>
<u n="643" who="S0013">cos she was saying she wasn't very keen on it and I said most of the people we know they don't actually do what well ours were a good example</u>
<u n="644" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0013">I mean photography and selling wine and</u>
<u n="646" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0013">what's the erm but even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s I mean she did psychology and</u>
<u n="648" who="S0012">and now she's working with children</u>
<u n="649" who="S0013">and now she's doing English</u>
<u n="650" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah they kind of they kind of</u>
<u n="651" who="S0013">they don't have to</u>
<u n="652" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="653" who="S0012">it's just training <unclear>them</unclear> as well isn't it?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0013" trans="overlap">but it it's erm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0012">you know I mean you get really good er trains of thought different trains of thought when you go to university cos you get taught in a different way</u>
<u n="656" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0012">and that's what's really interesting</u>
<u n="658" who="S0152">she you know and it was like well they should be out at work doing work on the job and I said well look I said there isn't much difference between I said there's your we went to school at the same time I said but the school that I went to when you're in the sixth-form it's a comprehensive school they they try to push you to <trunc>univ</trunc> not push you they encourage you to go to university</u>
<u n="659" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0152">and at that point in time there was grants available</u>
<u n="661" who="S0012" trans="overlap">there was</u>
<u n="662" who="S0152">for you to have so you know you got your grant for this and it and it was a lot easier so that's no different to you <pause dur="short"/> she says well I'm I'm old school I went no I said if I think about my my sister my sister is almost the same age as your parents there's like six years difference between them</u>
<u n="663" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0152">I said my sister's children didn't go to university because my sister didn't see the importance of it</u>
<u n="665" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0152">and my and my nephew and my niece didn't wanna do that and they were too much how wanna do this one that they wanted to get out they wanted to leave home as quickly as possible I said you from what you've said your dad right I've kept you for so long now you're to now you're going out to work to earn your keep I said I'm not being funny I said but back to being Norfolk mentality for certain females</u>
<u n="667" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0152">I said was I leave school I get a job I find a a guy I get married I have children I stay at home</u>
<u n="669" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0152">and that was a big thing for a lot of Norfolk girls</u>
<u n="671" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah well</u>
<u n="672" who="S0152">it still is for a lot of Norfolk girls</u>
<u n="673" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0012">but it is for the for the countryside in general you get you get like in er Lincolnshire I mean that's really sort of self inbreeding if you like you know that type of thing went on and went on in Norfolk went on in the the real countryside whereas you didn't get that sort of thing in <trunc>pla</trunc> in big cities I mean you didn't get it in <anon type="place"/> I mean <anon type="place"/> was an alien alien place to us</u>
<u n="676" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0012">it was I mean huh come from <anon type="place"/> stupid lot you know that was alien and you get that type of er <pause dur="short"/> sort of er well dislike between the the countryside and the city people you do</u>
<u n="678" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah you know I said it's about expectations you know as a as a parent I want the best for my children</u>
<u n="679" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0152">because my parents no matter what they did they did the best for they did the best for me</u>
<u n="682" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0152">and they they encouraged me to do what I wanted to do</u>
<u n="684" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0152">my you know I said you were fortunate you had a mum and dad you still have a mum and dad</u>
<u n="686" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0152">I don't</u>
<u n="688" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="689" who="S0152">but my mum went to work so that I could stay on in the sixth-form because well people who stay on in the sixth-form do <unclear>one</unclear> cos they don't wanna work</u>
<u n="690" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0152"><trunc>n</trunc><trunc>n</trunc>no I work</u>
<u n="692" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0152">I worked from a very early age part-time to earn money so I could do things</u>
<u n="694" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="695" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0152">I said and then <unclear/> well you went to university no I went to university after I'd been working for seven years</u>
<u n="697" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0152">because I did day I did on the job training</u>
<u n="699" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0152">for the job that I did and then I took two years out to do my degree course and then in that time I did my other qualifications that I needed to do I said but my parents didn't hold me back and turn round and say <trunc>you</trunc>you've not gotta go out to work because we've kept you for X amount of years</u>
<u n="701" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear>I</unclear> know no</u>
<u n="702" who="S0152">because parents don't you know caring parents and parents who want the best for you don't do that</u>
<u n="703" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="704" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="705" who="S0152">I said and to turn round and say that you <trunc>sh</trunc> they shouldn't do this and I you know and I tried to explain about you do your GCSEs it opened a door so you can do your A levels it shows</u>
<u n="706" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="707" who="S0152">an employer that you can work to a certain level</u>
<u n="708" who="S0012">yeah it does yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0152">you do your A levels it shows an employer you can work to that level</u>
<u n="710" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0152">you do your degree course it shows the employer that you can do so at the end of most degree courses there are big companies out there who've come along and I've forgotten what they call them but they have they like have a workshop or something like that</u>
<u n="712" who="S0012">they do yeah yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0152">where you go and they're touting for people to come and work for them</u>
<u n="714" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0152">er it has a name and at the and at the end you go and <trunc>it</trunc>it's like being headhunted they look at your degree and they look at you and you get a bit of and they come and invite you</u>
<u n="716" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0152">and it's well it cost X amount and I says well nothing is free</u>
<u n="718" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well it isn't any more is it? I mean you used to get er education almost free from the university you went to university</u>
<u n="719" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm that was</u>
<u n="720" who="S0152">it was</u>
<u n="721" who="S0012">even got fed do you?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0013">yes we did</u>
<u n="723" who="S0152">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0152">you know when when I think about when I did my <trunc>deg</trunc>degree I got two grants I got my grant</u>
<u n="726" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0152">for going to university</u>
<u n="728" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0152">which paid my my fees and all <unclear/> the bits and pieces that that go with it and I got a bursary</u>
<u n="730" who="S0012">that's yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0152">and my bursary was because of shortage of teachers in that subject</u>
<u n="732" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0152">and they gave me an extra bursary</u>
<u n="734" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="736" who="S0152">oh I don't know fifteen hundred pound or</u>
<u n="737" who="S0012">something yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0152">something like that a year and at that point in time fifteen hundred pound was was a lot in the way that</u>
<u n="739" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well of course it was yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0152">and the way that I balanced it</u>
<u n="741" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0152">and I got a tool allowance as well I got a tool allowance each year</u>
<u n="743" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0152">well I didn't need my tool allowance</u>
<u n="745" who="S0012">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0152">because I'd got the majority of the tools I just needed to top it up and used my tool allowance to buy electronic components or things like that that I might need to do something else or to buy wood that I will that they didn't have in the store</u>
<u n="747" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0152">to make</u>
<u n="749" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="750" who="S0152">but I had you know you know and I'm you know if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanna go you know go go off to university I'm not gonna say you can't</u>
<u n="751" who="S0012">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0152">you know they have to <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="753" who="S0013" trans="overlap">what I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know it's an experience isn't it</u>
<u n="754" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0013">that is it really worth</u>
<u n="756" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yes also an experience</u>
<u n="757" who="S0013">worth doing isn't it? even I mean it I <trunc>sup</trunc> you can carry on with your do your horse riding afterwards you know <unclear/> to got that background you've got more of a chance for everything haven't you?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0012">I think they used to have</u>
<u n="759" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yours must be difficult to do after a break cos it's much easier to go to sixth-form <unclear>than work</unclear></u>
<u n="760" who="S0152">yeah it was having day release cos I did day release</u>
<u n="761" who="S0013">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="762" who="S0152">to do my HND</u>
<u n="763" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="764" who="S0152">so I did a HN so I did I did an ONC a HND</u>
<u n="765" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="766" who="S0152">and then because I'd got the higher national diploma you could convert it to a degree at the college that I went to but that qualification also got you into being able to do your degree course and the experience of working in the school</u>
<u n="767" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="769" who="S0152">but it was hard</u>
<u n="770" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="771" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0152">it was hard</u>
<u n="773" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0152">you know the easy bit was the teaching bit that was the easy that was the easy bit</u>
<u n="775" who="S0013">mm mm</u>
<u n="776" who="S0152">the hard bit was actually sitting down each week and writing a thousand word essay each week cos the course that I was on that's what you had to do</u>
<u n="777" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="778" who="S0152">a thousand word essay and some were fifteen hundred some were two thousand depending on whether it's an A B or C unit</u>
<u n="779" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="780" who="S0152">and you had to do forty-five A units which was basically one a week</u>
<u n="781" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0152">and you had to do thirty B units</u>
<u n="783" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0152">and then you had to do fifteen C units</u>
<u n="785" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0152">and you could do them in any order that you wanted</u>
<u n="787" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="789" who="S0152">as well as your semester work which was like this semester you do graphic design and you do electronics and you do</u>
<u n="790" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="791" who="S0152">resistant materials so that was one element and then there was another element where you did computing and stuff and you had you had three semesters each year one semester was your teaching practice</u>
<u n="792" who="S0012">well yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0152">plus each year you had a teaching practice and and it wasn't like your six weeks it was a fourteen week teaching practice</u>
<u n="794" who="S0012">so you the student going out who <vocal desc="laugh"/> we used to really have good fun with students when they came to <unclear/> the student teacher</u>
<u n="795" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0012">some of them were brilliant</u>
<u n="797" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0012">and some of them we</u>
<u n="799" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0152">now I was fortunate I suppose cos I was that little bit older type thing I I didn't know that much of an issue but I was but yeah but that's what that's what I did</u>
<u n="802" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0152">and then you know you move a you move about a bit</u>
<u n="804" who="S0012">you do yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0152">but the experiences that you gain by doing things</u>
<u n="807" who="S0012">well this is what it's all about an experience</u>
<u n="808" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0012">total experience all the way through</u>
<u n="810" who="S0013">I don't think I could have gone out to work anyway as I was too young in my head and I'm I wouldn't have wanted just to go to to work and I wouldn't have done <unclear/> I don't think</u>
<u n="811" who="S0152" trans="overlap">well I just find it I just find it but that</u>
<u n="812" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I needed that education extra</u>
<u n="813" who="S0152">but I you know but</u>
<u n="814" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0152">but my parents were always wanting you know wanting to do something for me if you know I went to private school</u>
<u n="816" who="S0013" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0152">I don't know whether you knew that but I went to private school</u>
<u n="818" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0152">yeah really</u>
<u n="820" who="S0012">huh</u>
<u n="821" who="S0152">now to begin with I went I went to I went to <anon type="place"/> school <pause dur="short"/> and I hated it</u>
<u n="822" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0152">I really hated it with a <trunc>p</trunc> didn't like it at all and then there was three people in my road and they were were no different</u>
<u n="824" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="825" who="S0152">one one one person had a corner shop</u>
<u n="826" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0152">another parent worked for the Co-op Bakery and then there was there was <pause dur="short"/> and there was another girl <unclear/> the one opposite <pause dur="short"/> she went and then there was me and we and I moved there and went to this went to this private school in <anon type="place"/> and they were all there and in the end it was quite interesting just like my dad used to take us of a morning because he came from work and he took the two girls <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad mum and dad owned a shop so we were in competition with them</u>
<u n="828" who="S0012">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0152">but my dad took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="830" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0152">to <trunc>sch</trunc> to school so he took four of us to school of a morning</u>
<u n="832" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0152">and then their parents would pick us up</u>
<u n="834" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="835" who="S0152">of an evening so dad took us of a morning and my and their parents took it in turn to bring us home</u>
<u n="836" who="S0012">oh that was nice of them</u>
<u n="837" who="S0152">so it it was quite nice</u>
<u n="838" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0152">and I went there until I was ten</u>
<u n="840" who="S0012">did you? oh well</u>
<u n="841" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="842" who="S0152">so from the so from the age of <trunc>s</trunc> I think I was there for five years and then once on my holidays we got this note saying <pause dur="short"/> the head teacher had run off with all the money</u>
<u n="843" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0013">oh no oh dear</u>
<u n="845" who="S0152">and therefore the school wouldn't be opening again in the <trunc>Sept</trunc> in the September</u>
<u n="846" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="847" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh <unclear>crikey</unclear></u>
<u n="848" who="S0152">and in the September we all had to find</u>
<u n="849" who="S0012">a school</u>
<u n="850" who="S0152">another schools to go to and</u>
<u n="851" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="852" who="S0152">my mum couldn't get me in to the school that I should have gone to</u>
<u n="853" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="854" who="S0152">and I remember there being a big argument</u>
<u n="855" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="856" who="S0152">a real big argument <pause dur="short"/> and my mum did say a few things which would be classed as racist now</u>
<u n="857" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0152">and and it's interesting because the school they wanted to send me where there was spaces was actually part of the Trojan horse thing that happened in Birmingham a couple of</u>
<u n="859" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="860" who="S0152">twelve months ago</u>
<u n="861" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0152">so you know we're talking we're talking seventy-two here</u>
<u n="863" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0152">and my mum says he's not going there and in the end I used to have to catch a bus which was like an eight mile trip to the school that I went to</u>
<u n="865" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="866" who="S0152">and where I'd been taken to school every morning all of a sudden on a Monday morning I'm catching a bus to take me to this school to this school</u>
<u n="867" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="868" who="S0012">well yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0152">and went that way and then that was just a normal primary school then bit like</u>
<u n="870" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0152"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0152">and I <trunc>re</trunc> went then going there I've met up with students who I used I'd to</u>
<u n="874" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0152">to go to school at this private school</u>
<u n="876" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="877" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="878" who="S0013">huh</u>
<u n="879" who="S0012">huh</u>
<u n="880" who="S0152">and then it was like and then I went to a normal comprehensive school <pause dur="short"/> but my parents always felt that education was important</u>
<u n="881" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="883" who="S0152"><trunc>want</trunc>wanting wanting</u>
<u n="884" who="S0013" trans="overlap">they were right <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="885" who="S0152">wanting the best</u>
<u n="886" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0012">I never looked for I didn't even know to be honest with you</u>
<u n="888" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0012">that there was further education when I left school</u>
<u n="890" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="891" who="S0152">it was all apprenticeships though wasn't it?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0012">they were apprenticeships yeah and that what I did I didn't know I had engineering apprenticeships of that's what and there's not apprenticeships or they're starting off again</u>
<u n="893" who="S0152" trans="overlap">they're starting again but they're this was again this was a <trunc>th</trunc>there are apprenticeships out there but they way they were working was you had to find a company who would take you</u>
<u n="894" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="895" who="S0152">on an apprenticeship and then you got your course attached to you</u>
<u n="896" who="S0012">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0152">to be it's not like you're going let's you know like my dad and and you where you go to the company cos my dad worked for the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0152">and and passes and <unclear/> was the was the other company</u>
<u n="900" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="901" who="S0152">they're all the same company but the <anon type="place"/> was the company and the <anon type="place"/> was like Scott's Scott and Holland's</u>
<u n="902" who="S0012"><unclear/> to Scott</u>
<u n="903" who="S0152"><unclear/> to Scott's</u>
<u n="904" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0152">where they make generators and things like that</u>
<u n="906" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="907" who="S0152">so he did his apprenticeship</u>
<u n="908" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0152">for them <pause dur="short"/> but it's a mega big company</u>
<u n="910" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0152">a mega big company</u>
<u n="912" who="S0012">well <unclear/> was the biggest company in in <anon type="place"/> er er engineering company Lauren Scott's and Electro <unclear/> is what it was called</u>
<u n="913" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="914" who="S0012">and that was a massive massive company</u>
<u n="915" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0012">I mean during the war they tried to bomb it because they were they were doing erm ammunition at the time then and women were were working there</u>
<u n="917" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0012">yeah that's a massive company I don't know what happened to it?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0152">it's it's I think it's got</u>
<u n="920" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I suppose that was taken over by some some some</u>
<u n="921" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I took I had a visit there a few years ago school visit there a few years ago</u>
<u n="922" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0152">I'm not too certain what it's doing now I think it is actually closed</u>
<u n="924" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="925" who="S0152">but I <trunc>re</trunc> I remember going to the <anon type="place"/> now in that area of Birmingham you had the <anon type="place"/> which was round about five miles from Fort Dunlop</u>
<u n="926" who="S0012">yeah? oh right</u>
<u n="927" who="S0152">which was which Fort Dunlop was next door to where the Jaguar plant is now which is at Castle Bromwich and Castle Bromwich was where they built the spitfires</u>
<u n="928" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0152">so during the war and I wish I'd asked more questions but dad never went to war dad dad never was in the army</u>
<u n="930" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="931" who="S0152">because he was needed</u>
<u n="932" who="S0012">yeah well there was a lot of people like that yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0152">he was needed in the factories to be actually making the stuff</u>
<u n="934" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="935" who="S0152">for</u>
<u n="936" who="S0012">well somebody had to make it all didn't they?</u>
<u n="937" who="S0152">you know because he'd done his because certain engineers didn't go</u>
<u n="938" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="939" who="S0152">and he never he would he would never say what he did</u>
<u n="940" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="941" who="S0152">during the war he just said I made stuff he would never say what he made</u>
<u n="942" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="943" who="S0152">now I and that was something that those those people had they <trunc>s</trunc> I think that they signed agreements to say they wouldn't talk about</u>
<u n="944" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0152">what they did</u>
<u n="946" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="947" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0152">you know and he was he was a he was a tool maker</u>
<u n="949" who="S0012">yeah we'll that's a very important job a really important job that one is er we had two tunnel makers I was a tunnel maker at one time but er <pause dur="short"/> they were the people that made the tools that that did the job for the they had to make the tools design the tools and do everything</u>
<u n="950" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's what he was and then when the automation came in he was his job title was an <trunc>auto</trunc><trunc>automate</trunc><trunc>automat</trunc>automatic tool maker</u>
<u n="951" who="S0012">oh oh <unclear>I</unclear> was that <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0152">that's that's what he did</u>
<u n="953" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="954" who="S0152">yeah and you kind of think okay so you know he must have been er no I was twelve when he died</u>
<u n="955" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well very important</u>
<u n="956" who="S0152">wouldn't never really had watched talk about it because when did I when did I see him? I saw him when he came home from work on the morning as he was taking us to school</u>
<u n="957" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="958" who="S0152">I didn't see him of a night time because at six o'clock he got up had his tea and then left to go to work cos he worked nights for forty-five years</u>
<u n="959" who="S0012">oh yeah</u>
<u n="960" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0152">and he he didn't work on a Friday Saturday Sunday but he worked Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday</u>
<u n="962" who="S0012">nights yeah</u>
<u n="963" who="S0152">nights <pause dur="short"/> I was always with him when during the day before he went to bed cos he'd go to the cash and carry so I always went everywhere with him</u>
<u n="964" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0152">driving about but at at that age you don't really talk about</u>
<u n="966" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="967" who="S0152">what you do at work or anything it's because you're taking you're taking yourself here and you're taking yourself there and you do it</u>
<u n="968" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0152">holidays we went on holiday you're on holiday aren't you you don't talk about</u>
<u n="970" who="S0012">that's that was we er vote er England or Britain then cos the holidays were the first two weeks in August</u>
<u n="971" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="972" who="S0012">for everybody</u>
<u n="973" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0012">every single place in in well in <anon type="place"/> at least all shut down for the first two weeks in August and everyone went with their handkerchiefs on their head to Yarmouth <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="975" who="S0152">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="976" who="S0012">and and Hemsby and places like that from here and when you think that er criminals knew that people would would be on holiday</u>
<u n="977" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0152">but the thing is you did</u>
<u n="979" who="S0013" trans="overlap">didn't seem it happen</u>
<u n="980" who="S0012">yeah it didn't seem to happen</u>
<u n="981" who="S0152" trans="overlap">but you didn't have the same type of things as you have now</u>
<u n="982" who="S0012">no you don't</u>
<u n="983" who="S0152">everybody had the same things in their house</u>
<u n="984" who="S0012">yeah they did yeah</u>
<u n="985" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0012">and everybody left their doors open</u>
<u n="987" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="988" who="S0012">everybody I mean my mum used to come out of one house walk into another one so hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and come in have a cup of tea and that'd be it you know</u>
<u n="989" who="S0152">yeah so but you know I'd like to know you know in some respects I'd like to know what he did</u>
<u n="990" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0152">but you know I can't can't do anything I can certainly like engineering <unclear/> you know what an engineering <unclear/> smells like as so as I smell that automatic that's dad type thing</u>
<u n="992" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="993" who="S0152">cos all his clothes smelt of engineering oil</u>
<u n="994" who="S0012">that's right yeah <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="995" who="S0152">you know and because we had the shop dad used to have a suitcase where he took the shop to work</u>
<u n="996" who="S0012">did he? yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0152">well he had a little he had a little suitcase like this and</u>
<u n="998" who="S0013" trans="overlap">then</u>
<u n="999" who="S0152">and he sold cigarettes and tobacco and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0152">and sweets to the workmen</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0152">and he made as much money</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> then</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0152">of a night time selling those if he didn't do that I don't know how the shop would have survived</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0152">looking looking back on it</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0152">cos</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0013">cos it basically your mum <unclear/></u>
<u n="1013" who="S0152">yeah yeah my mum had the <trunc>sh</trunc> my mum had the shop</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0152">you know and we didn't you know when you think about you go shopping you know if you go shopping and you spend eighty pound <pause dur="short"/> now</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0152">it's nothing eighty pound on a Sunday was a bad Sunday</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0152">that was the whole day that was the takings on a Sunday</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0152">if we didn't reach a hundred pound on a Sunday</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0152">in the shop and we were open from ten till eight the rest of the week was gonna be difficult</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0012">ah yes my my mum every note they used to <unclear>cash up</unclear></u>
<u n="1026" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0012">and write down every every thing that they cashed up I mean I remember taking in ninety-six pound on a Saturday and this is all day Saturday and then he said this is a disaster <vocal desc="laugh"/> and you know cos</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0012">there'd be people on holiday at the time and and you know <unclear/> says sometime and then the takings went right down but they had to open all the time</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0012">but when people are on holiday they're <unclear>reading</unclear> we never had a holiday</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0012">we never had a holiday</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0152">no our holiday our shop was closed on a Tuesday it closed at it opened at half past eight on a Tuesday and closed at half past nine on a Tuesday and then opened back at four o'clock</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0152">on the afternoon</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0152">but we were open every day</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0012">we</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0152" trans="overlap">nine nine till nine till nine every day</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0012">mum's shop weren't allowed to open on a Sunday</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0013" trans="overlap">Wednesday afternoon</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0012">so what dad used to do was cook an enormous amount of fish and chips and people used to come in at three o'clock on the Sunday <trunc>morn</trunc> in in the morning to get the fish and chips because they were out <unclear/> so he used to cook them all you're not allowed to cook after twelve o'clock so he used to cook it all before twelve and put it in the warmers then people used to come in and they were all <unclear/> well I remember dad me dad be outside clearing up of course people usually chucking their litter about they'd be clearing up the front of the shop at four o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0152">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0012">you know we're</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0152">and and that's what you did</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0012">that's what he did yeah</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0152">you know and if you know the shop would never close if we were going on holiday for a week we had to get somebody to look after the shop</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0152">now my sister lived four doors down three doors down <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> she would look after the shop</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0152">occasionally but nine times out of ten that sister would come on holiday with us</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0152">so it was my other sister who would come and stay and look after the shop</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah hard times weren't they? they were hard times</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0152">then we had day trips so on a Tuesday because we didn't open till four o'clock my sister would look after the shop or we had like a <vocal desc="sneeze"/> excuse me we had we had somebody like who helped out in the shop and they would come and open up</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0152">until nine o'clock and we'd go on a daytrip to Rhyl or a day trip to Weston-Super-Mare or</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0012">yeah huh</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0152">and those were the those were the places that we we went to</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0012">the last time I remember us going out with we took the whole our neighbours to Yarmouth we did we didn't leave until four o'clock in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> and we course that was light at night and we'd get there late and there was nothing to do for us kids and then we'd come home they'd they'd be in the pub we'd be outside and <unclear>playing</unclear> and then we'd come home and that was our day out and that was when I was ten years old I was I remember that before we go off to the shop this was</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0012">and then we moved to <anon type="place"/> and we never had another holiday</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0152">mm yeah we always I mean we always ended up going to Great Yarmouth for our holidays really</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0152">but all the holidays with my dad was at Great Yarmouth</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0012">yeah what is it they there used to a lot going on at Great Yarmouth at one time but that become dead and alive all in the end innit? I dunno whether you've been lately or what</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I was I went a couple of months ago it's I was so I mean I was so disappointed when I came back here</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0152">cos I'd <trunc>ex</trunc> you know how you you have an image in your head of what</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah holidays</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0152">of holidays and what they were like and we used to go with a couple that we called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1073" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could never have children she had so many miscarriages but they were like aunt and uncle really</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0152">and dad would cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> couldn't drive dad would drive and we'd come here and it was mum and dad aunt and <trunc>unc</trunc> and myself and I remember staying at a couple of hotels in <anon type="place"/> and the last hotel that I stayed at in Great Yarmouth was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1077" who="S0012">what's that one that big one in that those horseshoe circle innit</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0012">where you drive around and <unclear/> people around</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0012">that's where I hit a coach</u>
<u n="1082" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1083" who="S0012">when I was seventeen I took the car down there and we had the boys were with us and I drove down and this coach was there and there was a car parked opposite and this bloke said you can get through there I said I can't get through there he said yes you can and I hit this coach and the coach driver got out and I didn't do any damage to the coach driver but my bumper fell off that was still in a forty-eight Ford Ford</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0012">and er that and I did three types of accident in one day there I backed up to get out of the way and this bloke come along in the on his bike and I hit it oh no he he crossed crossed the road and I hit him and he hit the roof with his head and knocked a a dent in the roof and he come round and he said don't worry boys I'm fine <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he walked off up the road <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I can't believe it I mean three not big accidents but three little accidents well and they boys had to <unclear/> the the bumper the front bumper in the back with the in the car so that was poking up between the seats</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0012">and and I nearly on the windscreen you know it small them <unclear>motors</unclear> were</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0012">and we had to go all the way home like that as well</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0012">and I tried to hide it up from my dad and I took down to this little er garage down er <anon type="place"/> there was a little garage down there where I knew the people and they put it all back together for me and nobody knew <vocal desc="laugh"/> god dear yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0152">but but Yarmouth is like you know and I the little you had that race track in the middle the pedal cart race track</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0012">yes you did yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0152">do you remember that?</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0152">and the horse and carts and everything and</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0012">yeah the horse and carts were going up there all day long going up and down up and down</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0152">and you had the jetty cos the jetty's not there any more the jetty's disappeared</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0012">has it?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0152">yeah the jetty is gone</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0152">no longer there you had the two</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0012" trans="overlap">there's Wellington Pier and Britannia Pier</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0152" trans="overlap">Britannia that's still there that's still there</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0152"><trunc>br</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but Wellington Pier is only half now because it's gone rotten at the other end</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0152">so you can't go past the theatre</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0012">you can't go past the theatre</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0152">no the side on the left hand side as you're looking at the beach that used to be the quiet side</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0152">going up towards the fun fair</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0012">that's it yeah</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0152">but there's dunes there now</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0012">is there?</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0152">and they hadn't used to be dunes</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0012">they never was dunes they I remember used to say three miles of golden sands</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0152">yeah there's dunes there's dunes down that side there's the Caister side that used to be dunes</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0152">down that</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0152">the far end down by the the race course erm the too many build the the model the miniature model village is still there</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0012">is it still there?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0152">the winter gardens is still there but it is fucking old and it's</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0012" trans="overlap">they used to have such a lovely flower show it was all along the front</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0012">all along that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1128" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0012">and all you know they used to the flowers used to say <trunc>we</trunc>were like a clock</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0012">ticking round they had a big clock in the middle it and they used to dress this clock up with flowers and that used to tick round and that was a fantastic place at one time</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0152" trans="overlap">we'll have to have a visit on a Sunday or something</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0012">used to be a lovely place</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0152" trans="overlap">just go and have a little visit it's better going in the <trunc>au</trunc> in now</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0152">cos there ain't many people about but it is it's not how it used to be</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0012">but loads of people have stood behind us that used to be the biggest place in Norfolk</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah loads and loads and you could never park</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no you can't park yeah</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0152">it was difficult to park I'm since I've been back I've never had a problem parking there</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0012">weird innit well I went right down I don't know why I went right down because that became like a slum you know and the whole and the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah this ain't much different</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0152">it isn't much different <pause dur="short"/> it isn't much different</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0012">huh</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0152">isn't much different <pause dur="short"/> right I suppose I'd better go and get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> now</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0013">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1148" who="S0012">well what's the time?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0152">ten to one</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0012">crikey flying times</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0152">it does it does fly very quickly <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0012">well thank you for that</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0013"><unclear/> lovely</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0012">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
