<text id="S6AP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:47:55</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-06-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0281 S0355</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Business idea, friends, international news.</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about recent news and present personal situation.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Inquiring, Anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0355">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hove, Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hove, Sussex</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>64 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Business Owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">yes so erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gave me er an idea er cos he he's er more or less decided to work for himself <pause dur="short"/> and start his own business and he said he went down to <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> erm Hong Kong and managed to er</u>
<u n="2" who="S0355"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0281">to get erm a visa for starting his own business</u>
<u n="4" who="S0355">in China?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0355">right? <pause dur="short"/> what does he fancy doing there?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0281">well he's gotten an idea I'm not sure quite exactly what it entails but it's about er <pause dur="short"/> I think er starting up some business online <pause dur="short"/> er he's very good with computers unlike me <pause dur="short"/> erm and <pause dur="short"/> I think he went down to Hong Kong and managed to convince them that <pause dur="short"/> what he'd got planned was feasible so I think I think he's got it</u>
<u n="8" who="S0355">cos Hong Kong's Chinese now isn't it? of course yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but unfortunately they <pause dur="short"/> they <trunc>ca</trunc> well it is erm <pause dur="short"/> it was the <trunc>sy</trunc>system with Hong Kong is that it it's now Chinese but they got er <pause dur="short"/> two erm <pause dur="short"/> two systems one country er they got sovereignty over it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="11" who="S0281">it's like er <pause dur="short"/> erm territories you know like France has got Monaco and and er <pause dur="short"/> andorra <pause dur="short"/> which they share with Spain but erm but it's it is Chinese the Chinese government have got the er the ultimate say over everything <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> they put the kibosh on that er <pause dur="short"/> that democracy movement that that started last year when they had riots</u>
<u n="12" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="13" who="S0281">er I was surprised to be honest that the that the Chinese government let them <pause dur="short"/> go as far as they did</u>
<u n="14" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="15" who="S0281">but now they they sort of rode out the they're very clever the Chinese er government and er they rather than clamp down on it really harshly which a lot of people including myself were expecting <pause dur="short"/> er they let it ride and now have bought in when er all the the hoo-ha and the world attention's not on it they're <pause dur="short"/> er making sure restrictions making sure they you know they don't do it again <pause dur="short"/> so er <pause dur="short"/> but finding work down there wouldn't be wouldn't be possible <pause dur="short"/> because they've got the same <pause dur="short"/> restrictions about <trunc>si</trunc> being sixty-five there <pause dur="short"/> as they have <pause dur="short"/> in</u>
<u n="16" who="S0355">China</u>
<u n="17" who="S0281">in erm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0355">the mainland</u>
<u n="19" who="S0281">in <trunc>Chi</trunc> in mainland China yeah and er most of Asia South East Asia all the same Malaysia Indonesia <pause dur="short"/> thailand <pause dur="short"/> it's all the same</u>
<u n="20" who="S0355">they probably think they're helping people <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0281" trans="overlap">sixty-five that's it</u>
<u n="22" who="S0355">ah dear dear dear <pause dur="short"/> but so how did he give you hope?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0281">well thinking you know if he's got it maybe I could get it <pause dur="short"/> if I I've gotta contact him <pause dur="short"/> erm again erm find out exactly how he did it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> so <pause dur="short"/> that's two things I can try <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what and <trunc>the</trunc>then if you then you'd move back into mainland China?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0281">well you can just go down there and try and get the visa</u>
<u n="26" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0281">come back <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0355">do you think you'd run into that age thing again though?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0281">I don't think it applies if you're starting a business er business I don't think so</u>
<u n="30" who="S0355" trans="overlap">doesn't it? <pause dur="long"/> from what I was looking at there what they wanted <pause dur="short"/> was quite a bit of er <pause dur="short"/> paperwork involved</u>
<u n="31" who="S0281">well <trunc>s</trunc> always is with bureaucracy and China is even worse than here as far as you know those types of bureatic things <pause dur="short"/> bureaucratic things <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know just have to try my best <pause dur="short"/> see what happens</u>
<u n="32" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0281">it does worry me <pause dur="long"/> I dunno maybe I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is always positive about this you know this er <pause dur="short"/> erm police check thing that erm shouldn't it shouldn't affect my application but <pause dur="short"/> we have to see</u>
<u n="34" who="S0355">that would affect what?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0281">my application for a business permit</u>
<u n="36" who="S0355">it shouldn't?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0281">well that's what she thinks</u>
<u n="38" who="S0355">right <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> well maybe it'll <trunc>helf</trunc>help having family there</u>
<u n="39" who="S0281">oh yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0355">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0281">hope so <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> always look on the bright side of life do do do do do do <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="whistle"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0281">yeah how are you facing the thought of Friday is it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0355">well with dread in a way</u>
<u n="47" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0355">very nervous about it if I want to to admit it <pause dur="short"/> it's on my mind</u>
<u n="49" who="S0281">yeah I'm sure it is</u>
<u n="50" who="S0355">my health's on my mind anyway my arm you know if it gets this arm I'm fucked and it's the started a little bit up there but <pause dur="short"/> I had a <pause dur="short"/> one of my <pause dur="short"/> green drinks this morning erm just got to up my intake of green vegetables stick to protein leave out the <pause dur="short"/> erm whatsits and the er</u>
<u n="51" who="S0281">carbs?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0355">carbs <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah so</u>
<u n="53" who="S0281">does exercise help your arm at all?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0355">it would yeah that would help me out?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0281">maybe I noticed you had weights in your bedroom</u>
<u n="56" who="S0355">yeah but cycling is the nicest one for me</u>
<u n="57" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0355">yeah cycling <pause dur="short"/> I enjoy my cycling</u>
<u n="59" who="S0281">would you be able to do it with your hand in a bandage?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0355">no I don't think so but then again I suppose I could do some walking but it's not the same as cycling <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="61" who="S0281">yeah I was thinking about that today about exercise and you won't be able to drive so you won't be able to go out to the countryside just <pause dur="short"/> yeah walk at the</u>
<u n="62" who="S0355" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0281">do some walks along the sea front</u>
<u n="64" who="S0355">well yeah that's it yeah I'll do that yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds good I</u>
<u n="65" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I went to the doctor for a blood test the other day and she <trunc>s</trunc> one of the questions she asked me was do you do any exercise? <pause dur="short"/> went no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what not even walking? no I <trunc>fe</trunc> well I occasionally walk do a walk at the weekend</u>
<u n="66" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0281">but er</u>
<u n="68" who="S0355">ah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0281">she said do you smoke? <pause dur="short"/> I said yeah two or three</u>
<u n="70" who="S0355">oh dear <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> what did she say then?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0281">oh erm <pause dur="short"/> she said well there's a counsellor here er helps people stop smoking</u>
<u n="72" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0281">but there again if I really wanted to I could do it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0355">I know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0281">it's not like I'm addicted <pause dur="long"/> so erm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0355">what was that?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0281">at the moment I don't really feel you know in a mental state I don't really feel er <pause dur="short"/> up to it <pause dur="short"/> feel like doing it you know?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0355"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="79" who="S0281">I bet you've got the same problem haven't you?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0355">oh I'm terrible I'm just so fucking down</u>
<u n="81" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0355">I feel just awful but you know I <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I think once this thing that that's hanging over me this operation once that's</u>
<u n="83" who="S0281">right</u>
<u n="84" who="S0355">I've got though that then I will er <pause dur="short"/> ah two messages from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0281">huh <pause dur="short"/> what's she got to say for herself? <pause dur="long"/> is she still seeing that <pause dur="short"/> guy she married <pause dur="short"/> that Arab?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0355">oh I don't know I don't know just <pause dur="short"/> just listening to it the saga going on there makes me feel ill</u>
<u n="87" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0355">you know what he <pause dur="short"/> what she's doing what she does and <pause dur="short"/> you know she obviously still feels for the guy it obviously shook her a lot</u>
<u n="89" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0355">you know but he did it to get over here to England that's why</u>
<u n="91" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mission accomplished</u>
<u n="92" who="S0355">yes and now he's remarried <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0281">oh I didn't realised she was she was divorced</u>
<u n="94" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh no she's it it is <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know if he has because I think <pause dur="short"/> he could he's so sneaky that I think Muslims can take more than one wife</u>
<u n="95" who="S0281">ah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0355">and er <pause dur="short"/> the the thing is that er <pause dur="short"/> he says that he's divorced her over there but he <trunc>mi</trunc> he might not have done so <pause dur="short"/> you know when</u>
<u n="97" who="S0281">I wonder how that affects law here because I mean it's</u>
<u n="98" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I don't I'm not sure I wondered that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that crazy French girl that used to be a friend of ours? <pause dur="short"/> she did this</u>
<u n="100" who="S0355" trans="overlap">remind me what she was like?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0281">well crazy young girl she was er <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0355">what? what?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0281" trans="overlap">very bouncy personality</u>
<u n="104" who="S0355">when when was this?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0281">actually I don't think you know her no he she became a regular of ours and a friend of ours after <pause dur="short"/> after you were down there</u>
<u n="106" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="107" who="S0281">but she did the same thing she she <pause dur="short"/> met some guy and felt sorry for him and got married to help him get a</u>
<u n="108" who="S0355">green card visa</u>
<u n="109" who="S0281" trans="overlap">green card yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0355">well <pause dur="short"/> I think it was he did it by <pause dur="short"/> charming her for you know making her fall in love with him and er <pause dur="short"/> you know wooing her and and I think that's that's not good <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="111" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="112" who="S0355">it's very that's underhand that's er</u>
<u n="113" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0355">I think that's terrible and and he's met other women while he's been over here and strung them along and</u>
<u n="115" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0355">so he's er woman banging at the door threatening <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0281">yeah?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0355"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been well he's not living with me thank you <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and er <pause dur="short"/> just strung a woman along she <pause dur="short"/> borrowed money and I think she'd given him money and done this and done that you know he just <pause dur="short"/> he was using her she it was she again an older woman</u>
<u n="119" who="S0281">do you want some orange juice?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0355">sorry?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0281">do you want some orange juice? oh you got beer</u>
<u n="122" who="S0355" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> no I've got a beer thanks <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0281"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0355">and every every time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er <pause dur="short"/> every time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm talks about it you know it's it's difficult for her I know</u>
<u n="125" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="long"/> but I suppose but <pause dur="short"/> in the end everybody's got problems just like most of us we've gotta <pause dur="short"/> try and get our heads round it and <pause dur="short"/> do the best we can</u>
<u n="126" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0281">nobody else can do it for you</u>
<u n="128" who="S0355">no</u>
<u n="129" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it gives you moral support but <pause dur="short"/> it's erm <pause dur="short"/> you know this whole cliché about <pause dur="short"/> something doesn't break you it makes you stronger</u>
<u n="130" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="131" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah question is if it breaks you or not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0355"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0281">it's er it might not just be make or break it might be just a long lingering <pause dur="short"/> petering out</u>
<u n="134" who="S0355">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0281">well if you've got a situation that <pause dur="short"/> might seem insoluble erm <pause dur="short"/> circumstances just wear you down</u>
<u n="136" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true <pause dur="short"/> yes I've <pause dur="short"/> I can identify with that yeah as what's happening to me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0355">well every year I don't know how I'm going to pay my income tax this year I don't <pause dur="short"/> you know it's not like I live fucking like a <pause dur="short"/> lord <pause dur="short"/> and my mortgage is paid <vocal desc="sigh"/> so you know <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="139" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you got something come coming in from the rent</u>
<u n="140" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh I've got a bit yeah <pause dur="short"/> the money I've got now probably <pause dur="short"/> probably four hundred odd quid I've got to put in the bank to pay an electric bill of two hundred and forty-six</u>
<u n="141" who="S0281" trans="overlap">what about <pause dur="short"/> since you're gonna be stuck at home for a while <pause dur="short"/> exploring the idea of <pause dur="short"/> maybe trying to <pause dur="short"/> give your advice regarding <pause dur="short"/> building problems in general and iron work in particular online? <pause dur="short"/> try and <trunc>wo</trunc>would that work? you you charging for advice online?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0355" trans="overlap">not really</u>
<u n="143" who="S0281">no?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0355">I have no you'd have to <pause dur="short"/> be insured for that</u>
<u n="145" who="S0281">insured?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0355">oh you're responsible for any <trunc>in</trunc>information you give</u>
<u n="147" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="148" who="S0355">if I give the wrong info</u>
<u n="149" who="S0281">oh yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0355">so you'd have to have at least a million probably two million pounds worth of insurance</u>
<u n="151" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0355">well I carry a million <unclear>nearly</unclear> a million and a half</u>
<u n="153" who="S0281" trans="overlap">do you?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0355">but I've had to let that go cos that cost me two hundred odd quid a year</u>
<u n="155" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0355">I haven't been able to renew it but <pause dur="short"/> you know hopefully <pause dur="short"/> more work coming in whatever and I'll get back to <pause dur="short"/> to it I'll have to start going into work as soon as I can really <pause dur="short"/> you know probably within two weeks to try and get er</u>
<u n="157" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well at least it's the left hand not the right</u>
<u n="158" who="S0355">well that's true <pause dur="short"/> that's it isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> it's true <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0355">I'll get it done get it done</u>
<u n="161" who="S0281">it's a lovely evening</u>
<u n="162" who="S0355">isn't it beautiful?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0281">the wind's dropped as well I think</u>
<u n="164" who="S0355">it's what?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0281">the wind's dropped</u>
<u n="166" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="short"/> I listened to the weather forecast you know the the shipping forecast the other night</u>
<u n="167" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0355">I don't know if it was the night before last I think it was it wasn't I don't think it was last night but it said er <pause dur="short"/> gales everywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0355">gales <trunc>everywh</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>unacceptable</unclear></u>
<u n="171" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh I saw the weather forecast earlier and there's erm some nice weather coming up</u>
<u n="172" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0281">it said it might rain <pause dur="short"/> a little tomorrow</u>
<u n="174" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0281">later on <pause dur="short"/> but there's a high pressure system coming in <pause dur="short"/> temperatures around mid-twenties that should be nice <pause dur="short"/> might even be able to sunbathe on the beach <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0281">I was surprised when we were down in Nice you know <pause dur="short"/> er how erm <pause dur="short"/> how few topless women there were there was still the odd one but er <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> explained it by saying it was er <pause dur="short"/> the Arabs' fault er the the hassle they get from <pause dur="short"/> even throw stones at them sometimes apparently</u>
<u n="178" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I er <pause dur="short"/> saved a girl from from serious sexual assault in a <pause dur="short"/> when I was in Paris with my girlfriend and er we were at the Arc de Triomph on New Year's Eve</u>
<u n="179" who="S0281">and you decided against it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah but no she she was dragged to the ground by <pause dur="short"/> half a dozen at least probably more Arabs dragged this single woman to the ground</u>
<u n="181" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="182" who="S0355">were groping her putting their hands up her skirt you know she she was just doing nothing and I just waded into them</u>
<u n="183" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah? <pause dur="short"/> mm well done</u>
<u n="184" who="S0355">well I didn't hit anyone <pause dur="short"/> I just said get off her <pause dur="short"/> helped her up and said you go and stand with us</u>
<u n="185" who="S0281">mm well done</u>
<u n="186" who="S0355">but you know a respectable woman she was you know shocked she was really frightened</u>
<u n="187" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> the thing is when <trunc>peo</trunc> often when people talk about er interracial problems like well there are here and <pause dur="short"/> but even more so France it's er it's to outsiders it might sound racist <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> when you live there and see on a daily basis what happens erm it's it's another thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0355">what what what things do you remember seeing when you were there that the Arabs?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well if you're going to score some dope it's going to be from an Arab</u>
<u n="190" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="191" who="S0281">which which is you know in itself is fine but <pause dur="short"/> erm if you're going to get er attacked or robbed or whatever chances are that it's gonna be an Arab who does it and that that's not racist to say so it's just the way things are you know? and er <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know the the young kids <pause dur="short"/> the they call them <foreign lang="fre">beurres</foreign> in France which is always sort of a strange nickname for them cos <foreign lang="fre">beurre</foreign> <trunc>tran</trunc> literally used to mean butter right but now the butters <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="192" who="S0355">why do they call them that?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0281">I don't know I don't know but erm ah there are big problems in especially in Paris er with all the er the Arabs and the blacks <pause dur="short"/> er they live in ghettos and er the inner cities are terrible places</u>
<u n="194" who="S0355">are they?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0281">oh yeah no go areas some of them</u>
<u n="196" who="S0355">wow</u>
<u n="197" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="198" who="S0355">wow it's that bad?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it really is <pause dur="short"/> well remember that that story I told you about when we were walking along the prom <pause dur="short"/> in Nice about I remember watching er <pause dur="short"/> the American bombers go ahead when the first Iraqi war opened you know? and I told you that er I saw a queue <trunc>out</trunc>outside the arms shop <pause dur="short"/> you know people would</u>
<u n="200" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0281">cos of the the whites were really scared that it was gonna kick off <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="202" who="S0355">well it's only the other side of the Mediterranean isn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0281">well yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0355">it's not far away</u>
<u n="205" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but er but it didn't materialise <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0355">no</u>
<u n="207" who="S0281">but er there is you know this fear in France is <trunc>di</trunc> really a divided country <pause dur="short"/> when that erm Charlie Hebdo thing happened</u>
<u n="208" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0281">that radicalised a lot of people</u>
<u n="210" who="S0355">what?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0281">exodus from France so French citizens <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0355">where did they chose to go?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0281">well London's a favourite spot but also</u>
<u n="214" who="S0355">really?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0355">what for Parisians?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0281">yeah they're there are many more er French leaving er France than ever before <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="218" who="S0355">good god</u>
<u n="219" who="S0281">oh yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0355">it's like the end of the Roman Empire isn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="222" who="S0355">the fall of the Roman Empire</u>
<u n="223" who="S0281">it and especially Jewish families I know you you don't have much sympathy for them but er they</u>
<u n="224" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0281">they they er they're really fearing er <pause dur="short"/> well what they can see as <pause dur="short"/> inevitable that er there's tax on synagogues and and Jewish schools and things you know</u>
<u n="226" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh I see yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0281">and there are there are armed soldiers outside all these places now</u>
<u n="228" who="S0355">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="229" who="S0281">you don't remember we see those armed guys up above the station?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0355">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0281">they're everywhere <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> doesn't bode well does it? when you've got paramilitary and military erm forces er <pause dur="short"/> on more or less permanent guard outside Jewish places</u>
<u n="232" who="S0355" trans="overlap">places</u>
<u n="233" who="S0281">smacks of you know pre-war Germany doesn't it?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0355"><vocal desc="misc"/> well</u>
<u n="235" who="S0281">so they're they got record immigration to <trunc>ba</trunc><trunc>ba</trunc> they're going to er Israel I think yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> but I was talking to those French girls you don't remember? I went out <pause dur="short"/> had a one evening a few a month or so ago?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="237" who="S0281">and they you know they don't they don't know the answer either <pause dur="short"/> well it's gonna happen they said themselves you know they they they're always wary about going out <pause dur="short"/> being attacked</u>
<u n="238" who="S0355">by Arabs?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> mainly</u>
<u n="240" who="S0355">wow</u>
<u n="241" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not only but I think that's a you know the main cause and er well we spoke about this Charlie Hebdo thing and <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> they just said well you know the the basic question wasn't it? the the the moral <trunc>philosoph</trunc>philosophical questions about er whether they were <pause dur="short"/> right or wrong to publish those things that that instigated the attacks <pause dur="short"/> whether either in a democracy that er one of the oldest in the world <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's the oldest <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="242" who="S0355">I thoughts the Greeks</u>
<u n="243" who="S0281">well it wasn't a true democracy as such it was only you had to be a citizen didn't you? and they had slaves and</u>
<u n="244" who="S0355">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0281">so erm whether you should have the right to <pause dur="short"/> say something <pause dur="short"/> negative about somebody but <pause dur="short"/> is it <vocal desc="sigh"/> on the other hand do you have the right to insult something or somebody is considered sacred <pause dur="short"/> like Mohammed okay? <pause dur="short"/> so that's the the thing that that started it wasn't it? when they they and er <pause dur="short"/> and you saw the Americans they they what happened there?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0355">I think you have to respect people <pause dur="short"/> have respect for people</u>
<u n="247" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah but the the the question is should on one hand <pause dur="short"/> in a democracy where you've got the right to say what you think about something <pause dur="short"/> should that be <pause dur="short"/> your <pause dur="short"/> er right to do so? <pause dur="short"/> but on the other hand</u>
<u n="248" who="S0355" trans="overlap">by thinking <unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0281">it it would you be <pause dur="short"/> could you be accused of incitement to riot?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0355">you could be accused of that <pause dur="short"/> quite probably but there again there are many good Muslims who didn't</u>
<u n="251" who="S0281">sure</u>
<u n="252" who="S0355">riot about it who who erm who just said well that's you know I don't even want to know about it you know and I forgive them</u>
<u n="253" who="S0281">well I think most Muslims do take that</u>
<u n="254" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I think most Muslims do take that line</u>
<u n="255" who="S0281">yeah but</u>
<u n="256" who="S0355">erm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0281">we only hear about the minority don't we? the extremists</u>
<u n="258" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I can <trunc>st</trunc> I can show you I can show you websites on there <pause dur="short"/> of Jews saying things from I'm glad we murdered your Christ your Jesus we I I promise you I can show you websites and they're not by as a matter of fact these are Jews <pause dur="short"/> to things on television mocking Christianity mocking people's belief in swearing and all this on Jewish television so I don't er <pause dur="short"/> you know I I er I felt it before as a Christian and even though I'm not <pause dur="short"/> I don't go to church often but <pause dur="short"/> it offends me <pause dur="short"/> it does offend me very much <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="259" who="S0281">it's a very delicate line this because it it carries on over to erm <pause dur="short"/> er how what you you consider is necessary to be a good er <pause dur="short"/> devotee of a certain religion like for example head gear headwear <pause dur="short"/> not only includes in the Arab veil for women</u>
<u n="260" who="S0355">Catholic nuns</u>
<u n="261" who="S0281">well yeah yeah and but <trunc>e</trunc> the the French government the parliament they they they ruled that erm they er <pause dur="short"/> they can't wear it er erm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0355">the hijab</u>
<u n="263" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0281">so <pause dur="short"/> when <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> again Sikhs you know should <pause dur="short"/> why why shouldn't Sikhs have their turbans and?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0355">well quite it's what makes enriches the world isn't it?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0355">I think the dangerous thing is when you start putting your stuff on other people as Muslims would put their stuff Christians put their stuff</u>
<u n="269" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think the you you it makes sense that <pause dur="short"/> countries like Britain and France have to er <pause dur="short"/> change with the times and while on the one hand France is a secular state and has this rigid partition between er the clergy and the government</u>
<u n="270" who="S0355" trans="overlap">clergy and state</u>
<u n="271" who="S0281">the state yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> well there's that er I think er that they they should er be more flexible er <pause dur="short"/> because most of these immigrants they're not gonna go away <pause dur="short"/> so France like Britain is a multicultural country and <pause dur="short"/> you can't expect to live in the past</u>
<u n="272" who="S0355">no <pause dur="short"/> well I I'm quite sure quite probably years ago people were multicultural you know and people all over different religions and different er ethnicities were living all over the world weren't there</u>
<u n="273" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well they were <pause dur="short"/> they were</u>
<u n="274" who="S0355">you know here and</u>
<u n="275" who="S0281">but it's so much more intensified isn't it these days? <pause dur="short"/> with the just the numbers</u>
<u n="276" who="S0355">well I saw something the other day it said oh in they were doing a story on Rome and it said in <pause dur="short"/> whenever it was twelve fifty or whenever <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> there were more people living in Rome than there are today <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0355">so and I suspect the same is true <pause dur="short"/> I know certainly of Edinburgh <pause dur="short"/> there were probably more people living in Edinburgh for certainly and if you look at it at at everything you'll probably find there were more people living in London because people you know that little cottage I had in</u>
<u n="279" who="S0281"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0355"><anon type="place"/>? yeah I mean there were four families living in there</u>
<u n="281" who="S0281">good lord</u>
<u n="282" who="S0355">four families</u>
<u n="283" who="S0281">well I think the numbers are certainly they used to be around one or two million for a long time didn't they? wasn't it? and then I seem to remember when we were kids that from geography lessons the population of London was about six to eight million something like that I think it's maybe a lot more now</u>
<u n="284" who="S0355">yeah but when you when you look where at that area the city of London that once was <unclear/> the people living in that area then say six million or whatever and now in that square mile there are probably less people living in that square <trunc>me</trunc> square mile than there were then</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0355">although the city's <pause dur="short"/> expanded the <pause dur="short"/> you know people live in expect to live in in <trunc>fl</trunc> in a flat don't they? in a small flat <pause dur="short"/> with with services but er you know? <pause dur="short"/> but I was reading a a book it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s I think I've given it back to her but it was erm a it was a Labour MP wrote it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0355">I I think it was I think it was a guy called Alan Clark or John Clark <pause dur="short"/> and he described how he lived in the fifties with his mother and father in this erm <pause dur="short"/> building that's in this part of London that's probably now pulled down <pause dur="short"/> but they in one room they had one room upstairs oh oh no they had two rooms and there were four of them and like two rooms upstairs in this house and the loo was a bucket and they had to take the bucket down to the road it was just appallingly</u>
<u n="289" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0355">erm <pause dur="short"/> it was poverty it was grinding poverty</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281">most of it just got thrown out the window think didn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0355">yeah well it used didn't it?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0355" trans="overlap">god <pause dur="short"/> guard a loo</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281">I remember <pause dur="short"/> when er I used to stay in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s place it was behind where we used to live in <anon type="place"/> terrace</u>
<u n="296" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281">and their house was directly behind ours in <anon type="place"/> street <pause dur="short"/> they used to have an outside toilet</u>
<u n="298" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281">and a tin bath</u>
<u n="300" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah a lot of places did</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281">wow amazing to think <pause dur="short"/> how well her kids have done <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0355">ah dear</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281">yeah she'd be proud of them <pause dur="long"/> mm <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah one of my regrets is that I didn't know my parents as people you know?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I I didn't either I didn't know mine as people and they lived far longer years so <pause dur="short"/> do you ever know them you know?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281">well true enough</u>
<u n="306" who="S0355">you know <pause dur="short"/> I know what you're saying <pause dur="short"/> but er <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> seems like too nice a evening to stay in <pause dur="short"/> there again I suppose it's gonna be over soon it's eight o'clock already but</u>
<u n="308" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I need to get out of my overalls I need to have a wash <pause dur="short"/> spruce myself up and then cook some <pause dur="short"/> dinner</u>
<u n="309" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0355">it's what I need to do <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0281">working again tomorrow?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got to wash some <pause dur="short"/> wash my slippers and wash my erm <pause dur="short"/> pyjama bottoms tomorrow cos I've got to go in like that was clean that erm <pause dur="short"/> dressing gown I've got to go in my dressing gown</u>
<u n="313" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well you you <pause dur="short"/> really?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0281">oh <pause dur="long"/> do you know what time you'll be back? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0355">well they said go in early so they may start at eight o'clock nine o'clock nine ten eleven twelve one <pause dur="short"/> probably be back here they keep you in there for an hour or two <pause dur="short"/> probably be back here three or four something like that</u>
<u n="317" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0355">but I'll come just come in my dressing gown <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> pyjamas <pause dur="short"/> swallow some painkillers and go to bed</u>
<u n="319" who="S0281">I'm surprised they ask you to wear pyjamas if it's only a local anaesthetic</u>
<u n="320" who="S0355">well <pause dur="short"/> they got to get you you haven't they? they have to get to your</u>
<u n="321" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0355">heart if it stops or something quick and</u>
<u n="323" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="324" who="S0355">stick needles in you and</u>
<u n="325" who="S0281">yeah I suppose you're right yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0355">get to bring my own slippers that don't fall off easily apparently <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0355">so I've got my camping slippers</u>
<u n="329" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0281">camping slippers</u>
<u n="331" who="S0355">camping slippers</u>
<u n="332" who="S0281">wow</u>
<u n="333" who="S0355" trans="overlap">do some camping after</u>
<u n="334" who="S0281">your campy slippers</u>
<u n="335" who="S0355">er <pause dur="long"/> ah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0281"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0355">oh dear <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0281">breathe deep the gathering gloom</u>
<u n="339" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0281">watch lights fade in every room <pause dur="short"/> bedsitter people look back and lament on another useless day's energy spent</u>
<u n="341" who="S0355">ah <pause dur="short"/> well my mate said to me today he said I <pause dur="short"/> I'm going down to Portugal I said oh when's that? he said July <vocal desc="laugh"/> I went July? you're joking it's roasting down there <pause dur="short"/> well apparently</u>
<u n="342" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0355">that's when all the Portuguese leave <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>don't they?</unclear></u>
<u n="344" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0355">but erm <pause dur="short"/> well good luck to him</u>
<u n="346" who="S0281">mm why did he choose Portugal?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0355">sorry?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0281">why did he choose Portugal?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0355">because he's got a free ride down there <pause dur="short"/> and er yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="351" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> his mate was going down there and said do you want to come along for the ride? and he went yeah okay</u>
<u n="352" who="S0281">mm nice one</u>
<u n="353" who="S0355">but er he lives on a on twenty on fifty quid a week he lives on</u>
<u n="354" who="S0281">wow <pause dur="short"/> how can you do that?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0355">well he lives in a squat <pause dur="short"/> I know you they don't allow you to squat nowadays but they no one's chucked them out of there</u>
<u n="356" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> where in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0355">erm I'm not I he I don't know where he is <pause dur="short"/> he lives in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm yes it's in <anon type="place"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but he er</u>
<u n="358" who="S0281">there used to be a law in France <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it still exists but er <pause dur="short"/> that during the winter months you can't be evicted</u>
<u n="359" who="S0355">oh that's handy isn't it?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0281">yeah except that landlords <vocal desc="laugh"/> are very wary about</u>
<u n="361" who="S0355">who they</u>
<u n="362" who="S0281">yeah who they take on and also erm finding any people I suppose newly renting something around that time before just before winter kicks in</u>
<u n="363" who="S0355">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> gosh how about that?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0281">yeah so what some people do is er just stop paying the rent <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0355">ah <pause dur="short"/> sad isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> why can't we just get all get on with it <vocal desc="laugh"/> pay your rent and do stuff and <pause dur="short"/> but there again I suppose people fall victim to circumstance where they maybe kinda</u>
<u n="366" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0355">can't pay the rent but <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> it's the first thing you do pay isn't it?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0355">it's for sure that's the first thing you do <pause dur="short"/> before booze or anything else</u>
<u n="370" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0355"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> god knows <pause dur="short"/> ah it just yeah <pause dur="short"/> got to look on the bright side of life <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I feel tired</u>
<u n="372" who="S0281">yeah?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0355"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> texted me <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> that all went a bit haywire last night her texting I just <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's like a nightmare and er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> why does she use abbreviations and things like that? <pause dur="long"/> or is it just the syntax</u>
<u n="375" who="S0355">it was what?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0281">syntax <pause dur="short"/> the way she constructs sentences not making the meaning clear?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0355">well yeah but I think she was pissed</u>
<u n="378" who="S0281">ah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0355">let's have a reply to say <pause dur="short"/> she's getting her knickers in a twist with her phone</u>
<u n="380" who="S0281">huh?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0355">she's getting her knickers in a twist about her phone</u>
<u n="382" who="S0281">yeah why?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0355">oh she's saying that er <pause dur="short"/> her phone's doing things like saying message not sent received a draft <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> getting her knickers in a twist about it basically</u>
<u n="384" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0355">I mean I can't I I know why my phone saves it to drafts but you've got to hit the wrong buttons and you know or <pause dur="short"/> there's loads of different reasons I don't know what her phone is doing or why you know?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0355">it's er I haven't a clue</u>
<u n="388" who="S0281">yeah I've gotta go to <pause dur="short"/> apple and try and sort out my phone I can't get my hotmail messages on my phone now for some reason it says I don't have the right password which I don't understand see <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
