<text id="S6BR">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:35:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0456 S0474</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Pikko Mikko Pub, Joensuu, Finland</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Nokia, mobile telephony, new phone, setting phones.</topics>
		<activity>Unpacking new phones while abroad.</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0456">
				<exactage>44</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/ German</nat>
				<birthplace>Salzkotten</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>German</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scouse</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer (English Language and Literature)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0474">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wirral</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Merseyside</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Wirral, Bebington</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>phD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0474">that was perfect timing</u>
<u n="2" who="S0456">yes</u>
<u n="3" who="S0474">cheers</u>
<u n="4" who="S0456">chin chin</u>
<u n="5" who="S0474">do you think those bricks over there are for that building or for the <unclear>pavement</unclear>?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0456">they look like <trunc>flag</trunc>flagstones don't they? <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah they've</u>
<u n="7" who="S0474" trans="overlap">before you mean?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0456">dug out in front of the building</u>
<u n="9" who="S0474">oh yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0456">so a big moment and out comes a giant carrot</u>
<u n="11" who="S0474">you excited? <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0456">yeah I <unclear/> to take me so</u>
<u n="13" who="S0474">oh we've got a plug <pause dur="short"/> oh cos it's not</u>
<u n="14" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah so here it's already on EU and this is this is these ones are brilliant because you just put it in and then screw it fast</u>
<u n="15" who="S0474">wow it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> we don't need these bits yet do we? it's handy to have a foreign plug</u>
<u n="16" who="S0456">yeah so <unclear/> wherever you like now <pause dur="short"/> by way of comparison <pause dur="short"/> yours looks better</u>
<u n="17" who="S0474">it's so much lighter but it's cos it hasn't got a battery in</u>
<u n="18" who="S0456">ah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0474">ah it's smaller but it's a bit thicker <pause dur="short"/> which is probably better for your hands</u>
<u n="20" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0474" trans="overlap">what do you call it ergonomic?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0456"><trunc>ercon</trunc>ergonomics <pause dur="short"/> yeah it definitely looks</u>
<u n="23" who="S0474" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/> nice</u>
<u n="24" who="S0456">like the success is more down to that doesn't it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0456">instead of the frame it is <pause dur="short"/> well you can tell <unclear/> a bit more used it's it's only a fraction larger</u>
<u n="27" who="S0474">apparently as well this is more this is a protective casing and it</u>
<u n="28" who="S0456" trans="overlap">it uses a yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0474">it's made out of <trunc>sor</trunc></u>
<u n="30" who="S0456" trans="overlap"><unclear>shell</unclear></u>
<u n="31" who="S0474">the material is like solid the colour so if you scratch it it's still the same colour if you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0456">yeah well same as this one</u>
<u n="33" who="S0474">yeah and also the buttons are water water and dust proof</u>
<u n="34" who="S0456">ah huh very <unclear/> well if you open it and then you can find out hang on where's the battery here? <pause dur="short"/> ah and look it speaks French</u>
<u n="35" who="S0474">huh</u>
<u n="36" who="S0456">oh no it speaks everything</u>
<u n="37" who="S0474" trans="overlap">and Spanish</u>
<u n="38" who="S0456">and Spanish you can have the Spanish one or German it just doesn't speak Finnish or English</u>
<u n="39" who="S0474">I think I'll let you take it out of its case</u>
<u n="40" who="S0456">oh yeah I remember I had had that issue before you can</u>
<u n="41" who="S0474">it feels more like a toy than this one do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0456">thank you what did I do with my? apparently you press it here and then there <pause dur="short"/> but then that didn't work for <unclear/> everything else</u>
<u n="43" who="S0474" trans="overlap">I kind of nearly did it</u>
<u n="44" who="S0456">yeah it is something like this <pause dur="short"/> come on phone</u>
<u n="45" who="S0474">maybe if you tip it the other way up so you get it out like a cake</u>
<u n="46" who="S0456" trans="overlap">no I</u>
<u n="47" who="S0474">like this</u>
<u n="48" who="S0456">like a cake?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0474">yeah like you know when you're getting a cake out of a tin or an ice cube</u>
<u n="50" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah that's the</u>
<u n="51" who="S0474">out of a tray</u>
<u n="52" who="S0456" trans="overlap">that's the idea but I've got it now anyway</u>
<u n="53" who="S0474">oh</u>
<u n="54" who="S0456">I had yeah I have it yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0474">yay</u>
<u n="56" who="S0456">dual sim?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0456">so you can actually get a Finnish sim if you'd like or a Spanish one or</u>
<u n="59" who="S0474" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="60" who="S0456">or a South American one so yours is dual sim and mine claims to be</u>
<u n="61" who="S0474" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0456">yeah it's standard size</u>
<u n="63" who="S0474">well if we knew I had the post stock I'd get a Finnish fin now sim a Finnish sim</u>
<u n="64" who="S0456">well you would get a pay as you go <pause dur="short"/> they're not expensive anyway <pause dur="short"/> thing is I can always ask whether I can have a second sim</u>
<u n="65" who="S0474">ask who?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0456">ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0474">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh wow so we but so it works with your number? two sims</u>
<u n="68" who="S0456">I wonder <pause dur="short"/> I wonder whether it's <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> right you'd better get your <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0474" trans="overlap">so essentially would be the same person</u>
<u n="70" who="S0456">well I'll I'll have to find out er so the battery is smaller</u>
<u n="71" who="S0474">okay</u>
<u n="72" who="S0456">but</u>
<u n="73" who="S0474">I definitely think the water shortened the life of my battery</u>
<u n="74" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0474">either that or or it wasn't a good a good model for battery life and this is the improved one</u>
<u n="76" who="S0456">well they're both <pause dur="short"/> three point seven volts this one has slightly fewer amp here micro amp here</u>
<u n="77" who="S0474">does it matter which one I put it in? it doesn't does it?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0456">no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0474">I can lead a double life with this can't I? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0456">oh god don't tell me that there'd be all these men that are after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> don't don't close it yet you need something else</u>
<u n="81" who="S0474">oh yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0456">have you found the slots?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0456">okay <pause dur="short"/> do you want to press down?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0474">it was like you predicted that I was gonna get this phone</u>
<u n="86" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> predictive phoning rather than predictive texting</u>
<u n="87" who="S0474">mm yeah I love it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0456">we don't oh it has enough charge brilliant</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="89" who="S0456">yeah that's a bit like mine hello <pause dur="short"/> and the yes like mine you can't use the <unclear/> for this</u>
<u n="90" who="S0474">oh is it automatic or English?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0456">no English I didn't automatic might be Finnish</u>
<u n="92" who="S0474">auto update time we'll put that on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0456">yeah that's what mine said <pause dur="short"/> continue</u>
<u n="94" who="S0474">no sim card <pause dur="short"/> oh no there's just that one <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>use</unclear> this one</u>
<u n="96" who="S0474">ah yeah what's it called?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0456" trans="overlap">hang on no <trunc>sign</trunc> oh no sim card for that one</u>
<u n="98" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0456">yeah oh how clever is that?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0456">yeah you've got very little charge <unclear>Giffgaff</unclear> and there we go time <pause dur="long"/> and that I don't know what the green one is</u>
<u n="102" who="S0474"><unclear>for</unclear> calls I think</u>
<u n="103" who="S0456">oh yeah call <unclear/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0474">missed or received <pause dur="short"/> no calls yet</u>
<u n="105" who="S0456">just look for your messages <pause dur="short"/> depends whether they were</u>
<u n="106" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0474">oh look twenty-twelve</u>
<u n="109" who="S0456">I'm there twice <pause dur="short"/> what does it say?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0474">hope you got my love letter a picture <unclear>leaving</unclear> now</u>
<u n="111" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0474">oh there's only three messages on it not yours is that all sims hold these days? three messages?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0456">I I don't know</u>
<u n="114" who="S0474">there might be a way of shuffling them round the different apps but if you go on this one and click on it there you can switch sim</u>
<u n="115" who="S0456">yeah which obviously I can't yeah I think it <unclear/> that? but I've only got one sim slot the other is doesn't exist</u>
<u n="116" who="S0474">yeah should be able to put the torch on a hot key</u>
<u n="117" who="S0456">yeah I haven't done any hot keys cling cling</u>
<u n="118" who="S0474">chin chin</u>
<u n="119" who="S0456" trans="overlap"><unclear/> happy <pause dur="long"/> yeah I mean that looks like the matt version doesn't it? and this is the shiny blue version</u>
<u n="120" who="S0474">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this probably looks more expensive doesn't it?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0474" trans="overlap">the way the buttons are than this</u>
<u n="123" who="S0456">we know it isn't</u>
<u n="124" who="S0474">I think it's lighter</u>
<u n="125" who="S0456">that's good</u>
<u n="126" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0456">I can definitely confirm that that one is more expensive than that one</u>
<u n="128" who="S0474">thanks <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> might even be able to go on the internet have a quick look at something what should I go on Yahoo? or what's the all this?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0456" trans="overlap">won't you get that abroad?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0474">don't know oh probably not should I try? I've got ETP on there</u>
<u n="131" who="S0456">I've got I've got <pause dur="short"/> I never tried myself <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0474">could be easy</u>
<u n="133" who="S0456" trans="overlap">don't you have to connect first?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0474">dad roaming is off</u>
<u n="135" who="S0456"><unclear/> connect er okay same as you so connection is this one I guess connectivity mobile data <pause dur="short"/> cos I was thinking</u>
<u n="136" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0456">whether <pause dur="short"/> I should not swap sims because I will have all this mobile data with that one</u>
<u n="138" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0456" trans="overlap">but not with Giffgaff so I have it anyway it doesn't really matter that I haven't got wi-fi but mobile data just takes more battery and stuff okay so let's see</u>
<u n="140" who="S0474" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0456">I've got mobile data</u>
<u n="142" who="S0474" trans="overlap">well the irony is it's you that needs the dual sim <pause dur="short"/> and I've got the phone</u>
<u n="143" who="S0456">data roaming's off ah hang on creating a secure connection <pause dur="long"/> but I think it is on roaming so</u>
<u n="144" who="S0474" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="145" who="S0456">maybe not a good idea</u>
<u n="146" who="S0474">yeah I would <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> red that's not red any more it used to be red and green didn't it?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah my mum she was on my phone once and she said how'd you get back? she forgot you know the red and the green</u>
<u n="149" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0474">cos you don't have that any more you just have one single button on an Iphone don't you? really one touch button</u>
<u n="151" who="S0456">doing what?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0474">just a circle so you can't you don't have</u>
<u n="153" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah but for what?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0474">a green and a red any more <pause dur="short"/> you know that <unclear/> to rely on</u>
<u n="155" who="S0456" trans="overlap">oh yeah but if you but if you have a but if you</u>
<u n="156" who="S0474" trans="overlap">green for go red for stop</u>
<u n="157" who="S0456">but if you if you do a call then you have to</u>
<u n="158" who="S0474">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but if you're stuck on the screen somewhere with a touch one you've always got the option to get out of it by pressing the red</u>
<u n="159" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0474">if you do it as a smart <unclear/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0456">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well with this one you have this one this one get you out</u>
<u n="162" who="S0474">oh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0456">and if nothing else helps you go for the er power button</u>
<u n="164" who="S0474">should I leave the the screen still stuck?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mine is on it erm I leave mine on until they literally fall off <pause dur="short"/> and yours says lock your <unclear/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0474">I wonder if this will be rare soon because I we didn't see any more did we? they seem to update it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0474">I think because it I read a review somewhere and it says it's got the internet but it's in no way a smart phone it's a feature phone and it's trying too hard to be a smart phone by having the apps</u>
<u n="169" who="S0456">oh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0474" trans="overlap">I guess like this one as well</u>
<u n="171" who="S0456">yeah like like this one this one</u>
<u n="172" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0456">yep cos there this is the funniest bit this one has <pause dur="short"/> even the screen is but it is <unclear/> so the screen is bigger it's flatter but otherwise the functionality seems to be exactly the same</u>
<u n="174" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0456">apart from my hot key directly to the internet but yeah yeah I definitely have only one sim as you can see in the description I had one sim like that and one from the side and the bit from the side was empty</u>
<u n="176" who="S0474">oh well this phone comes as both</u>
<u n="177" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0474">the one in the UK I think only they only market it as a single sim maybe that's why we couldn't find it and it was this one <unclear/> looking for</u>
<u n="179" who="S0456">unless it was a slightly different number</u>
<u n="180" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0456">you want to send me a text to sort of you know it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to take those noises off it as well</u>
<u n="183" who="S0456">mm <pause dur="long"/> oh can you send me a text to the erm Finnish one</u>
<u n="184" who="S0474">erm don't know if they'll have it here</u>
<u n="185" who="S0456">you did find it eventually</u>
<u n="186" who="S0474">how do you get contacts up again? <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I don't think it was in <pause dur="short"/> ah I can't see what the number is</u>
<u n="187" who="S0456">yeah go back to just contacts and then just see</u>
<u n="188" who="S0474">oh <pause dur="short"/> I have got a feeling it's not in here for for some strange reason</u>
<u n="189" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah make it easy <pause dur="short"/> I'll send you one and then you know whether you can receive one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0474"><unclear>yeah</unclear> good thinking</u>
<u n="191" who="S0456">there we go choose erm I can even call you right I'll do that so you'll <unclear>actually</unclear> hear your ringtone it'll be the same as this one bet you <pause dur="long"/> it's going all the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<event desc="sound of mobile phone"/>
<u n="192" who="S0456">I've muted it before I stopped it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0474">oh I have got you there <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> British the <anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0456">well yeah of course this is yeah silly me</u>
<u n="195" who="S0474" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0456">so you can send me a text <pause dur="long"/> okay <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I wonder whether you have the same kind of screen thing as well we'll find out later on <pause dur="short"/> and make something really really difficult <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0474">mm what checking the calculator works</u>
<u n="198" who="S0456">yeah one plus ninety-nine is a hundred so calculator works <pause dur="long"/> and I've got a feeling that some kind of building here <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/> but you take a picture of the flying remember to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> takes a little while to get used to the keys</u>
<u n="200" who="S0456">yeah I think these ones are better defined but you would have to have you have to be very good for a few tactile <unclear/> that was <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0474">ah yours are cool <pause dur="short"/> uhu here's the <pause dur="short"/> students or whatever they are</u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<u n="202" who="S0456">these are still my two favourite texts including loads of exes as well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0474"><unclear/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0456">yeah they look very nice don't they? far nicer than the the old remember the very old phones with the grey screens?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0456">it looks even nicer than an Iphone <pause dur="short"/> ah they <unclear/> it up because there's another one of these is that me or you?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0474">no it's me</u>
<u n="208" who="S0456">er</u>
<u n="209" who="S0474" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the bicycle as my ringtone</u>
<u n="210" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah ding dong ding dong</u>
<u n="211" who="S0474">oh let my try coconuts</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="212" who="S0474">no I'll have bicycle</u>
<u n="213" who="S0456">this is what they're digging it up for look there's a new grey box well it's olive</u>
<u n="214" who="S0474">oh yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0456">don't know what's inside <unclear/> something <unclear>or other</unclear></u>
<u n="216" who="S0474">electrics or something</u>
<u n="217" who="S0456">yeah it'll be another one of those strange things that always bleep even though nobody's crossing the road in all the time here I've only ever seen one blind person</u>
<u n="218" who="S0474">oh we saw that man what was going blind in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0456">did we?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0474">yeah I remember he came in and chatted to us I think he bought you a drink</u>
<u n="221" who="S0456">oh yeah the the old fella with the big story</u>
<u n="222" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0456">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah well you've never seen him since</u>
<u n="224" who="S0474">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0456">that's a familiar <unclear/> on bikes</u>
<u n="226" who="S0474">I've got a voice recorder</u>
<u n="227" who="S0456">yeah so have I <pause dur="short"/> do you want to record the recordings then?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0474">no</u>
<u n="229" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's what erm Tony Benn did <pause dur="short"/> because he felt that er he he got misrepresented so often in with interviews etcetera so every time he was interviewed or anything he recorded it he actually was erm into those kind of gizmos long before it became fashionable</u>
<u n="230" who="S0474">we've got one photo on the phone <pause dur="short"/> I don't know when the heck it was taken cos I never had it on here</u>
<u n="231" who="S0456">this looks like</u>
<u n="232" who="S0474">would you say the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0456">no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0474">where?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0456">the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0474">oh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0456">see the rose? because</u>
<u n="238" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0456">obviously it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="240" who="S0474">strange</u>
<u n="241" who="S0456" trans="overlap">and that's therefore the Yorkshire rose <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know why you would have it on on a phone you've never used</u>
<u n="242" who="S0474">no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a time travelling phone <pause dur="long"/> you will have set up yours long before I've done anything to that one all I've ever done is switch off the noise</u>
<u n="244" who="S0474">do you know what a glance screen is?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0456">a glance screen? no it might be if if if <unclear/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0474">if you're watching something on it you know you wouldn't watch something for an hour on this would you?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0456" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> unless glance screen means it never goes black</u>
<u n="248" who="S0474">oh</u>
<u n="249" who="S0456">so for one hour you can always look at the most important items <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0474">oh is that what's her name?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0456"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0474" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0456">mm that looks very I haven't even <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="254" who="S0474" trans="overlap">it looks like a businessman's phone though</u>
<u n="255" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0474">cos it's like the city</u>
<u n="257" who="S0456">this is this is like</u>
<u n="258" who="S0474" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0456">er architect</u>
<u n="260" who="S0474"><unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0456">where did you find them? in the gallery?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0474">settings</u>
<u n="263" who="S0456">photos?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0474">I've only got three on this I've got loads on that one but I'll make my <unclear>own</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0456">yeah well that's the whole point isn't it?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0474" trans="overlap">display settings <unclear/> paper <pause dur="short"/> default <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0456" trans="overlap">that's what I've got yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0474">there's a few default <pause dur="short"/> unless you want your photos</u>
<u n="269" who="S0456"><unclear/> received back</u>
<u n="270" who="S0474">back yeah that's my</u>
<u n="271" who="S0456">that's <unclear/> only got these <pause dur="short"/> mm this is quite nice</u>
<u n="272" who="S0474">oh yeah that's <unclear>nice</unclear></u>
<u n="273" who="S0456" trans="overlap">apart from the black edges <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0474">that's not it oh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0456">this is this has something to do with but it's not perfect because it's such low risk I think I like this one</u>
<u n="276" who="S0474">yeah tell you what we'll do</u>
<u n="277" who="S0456" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh look you can <pause dur="short"/> oh you can fit it to display</u>
<u n="278" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0456">yeah tell me what</u>
<u n="280" who="S0474">we'll get some photos tomorrow in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0474">I might have a nice one of the lake actually <pause dur="short"/> that's cool it goes nice with the white and black frame</u>
<u n="283" who="S0456">I have to is it in settings? where did you find your <pause dur="short"/> where did you do the auto <trunc>f</trunc> time?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0474">er yeah go to settings</u>
<u n="285" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0474">erm display settings</u>
<u n="287" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0474">then you should have got a what what was it you were looking for?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0456">auto time</u>
<u n="290" who="S0474">auto time what?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0456">yeah your <unclear>time</unclear> automatically</u>
<u n="292" who="S0474">oh erm date and time I presume</u>
<u n="293" who="S0456">notifications <unclear/> I haven't got it</u>
<u n="294" who="S0474">oh</u>
<u n="295" who="S0456">is it in profiles? must be</u>
<u n="296" who="S0474">no <pause dur="short"/> you I thought you just had it go back up to display settings er sorry down sorry</u>
<u n="297" who="S0456"><unclear/> notifications <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> how can you find it? how can you find it when I can't?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0474">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0456" trans="overlap">you're too used to Nokias and I'm not any more <pause dur="short"/> okay so it's on come on come on change it doesn't want to change</u>
<u n="300" who="S0474">what do you want it to change into?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0456">well if it's on it should be <trunc>chang</trunc> yours changed instantly</u>
<u n="302" who="S0474">automatic time you mean?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0474">it is twenty-one forty-eight though</u>
<u n="305" who="S0456">yeah of course it isn't</u>
<u n="306" who="S0474">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know you have to type in the right time first of all</u>
<u n="307" who="S0456">no you didn't do anything did you?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0474">I know <pause dur="short"/> maybe we put a wrong time in by accident and now yours thinks it's that time?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0456">I've got no idea why why that should be the case</u>
<u n="310" who="S0474">hang on can't do key lock how do you do key lock on this phone?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0456">key lock? it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0474">key lock</u>
<u n="313" who="S0456">what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0474">you know where you lock your keys on you must hold it <pause dur="short"/> no?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0456">lock your keys?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0474">you know so you can't nudge them</u>
<u n="317" who="S0456">oh it goes off well you can lock them it's isn't it the top one and the X one? <unclear/> settings <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0474">security settings <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="319" who="S0456">it must be inside this one cos you it's not this</u>
<u n="320" who="S0474" trans="overlap">key code settings</u>
<u n="321" who="S0456">it's not in display settings is it? where do I look at?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0474">what what are you looking for now?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0456">to do the time</u>
<u n="324" who="S0474">oh down keep going down there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0456">on off on <pause dur="short"/> these are <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> what does it display on yours? <pause dur="short"/> what if you carry a?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0474"><unclear/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0456">so is mine <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know why my phone doesn't do it <pause dur="long"/> so how do I change it manually?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0474">erm go back go to where you were type it in</u>
<u n="329" who="S0456">type it in?</u>
<event desc="background talk"/> <pause dur="long"/>
<u n="330" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0474">what are you?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0456" trans="overlap">no no ah it's some strange time zone that's why even but even the date is wrong <pause dur="long"/> international er west</u>
<u n="333" who="S0474">see that's GMT minus twelve you're plus two</u>
<u n="334" who="S0456">I'm going back it's <pause dur="short"/> oh it was <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> time <unclear>forward</unclear> twenty-four hours date even the date is should be out of sync so auto updates will get it</u>
<u n="335" who="S0474">when we do update though it means it's set at something and then if you change er time zone from then on it will change</u>
<u n="336" who="S0456">yeah but how did yours know?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0474">oh I dunno</u>
<u n="338" who="S0456">it was because it was on before you mean? <unclear/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0474">that's it yeah just go <unclear/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0456">it just hasn't got the time because I haven't done that ah should be okay <unclear/> certain time <pause dur="short"/> and the time is something <trunc>complet</trunc></u>
<u n="341" who="S0474">nineteen ninety-four</u>
<u n="342" who="S0456" trans="overlap">hang on even though I've done the times zone properly yeah and and thirty-four <unclear/> okay but that's what I mean even you didn't tell it what time zone it's in but it just got it straight away <pause dur="short"/> strange yeah that that looks</u>
<u n="343" who="S0474">looks cool I think</u>
<u n="344" who="S0456" trans="overlap">I just have to change the colour of these now</u>
<u n="345" who="S0474">what do you do about key lock then?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0456">I thought the key lock is this one</u>
<u n="347" who="S0474">no it's</u>
<u n="348" who="S0456" trans="overlap">but okay it doesn't look</u>
<u n="349" who="S0474">always the middle ones</u>
<u n="350" who="S0456">it automatically locks at some point</u>
<u n="351" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah oh you put yours on I've just put mine on now the minimum time you can have is ten seconds though <pause dur="short"/> so if you stop and wanna do that you <unclear>won't</unclear> have to wait before you put it <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0456">where did you do that then?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0474">go to settings erm down down down <pause dur="short"/> put</u>
<u n="354" who="S0456">feedback security costs phone settings</u>
<u n="355" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0456">key <unclear/> <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0474">key guard settings</u>
<u n="358" who="S0456">oh yeah there we go</u>
<u n="359" who="S0474">automatic key guard <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0456">oh I can go lower than this</u>
<u n="361" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah no you can't it won't let you it's a silly one they give you the option</u>
<u n="362" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's Finnish what do you expect? <pause dur="short"/> I don't use a code because I'm just gonna forget them <pause dur="short"/> okay back <unclear/> I wanted to turn my picture on so <pause dur="short"/> because then I can have <pause dur="long"/> I can have it upside oh <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0474">you can choose</u>
<u n="364" who="S0456">no</u>
<u n="365" who="S0474">that's</u>
<u n="366" who="S0456">okay so that's <unclear/> it is a bit more left than that <pause dur="short"/> I wonder whether let's <unclear>over there</unclear> you can do it only once</u>
<u n="367" who="S0474">were there any more at the bottom?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0456"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0474">yeah so</u>
<u n="370" who="S0456">you know I wanted it not ninety degrees but a hundred and eighty degrees</u>
<u n="371" who="S0474">so the red's at the top</u>
<u n="372" who="S0456">no the red is at the bottom <pause dur="short"/> well hard to <unclear>open it</unclear> now <pause dur="short"/> see so I have if the red is at the top</u>
<u n="373" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0456">then all of this shows ah it doesn't matter though does it? it's not my main phone anyway <pause dur="short"/> but this is this is brilliant because now as long as you have got something that just just this works almost like a a plug but</u>
<u n="375" who="S0474">why what is it? sorry <pause dur="short"/> oh you've got the <unclear/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0456" trans="overlap">right you know what happens you use this one</u>
<u n="377" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0456">and this is what you use here but you can slot it in</u>
<u n="379" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0456">screw this fast and then that I think fast is this <pause dur="short"/> spun <unclear/> see it's not just that the light wasn't working the light was actually missing and because this is earth it doesn't have to be much and because there's no earth in this one anyway so you have just these two I have that for my erm <pause dur="short"/> I think for my CD player <pause dur="short"/> and this is what you really wanted</u>
<u n="381" who="S0474" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="long"/> what's that? headphones?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0456">yeah I've got it as well</u>
<u n="383" who="S0474">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="384" who="S0456">yeah well they're very cheap that's these ones are the same ones that I've got for the small Ipod they keep falling out of my ears not my eyes <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> look what we've got we've got a mess of finger popping <unclear>items</unclear></u>
<u n="385" who="S0474">for what? oh I bet the recorder would love that <pause dur="short"/> new look you can have it this way if you want I think I prefer this kind of menu</u>
<u n="386" who="S0456">oh to <unclear>goo</unclear> yeah they they all start <unclear/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0474">yeah <pause dur="short"/> otherwise too many things confront you at the same time</u>
<u n="388" who="S0456">it's whatever turns you on it's your phone you can do whatever you like yeah no wonder you kept it outside it doesn't fit in here</u>
<u n="389" who="S0474">oh yeah that's the way it's meant to be</u>
<u n="390" who="S0456" trans="overlap">two sims and one sim and two sims oh it shows you what to do <pause dur="short"/> being extremely clever <pause dur="short"/> can still put your own phone on top <pause dur="long"/> the boxes have definitely shrunk haven't they? I remember my first thirty-one ten or whatever it was and the box was at least three times this size</u>
<u n="391" who="S0474">wow oh look you can er hold that down to change the sim</u>
<u n="392" who="S0456">ah see mine is to go straight to the radio <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> thinking I'll stop it now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0474">ah yeah I've got my torch</u>
<u n="394" who="S0456">what the shortcut you mean?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0456">you always had the torch</u>
<u n="397" who="S0474">do you wanna know what it is? yours might be the same up on your menu key <pause dur="short"/> oh that's great</u>
<u n="398" who="S0456">this one? <pause dur="short"/> but I have to</u>
<u n="399" who="S0474">yeah unlock it first</u>
<u n="400" who="S0456" trans="overlap"><unclear>make</unclear> it first <pause dur="short"/> do I have the <unclear/> okay so just up</u>
<u n="401" who="S0474">just press unlock first and then up yeah hold it a bit there you go you can let go now it'll stay on</u>
<u n="402" who="S0456">oh no it didn't <pause dur="short"/> oh see I can send signals what is it if I press it for if I press the whole if I press it down?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0474">no they all do different things</u>
<u n="404" who="S0456">does yours stay <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="405" who="S0474">oh no maybe it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah it does if you click it twice oh that's more</u>
<u n="406" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah double click</u>
<u n="407" who="S0474"><unclear/> than I thought and then I've got my calendar there messages there which is handy and contacts there</u>
<u n="408" who="S0456">yeah this is message this is calendar <pause dur="short"/> you have menu and then <unclear>camera</unclear> direct</u>
<u n="409" who="S0474">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0456">go on</u>
<u n="411" who="S0474">what do you want me to?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0456">you can take pictures of ours taking pictures</u>
<u n="413" who="S0474">oh okay</u>
<u n="414" who="S0456">so yours on the control <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="415" who="S0474" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0456"><unclear>the key</unclear></u>
<u n="417" who="S0474" trans="overlap">oh yeah I haven't seen my picture coming</u>
<u n="418" who="S0456">beep <pause dur="short"/> think you were moving thought I was moving try again one more</u>
<u n="419" who="S0474">okay I don't see what the point of this is it looks silly</u>
<u n="420" who="S0456">and stay</u>
<u n="421" who="S0474"><unclear/> you've still got your torch on you know</u>
<u n="422" who="S0456">oh</u>
<u n="423" who="S0474"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0456">well so we've got more lights</u>
<u n="425" who="S0474">can you take a picture of me with mine? in case I lock lock lose my phone people will know this is my phone</u>
<u n="426" who="S0456">yes <pause dur="short"/> they haven't got the best light here that's a shame smile <pause dur="short"/> not <unclear/> will be after this <pause dur="short"/> for his gallery of things that you've never seen before <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0474">how long do we do it for?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0456">ages</u>
<u n="429" who="S0474">really?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0456">yeah really</u>
<u n="431" who="S0474">well what about if we do it in like two different settings?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0456">you can we can do do two</u>
<u n="433" who="S0474" trans="overlap">that would be better cos</u>
<u n="434" who="S0456">recordings</u>
<u n="435" who="S0474">then the next one we'll have like a different topic</u>
<u n="436" who="S0456">yeah we can have a different topic you want to stop it here?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0474">yeah does it have to be a full hour? is that better? <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
