<text id="S6GC">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:38:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0083 S0085 S0086</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Walking, cycling, driving</topics>
		<activity>Family watching television, eating dinner, chatting.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0083">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Essex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0085">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cuckfield, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retail</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0086">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cuckfield, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0086">it's freezing <pause dur="short"/> super duper cold</u>
<u n="2" who="S0085">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0086">basically got home from work yesterday and was going come round then cos I didn't go to the gym yesterday</u>
<u n="4" who="S0085">oh right</u>
<u n="5" who="S0086">got home and I made the mistake of getting into bed</u>
<u n="6" who="S0085">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0086">and then didn't move for the entire evening <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of tv"/> Ha <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> is it good then? Smallville?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0085">I don't mind it</u>
<u n="9" who="S0086">the girl I used to live with was absolutely obsessed with it <pause dur="short"/> but I I just assumed it was sort of a girly programme</u>
<u n="10" who="S0085">no it's good <pause dur="short"/> anything with superman in it's going to be good</u>
<u n="11" who="S0086">so are you looking forward to the Avengers? That's not superman I know but it's all the rest isn't it?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0085" trans="overlap">it's not superman no <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was funny that all those different characters have all made individual films</u>
<u n="13" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0085">and then they thought oh we can make some more money and then put the all in the same film</u>
<u n="15" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't know if there was originally a marvel comic of the Avengers <pause dur="short"/> I presume there was</u>
<u n="16" who="S0085" trans="overlap">it's a <trunc>pre</trunc> it's quite a shocking thing to do <pause dur="short"/> there was yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0086">and that's why they're doing <pause dur="short"/> so it's not like they've just randomly plucked things out the air</u>
<u n="18" who="S0085" trans="overlap">but it's like they've got Iron Man that Thor <pause dur="short"/> all the actual people that made the film the actors in it they all got them all together <pause dur="short"/> I thought that was weird</u>
<u n="19" who="S0086" trans="overlap">I know it's good isn't it? They didn't get new actors you mean?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0085">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0086">well I suppose it's continuity in a way isn't it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0085">it is yeah <pause dur="short"/> it just surprised me that it came out so soon</u>
<u n="23" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh tired <pause dur="short"/> you alright dad?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there we go</u>
<u n="25" who="S0086">oh thank you <pause dur="short"/> I've stolen your seat</u>
<u n="26" who="S0083">it's alright no <pause dur="short"/> I wanted you to sit there</u>
<u n="27" who="S0086">oh thank you</u>
<u n="28" who="S0083">you haven't eaten have you?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="30" who="S0083">Cos I'm going to do some food</u>
<u n="31" who="S0086">what's on the menu?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0083">I'll just do some <trunc>chi</trunc> I've got some chicken so I'll do some chicken</u>
<u n="33" who="S0086">oh lovely <pause dur="short"/> how's your day been? So you no weren't weren't feeling very well yesterday?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0083">well it was <pause dur="short"/> eh was it yesterday? Monday <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was yesterday <pause dur="short"/> time time seems to go by rather strangely now for me <pause dur="short"/> you know sometimes it seems a long time ago and I think actually it was only yesterday and other times it's gone quickly</u>
<u n="35" who="S0086">when you're busy it goes quickly doesn't it? And you've <trunc>go</trunc> you are quite active</u>
<u n="36" who="S0083">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> now what happened <pause dur="short"/> erm I had every intention of doing that Reiki on Monday <pause dur="short"/> but I slept very badly <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why I kept waking up <pause dur="short"/> I mean I must have <trunc>wo</trunc> woken up I don't know four times <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> I mean I did go to sleep em but I kept waking up <pause dur="short"/> so I was tired <pause dur="short"/> but when I was asleep you know for the times I was asleep I must have slept the last sort of bout of sleep I must have slept awkwardly because when I got up not only was I very tired but I had backache</u>
<u n="37" who="S0086">oh no</u>
<u n="38" who="S0083">you know sometimes you sleep awkwardly sometimes you've got you know neck ache or sometimes you know if you were sleeping on your arm your arm hurts for a while</u>
<u n="39" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0083">em <pause dur="short"/> well I obviously slept in an awkward position for my back and the last thing you want to do if you got backache is go on a</u>
<u n="41" who="S0086">ten mile hike</u>
<u n="42" who="S0083">well not ten but <pause dur="short"/> six</u>
<u n="43" who="S0086">but even still</u>
<u n="44" who="S0083">yeah so I didn't bother <pause dur="short"/> and I looked I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I looked at the met office forecast yesterday I looked  I looked  at it for tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> thinking you know once I made my mind up I thought well I'd better just check and see what Wednesday is going to do <pause dur="short"/> and they said today it will be cold and less windy than yesterday <pause dur="short"/> and tomorrow it will be bright erm <trunc>wi</trunc> clouding over in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> but when I looked at it about ten minutes ago they say it's going to rain tomorrow</u>
<u n="45" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="46" who="S0083">so I'm really annoyed now cos I the last thing I want to do is do a Reiki in the rain <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know what to do I've <trunc>a</trunc> just have to wait and see <pause dur="short"/> unless you really want the car <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you want the car take it but</u>
<u n="47" who="S0086">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you're not taking it I'll do some food shopping after work but <pause dur="short"/> you'll be back by then anyway</u>
<u n="48" who="S0083">well trouble is I won't know whether I'm taking or not until tomorrow morning cos I don't know whether it's going to rain</u>
<u n="49" who="S0086">well this I mean and it's not a problem to me <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> whether I go food shopping tomorrow or Thursday</u>
<u n="50" who="S0083">yeah it's just  it's just  a nuisance really?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0086">it is a real annoyance <pause dur="short"/> it was a good job you didn't go walking yesterday though <pause dur="short"/> it was so cold</u>
<u n="52" who="S0083">it was cold <pause dur="short"/> eh it was the wind I think <pause dur="short"/> you know if you've got if you're not feeling all that good and it's a very cold wind <pause dur="short"/> eh you do actually feel very very bad when you're out walking cos there's nothing you can do to get warm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0083">erm I I mean a cold wind is bad enough if you're feeling fit <pause dur="short"/> because there's still nothing that you can do to keep warm but at least you don't feel too bad <pause dur="short"/> but if you're feeling you know if you've got something wrong and it's very very windy and cold then you really do notice it <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I'm I'm pleased I didn't go but it's just <pause dur="short"/> I could do I could have done with the sort of weather we've had today tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> cos it's it's you know it's alright or walking in this weather</u>
<u n="55" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah this weather's not very good <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0083">but the problem is you see I <pause dur="short"/> I'm doing a Reiki because last Wednesday I went with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do the same Reiki Because there were two of us I was talking <pause dur="short"/> and I thought well he's doing it anyway I'm just coming along you know keeping him company <pause dur="short"/> but unfortunately when we got about I don't know half the way round he was in a bit of a state</u>
<u n="57" who="S0086">oh really?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0083">not only has he got bad ankles</u>
<u n="59" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0083">but he's also got the first stages of diabetes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0086">oh has he? Oh gosh</u>
<u n="62" who="S0083">well it happens to a lot of people when they get older <pause dur="short"/> and he's over seventy now so erm erm <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="63" who="S0086">is that?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0083">and he was struggling a bit you know <pause dur="short"/> he brought stuff with him you know he brought glucose tablets and stuff to eat cos the thing you must do when when you erm have diabetes is have meals at the proper time</u>
<u n="65" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0083">eh cos if you don't you keel over <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> but he was in a bit of a state really <pause dur="short"/> so I said well I I you know <pause dur="short"/> I'll either do it all you know for you <pause dur="short"/> he said no I I <trunc>wa</trunc> want to come along <pause dur="short"/> so I said well okay fine but you know I'll if you want to stop at any time when you do the walk I'll take over</u>
<u n="67" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="68" who="S0083">which means that I've really got to know</u>
<u n="69" who="S0086">know where you're going</u>
<u n="70" who="S0083">Cos a lot of you know <pause dur="short"/> as I say the first half of the walk I wasn't really taking any notice <pause dur="short"/> and even the second half I wasn't I hadn't all thought it through really I just said oh I'll do it for you and then I suddenly thought when I got home actually I'd better make sure I know where I'm going <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've got it all written down erm but there's just a few places that I when I've looked at my notes I'm thinking do I actually remember where that is? And so</u>
<u n="71" who="S0086">and is that next Monday is it?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0083">yeah so I've got  I've got  my own one on Saturday that I'm leading</u>
<u n="73" who="S0086">oh blimey</u>
<u n="74" who="S0083">the one I've  The one I've  erm been</u>
<u n="75" who="S0086">planning for a while</u>
<u n="76" who="S0083">planning for for quite a while <pause dur="short"/> erm eh <pause dur="short"/> but I wouldn't come on that one if I were you because</u>
<u n="77" who="S0086">really? Because I was going to</u>
<u n="78" who="S0083">well you can  you can  but there's not there's no facilities anywhere <pause dur="short"/> see what I like to do is find somewhere we have a pub half way round <pause dur="short"/> there is a pub half way round but it's closed <pause dur="short"/> well not closed <pause dur="short"/> it's not open till</u>
<u n="79" who="S0086" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't open during the day?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0083">it's not open during the day <pause dur="short"/> which is a nuisance <pause dur="short"/> I thought well on a Saturday I thought it's bound to be open but it's not <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and I've got one coming up in April that I'm leading</u>
<u n="81" who="S0086">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0083">so that might be a better one <pause dur="short"/> there will definitely be somewhere to you know stop off go use the loos and all that stuff</u>
<u n="83" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0083">so it might be better to wait until April actually <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm slightly annoyed with <pause dur="short"/> I mean the walk I'm doing on Saturday comes out of the book <pause dur="short"/> not not one of our books but the <anon type="place"/> group <pause dur="short"/> and they say that there are two pubs on the route <pause dur="short"/> erm but of course erm pubs close <pause dur="short"/> so so erm one is closed and one got fire damaged I think</u>
<u n="85" who="S0086" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh no</u>
<u n="86" who="S0083">so <pause dur="short"/> and it's one of these funny walks that erm when you sort of get to sort of place where you can have <trunc>lun</trunc> you know in terms of time em there's nothing there <pause dur="short"/> so I'm hoping it's going to be a <trunc>mi</trunc> a mildish day <pause dur="short"/> I mean when I did the last Reiki it was great <pause dur="short"/> I mean a couple of weeks ago er we had a sort of a mild period and it was dry and it was great cos I just sat under a tree and ate ate my sandwiches <pause dur="short"/> but of course if it's  if it's  pouring with rain or blowing a gale it's the last thing you want really</u>
<u n="87" who="S0086" trans="overlap">ah nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's that just unpredictability of the good old British weather <pause dur="short"/> I suppose you're all quite hardy <pause dur="short"/> I mean no one wants to walk in the rain but at least you're all quite prepared for it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean well you do get a cross section of people that you know <pause dur="short"/> particularly in spring time when people start thinking oh I'd better do something <pause dur="short"/> like last year I mean this one's a bit earlier than the one last year <pause dur="short"/> one was at the end of March last year <pause dur="short"/> whereas this one is the tenth <pause dur="short"/> but I still think we're going to get people that come out thinking oh you know</u>
<u n="89" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> spring's in the air</u>
<u n="90" who="S0083">I'll eh I'll do more  I'll do more  Yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0086">although this week has been cold <pause dur="short"/> you know like you were saying last week or the week before it was quite mild wasn't it?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping that might put people off for a bit cos it you know it's <pause dur="short"/> because I  Because I  couldn't do a Reiki before Christmas and then we had all that cold weather in February <pause dur="short"/> it's all caught me off guard this thing really</u>
<u n="93" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0083">and it's slightly annoying cos I like my walks to be good <pause dur="short"/> you know I I like  I like I like  to feel myself that I've actually given them their money's worth <pause dur="short"/> even though they're they're not  they're not  paying anything <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but I <pause dur="short"/> I just feel this walk is a bit of a not quite what I want it to be</u>
<u n="95" who="S0086">is the route nice though?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0083">no <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Right</u>
<u n="98" who="S0083">well it's it's not actually <anon type="place"/> as such but it's going on to be <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's Lord  estate so you remember I told you?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0086">oh yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0083">Lord <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0086">hasn't he got thirty-two thousand acres or something?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0083">I've I've obviously chosen a few acres that are not too interesting <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's some woodland there <pause dur="short"/> erm I mean if this pub had been open it would've been much it would have actually made it a decent sort of walk because you know alright you get there quite quickly and you know like and <pause dur="short"/> if it was open I might have found the detour or something so we didn't get there before twelve thirty but but erm erm <pause dur="short"/> it's not going to be so there's no point in adding extra <pause dur="short"/> I don't think there is any extra</u>
<u n="103" who="S0086">well especially if there are no facilities at all you kind of want to have a shorter walk don't you <pause dur="short"/> you don't want to be going all day if there's nowhere to you know have comfort breaks</u>
<u n="104" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> well that's that's what I was thinking so <pause dur="short"/> what I don't know is whether <pause dur="short"/> I phoned the woman in the pub and she said they're not open <pause dur="short"/> I presume that all the erm you know loos and things are locked up <pause dur="short"/> some of these old country pubs have their loos out the back <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/> I mean a lot of them don't these days <pause dur="short"/> cos you've got restaurants they're all inside</u>
<u n="105" who="S0086">yeah it would make sense to</u>
<u n="106" who="S0083">erm <pause dur="short"/> so it will all be locked up <pause dur="short"/> it's just such a nuisance <pause dur="short"/> all out in the open</u>
<u n="107" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="108" who="S0083">it's just a nuisance that's all</u>
<u n="109" who="S0086">yum <pause dur="short"/> I love dinner</u>
<u n="110" who="S0083">I'll put this light on so we can see what we're doing</u>
<u n="111" who="S0086">can I have that water please <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? It's for me rather than dad <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> yum <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0083">how's work <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? Busy at the moment?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0086">it's good yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really busy <pause dur="short"/> did I tell you that my boss is going to New York?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0086">so Friday is her last day</u>
<u n="116" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0086">so I've already taken over a couple of her projects <pause dur="short"/> it's starting to get busy with my own so <pause dur="short"/> but that's fine I like it to be busy <pause dur="short"/> it's better that way</u>
<u n="118" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> time goes quicker</u>
<u n="119" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's nice to feel involved <pause dur="short"/> so yeah it's going  it's going  okay <pause dur="short"/> I still quite like it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's difficult to know really <pause dur="short"/> it seems quite an exciting time to work at the press cos it's everything's sort of changing</u>
<u n="120" who="S0083">yes</u>
<u n="121" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0083">I've got another eh update from uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh the story</u>
<u n="123" who="S0086">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> is that just him rewriting or is it on the advice of others?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0083">no I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had a look at it <pause dur="short"/> and he's  And he's  altered a few things</u>
<u n="125" who="S0086">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to have a look</u>
<u n="126" who="S0083">I said to him I'd have a look and I haven't got round to it yet</u>
<u n="127" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0083">I'm gonna  I'm gonna  print I can't remember how many pages? Is it seventy pages someone said?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0086">yeah it's long</u>
<u n="130" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0086">I can do it at work and bring you round a copy <pause dur="short"/> if you email me the latest version <pause dur="short"/> save your printing paper</u>
<u n="132" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah I was thinking of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> having a look as well</u>
<u n="133" who="S0085">no good</u>
<u n="134" who="S0083">no? Have you read it?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0085">no I didn't mean it's no good <pause dur="short"/> I meant I'm not good <pause dur="short"/> I don't read books so I'm not going to be able to say</u>
<u n="136" who="S0086" trans="overlap">I was gonna say that's quite harsh</u>
<u n="137" who="S0085">yeah I didn't mean that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0086">no good <pause dur="short"/> that's the official critic</u>
<u n="139" who="S0085">I'm sure it's very good but I'm just saying that I know nothing about things like that</u>
<u n="140" who="S0083">Don't forget it's written from the point of view of somebody that makes films <pause dur="short"/> and you watch a lot of films so</u>
<u n="141" who="S0085">yeah but I think most films are rubbish</u>
<u n="142" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> you can always read the first page and see how you go <pause dur="short"/> it might really grip you</u>
<u n="143" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0086">yeah I'm definitely going to have to get round to that</u>
<u n="145" who="S0085">I just meant my my opinion's not worth anything</u>
<u n="146" who="S0083">why not?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0085">Cos I don't read</u>
<u n="148" who="S0083">but that's not <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's whether it the story appeals to you on the as I say on the basis that it started off as an idea for a film</u>
<u n="149" who="S0085">yeah but stories that appeal to a lot of other people don't appeal to me so it's not <pause dur="short"/> if you said well this this thing doesn't appeal to me that's no indication of anything <pause dur="short"/> because nothing appeals to me <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't go changing it thinking oh this isn't appealing like</u>
<u n="150" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0085">you still got echoes on it?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0086">yeah it's rubbish <pause dur="short"/> but Vodaphone are getting a new one to me</u>
<u n="153" who="S0085" trans="overlap">get a new one</u>
<u n="154" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0085">let me keep that one</u>
<u n="156" who="S0086">you have to give it back sadly</u>
<u n="157" who="S0085">damn</u>
<u n="158" who="S0083">it's got echoes nobody will be able to hear what <pause dur="short"/> well that that actually <pause dur="short"/> they can hear themselves but they can't hear you that's the problem <pause dur="short"/> you can hear the echo but you can't</u>
<u n="159" who="S0086">and you can't hear me?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0083">well when <pause dur="short"/> the last time I spoke to you I couldn't hear you at all</u>
<u n="161" who="S0086">oh yeah you just yeah that was a bit of a</u>
<u n="162" who="S0083">I could just hear the echo <pause dur="short"/> and the strange thing was I thought I had a crossed line because I didn't realise that my voice is so much like uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> I just sounded like I was speaking to uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0083">but unless he was repeating exactly the same the words that I was using it was actually my voice</u>
<u n="165" who="S0086">how funny <pause dur="short"/> it used to be I think <pause dur="short"/> you know obviously it's a family thing but <pause dur="short"/> I know when erm people used to call me at the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos before mobile phones or if if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used used to answer if mum answered they would start speaking to them as if it were me cos we always sound the same on the phone</u>
<u n="166" who="S0083">well I'm I'm getting so bad at at recognising people's voices that the other day when I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> after this you know sort of I when he had a rather nasty turn after we did the Reiki I phoned him that evening actually to make sure he was okay <pause dur="short"/> and his wife answered the phone his wife's called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> but she's got quite a deep voice for a woman and I thought it was him <pause dur="short"/> cos he hasn't got a high voice for a man but sometimes his voice sounds a bit high pitched occasionally</u>
<u n="167" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="168" who="S0083">so I'm terrible at the moment <pause dur="short"/> well probably from now on</u>
<u n="169" who="S0086">I'm tired with the phone <pause dur="short"/> now that I've been recording all the conversations and playing them back I can hear my own voice <pause dur="short"/> cos you have to fill in an accompanying recording sheet that says that gives the first line of what people say and what was discussed <pause dur="short"/> you know like a brief overview <pause dur="short"/> and I can hear my voice and I just think it sounds so common</u>
<u n="170" who="S0083">right our voice never sounds the way we think it sounds</u>
<u n="171" who="S0086" trans="overlap">most people said that <pause dur="short"/> no it's funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0085">that's why it's best not to record yourself</u>
<u n="173" who="S0086">well no one's going to hear it really <pause dur="short"/> in fact no one is going to hear it apart from the person</u>
<u n="174" who="S0085">no but I I wouldn't want to listen to myself back <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't enjoy that at all</u>
<u n="175" who="S0086" trans="overlap">I find it hilarious <pause dur="short"/> cos I sit in the office filling in this sheet before I submit it and I find myself giggling away <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm quite funny <pause dur="short"/> I had to leave one of them the other day cos mum was telling me all about you know her friend <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> </u>
<u n="176" who="S0083">yes</u>
<u n="177" who="S0086">all about his new story</u>
<u n="178" who="S0083">oh right</u>
<u n="179" who="S0086">but it's all a bit hush hush so I had to delete it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0083">yeah under wraps yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> she suddenly realised I was recording it she was like quick delete it delete it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0085">yeah but what's going to happen <pause dur="short"/> someone at your work is going to steal his idea or something?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0086">well yeah no <pause dur="short"/> it's just at that early stage where they don't anything <pause dur="short"/> it's all a bit</u>
<u n="184" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0086">oh yum yum yum <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so when is erm <pause dur="short"/> was it the woman from the church who's doing the the Bach recital? Or the woman from the shop?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0083">the shop <pause dur="short"/> she's in the choir</u>
<u n="187" who="S0086">the <anon type="place"/> whatever it is</u>
<u n="188" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I might get tickets but I keep forgetting to look on the website <pause dur="short"/> I don't like buying tickets on the website <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping you can buy them there because cos it's it's called the <anon type="place"/> Concert Hall</u>
<u n="189" who="S0086">well you could always give them a ring and see if you can pop by one one day <pause dur="short"/> or pay for I over the phone and go and collect them</u>
<u n="190" who="S0083">that's what I don't  That's what I don't  like doing it</u>
<u n="191" who="S0086">you don't want to do it over the phone either <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="192" who="S0083">I don't trust it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0083">I don't trust machines with my details and I certainly don't people with it</u>
<u n="195" who="S0086">right good</u>
<u n="196" who="S0085">you're more likely to have someone steal your details in person</u>
<u n="197" who="S0086">mm yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0085">than over the phone or the internet</u>
<u n="199" who="S0086">no you're not are you?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well you're more likely to have someone steal your details over the phone rather than</u>
<u n="201" who="S0085" trans="overlap">you are <pause dur="short"/> apparently statistically more people will steal you details in person than over the phone</u>
<u n="202" who="S0083" trans="overlap">how can they do that?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0086">how is that possible if you went it to a bank?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0085">happened to Mum</u>
<u n="205" who="S0083">oh yeah I see what you mean yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you give your cards</u>
<u n="206" who="S0085">people will take them in shops in restaurants</u>
<u n="207" who="S0086">yeah but that's why you can't let your card out of your sight</u>
<u n="208" who="S0083" trans="overlap">you should never let it out of your sight yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0085">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but what what <pause dur="short"/> the point I was trying to make is you would think oh it's much safer if it's with me whereas a lot of the time unless you're careful it's less safe</u>
<u n="210" who="S0083">yes you must never let it out of your sight <pause dur="short"/> whatever they say</u>
<u n="211" who="S0085">Cos the internet is is pretty safe if you use the right sites</u>
<u n="212" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you just have  you just have  to be a bit savvy</u>
<u n="213" who="S0085">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0083">yeah I think it's the that that's the point <trunc>u</trunc> using the right sites</u>
<u n="215" who="S0086" trans="overlap">it's being secure whatever you're doing</u>
<u n="216" who="S0085">and if if you buy stuff from Amazon even though I don't like doing it I'm sure it's probably one of the safest sites that you can use</u>
<u n="217" who="S0086">oh it absolutely is yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0083">because em all their</u>
<u n="219" who="S0086">billions of people use it every day</u>
<u n="220" who="S0083">all all the security they have <pause dur="short"/> I mean if they got a bad name people people being you know having their information duplicated</u>
<u n="221" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0083">Amazon would go out of business</u>
<u n="223" who="S0086">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I did write a really strongly worded email today <pause dur="short"/> I requested my credit rating a couple of weeks ago because I wanted to speak to HSBC about getting an <unclear/> overdraft <pause dur="short"/> it's all a bit by the by now because I've been doing these recordings it's going to help me pay off the little debt that I had so I'm going to be okay</u>
<u n="224" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0085">what they pay you to do it?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0085">nice <pause dur="short"/> where's our cut then?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0086">I'll bring you round some biscuits</u>
<u n="229" who="S0085">nice</u>
<u n="230" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but I requested it and it didn't didn't make any sense <pause dur="short"/> and there's no phone number that you can call you have to email or write a letter</u>
<u n="231" who="S0083">I know it's it's awful isn't it?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that was about two months ago and they've just finally sent me and email saying what was your query no we can't call you back <pause dur="short"/> and I said it's <trunc>ridi</trunc> absolutely ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> I just want them to explain because on your credit rating they give you like a status history of reach of the accounts that you've ever had credit with <pause dur="short"/> and I've never had a credit card but I have had erm mobile phone accounts and once I had a New Look card when I worked in New Look <pause dur="short"/> and obviously that's all paid off Vodaphone is on-going <pause dur="short"/> and there's a series of numbers next to your status history but it doesn't tell you what the numbers denote so then I couldn't understand <pause dur="short"/> erm and I I can't find it anywhere <pause dur="short"/> and they just the details they give you of Vodaphone erm are just some P O box somewhere <pause dur="short"/> so you don't feel confident that if you've contacted the they would even know</u>
<u n="233" who="S0083">there's erm there's something on the internet I can't think of the name now which gives you your credit sort of history and credit rating</u>
<u n="234" who="S0086">yeah it's your credit money <trunc>ex</trunc> credit experts</u>
<u n="235" who="S0083">is it <trunc>app</trunc> apperion apperion or something?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0086">experian</u>
<u n="237" who="S0083">experian</u>
<u n="238" who="S0086">that's who I went with <pause dur="short"/> so Experian actually have sold on the <trunc>r</trunc> that that on to the credit expert <pause dur="short"/> it's all sort of linked</u>
<u n="239" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0086">so you can you don't have to set up and account with them you can just request it for two pounds which is what I did but then you're not given any sort of support <pause dur="short"/> whereas if you go through with a credit expert you have to pay a monthly fee but they explain everything to you and it I think it probably is a bit more detailed <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0083" trans="overlap">more <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it depends on how A on the one hand necessary</u>
<u n="242" who="S0086">exactly</u>
<u n="243" who="S0083">or if it's not necessary how eager you are to find out about your credit history cos</u>
<u n="244" who="S0086">they say that you should do it every year don't they?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0083">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0086">but it was more because before I went travelling I applied for a credit card and was declined <pause dur="short"/> and I wanted to know why that was because there's obviously something on there that's a problem <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to check that before I applied for anything with HSBC to help me clear my overdraft <pause dur="short"/> but as I said that probably shouldn't be an issue now</u>
<u n="247" who="S0083">alright good <pause dur="short"/> that's good <pause dur="short"/> so have you got your bike back?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0083">oh right <pause dur="short"/> it's still there</u>
<u n="250" who="S0086">they had to order in the forks</u>
<u n="251" who="S0083">and they're waiting for them to come in are they?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0086">yeah so I've still got the courtesy bike which is a nightmare not having any gears</u>
<u n="253" who="S0083">no <pause dur="short"/> it's very hard work going anywhere isn't it when you've only got one? Having said that I was gonna I might have mentioned this before so forgive name but I'll say it again just in case I didn't <pause dur="short"/> when I worked in the city now and again I used to see couriers <pause dur="short"/> there weren't many people at the time I worked in the city who rode bicycles <pause dur="short"/> but own and again you'd see a <trunc>s</trunc> a bicycle courier like you get a motorcycle courier or or a car courier <pause dur="short"/> and then places where there's lots of traffic you know motor eh motor sorry say that again cycle couriers make more sense because they can zip in and out <pause dur="short"/> and erm because I'm interested in bicycles when I first noticed them cos they often had bags on their backs saying you know X Y Z courier company or X Y Z bike courier or something <pause dur="short"/> erm because I'm interested in bikes I sort of noticed them and I noticed the bikes that they were riding <pause dur="short"/> this was I don't know ten years plus ago <pause dur="short"/> and they were all erm the sort of light weight bikes with lots of gears as you would expect <pause dur="short"/> erm but suddenly erm probably a couple of years before I retired so about erm what was that about nine years ago erm I noticed that they'd all gone on to single gear bikes <pause dur="short"/> erm and instead of being sort of the handle bars that dropped down they were  they were  flat <pause dur="short"/> but instead of being the handle you know I mean <trunc>nor</trunc> normally when you're on a bike unless it's a erm a fold away bike which is often smaller and <trunc>l</trunc> and got less space <pause dur="short"/> erm but normally a straight handlebars are there aren't they you know about the width of your shoulders or maybe wider <pause dur="short"/> whereas these were much <trunc>narro</trunc> you know they were straight but they were much narrower <pause dur="short"/> and they had this erm single cog and it was almost as if the courier industry had suddenly made a a decision for the whole of itself because from that moment on and probably it's because I hadn't taken notice I mean I don't go and look at bikes all the time <pause dur="short"/> every time I saw a courier cyclist after that they all seemed to I think all of them I don't think I see saw another one with lots of gears they all seemed to have these single gears <pause dur="short"/> and what I noticed after a while is that they're all what's called fixed wheel <pause dur="short"/> in other words you know when you just think oh I'll stop peddling now so you stop peddling <pause dur="short"/> well that's because you've got a free wheel bike <pause dur="short"/> whether it's got twenty-seven gears or whether it's got one gear if you can stop peddling it's a free wheel <pause dur="short"/> a fixed wheel means that the cog at the back is fixed to the wheel erm in in the way I mean they they're all fixed to the wheel eh anyway but <pause dur="short"/> fixed to the wheel in in the sense that it won't eh allow you to stop peddling <pause dur="short"/> okay? And the reason people have them is because although they're a nightmare to get going cos they us very small cogs at the back and very big chain reels at the front <pause dur="short"/> although you've got to really and you see these guys you know really fit guys really sort of having to do all this <pause dur="short"/> once you get going erm the fact that the peddle come it's almost as if once you get going both you and the bike are taking the strain of it because the pedal is coming up without you pushing it down because the momentum of the bicycle is pushing the pedals round <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is you can't stop peddling because if it does if you do it throws you off you know</u>
<u n="254" who="S0086">oh my god</u>
<u n="255" who="S0083">well because it's going on that all the time you know because if you suddenly oh I've had enough of this and and suddenly you know your your leg will come up when you're not expecting it to</u>
<u n="256" who="S0086">sounds very dangerous very strange idea <unclear/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0083">I mean they've had them for years I mean when bikes were first invented that's all they were <pause dur="short"/> because em if you think of the penny farthing which was one of the first bikes I mean apart from the ones that they just had wheels and scooted along <pause dur="short"/> but erm the first proper bike was a penny farthing I should think <pause dur="short"/> and if you think about it it had this huge wheel on the front with pedals fixed you know little pedals fixed to the wheel so therefore you had to keep peddling because if you stopped peddling the pedals kept going <pause dur="short"/> and the same thing happened it would throw you off <pause dur="short"/> so originally all bikes as far as I'm aware were fixed wheel <pause dur="short"/> and then you know somebody came up with the idea of putting ball bearings in and what the ball bearings do is that they go they fit them all the way round the cog at the back</u>
<u n="258" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0083">which means that em eh once you stop peddling the wheel keeps going round back wheel keeps going round but the cog stays still because the ball bearings in the centre are spinning round okay?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="261" who="S0083">and then when you pedal again em it picks up the momentum <pause dur="short"/> well fixed wheels don't have those ball bearings in the centre <pause dur="short"/> eh they just have eh a fixed cog <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I just <pause dur="short"/> the whole point of that story is that suddenly when I <trunc>s</trunc> noticed one of these em bikes with only one cog eh for couriers I didn't see any others <pause dur="short"/> every time I saw a courier they had one of these bikes and now that what was that? Seven years no longer nine years ago <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> again if I go to the city of London it's all the same they're all  they're all  riding bikes with narrow straight handle bars and erm and and fixed wheels on them <pause dur="short"/> I mean some have got dropped handle bars but the majority of them have got narrow straight handle bars</u>
<u n="262" who="S0086">like my bike</u>
<u n="263" who="S0083">like yours yeah but narrower than yours</u>
<u n="264" who="S0086">but narrower yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't like the sound of it to be honest <pause dur="short"/> I think it sounds quite dangerous because if you if you're slowing down for example if you're coming up to traffic lights or something</u>
<u n="265" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well that's the other thing you don't need a back break</u>
<u n="266" who="S0086">okay yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0083">you only need one break</u>
<u n="268" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that is dangerous having</u>
<u n="269" who="S0083">because you you can control the back wheel by peddling slower <pause dur="short"/> I mean you can't stop peddling</u>
<u n="270" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="271" who="S0083">straight away I mean you can eventually obviously because you can come to a stand still</u>
<u n="272" who="S0086">but you have to slow yourself</u>
<u n="273" who="S0083">but when the bike moves the peddles move <pause dur="short"/> because the chain is driving it because the the cog on the back is fixed</u>
<u n="274" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0083">em so <pause dur="short"/> if you  If you  you know cos you need to be sort of a healthy sort of you know eh guy <pause dur="short"/> if you decide you're going to stop eh you know in twenty yards time you just slow down the rate of peddling and apply the front break</u>
<u n="276" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="277" who="S0083">but it is <trunc>dan</trunc> you got to <pause dur="short"/> I mean it is for people that really know what they're doing and it's really <pause dur="short"/> I I wouldn't like one</u>
<u n="278" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> and you'd have to be careful changing from a free wheel to a fixed because you you'd forget</u>
<u n="279" who="S0083">you can get yourself into a  You can get yourself into a  lot of trouble if you're not careful</u>
<u n="280" who="S0086">yeah it would throw you off</u>
<u n="281" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0086">I don't know why <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I mean in in you know I mean being thrown off along a country lane is one thing <pause dur="short"/> you might do yourself a lot of damage but eh the chances of you being run over are <trunc>pre</trunc> pretty slim but</u>
<u n="284" who="S0086" trans="overlap">get run over</u>
<u n="285" who="S0083">but you know being thrown off in the city of London is probably certain death I should think</u>
<u n="286" who="S0086">absolutely</u>
<u n="287" who="S0083">there's cars everywhere</u>
<u n="288" who="S0086">I couldn't imagine anything more scary <pause dur="short"/> well no that's no true obviously but it's so scary cycling in London <pause dur="short"/> although I'd never do it</u>
<u n="289" who="S0083">oh it is cos there are very few lanes and cars are not used to seeing cyclists and they just ignore them really <pause dur="short"/> I mean they never look for cyclists</u>
<u n="290" who="S0086">never look no</u>
<u n="291" who="S0083">and it's always not always but the majority of I mean the I can't remember now how many people get killed in London every year who are riding bikes but it's a huge amount</u>
<u n="292" who="S0086">it's a lot actually</u>
<u n="293" who="S0083">and invariably it's because eh the driver of the usually lorry eh hasn't seen the cyclist cos you know the cyclist is too close or too near or he's one the wrong side</u>
<u n="294" who="S0086">they never check their wing mirrors</u>
<u n="295" who="S0083">well if they do they erm you know the wing mirrors only show the the eh erm view erm eh that's that's behind them well a lot of that view if you look in the mirror is going to be the lorry itself <pause dur="short"/> you know because the lorry's are very long erm <pause dur="short"/> and so therefore if you want to be seem you've got to be one side you know quite distinctly one side or the other side <pause dur="short"/> or miles behind it so that that driver can see you behind the back of his lorry</u>
<u n="296" who="S0086">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="297" who="S0083">erm erm but it's things like roundabouts where eh lorries can't see you <pause dur="short"/> and sometimes you know a cyclist can be going around a roundabout if if a cyclist has come out of a cycle lane and a car will just whizz you know how quickly cars go round roundabouts <pause dur="short"/> a car will just whizz round and knock the cyclist off because he's just going too fast <pause dur="short"/> and that's often what happens <pause dur="short"/> you know people people get killed on roundabouts quite a lot</u>
<u n="298" who="S0086">scary isn't it? I mean cyclist don't necessarily help themselves you know with the the cyclist who died recently was squashed by a lorry because they were turning left at traffic lights <pause dur="short"/> the cyclist crept up the side erm while the lights were on red and the lorry didn't look and the cyclist was too close and she died because she was too close <pause dur="short"/> and you think actually that's in <trunc>r</trunc> in <anon type="place"/> you know  you know  to always check your wing mirrors all the time especially when you're taking a corner because you just don't know</u>
<u n="299" who="S0083">or if you're a cyclist you have to assume that the lorry is not going to therefore stay behind it don't don't get up the side of it</u>
<u n="300" who="S0086">exactly <pause dur="short"/> cos it might cos lots of people actually you know rubbish drivers they will not indicate until it's green <pause dur="short"/> so they won't sit there with their indicators on</u>
<u n="301" who="S0083">no absolutely</u>
<u n="302" who="S0086">they'll indicate when they can move</u>
<u n="303" who="S0083">or not at all</u>
<u n="304" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or not at all</u>
<u n="305" who="S0083">erm <pause dur="short"/> but the other thing eh that happens is erm that a cyclist will come up to a lorry waiting at the lights and will think ah I'll get a long the inside and the difficulty of the cyclist is knowing when the lights are going to change <pause dur="short"/> I mean if the light's red it might have been red for a second or it might have been red for five <trunc>min</trunc> well not five minutes but it might have been red for a minute</u>
<u n="306" who="S0086" trans="overlap">couple of minutes yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0083">so if you're  if you're  going along the side and suddenly they turn green and a lorry moves <pause dur="short"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> you're going to get squashed</u>
<u n="308" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="309" who="S0083">so it's always better to hold back</u>
<u n="310" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I do</u>
<u n="311" who="S0083">unless unless you can  unless you can  see you know that the lights have just changed</u>
<u n="312" who="S0086">just literally yeah <pause dur="short"/> literally changed</u>
<u n="313" who="S0083">you know literally changed to red so you can get down there before and get in front of the lorry <pause dur="short"/> so that the lorry driver can see you rather than up the side of it</u>
<u n="314" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you just <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah you just wouldn't take the risk would you?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0083">no no</u>
<u n="316" who="S0086">it's too dangerous</u>
<u n="317" who="S0083">it's far too dangerous no <pause dur="short"/> and it and the other thing is you know driver's a careless they don't look they don't signal <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> they</u>
<u n="318" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> just so much traffic <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> you'd think in this day and age you know post erm the July bombings there's been a massive surge of people on bikes in London hasn't there? Because people didn't want to take the tube <pause dur="short"/> you think given that  given that  there are so many more bikes on the road not like <anon type="place"/> but still there's a lot of them <pause dur="short"/> you'd think that people would be more aware of them but I guess that's changing their minds that they're not expecting to see lots of cyclists</u>
<u n="319" who="S0083">and and drivers are in a hurry</u>
<u n="320" who="S0086">and there's just so much traffic</u>
<u n="321" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> drivers are in a hurry they're you know they it's usually a rush hour accident isn't it? You know they're they're either going to work or coming home from work <pause dur="short"/> the driver either wants to get there or get home <pause dur="short"/> he's not thinking he's just thinking about getting home and eh doing all the things he normally does in relation to other motor vehicles but forgetting to take the extra care for someone that's on two wheels <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I mean it's just <pause dur="short"/> I mean I as I said to you when we spoke about this before <pause dur="short"/> really if we're going to cure this problem we need to do what Holland you know the Netherlands did twenty thirty years ago <pause dur="short"/> and just change all the laws and put in cycle lanes everywhere eh and make it clear that drivers will lose their license immediately you know that if if a cyclist is injured the <trunc>dr</trunc> the driver will lose his license <pause dur="short"/> if it's proven that the cyclist eh you know caused the accident or there was you know some doubt or whatever then obviously the license may come back <pause dur="short"/> but unless you're really strict with drivers all this will still go on because they just don't care <pause dur="short"/> most a lot of them don't care <pause dur="short"/> you know and particularly bus drivers don't seem to care at all</u>
<u n="322" who="S0086">and taxi drivers</u>
<u n="323" who="S0083">so again with bus drivers the thing to do because they rely on it for their living is you know make them forfeit their licence</u>
<u n="324" who="S0086">absolutely</u>
<u n="325" who="S0083">Cos then they wouldn't wouldn't be able to drive <pause dur="short"/> but erm unless something like that happens then and and it won't because you know this country they won't spend any money doing things like that</u>
<u n="326" who="S0086">no way</u>
<u n="327" who="S0083">then the <trunc>situa</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> and people will complain about it isn't it terrible but nothing will happen <pause dur="short"/> I mean the <anon type="place"/> cycling campaign has done a lot of good work but that's because <anon type="place"/> has always had a lot of cycles in the city you know from the undergraduates and the workforce you know in the  in the  nineteen well up until the nineteen sixties and seventies <pause dur="short"/> you know workers cycled cos they couldn't afford cars <pause dur="short"/> or they walked <pause dur="short"/> erm and eh students erm did the same cos students didn't have cars in those days <pause dur="short"/> very few of them did <pause dur="short"/> so you know <anon type="place"/> and all university cities have kept the cycle as being a prime use of of you know a prime type of transport <pause dur="short"/> but in other cities since the nineteen sixties and seventies where there's people who have moved up form walking or cycling to cars</u>
<u n="328" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0083">they don't have the same erm understanding about cyclists</u>
<u n="330" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a worry</u>
<u n="331" who="S0083">so yeah so it is <trunc>dan</trunc> I mean it is dangerous even in <anon type="place"/> but it's far more dangerous in other cities <pause dur="short"/> far more</u>
<u n="332" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> where motorists just aren't expecting to see cyclists</u>
<u n="333" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> very very dangerous</u>
<u n="334" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0083">so not worth it <pause dur="short"/> anyway have a seat over there I'm going to sit over here for a while</u>
<u n="336" who="S0086">well no you sit on that chair dad</u>
<u n="337" who="S0083">no no I'm going to sit on eh this chair cos eh otherwise if I sit in front of the television I tend to doze off so</u>
<u n="338" who="S0086">right then shall we watch some Lost?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0086">unless you're really keen on watching erm Smelly Oaks</u>
<u n="341" who="S0083">I'm going to get myself and apple <pause dur="short"/> is anybody want any?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0086">oh an apple would be nice thanks dad <pause dur="short"/> to improve my one a day <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> apple?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0085">no</u>
<u n="344" who="S0086">really? Think of your insides</u>
<u n="345" who="S0085">no</u>
<u n="346" who="S0086">your poor little insides <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I went to gig last week did she tell you?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0085">no</u>
<u n="348" who="S0086">we went to see Laura Marling <pause dur="short"/> sort of like a folk singer <pause dur="short"/> we went to the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> it was really good <pause dur="short"/> but because it's sort of guitar slow folky acoustic stuff it's really nice but standing up for four hours just sort of swaying a bit</u>
<u n="349" who="S0085">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0086">I was so tired by the end <pause dur="short"/> it was good though <pause dur="short"/> it made me realise I don't see much live music anymore <pause dur="short"/> have you been down to the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0085">no not in a while?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's all a bit hit and miss in there isn't it?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0085">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0086">what about <anon type="place"/> you used to go there didn't you?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0085">yeah it's closed</u>
<u n="356" who="S0086">has it actually closed?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0085">you been you live on that road <pause dur="short"/> have you not seen it? It's boarded up</u>
<u n="358" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0085">no not <anon type="place"/> I'm thinking of what's the one I'm thinking of?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0085">yeah that's that one <pause dur="short"/> it's boarded up</u>
<u n="362" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know that's closed</u>
<u n="363" who="S0085">no I don't ever go to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/> was good I don't understand they really they revamped it</u>
<u n="365" who="S0085">yeah they redid it and then closed it straight away</u>
<u n="366" who="S0086" trans="overlap">and closed it down <pause dur="short"/> which is weird and it's still got a sign on it to let <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0085">what are we on twenty-one?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0086">are we <pause dur="short"/> ooh thanks dad <pause dur="short"/> is that what we were on?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0083">twenty-one <pause dur="short"/> yeah we were quite a way through</u>
<u n="370" who="S0086">nearly finished</u>
<u n="371" who="S0085">no we watched that one</u>
<u n="372" who="S0086">the Greater Good yeah we did watch that one <pause dur="short"/> so we're on twenty-two?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0085">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="374" who="S0086">who's your favourite character dad?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0083">erm I like Hurley</u>
<u n="376" who="S0086">hurley yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0085">Jacob is by far the best character</u>
<u n="378" who="S0083">yeah but he's not in it very much</u>
<u n="379" who="S0086">yeah but he he doesn't come in till the end</u>
<u n="380" who="S0085">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but he is the best character</u>
</body>
</text>
