<text id="S6J2">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:09:22</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Men, health, food </topics>
		<activity>Friends eating dinner, chatting.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0084">you don't want to be reminded of the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know if I get rid of it whether I'll regret it</u>
<u n="3" who="S0084">we <pause dur="short"/> I mean it <pause dur="short"/> you know box it up and keep it at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> if there's no worry about space issues just keep it and see how you feel when you actually have a place of your own</u>
<u n="4" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0084">there's no point making hasty decisions about stuff like that</u>
<u n="6" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this one's a good one <pause dur="short"/> that's got the pictures in</u>
<u n="7" who="S0084">pictures of what?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0041">just pictures I've painted or drawn</u>
<u n="9" who="S0084">oh nice <pause dur="short"/> what's in the bottom one?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0041">uni stuff <pause dur="short"/> uni stuff <pause dur="short"/> bank stuff <pause dur="short"/> shit loads of dictionaries and files</u>
<u n="11" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0041">keep sakes <pause dur="short"/> a present for my mum that she never got</u>
<u n="13" who="S0084">Cos she's a cow</u>
<u n="14" who="S0041">she's a cow <pause dur="short"/> bit of Zumba and Pilates on the top of all that</u>
<u n="15" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> I might have to do a bit of Zumba in the house</u>
<u n="16" who="S0041">zumba</u>
<u n="17" who="S0084">zumba bumba <pause dur="short"/> well it sounds a bit of a traumatic Wednesday evening</u>
<u n="18" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0084">but necessary</u>
<u n="20" who="S0041">yeah necessary</u>
<u n="21" who="S0084">A necessary trauma</u>
<u n="22" who="S0041">I feel a little bit like I can't breathe</u>
<u n="23" who="S0084">oh god <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure what that's what's supposed to happen</u>
<u n="24" who="S0041">he said I never thought that I'd be the person to let you down like that <pause dur="short"/> to that extent <unclear/> die <pause dur="short"/> who do you think feels worse?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0084">oh god <pause dur="short"/> well it needed to be said didn't it <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing</u>
<u n="26" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I feel better that I've got everything off off my chest <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="27" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0041">I feel like he understands and I said to him about even about the <trunc>w</trunc> in the <trunc>hot</trunc> so we were in the hotel and we had a conversation very similar to this in which I kind of took responsibility for the the way that we I behaved if we were together and that I kind of panicked if something went wrong</u>
<u n="29" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0041">and I said but you never said anything back <pause dur="short"/> did you not think no wonder I panicked?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0041">I never behave like that with anybody else I've ever known</u>
<u n="33" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0041">well except for you because you're the only person that I felt so concerned that if something went wrong I wasn't picking just me up <pause dur="short"/> I was picking you up as well</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0041">and now I don't need to pick you up</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0041">and I said you <trunc>nev</trunc> you never thought thought about it at all <pause dur="short"/> you never gave anything <pause dur="short"/> you never evaluated you</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no it was all <pause dur="short"/> it was all you know to do about you and your faults</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084" trans="overlap">so how did you leave things then?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0041">erm <pause dur="short"/> he said send send his love to my dad and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and basically see you around</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0041">and he said you know I hope you do keep me posted with navy things as you go through the the process</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0041">I suppose I'll just text him like I'd text his mum</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084">well it's up to you isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I mean it <pause dur="short"/> if it were me I wouldn't as I I've said to you</u>
<u n="48" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no I'm not</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">I've put you off the plate back in here <pause dur="short"/> for the warming</u>
<u n="50" who="S0041">the warming <pause dur="short"/> I'll probably wait to see if I hear from him on my birthday</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0041">if I don't I won't text him</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">I'm sure he will definitely text you on your birthday <pause dur="short"/> well I would have thought so</u>
<u n="54" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> you never know with this guy <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's just I think it's easier to pretend he doesn't exist now</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">I think this is the bit where you walk away</u>
<u n="56" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084" trans="overlap">you've said your piece <pause dur="short"/> you've said what you wanted to say</u>
<u n="58" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I've said my bit and feel better about it and</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">anything else that's getting said now is just going to be raking up the same issue</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">it's going to hurt again and again and again</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041">quickly yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think so too <pause dur="short"/> that's that's good for me <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0041">he said er do you know you're the most amazing person I know <pause dur="short"/> he said cos no matter what happens <pause dur="short"/> no matter what you you do you always take the situation and make make yourself the best you can be out of it <pause dur="short"/> and I see you  I see you  every time becoming a better person because of things</u>
<u n="64" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0041">and I'm thinking in my head that's just what adults do <pause dur="short"/> that's what you do <pause dur="short"/> that's a natural reaction</u>
<u n="66" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0041">erm and  he said I read  he said I read a an article today er it was a design thing <pause dur="short"/> erm and it was basically about <trunc>get</trunc> <event desc="sound of bang"/> getting rid of a sorry <pause dur="short"/> getting rid of everybody needs to get rid of things in their life that are surplus to requirement</u>
<u n="68" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="69" who="S0041">you know that you're not <pause dur="short"/> that don't help you <pause dur="short"/> that actually hinder you <pause dur="short"/> and he said I've realised I've become one of those people for you</u>
<u n="70" who="S0084">A bit fucking melodramatic isn't it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0084">erm well I mean it that whole self <trunc>loa</trunc> that's that's the same thing isn't it <pause dur="short"/> the self loathing that oh I can't do anything about it it's changed my personality <pause dur="short"/> bollocks</u>
<u n="73" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0084">it's just that <pause dur="short"/> you know it's it's like he's not taking responsibility he's just saying woe is me <pause dur="short"/> I'm such a bad <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm such a bad friend <pause dur="short"/> oh dear oh dear <pause dur="short"/> he never does anything about it because this is hardly the first time you've said you're letting me down <pause dur="short"/> can you man up?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0084">I mean how many times have you had this conversation? You know I mean I appreciate today it's probably a bit more sever than he's used to</u>
<u n="77" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0084">but London was pretty bad</u>
<u n="79" who="S0041">yeah that was pretty bad</u>
<u n="80" who="S0084">and the time before that when he you know you were saying <unclear/> here</u>
<u n="81" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's like he can't gauge severity</u>
<u n="82" who="S0084">it's like I mean he he gets upset every time you have this conversation <pause dur="short"/> and even if that's his gauge for how serious a conversation is he can see that you're hurting which then upsets him <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> so you know it's not malicious <pause dur="short"/> he just isn't doing anything to change it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I was I remember you know if we used to argue he <trunc>kin</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> it's as if he didn't quite grasp how angry I was</u>
<u n="84" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0041">and I I once screamed at him so bad <pause dur="short"/> I threw him out of the car <pause dur="short"/> I've never been that angry with anyone <pause dur="short"/> but it's like he couldn't <pause dur="short"/> it's like he didn't quite get how how bad it was</u>
<u n="86" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0041">and that's I think that's a bit of an autistic thing</u>
<u n="88" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0041">like the way he walked in here today as if he knew it was wrong but he didn't know how wrong <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> to me</u>
<u n="90" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he didn't know what was wrong <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0084">even though when you left things in London you said <unclear/> is it you want? If you want to be friends man up</u>
<u n="93" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0084">and he just hasn't done that</u>
<u n="95" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="96" who="S0084">Cos obviously he wasn't here last week <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="97" who="S0041">I'm a bit scared about the flipping</u>
<u n="98" who="S0084">I'm feeling very confident for you</u>
<u n="99" who="S0041">what about if the olive goes everywhere though?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0084">I'd do it over the hob and then at least it can be saved as opposed to over the floor</u>
<event desc="sound of pancake flipping"/>
<u n="101" who="S0084">wooh <pause dur="short"/> you didn't end up with a pancake hats though</u>
<u n="102" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> open up <pause dur="short"/> it clearly wasn't ready for flipping <pause dur="short"/> wasn't quite  wasn't quite  cooked yet <pause dur="short"/> just burn you up on there now</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">Cook cook cook</u>
<u n="104" who="S0041">I'm just feeling like I'm draining my resources are just gone</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084">well as hard as it is at least you know you've made the right decision</u>
<u n="106" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's probably never going to man up in his whole whole life</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084">probably not in the short term <pause dur="short"/> not in the time that you needed to because he would have done by now</u>
<u n="108" who="S0041" trans="overlap">uh uh</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084">I know maybe it's you know it's asking quite a lot from him <pause dur="short"/> maybe he just needs the time <pause dur="short"/> you know normally it's when you're single that you really sort of have that self reflection and he's not really done that because he's just launched himself straight into something</u>
<u n="110" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">that looked to be fairly easy going but has quickly become quite serious <pause dur="short"/> you know planning all your weekends together <pause dur="short"/> you know booking a holiday with each other when you've only had like three dates</u>
<u n="112" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084">do you reckon that's probably another sign of him not being able to gauge what's acceptable because you wouldn't book a holiday with somebody you've only seen three times</u>
<u n="114" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no you wouldn't</u>
<u n="115" who="S0084"><unclear/> mental issues of the brain</u>
<u n="116" who="S0041">mental issues of the brain yo <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> don't really know when you know these are cooked</u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">is that cooked?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0041">Don't know</u>
<u n="119" who="S0084">aren't they supposed to be more brown than that?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0041">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">does it need to be flipped again?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0041">do you think?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084">it's an <trunc>a</trunc> it's an alien <pause dur="short"/> aliens coming out</u>
<u n="124" who="S0041">oh I'm a bit scared of the flipping <event desc="sound of pancake flipping"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">wooh <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041">that's cooked on that side now isn't it?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> apart form the alien growth on the middle <pause dur="short"/> that's fine <pause dur="short"/> that looks delicious <pause dur="short"/> delicious and nutritious <unclear/> again</u>
<u n="128" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I went around to my mum's today at lunch <pause dur="short"/> it was really nice actually because I had the car and I my head was hurting quite a lot this morning so I just thought oh fuck it I'll taka a <trunc>long</trunc> longer lunch <pause dur="short"/> I worked through my lunch yesterday</u>
<u n="130" who="S0041" trans="overlap">argh</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084">and I drove over there <pause dur="short"/> it was quite nice <pause dur="short"/> my sister was off work as well <pause dur="short"/> she had the day off so they were there and <unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0041" trans="overlap">argh</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084">my sister made me  a cheesie  a cheesie toastie <pause dur="short"/> it was nice <pause dur="short"/> we were talking about life and the universe which was a bit full on for a lunch time</u>
<u n="134" who="S0041">seems to be a bit of full on Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">yeah it's all a bit serious <pause dur="short"/> no wonder my heads about to fall out my <trunc>he</trunc> my ears</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">no wonder</u>
<u n="138" who="S0041">is your sister still set on er a foreign life?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the course that she want really really really wanted to do which she didn't have to think about too much is the one in Berlin <pause dur="short"/> and you can't apply for that until April <pause dur="short"/> six months before you'd be due to start</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">well it's</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">yo <pause dur="short"/> I think she's applied for the one in Stockholm <pause dur="short"/> she's just waiting to hear and just as a sort of backup <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's all going okay</u>
<u n="142" who="S0041">you don't get to hear from six till six months before you're due to start?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">you can't apply until six months before</u>
<u n="144" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">pass <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what's going on there</u>
<u n="146" who="S0041">that's a bit extreme isn't it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Are your things on fire?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0041">only a little bit of black on the bottom</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084">I'm fine <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> I might need to try and leave work early tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I might work <unclear/> and ask why <pause dur="short"/> big boss <pause dur="short"/> as I have no boss <pause dur="short"/> whether I can leave a two-thirty and go and look at charity for burlesque costumes</u>
<u n="150" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="151" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she was looking at corsets online last night but I mean I could have told her that they're really expensive</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm and you can't get one this quickly now</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084" trans="overlap">seventy <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> so we're thinking some sort of erm netting possibly with some sort of top <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking charity or vintage shops <pause dur="short"/> for instance sort of feathers you know big feathers</u>
<u n="154" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes feathers</u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0041" trans="overlap">Peacock feathers <pause dur="short"/> peacock feathers</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> peacock feathers <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking of going all in black possibly <pause dur="short"/> you know maybe even some full length gloves if I can find them <pause dur="short"/> cos even if I found them on Amazon or something you can get next day delivery so</u>
<u n="158" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0084">I'm feeling quite confident about that <pause dur="short"/> laura the girl whose birthday it is <pause dur="short"/> she sent a message around to just the girls saying I think it would be quite nice having a few drinks before hand <pause dur="short"/> but erm I'm aware that we won't be wearing many clothes so if you don't want to go into town just let me know and I'll organise drinks at my house <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> house <pause dur="short"/> cos we will be naked <pause dur="short"/> I spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and said <pause dur="short"/> cos she hadn't spoken to me since <unclear/> and said I'm not coming out for your birthday</u>
<u n="160" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084">oh you have met her from <trunc>womb</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh you know Womble from New Years Eve?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084">I think the birthday turned out to be some sort of double date so I'm quite glad that I didn't go</u>
<u n="164" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084">Cos basically <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <unclear/> and Womble and his new girlfriend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> it was the four of them <pause dur="short"/> so I'm quite glad that I didn't just rock up at like ten O'clock for one drink and then all the couples went home to shag because that would have been really depressing</u>
<u n="166" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084">Cos I think that strange little DJ was supposed to go but I don't think he did <pause dur="short"/> so anyway I was feeling a bit guilty and I meant to text her myself but she beat me to eat <pause dur="short"/> apparently she's booking the flights for Australia on Saturday morning so I said I'll meet you in town at one which gives me time to make the Guinness cake in the morning <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping I'll be able to add to it tomorrow afternoon or at least gather an idea for something because I don't want to just try and find something on Saturday and like it would be a real panic</u>
<u n="168" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that would be bad</u>
<u n="169" who="S0084">and that's what I'm worried about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's why I kind of just want to meet her in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> in fact maybe I will just say that <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were saying about going for erm well for Guinness basically</u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084">because it's Saint Patrick's day so I mean meet for a few bevies in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> which could be dangerous because I'd have to factor in coming home getting changed and putting on the feathers and the pants combo <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="172" who="S0041">this looks a good one</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">that looks a perfect one</u>
<u n="174" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0084">what are you going to have in yours? Cheesy?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0041">er <pause dur="short"/> sugar and lemon juiceness</u>
<u n="177" who="S0084">red and yellow and pink and green and orange and purple and all the colours</u>
<u n="178" who="S0041">all the colours in the world ever</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0041">er mm mm mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0084">er I wonder if maybe we should open the window and close the door</u>
<u n="182" who="S0041">are we making smoke?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0084">I I couldn't see it before but I can see it now and that fire alarm is intense <pause dur="short"/> you do not want that to go off?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah I don't really want to witness that if I'm honest</u>
<u n="185" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> I might cry <pause dur="short"/> I mean that would finish my brain off quite frankly <pause dur="short"/> yep I'm feeling quite confident about that <unclear/> tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> cos there's loads of charity shops on Mill Road aren't there so I can start with over there <pause dur="short"/> check those out and then go to the Grafton Centre cos there's loads on that street</u>
<u n="186" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">erm  and then  and then your above Primark</u>
<u n="188" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="189" who="S0084">and the vintage shop</u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">do you know the best place to go to for stuff like that would be Camden Market wouldn't it</u>
<u n="191" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> it would be <pause dur="short"/> bit of a trek <foreign lang="fre">pour moi</foreign> Camden Market's really great because you can haggle which I quite like</u>
<u n="192" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they do loads of stuff like that</u>
<u n="193" who="S0084">they've got loads of just random shit <pause dur="short"/> cos the thing is you don't want it to look cheap whatever it is you're wearing <pause dur="short"/> that's probably <pause dur="short"/> it's quite cheap <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw loads actually while I was there</u>
<u n="195" who="S0084">did you?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I took a photograph of a blazer actually cos it was a very strange shop that erm did that type of gothic corset in a day type attire</u>
<u n="197" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0041">erm and also did a really amazingly tailored blazer <pause dur="short"/> I've got a photograph of it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> that I've downloaded and I've never seen anything like it <pause dur="short"/> it is amazing <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of got this bit that goes across which makes a lapel on one side but not on the other side <pause dur="short"/> it's really difficult to explain <pause dur="short"/> grey <pause dur="short"/> amazing</u>
<u n="199" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> how much was it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0041">it didn't have a price on it</u>
<u n="201" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> pricey</u>
<u n="202" who="S0041">yeah and it but the rest of the stuff in there was quite kind of around the forty pound mark so I don't think it would have been ridiculous</u>
<u n="203" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">you weren't tempted?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">very tempted but potless <pause dur="short"/> it was before payday wasn't it?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0041">yeah and also it would have suited your figure but I think once you put <trunc>bru</trunc> boobs in it or waist in it it would have looked awful <pause dur="short"/> you needed to have a nice petite frame cos it was really kind of smooth <pause dur="short"/> it was gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> I'll show you the picture</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> did you get the photos done from the camera? Was it alright on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? It didn't kill it?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> oh on your camera <pause dur="short"/> no I haven't tried that yet <pause dur="short"/> I did get the ones that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm sent that I cut <pause dur="short"/> on my email that I couldn't open <pause dur="short"/> I opened it on Firefox instead</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh good</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041">ah ah ah get over <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> you're doing that</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">that's fine</u>
<u n="214" who="S0041">that's fine</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084">that's how it's supposed to go man</u>
<u n="216" who="S0041">I'm trying to think of a place you could go for for stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> what about erm well like H and M underwear <pause dur="short"/> I haven't been in there for years and years but I remember getting a corset top from there once</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084">H and M <pause dur="short"/> yeah possibly <pause dur="short"/> I mean there are lingerie shops obviously in abundance <pause dur="short"/> it's just finding one that's affordable <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose once you've got one you've got one</u>
<u n="218" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">and I would like a nice one <pause dur="short"/> there's Triumph isn't there</u>
<u n="220" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking that</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084">or I could go in the lovely lingerie place in town and see if they've got a sale on <pause dur="short"/> erm Le Le Reve</u>
<u n="222" who="S0041" trans="overlap">the one near the <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084">in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's beautiful <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a look in there <pause dur="short"/> but they've always got a ten pound bin <pause dur="short"/> it's just whether you could come up trumps really <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0041">I think it will be a really fun night though</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084">it should be really good <pause dur="short"/> should be <pause dur="short"/> I think the music's going to be quite good and there's cabaret acts which is always quite fun <pause dur="short"/> and like a drag queen compère and it I mean it should be a good crack I think <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite looking forward to it <pause dur="short"/> I think erm I almost have this moment where I don't want to go <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> people that I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> it's going to be a bit of an effort <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> know</u>
<u n="226" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I always think that</u>
<u n="227" who="S0084">I don't know who's going to be there and <pause dur="short"/> but then you go and you have a good time so <pause dur="short"/> it's like forcing myself to go</u>
<u n="228" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah you go and you think why was I? Yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> so I think I will force myself <pause dur="short"/> I mean the thing is even if you go and you leave by midnight at least you've gone and you've been out and you've met people and been sociable <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and you always have more fun than  you think you  you think you will I think <pause dur="short"/> you kind of hype it up a bit in your head don't you to be a bit difficult and</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">yeah and I suppose and I'm so out of the habit of doing that now <pause dur="short"/> you know getting dressed up <pause dur="short"/> really dressed up to go out</u>
<u n="232" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's nice to do it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">it is nice <pause dur="short"/> it felt really strange actually going out for my bosses birthday last week <pause dur="short"/> you know going to  Because we I hadn't been out really for since New Years Eve <pause dur="short"/> well out out</u>
<u n="234" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0084">and considering like before you would go out twice a week at least you know it seems seems out of the ordinary now to go out into town</u>
<u n="236" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's erm our <trunc>ho</trunc> hotel is hotel of the week at  this week which means we get two for one on house wine <pause dur="short"/> two for one on food <pause dur="short"/> two for one on pints of Becks</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Oh <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="238" who="S0041">soft drinks are a pound <pause dur="short"/> something</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084">that sounds pretty awesome</u>
<u n="240" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I found that out today <pause dur="short"/> but it's only like Tuesday to Friday which is well a bit of a dud deal if you ask me</u>
<u n="241" who="S0084">typical <pause dur="short"/> bastards</u>
<u n="242" who="S0041">well</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">I suppose that means <pause dur="short"/> oh well you can't really go drinking Friday can you</u>
<u n="244" who="S0041">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> shit it's it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding <pause dur="short"/> god <pause dur="short"/> it's going to be so stressful</u>
<u n="245" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0041">so stressful because she's having the ceremony there as well</u>
<u n="247" who="S0084">oh right whereas last time it was just the reception</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041">yeah last time it was just breakfast reception and most of that service is done by <unclear/> I tell them what to do and that's it <pause dur="short"/> I'm responsible for moving her music for playing <pause dur="short"/> imagine if I press it and something goes wrong</u>
<u n="249" who="S0084">oh god</u>
<u n="250" who="S0041">oh fuck me</u>
<u n="251" who="S0084">you've got to not worry about these things though <pause dur="short"/> just got to feel confident that you you've done the set up <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="252" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well tomorrow  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I are playing who's going to be the bride and pretend to walk down the aisle <pause dur="short"/> for timings</u>
<u n="253" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Nice <pause dur="short"/> it's weddings go go this weekend</u>
<u n="254" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0084">my friend at work <pause dur="short"/> rachel <pause dur="short"/> she's got a wedding but it's her housemate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s brother's wedding and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s supposed to be making the cake but she's been quite depressed recently and she hasn't even started like attempting to mock up the cake yet</u>
<u n="256" who="S0041">do you want cheese in here?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I think she's a bit worried <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0041">or do you want Nutella or do you just want it on a plate or?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0084">er</u>
<u n="260" who="S0041">what do you feel the need for?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0084">I might just have a spoon full of Nutella <unclear/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0041">do you want it in it while it's in the pan or?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">no that's fine thank you <pause dur="short"/> just spread it in <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> thanks</u>
<u n="264" who="S0041">there's also another one in here if you can fit it in</u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">I'll see how I go</u>
<u n="266" who="S0041" trans="overlap">fit it in your mouth hole</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084">I think it's the grill that smells cos I think the smoke comes off the grill</u>
<u n="268" who="S0041">I think it might be this <pause dur="short"/> whatever's on this ring?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> because the cleaner obviously doesn't clean it because that should be</u>
<u n="270" who="S0041" trans="overlap">she's shit <pause dur="short"/> that would make too much sense of course</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="272" who="S0041">to clean <pause dur="short"/> if you are a cleaner</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084">yeah no don't be silly <pause dur="short"/> I don't think she's even wiped the sides down</u>
<u n="274" who="S0041">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know why you</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084">I don't think she does anything to be fair</u>
<u n="278" who="S0041">I don't even know why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> pays her to be honest</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084">I think they're probably mates</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">probably best buds <pause dur="short"/> puts her through the books</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> would you like any Nutella? What are you having? Sugar?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0041">yeah I'm just going to have sugar thanks</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> sugar and lemon</u>
<u n="284" who="S0041">I'm going to steal some er out of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cupboard <pause dur="short"/> some goodness <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> that</u>
<u n="285" who="S0084">did I tell you it's my two year anniversary at work?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="287" who="S0084">this week</u>
<u n="288" who="S0041">is it?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> two years <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I started on the same day and she made chocolate ginger cake yesterday and I was so busy this morning I didn't even see her email that said I've made cake <pause dur="short"/> I was rushing around like a loon <pause dur="short"/> came back and had another meeting and <unclear/> message about it <pause dur="short"/> it was so good</u>
<u n="290" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh that's exciting</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I'd I'd completely forgotten <pause dur="short"/> it's really gone so quickly I can't believe it <pause dur="short"/> it's a worry actually <pause dur="short"/> maybe it just needed time to</u>
<u n="292" who="S0041" trans="overlap">worrying a good thing there though <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="293" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I think it just means that we're settled <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that's a good thing either really</u>
<u n="294" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think it is because it's <pause dur="short"/> it must mean that you're getting something from there which is a nice feeling isn't it <pause dur="short"/> to know that</u>
<u n="295" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's to feel like <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0041">you're gaining from what you're doing <pause dur="short"/> it does make a <unclear/> difference</u>
<u n="297" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> absolutely I think everyday I enjoy my job mostly <pause dur="short"/> I might have a few issues with a few people or what not <pause dur="short"/> but erm generally speaking I like my job so</u>
<u n="298" who="S0041">A few little hiccups <pause dur="short"/> perhaps</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but and I guess that's the dream isn't it <pause dur="short"/> finding a job you like <pause dur="short"/> that's the goal so</u>
<u n="300" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah it is actually <pause dur="short"/> yeah I suppose to not have a job for two years and to not want to get up in the morning and not want to go is quite an achievement really</u>
<u n="301" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean there were times last year you know I was doing the old job where I could quite easily have murdered somebody or everybody actually</u>
<u n="302" who="S0041">all of them</u>
<u n="303" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> get pancake <unclear/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0041"><unclear/> pancake <unclear/> mm <pause dur="short"/> chocolate to the tooth</u>
<u n="305" who="S0084">cold banana to the tooth</u>
<u n="306" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="307" who="S0084">wowsers</u>
<u n="308" who="S0041">microwave it</u>
<u n="309" who="S0084">microwave it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> microwave it <pause dur="short"/> quick <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> microwave <pause dur="short"/> you're a genius <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> </u>
<u n="310" who="S0041">I do have brains <pause dur="short"/> I told you I just hide them well</u>
<u n="311" who="S0084">huh?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">I do have brains <pause dur="short"/> I told you I just hide them well</u>
<u n="313" who="S0084">huh <pause dur="short"/> you've got the brains that's for damn sure</u>
<u n="314" who="S0041">hide the bad boys</u>
<u n="315" who="S0084">mine mine mine <pause dur="short"/> mine mine mine</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> I've eaten so much sugar these past few days</u>
<u n="317" who="S0084">well maybe it's just your body <pause dur="short"/> it's stitching itself back together and as it's all <unclear/> your willy</u>
<u n="318" who="S0041">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's from sitting on penis</u>
<u n="319" who="S0084">that's why because they'll drain it all out and then all the sugar comes out</u>
<u n="320" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's a double penis</u>
<u n="321" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041">because the other thing that's hurt is my spine which if you rearrange the words spells out penis</u>
<u n="323" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> dearie me</u>
<u n="324" who="S0041">double penis</u>
<u n="325" who="S0084">oh it's a double penis</u>
<u n="326" who="S0041">mm mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0041">do you need Golden Syrup on as well</u>
<u n="329" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="330" who="S0041">contraband</u>
<u n="331" who="S0084">I need to find a bit of something <pause dur="short"/> I've got a bit of cancer on mine</u>
<u n="332" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="333" who="S0084">it's tasty <pause dur="short"/> it's protein</u>
<u n="334" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> it can't be good for you though cos I always feel quite sick <pause dur="short"/> I've eaten a big bar of Dairy Milk <pause dur="short"/> one of those big ones this week</u>
<u n="335" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="336" who="S0041" trans="overlap">or over the past two days</u>
<u n="337" who="S0084">yep <pause dur="short"/> mini Eggs which is very good for you</u>
<u n="338" who="S0041" trans="overlap">two packets of Mini Eggs</u>
<u n="339" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0041">this whole yumminess</u>
<u n="341" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0041">A chocolate mini chocolate muffin</u>
<u n="343" who="S0084">yum <pause dur="short"/> it's good for you</u>
<u n="344" who="S0041">but that's like that's a bit of an astounding intake isn't it</u>
<u n="345" who="S0084">but that's but it's probably not even your full calorie intake because you're not eating any food</u>
<u n="346" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0084">like yesterday was the first dinner you've actually eaten</u>
<u n="348" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0084">so you're probably not even taking in your two thousand calories</u>
<u n="350" who="S0041">I've never even counted calories</u>
<u n="351" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="352" who="S0041">I find I'm really jealous that I can't though <pause dur="short"/> I'd totally make the most of that</u>
<u n="353" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0041">erm I couldn't actually sleep till about two O'clock this morning though <pause dur="short"/> I felt so sick</u>
<u n="355" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> it just it feels like my body doesn't want to digest what I'm eating</u>
<u n="357" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0041">like my dinner was just sat like in my chest for hour and hours</u>
<u n="359" who="S0084">oh mate</u>
<u n="360" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0084">well I hope didn't poison you with anything</u>
<u n="362" who="S0041">no cos it's everything I eat</u>
<u n="363" who="S0084">oh my god</u>
<u n="364" who="S0041">like at work today I had a piece of garlic bread that was like this big <pause dur="short"/> literally this big <pause dur="short"/> it was the corner of the ciabatta</u>
<u n="365" who="S0084">oh god</u>
<u n="366" who="S0041">and about as much pasta as would fit in a ladle <pause dur="short"/> maybe a little bit less</u>
<u n="367" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> and it just took ages and ages <pause dur="short"/> I had it but about one and that's the the only thing I've eaten</u>
<u n="369" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0041">I had I just didn't feel hungry</u>
<u n="371" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0041">I still didn't feel hungry before I made pancakes <pause dur="short"/> I just felt sick</u>
<u n="373" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="374" who="S0041">Cos it's like my body's a bit scared to digest stuff now</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically</u>
<u n="376" who="S0041">it does take awhile to get it over <pause dur="short"/> get it back going</u>
<u n="377" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> it does take a while to get over <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos your body's recovering still</u>
<u n="378" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sat in the office cos I sat thinking oh I'm really not doing very well here <pause dur="short"/> I'm like <vocal desc="misc"/> And <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went chunks <pause dur="short"/> and I went what? He said do you get that? The chunks <pause dur="short"/> you feel the chunks are going to come up and I was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> he was like yeah me too</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084" trans="overlap">urgh</u>
<u n="380" who="S0041">and everyone's like shut up</u>
<u n="381" who="S0084">urgh</u>
<u n="382" who="S0041">but he must have seen it in my face and being able to relate to it</u>
<u n="383" who="S0084" trans="overlap">the fear</u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">Cos he he had it really bad as well</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> your poor body</u>
<u n="386" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> been through the wars a bit <pause dur="short"/> it will be fine though <pause dur="short"/> that's what I have to keep <pause dur="short"/> do you still want to go to aqua fit tomorrow?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> what time is aqua fit?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0041">half six till half seven</u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041">but I don't finish work till six so I'm going to pack my bag <pause dur="short"/> erm and then literally drive back from work but I'll I come by this way anyway so <pause dur="short"/> if you want to  if you want to  join suit you're very welcome</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084">join suit</u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">oh I'm going to need another one <pause dur="short"/> do you want another one that's not got a bit of burn on</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">oh no I'm fine <pause dur="short"/> thank you yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0041">are you sure?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0084">I'm done <pause dur="short"/> it was delicious <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> erm half six till half seven</u>
<u n="396" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="397" who="S0084">so you're going to pack a bag</u>
<u n="398" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="399" who="S0084">you're going to come back and pick me up and we're going to go</u>
<u n="400" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="401" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="402" who="S0041">so I'll just drive <pause dur="short"/> I'll leave work by <unclear/> six and just drive to <pause dur="short"/> cos it's it's this way to <unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0084" trans="overlap">is it? I'm not it's not going to be out of your way to pick me up?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="405" who="S0084">Cos otherwise I could just meet you there</u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">no it goes <pause dur="short"/> I go down this road anyway cos I don't go across at the crossroads <pause dur="short"/> straight across</u>
<u n="407" who="S0084" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> so I just need to be ready to go at six so that I'm ready for when you're here</u>
<u n="408" who="S0041">yeah well probably be twenty past cos stupid East Road traffic</u>
<u n="409" who="S0084" trans="overlap">traffic <pause dur="short"/> oh it's a killer <pause dur="short"/> this morning oh my god I had near I had proper road rage with a woman this morning and erm  I was  I was on East Road coming up to where the traffic lights are by  And you know the road merges into one?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0041" trans="overlap">isn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0084">I get really fucked off if people creeping in from the left</u>
<u n="412" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0084" trans="overlap">really <pause dur="short"/> yeah really piss pisses me off</u>
<u n="414" who="S0041">from the  road?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0084">and this woman was trying to come into my road into the road</u>
<u n="416" who="S0041">which one do you want? Oh god <pause dur="short"/> sorry I am listening</u>
<u n="417" who="S0084">are they  are they  different?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0041">this one's thinner but blacker <pause dur="short"/> I think I want this one</u>
<u n="419" who="S0084"><unclear/> on the black one</u>
<u n="420" who="S0041">do you think? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> no I think it's this one <pause dur="short"/> I'm having you</u>
<u n="421" who="S0084">yeah don't have the cancer one <pause dur="short"/> so she tried to creep in as a way <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously you're all waiting in line</u>
<u n="422" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0084">everyone's really fucked off that you're having to queue <pause dur="short"/> but there she is creeping creeping creeping trying to put her foot down and I was like fuck off</u>
<u n="424" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0084">and she beeped at me</u>
<u n="426" who="S0041">did she?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0084">yeah so I obviously flipped her the finger and I was just like fuck off and she was going like that in the mirror <pause dur="short"/> because obviously then the red changed and it the light changed to red so she was stuck behind me fuming <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> really really annoys me cos that is a you know that lane it's not their right of way</u>
<u n="428" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's not <pause dur="short"/> you don't like you don't like actually have to let them in do you</u>
<u n="429" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0041">yeah I know I hate that as well <pause dur="short"/> this morning was really bad on the way to work <pause dur="short"/> like if I get the bus to work the bus comes at <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> the bus comes at like twenty to <pause dur="short"/> it's usually late and gets in at ten to to this bus stop <pause dur="short"/> I'm still at work on time for eight <pause dur="short"/> ten minutes it takes</u>
<u n="431" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0041">to drive thirty-five minutes this morning</u>
<u n="433" who="S0084">God thirty-five minutes</u>
<u n="434" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I didn't have to be at work till ten so it should have been after rush hour traffic</u>
<u n="435" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0041">oh I just no <pause dur="short"/> I just can't deal with it</u>
<u n="437" who="S0084">it drives you mad</u>
<u n="438" who="S0041">just no <pause dur="short"/> just no</u>
<u n="439" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0041">it was a <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was a definite killer and then on the way back from the doctors I went to <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> I went to the erm doctors at mid day cos on on the way to work I</u>
<u n="441" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh did you?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0041">yeah I drove via the surgery and just explained and said oh if you come back at twelve you can sit and wait</u>
<u n="443" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="444" who="S0041">but if you come just before twelve you'll be the first one to check in so you won't have to wait <pause dur="short"/> okay thanks</u>
<u n="445" who="S0084">I'll be here for that then</u>
<u n="446" who="S0041">I'll be here for that</u>
<u n="447" who="S0084">oh of course cos that's when they said that you'd have to go to hospital</u>
<u n="448" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> erm on the way back some guy cos you know it merges <pause dur="short"/> there's two lanes doesn't it that merge into one on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0084">oh yeah it fucks me off</u>
<u n="450" who="S0041">and at the very end you get to the point where you have to give one give one give one give</u>
<u n="451" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0041">he wasn't going to give one <pause dur="short"/> he wasn't going to let me in <pause dur="short"/> and I was like fuck that <pause dur="short"/> and he <unclear/> Merc in before me</u>
<u n="453" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0041">he got this little Punto and erm teenage guy</u>
<u n="455" who="S0084" trans="overlap">so you're in the left or the right?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0041">I'm in the left</u>
<u n="457" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0041">so I'd let like the car in front of me had gone and the one before had let him in</u>
<u n="459" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0041">so I'd let the big Merc in</u>
<u n="461" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0041">and then Punto put his foot down <pause dur="short"/> I thought he can fuck off <pause dur="short"/> so I put literally <pause dur="short"/> pulled so far forward that the Merc could have possibly scratched my car cos he was I was still like my bonnet was the full length of his boot and pulled my car the wrong way so that Punto couldn't move</u>
<u n="463" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0041">and he just looked at me and I went tada</u>
<u n="465" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0041">and this teenage boy was like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0084">I would have been so fucked off <pause dur="short"/> that road really pisses me off because there's no <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand why there's two lanes <pause dur="short"/> there's no reason apart from obviously when you come off the East er into <unclear/> roundabout you've got two lanes by the court because one is to turn left into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0084">fine <pause dur="short"/> at that point filter it down into one</u>
<u n="470" who="S0041">from the traffic lights?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0084">from the traffic light <pause dur="short"/> but because you've got that whole stretch and then it filters at at the next set of traffic lights everyone gets fucked off</u>
<u n="472" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yep yep <pause dur="short"/> and nobody turns into down the <anon type="place"/> down past that Heart thing <pause dur="short"/> you know you can go across the carriageway can't you <pause dur="short"/> the buses go there</u>
<u n="473" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0041">there's nobody every goes down there apart from there apart from buses so there's no reason that shouldn't be a bus lane</u>
<u n="475" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> although when I was in the queue this morning it we'd I'd stopped before like the British Heart Foundation furniture shop and there was a some sort of white lorry coming out of where the entrance to the <unclear/> cinema is</u>
<u n="476" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0084">and he pulled out and it obviously the traffic was coming from that direction because we'd stopped and for that traffic that stopped so he knew we were about to move <pause dur="short"/> and he pulled out and what should have happened is we're all queuing here and his road is here <pause dur="short"/> he pulled out up here</u>
<u n="478" who="S0041">that's so bad</u>
<u n="479" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I'm like what the fuck do you think you're doing?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and then he started nestling in <pause dur="short"/> so basically the same thing <pause dur="short"/> he was bumper to bumper literally touching the van in front so that he could sneak in</u>
<u n="482" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0084">oh man if that had been me I would have gone absolutely ape shit</u>
<u n="484" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0084">absolutely mental</u>
<u n="486" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'm laughing because that's something I would do</u>
<u n="487" who="S0084">that is something you would do <pause dur="short"/> I know it is and I would go mental <pause dur="short"/> because I think oh I'm going to do it the right way and getting really angry with everyone who doesn't do it the right way</u>
<u n="488" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0084">but then I think why don't I just do it the wrong way and then I'd be there quicker</u>
<u n="490" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's me <pause dur="short"/> I do awful things like that <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm going</u>
<u n="491" who="S0084">my speed in city's a bit of an issue as well because I really put me foot down</u>
<u n="492" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0084">because obviously by now I know where the speed cameras are</u>
<u n="494" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0084">but you just don't know <pause dur="short"/> like someone at work got caught going down <anon type="place"/> the other day</u>
<u n="496" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos you know it's twenty now? Yeah they've changed it <pause dur="short"/> the put signs on <anon type="place"/> to twenty miles an hour now <pause dur="short"/> they've changed it <pause dur="short"/> probably about six months ago</u>
<u n="498" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/><pause dur="short"/> the whole thing?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the length of it <pause dur="short"/> all of <pause dur="short"/> well I'm pretty sure it's all the way down but it's certainly from town end <pause dur="short"/> definitely past the bridge <pause dur="short"/> it's twenty</u>
<u n="500" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I did not know that <pause dur="short"/> I bomb down there on the way back from the sun bed</u>
<u n="501" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> well there's quite a lot signs <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's signs but the thing is I don't think speed are that big <pause dur="short"/> they're quite <pause dur="short"/> considering it's telling you how fast you're supposed to be driving you'd think they'd be massive</u>
<u n="502" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I've stopped looking now if I'm honest <pause dur="short"/> maybe because I've been down that road so often erm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> don't expect it to change <pause dur="short"/> yeah well that's it <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah someone at work got caught the other day <pause dur="short"/> got fined eighty quid for speeding</u>
<u n="504" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="505" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well they were doing thirty <unclear/> over their signs <pause dur="short"/> and I think well it's always been thirty up until a few months ago so if you've always driven it at thirty you're not going to</u>
<u n="506" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't question it would you</u>
<u n="507" who="S0084">you're not really going to look</u>
<u n="508" who="S0041">and the worst thing is <pause dur="short"/> on <anon type="place"/> as well there's so many cyclists <pause dur="short"/> like that's a shit <pause dur="short"/> I'm terrified to drive down there in case I kill someone</u>
<u n="509" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0041">you're not looking at this road signs <pause dur="short"/> you're looking at all the people</u>
<u n="511" who="S0084">so and because the roads are so narrow people just walk out on the off the pavement</u>
<u n="512" who="S0041">on the ward <pause dur="short"/> on the road yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0084">and that's that <pause dur="short"/> I nearly ran my colleague over this morning actually <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he'd <pause dur="short"/> I was on <anon type="place"/> because I come obviously come down <anon type="place"/> and then turn onto <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and erm he overtook another cyclist <pause dur="short"/> so he came out of the cycle line on <anon type="place"/> but came out into the road as I was going past and erm I was about to honk the horn and then I realised it was him and I was like</u>
<u n="514" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0084">Cos isn't it you know it's horrible when you're cycling and the cars beep at you <pause dur="short"/> you know you get really like oh my god</u>
<u n="516" who="S0041">I nearly died</u>
<u n="517" who="S0084">my heart's in my mouth</u>
<u n="518" who="S0041">I think I'm done</u>
<u n="519" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I think you have to eat the last one</u>
<u n="520" who="S0041">I don't think I can fit it in <pause dur="short"/> I feel a bit sick</u>
<u n="521" who="S0084">tough <pause dur="short"/> no actually may maybe maybe not</u>
<u n="522" who="S0041">I like just leave it <pause dur="short"/> move it in the fridge and then if I feel the need I might heat it up later</u>
<u n="523" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds like an absolute winner <pause dur="short"/> erm so aqua fit is half six to half seven</u>
<u n="524" who="S0041">half six to half seven yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0084">so we could be home by eight</u>
<u n="526" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> I would <trunc>bu</trunc> say by the latest quarter past <pause dur="short"/> but probably eight</u>
<u n="527" who="S0084" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> probably eight <pause dur="short"/> my dad wanted to go out for dinner tomorrow night but he doesn't get home from the shopping till seven</u>
<u n="528" who="S0041">well we can make sure <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>b</trunc> just thinking the drive back is about ten minutes</u>
<u n="529" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0041">I can just quick <pause dur="short"/> be quick changes</u>
<u n="531" who="S0084" trans="overlap">quick <pause dur="short"/> quick shower <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0041">be quick showerers</u>
<u n="533" who="S0084">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> in and out <pause dur="short"/> we could be at my dad's for eight <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> eight fifteen even that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds fine <pause dur="short"/> maybe I could just try and see him at the weekend <pause dur="short"/> the weekend's pretty busy though</u>
<u n="534" who="S0041">yeah you sound a bit booked up <pause dur="short"/> booked up for the weekend <unclear/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0084">well I'm supposed to be seeing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on Friday for gym and jars <pause dur="short"/> jars of beer</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">gym and gym? Er gym and beer?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0084">gym and beer</u>
<u n="538" who="S0041">I like gym and beer <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> go together?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0084">the two go hand in hand <pause dur="short"/> mm but that's if he finishes on time <pause dur="short"/> but I'm definitely going to go to the gym after work whether he comes or not <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> so I'll probably drive and then come home on Friday <pause dur="short"/> we'll see</u>
<u n="540" who="S0041">one thing the doctor did say was yes swim <pause dur="short"/> keep it moving</u>
<u n="541" who="S0084">oh good okay so at least you know</u>
<u n="542" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yep</u>
<u n="543" who="S0084"><trunc>W</trunc> did he say that the willy might have grown because of the exercise?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> the willy will do what it wants basically</u>
<u n="545" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's always going to just going to grow of it's own accord <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="546" who="S0041">should have gone but keep it moving so <pause dur="short"/> that's that</u>
<u n="547" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh man <pause dur="short"/> so when do you have to call them back by?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0041">this time next week</u>
<u n="549" who="S0084">oh right so it's not a week after the accident <pause dur="short"/> it's a week from now?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0041">the doctor's?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0084">if the willy hasn't gone down <pause dur="short"/> say within a few days</u>
<u n="552" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I have a week from now for willy</u>
<u n="553" who="S0084" trans="overlap">A week from now</u>
<u n="554" who="S0041">erm cos he measured measured willy today <pause dur="short"/> it was so funny</u>
<u n="555" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he actually measured it?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0041">yeah and like I was like okay so you're going to want to see this? He was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said okay so I'm going to take my tights down so you can see the full potential of the bulge because I feel like my tights hold it in <pause dur="short"/> he was okay then <pause dur="short"/> he said if you just want to turn around while I just get the tight down because it's really not that graceful</u>
<u n="557" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0041">erm he said okay before you do do you want me to get a nurse in here so it's not just the two of us? Cos I mean he's a guy and I was like oh no I don't care</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">erm <pause dur="short"/> totally was eyeing up my bum though by the way</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">the doctor?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw his eyes <pause dur="short"/> he was obviously truly trying not to but he kind of went <pause dur="short"/> cos I was <pause dur="short"/> he'd like measured my willy of course <pause dur="short"/> so I'm like stood there with my my dress around my waist <pause dur="short"/> pants galore</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah as you do yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">erm <pause dur="short"/> obviously chose the good pants because I knew I was going to have to get them out</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041">erm and so he measures the willy <pause dur="short"/> so the guy's knelt at crotch level measuring my willy with the tape measure</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041">and then afterwards I'm talking away to him while I'm putting my  putting my  tights up and pulling them up <pause dur="short"/> but obviously pulling them up means my dress is now around my waist so I can pull my tights up <pause dur="short"/> I mean he was totally copping a look</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084">was he?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">yeah you could tell he was like looking at me and then he was just like</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041">I think it was more an embarrassment of don't look don't look <pause dur="short"/> shit I looked <pause dur="short"/> like that</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I know I know <pause dur="short"/> that's hilarious</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">it was so funny</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084">although people just do it all the time <pause dur="short"/> I mean I find that I stare at women's boobs all the time because I can't help because I think I don't have boobs like that <pause dur="short"/> like what must it be like?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I stare at stomachs</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084">do you?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> all the time <pause dur="short"/> especially I think it must look so bad because it's usually you know teenage girls <pause dur="short"/> they wear like the hipsters and you can see the the kind of this much midriff <pause dur="short"/> I can't help it <pause dur="short"/> I just stare at it</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the midriff <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0041">I think that just must look so bad</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084">well I suppose better than staring at their boobs like I do</u>
<u n="582" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">although <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying he thinks that women stare at his crotch all the time and I was saying I don't think they do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think that's wishful thinking <pause dur="short"/> that's you've forgotten the difference between dream time and real time</u>
<u n="584" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> real time</u>
<u n="585" who="S0084">and you've got a bit confused <pause dur="short"/> he said no no no I walk down the street and they</u>
<u n="586" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I've never look at women's crotches <pause dur="short"/> men's crotches</u>
<u n="587" who="S0084">you just wouldn't would you <pause dur="short"/> why? I mean unless they're wearing super tight trousers <pause dur="short"/> and we're not living in the nineteen seventies so</u>
<u n="588" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and usually you'd go for bum rather than frontness</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah always bum <pause dur="short"/> although I'm quite partial to a man's erm shoulders and neck area <pause dur="short"/> that really gets me</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">favourite favourite <pause dur="short"/> so how sad we actually are <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I this <pause dur="short"/> you now <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">I have a  I have a  thing about backs</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">not just the whole shoulder neck area <pause dur="short"/> like the whole back</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">and erm there's a clip in Just Friends film at the end when he takes his top off and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I froze it <pause dur="short"/> pressed pause <pause dur="short"/> so he's just this perfect back was the screen saver for the TV for the day</u>
<u n="597" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">and people were coming around and saying what's that? It's just the screen saver <pause dur="short"/> but that's the television <pause dur="short"/> yeah so we pressed pause <pause dur="short"/> what of it? Perfect back</u>
<u n="599" who="S0084">that's a bit peculiar <pause dur="short"/> must say that I've never heard of that one before girls</u>
<u n="600" who="S0041">yeah but we might have accidentally done that for the day</u>
<u n="601" who="S0084">who's paying the electricity bill?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0084">bet you were their favourite tenants actually <pause dur="short"/> what with the whole what like turning the oven on when you got really cold</u>
<u n="604" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we did that yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0041">and just opened all the compartments of it</u>
<u n="607" who="S0084">yeah that's not normal <pause dur="short"/> it's putting it out there</u>
<u n="608" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0084">that's not what normal people do</u>
<u n="610" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they get a bit obsessed by <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm definitely more of a back <pause dur="short"/> back person</u>
<u n="611" who="S0084">what was she making? That smells wrong</u>
<u n="612" who="S0041">I've no idea <pause dur="short"/> we'd best wash that pan</u>
<u n="613" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she made death</u>
<u n="614" who="S0041"><unclear/> death <pause dur="short"/> I would never look at a guy's crotch <pause dur="short"/> never</u>
<u n="615" who="S0084">no I've never heard of that one <pause dur="short"/> I think it's all just wishful thinking</u>
<u n="616" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> that's the truth of the matter</u>
<u n="617" who="S0084">pancakes pancakes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="618" who="S0041">although I was thinking today after the whole doctor copping looks at you</u>
<u n="619" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0041">I mean I I was got a I had got my arse out really so</u>
<u n="621" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="622" who="S0041">poor poor bloke couldn't really do anything else but look</u>
<u n="623" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0041">erm I kind of got quite excited which makes me sound awful about how I'm going to maybe in about two months</u>
<u n="625" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0041">we're hoping for less than that because birthday's in less than that</u>
<u n="627" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0041">have more of a hot bod <pause dur="short"/> I'm totally going to utilise this to my advantage</u>
<u n="629" who="S0084">having a hot bod</u>
<u n="630" who="S0041" trans="overlap">because I've never done it before <pause dur="short"/> I've never had a hot bod before</u>
<u n="631" who="S0084" trans="overlap">having a hot <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">Cos when I was smaller than this</u>
<u n="633" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="634" who="S0041">the last time I was ever smaller than this was when I was twenty-one</u>
<u n="635" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="636" who="S0041">but my fit my shape was different <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't toned <pause dur="short"/> so I still felt really uncomfortable <unclear/> skin</u>
<u n="637" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know what how people do it? I've never had that confidence <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose you know <trunc>on</trunc> once you have started working out and you can see a difference that's confidence <pause dur="short"/> that's going to give you confidence in itself isn't it?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like even when I was in Italy the least I went out in was the little dungarees</u>
<u n="639" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0041">I did have a <trunc>sh</trunc> a sheer shirt on underneath</u>
<u n="641" who="S0084">but I mean you have got quite a level of confidence already haven't you <pause dur="short"/> if you think about you know sexy top and skirts</u>
<u n="642" who="S0041">the sexy top and skirt is a very new thing</u>
<u n="643" who="S0084">it's very very very lovely <pause dur="short"/> very risky <pause dur="short"/> I mean I would never wear it <pause dur="short"/> I mean cos obviously you know you put it on and you feel good you know you look hot <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="644" who="S0041">but I didn't even wear stuff like that when I was eighteen</u>
<u n="645" who="S0084">really? Well I think the confidence does come with age though doesn't it?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="647" who="S0084">it gets to a point where I think <pause dur="short"/> you sort of well fuck it</u>
<u n="648" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I realised the other day? I was I can't remember how I how my brain got on to that point but erm <unclear/> said to me I can't believe your next birthday's twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> I know it sounds like a substantial age and I don't any different to where I was when I was eighteen really</u>
<u n="649" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0041">well I do but not compared to say twenty</u>
<u n="651" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0041">I said but twenty-five sounds like a a serious age yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0084" trans="overlap">serious birthday <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0041">she says yeah it's a bit of a right of passage isn't it <pause dur="short"/> and I said you know when you were a kid and you though about twenty-five you'd be <pause dur="short"/> got to get married and stuff</u>
<u n="655" who="S0084" trans="overlap">having yeah babies</u>
<u n="656" who="S0041">babies yep <pause dur="short"/> all that</u>
<u n="657" who="S0084"><unclear/> Own a house</u>
<u n="658" who="S0041">yep all that cack</u>
<u n="659" who="S0084">have a career</u>
<u n="660" who="S0041">erm and I said oh I think you know things are just different now <pause dur="short"/> you don't <pause dur="short"/> people who are twenty-five in this generation won't won't have the same type of lifestyle of people of ten twenty-five or ten years ago</u>
<u n="661" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0041">erm but I realised I still compare myself <pause dur="short"/> you know if you are?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0041">no that's okay</u>
<u n="665" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0041">you know when you go <pause dur="short"/> when I see pictures of girls or I see other girls on the street <pause dur="short"/> you know you kind of compare yourself to them <pause dur="short"/> or if I see myself naked and worry about the wrinkles and stuff before</u>
<u n="667" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0041">I still compare myself to girls who are eighteen</u>
<u n="669" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> like no you can't do that though</u>
<u n="670" who="S0041">well I know but I do and I only realised it this week</u>
<u n="671" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0041">like my thought of you know being naked with the guy</u>
<u n="673" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0041">my ideal in what he's expecting</u>
<u n="675" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0041">is an eighteen year old body</u>
<u n="677" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0041">when really <trunc>ther</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's not a cat in hells chance</u>
<u n="679" who="S0084">well you <trunc>ca</trunc> no exactly <pause dur="short"/> you can't compare yourself <pause dur="short"/> that even if actually all men would prefer an eighteen year old body <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>do</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> or if you think that they do <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that they do because ultimately an eighteen year old doesn't know what to do with their body anyway</u>
<u n="680" who="S0041">well yeah that's true</u>
<u n="681" who="S0084">there are no womanly bits to it <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> it's not going to be attractive for them <pause dur="short"/> really you don't know what you're doing at that age so</u>
<u n="682" who="S0041">move my head <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="683" who="S0084">oh mate <pause dur="short"/> well no wonder <pause dur="short"/> crazy girl</u>
<u n="684" who="S0041">it's a bit weird innit?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0084">I mean you just <pause dur="short"/> I think you get to the point where you think where you think there's no point being hard on yourself <pause dur="short"/> like everyone would rather be a bit taller <pause dur="short"/> a bit shorter <pause dur="short"/> a bit fatter <pause dur="short"/> a bit skinnier <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ka</trunc></u>
<u n="686" who="S0041">yeah <unclear/> has always said that she's coming back with my legs and I said that's okay I'll come back with your belly</u>
<u n="687" who="S0084">well there you go you see <pause dur="short"/> when I <unclear/> <event desc="sound of banging cutlery"/> I mean apart from I mean even people who think that appear to be confident aren't <pause dur="short"/> they're just putting on a front <pause dur="short"/> you just have to <pause dur="short"/> it's about finding a body that you're comfortable in <pause dur="short"/> that's you know</u>
<u n="688" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0084">healthy and that you can be satisfied with</u>
<u n="690" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0084">no  aren't you?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0041">that's seven years ago</u>
<u n="693" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> But you can't do that <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="694" who="S0041">Seven years ago</u>
<u n="695" who="S0084">you're a maniac</u>
<u n="696" who="S0041">in  head it's only about three minutes ago <unclear/></u>
<u n="697" who="S0084">well no <pause dur="short"/> well look <pause dur="short"/> this is it because I always think of myself as twenty-one</u>
<u n="698" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="699" who="S0084">and I'm not</u>
<u n="700" who="S0041">sounds fair <pause dur="short"/> sounds fair to me</u>
<u n="701" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> it's not going to happen <pause dur="short"/> not going to happen <pause dur="short"/> and that is a very very sad thought <pause dur="short"/> now what do I need?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0041">what do you need?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0084">A new brain</u>
<u n="704" who="S0041">brain please</u>
<u n="705" who="S0084">Pinky <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/>The pinky and the brain brain brain brain brain<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="706" who="S0041">oh that guy that wanted to go to Colchester was texting me again today</u>
<u n="707" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0041">and I've just <pause dur="short"/> I didn't hear from him for awhile</u>
<u n="709" who="S0084">is this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? Or is this a different one?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0041">this is a different one</u>
<u n="711" who="S0084">I like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't heard from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for awhile <pause dur="short"/> he'll come out of the woodwork in about a week with something really random <pause dur="short"/> as if he's never been away <pause dur="short"/> pretty normal</u>
<u n="713" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> pretty normal</u>
<u n="714" who="S0041">yeah this is the guy that wanted me to go up this weekend to a concert and I was like not going to be doing that  you're a  you're a killer</u>
<u n="715" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't even know you</u>
<u n="716" who="S0041">Don't even know you <pause dur="short"/> erm and he's <trunc>mes</trunc> he's messaged me <pause dur="short"/> hey girl <pause dur="short"/> k girl <pause dur="short"/> how are you doing?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0084">hmm mm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0041">what's the point of that message? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> fine thanks <pause dur="short"/> stuck in traffic how are you?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0041">erm so  he starts  he starts talking a little bit flirty</u>
<u n="721" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0041">erm been to the doctor <pause dur="short"/> checked out the leg <pause dur="short"/> bit of a poke <pause dur="short"/> erm with a <trunc>fla</trunc> and a bit of a poke and a flash of my knickers and he tells me I think I'm going to be okay</u>
<u n="723" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="724" who="S0041">and he wrote back something like can I see? And I was like what? My my ugly leg or my knickers? And he was like well it would definitely be the knickers</u>
<u n="725" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0041">erm but then <pause dur="short"/> which is all kind of light hearted but then he was like <pause dur="short"/> don't know just a bit full on like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> you know <trunc>sho</trunc> do you mean erm would you in person or in a picture? And started down this kind of seedy type of route <pause dur="short"/> but it was all it all the messages were quite funny type messages</u>
<u n="727" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="728" who="S0041">and you know when you just think there's something not quite quite right about you</u>
<u n="729" who="S0084">you weren't comfortable?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> he seemed a bit like <pause dur="short"/> I don't <pause dur="short"/> he was it might have been that he's just a bit of a geek and he didn't really know how to come across properly</u>
<u n="731" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> be flirty</u>
<u n="732" who="S0041">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was just uncomfortable</u>
<u n="733" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="734" who="S0041">erm anyway so he sent me a message saying something about a pig and I was like er anyway there's loads of me on the stupid site so why don't you send me one of you cos there's only  one of  one of you on there?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="736" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and he said okay then <pause dur="short"/> sent a picture which clearly wasn't taken just then <pause dur="short"/> so this is a kind of a pre-empted ready picture to my email <pause dur="short"/> and I swear to god it's a different guy <pause dur="short"/> it must be a different guy</u>
<u n="737" who="S0084">really he looks that different to the photo?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0041">really different</u>
<u n="739" who="S0084">huh</u>
<u n="740" who="S0041">like either this guy's cos the guy that was on the photograph on the Plenty Of Fish thing</u>
<u n="741" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="742" who="S0041">he's quite buff <pause dur="short"/> not massive but like if he was girl he'd be a size twelve fourteen</u>
<u n="743" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="744" who="S0041">with muscle</u>
<u n="745" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="746" who="S0041">the picture he sent me <pause dur="short"/> he's definitely a size eight ten <pause dur="short"/> no muscles <pause dur="short"/> so either he's got like undergone some dramatic weight loss which if you're  if you're  gonna then I don't understand how that would happen</u>
<u n="747" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No</u>
<u n="748" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he's and then he he's got these kind of you know those T-shirts with like that are cut cut around the collar?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0084">oh right yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't like that</u>
<u n="750" who="S0041">see his collar bones <pause dur="short"/> they are bigger than mine <pause dur="short"/> like you know the girly the girliness  on a boy  on a boy</u>
<u n="751" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm no I don't like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's gone wrong <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm he's definitely gone wrong and I swear I was like holy crap <pause dur="short"/> I opened it at work because I I just wanted to see what it was</u>
<u n="753" who="S0084">maybe he's got a disease</u>
<u n="754" who="S0041">do you think? Maybe he's just a liar</u>
<u n="755" who="S0084">maybe it's just a different person</u>
<u n="756" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="757" who="S0084">so he's he's gone wrong then</u>
<u n="758" who="S0041">so he's gone wrong</u>
<u n="759" who="S0084" trans="overlap">scratch <pause dur="short"/> delete</u>
<u n="760" who="S0041">scratch <pause dur="short"/> delete <pause dur="short"/> so I just didn't then reply to his messages</u>
<u n="761" who="S0084">fine</u>
<u n="762" who="S0041">his message saying I've sent it <pause dur="short"/> and I thought I'm not replying to that <pause dur="short"/> so let's hope he doesn't</u>
<u n="763" who="S0084">really takes the hint with that <pause dur="short"/> I think if you took sent a photo to someone and they stopped replying you would take the hint wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I did when er I didn't hear from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0041">I just thought he'd opened the email seen my picture and wasn't that impressed <pause dur="short"/> so I thought fine <pause dur="short"/> whatever</u>
<u n="767" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but instead it took him ten days to open his emails <pause dur="short"/> maybe he lives in a yak farm and doesn't have access to internet</u>
<u n="768" who="S0041">yak farm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0084">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s the kind of person who would work on a yak farm isn't he <pause dur="short"/> let's be honest</u>
<u n="770" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> and I mean he might say he lives in London but I've heard that's where the yak farms are</u>
<u n="771" who="S0084">that's where all the yak farms are</u>
<u n="772" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0084">in the metropolis</u>
<u n="774" who="S0041">in the big smoke</u>
<u n="775" who="S0084">in the city</u>
<u n="776" who="S0041" trans="overlap">where the yaks can breathe</u>
<u n="777" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sweet sweet smoggy air <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> delicious <pause dur="short"/> what about the one who was asking you out for a drink yesterday with your penis leg?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0041" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> with my penis leg <pause dur="short"/> penis leg <pause dur="short"/> erm he I was messaging him and what what's happened here is that he is basically as I've been writing to him when I've sent my phone number it was too long ago <pause dur="short"/> and I know it was too long ago because he didn't put it in his phone in time <pause dur="short"/> so know he he's obviously too ashamed that he didn't put it in his phone in time to ask me for it again and I'm not going to give it out again <pause dur="short"/> er which is quite amusing</u>
<u n="779" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="780" who="S0041">but er he was saying do I want to go over there? To <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0084">oh <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> that was it yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0041">erm I was like well not really because one you could be a killer erm and two I don't really know your housemates <pause dur="short"/> he said well you know it was something about they were thinking about having a party</u>
<u n="783" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0041">erm why don't you come come over? And I was like that doesn't make it any better that there's going to be a house full of people that I don't know <pause dur="short"/> that's not a winner</u>
<u n="785" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="786" who="S0041">and he was like well you don't have to come on your own <pause dur="short"/> I said well why should I drag people out to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's shit</u>
<u n="788" who="S0041">it's shit</u>
<u n="789" who="S0084">I've heard it's shit</u>
<u n="790" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so erm I was like well why don't you come here? And he was like what now? It was eleven O'clock at night and I said well I was thinking exactly this second unless you want to see me rocking my PJs</u>
<u n="791" who="S0084">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> and who wouldn't?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0041">and he said and who wouldn't?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="794" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well he sounds quite sweet <pause dur="short"/> quite erm just <trunc>la</trunc> laddish really</u>
<u n="795" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0041">bright but he was he's obviously going to be a mentalist I mean he trains the army people</u>
<u n="797" who="S0084">oh god</u>
<u n="798" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0084">and is he quite buff this <trunc>o</trunc>? This is the really big buff one?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0041">that's not the really big buff one <pause dur="short"/> this is just semi big buff one</u>
<u n="801" who="S0084">oh man <pause dur="short"/> who's the really big buff one?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0041">the really big buff one is the one from London that's like thirty but thinks he's forty but he's not at all</u>
<u n="803" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0041">him that said you know don't really want to be staying over with your date's dad</u>
<u n="805" who="S0084">that would be awkward</u>
<u n="806" who="S0041">little bit <pause dur="short"/> little bit awkward</u>
<u n="807" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0041">you'd proper wet yourself though</u>
<u n="809" who="S0084">oh I'd love that <pause dur="short"/> that would be hilarious</u>
<u n="810" who="S0041">and you'd totally play on it <pause dur="short"/> can you buy me dinner? That's what dads do</u>
<u n="811" who="S0084" trans="overlap">go for a smooch?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0041">new coat next please <pause dur="short"/> that's quite amusing <pause dur="short"/> but I I've I've trapped myself in a bit of a corner now because now I don't remember which ones are which if you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> and aren't they all called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? They've all got the same name</u>
<u n="814" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0084">I bet a lot of them are called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> they all seem to be called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="816" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's definitely a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="817" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what happened to that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm and that's why you should call them all <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0041">and or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> every time I write them a message <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I'm getting bored of him</u>
<u n="819" who="S0084">I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> what was the one with the who the name of the one who was wanting to go to the hotel? Hurrah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> I I I was going to tell you last night but it was quite late and I didn't know if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was still here or not <pause dur="short"/> I was going through my emails all two thousand <pause dur="short"/> just hitting delete delete cos I was just so wrecked and I couldn't sleep because I felt sick <pause dur="short"/> anyway I found him he'd basically the night when I was sat here having a drink with crazy horse and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he was texting me all that shit and I I got him to send me an email of him <pause dur="short"/> videos <pause dur="short"/> porn videos that he'd made with his girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> I was like I want to see your face <pause dur="short"/> like I want to <unclear/> it's you</u>
<u n="821" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="822" who="S0041">like he sent one of him <pause dur="short"/> cumming on him</u>
<u n="823" who="S0084">right yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0041">you couldn't see his face <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't see <unclear/> so it could have been fake <pause dur="short"/> I was like no send another one <pause dur="short"/> anyway I thought he'd only sent that one and one other one which was really quite graphic of of guy and girl kind of we're talking money shot</u>
<u n="825" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0041">yeah and I was like holy fuck and then just at the end of it you see them move and it flips up so you could see two faces</u>
<u n="827" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="828" who="S0041">so you could her and you could see it was him <pause dur="short"/> the same person as the pictures <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh <pause dur="short"/> well last night when I was hitting delete I didn't realise he'd sent another seven <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0084">he's sending photos of his ex girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> if you were <unclear/></u>
<u n="830" who="S0041" trans="overlap">videos <pause dur="short"/> videos <pause dur="short"/> not photographs <pause dur="short"/> videos so</u>
<u n="831" who="S0084">with sound?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> and one of them was really graphic <pause dur="short"/> really graphic</u>
<u n="833" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh man that's so wrong</u>
<u n="834" who="S0041">so he'd sent those two erm and then he'd sent one that was just a couple of seconds long because you could see his face in it</u>
<u n="835" who="S0084">what a nob</u>
<u n="836" who="S0041">erm of this girl yep yep yep</u>
<u n="837" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he's sent <trunc>pho</trunc> <unclear/> And you're just you know one person <pause dur="short"/> how many girls is he sending videos to?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0041">loads more probably <pause dur="short"/> and one of them is really bad <pause dur="short"/> really bad <pause dur="short"/> erm one of them is money shotage again and she's against a bar <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's a really strange camera angle cos I couldn't so I couldn't really see but you get to see a lot of her</u>
<u n="839" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="840" who="S0041">yeah and an other one is really bad <pause dur="short"/> the camera is on the floor and she's <pause dur="short"/> pretend the camera is here on the floor <pause dur="short"/> she's stood here and he's bent double like this</u>
<u n="841" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="842" who="S0041">so you can see kind of the full length of her</u>
<u n="843" who="S0084">tits hanging out</u>
<u n="844" who="S0041">tits hanging out and everything <pause dur="short"/> completely a go go</u>
<u n="845" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="846" who="S0041">he's stood about here and  I don't  I don't know what he is doing <pause dur="short"/> something</u>
<u n="847" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="848" who="S0041">and then <trunc>sh</trunc> you hear er say really really clearly <pause dur="short"/> really clearly <pause dur="short"/> make me cum please</u>
<u n="849" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0041">really clearly it's like you you are mortified for her cos if anybody kind of minutely knew her <pause dur="short"/> you'd knew it by that <pause dur="short"/> full sentence <pause dur="short"/> not just groaning or anything</u>
<u n="851" who="S0084">oh no</u>
<u n="852" who="S0041">and then he <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> and then which makes it worse <pause dur="short"/> he from whatever he's doing don't know <pause dur="short"/> comes over and basically puts his mouth there <pause dur="short"/> full full view <pause dur="short"/> you've got the full view of everything from down there</u>
<u n="853" who="S0084">bloody hell</u>
<u n="854" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was bad <pause dur="short"/> I was like holy fuck like as if you would send this to anyone <pause dur="short"/> ever <pause dur="short"/> it really if <pause dur="short"/> she she's shamed by all of it <pause dur="short"/> that was he he was less visible in them than she was</u>
<u n="855" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that upsets me <pause dur="short"/> boys are so wrong <pause dur="short"/> how does he not see that that's wrong?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it was his ex girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0084">I mean unless she was a complete cow and cheated on him with every man he's ever known</u>
<u n="858" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0084">there was absolutely no justification for that <pause dur="short"/> that's disgusting <pause dur="short"/> his just sending that out to any old woman that he chats to <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="860" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0084" trans="overlap">anybody that he meets <pause dur="short"/> he says you know what? I've got some really good videos for you</u>
<u n="862" who="S0041" trans="overlap">you really could tell it was her <pause dur="short"/> there was  there was  nothing about it <pause dur="short"/> if you knew the girl you would know it</u>
<u n="863" who="S0084">oh Jesus</u>
<u n="864" who="S0041">I couldn't believe it <pause dur="short"/> couldn't believe it</u>
<u n="865" who="S0084">I mean you know everyone exchanges you know a bit of sexy photos whatever <pause dur="short"/> but actually to send private videos I would die <pause dur="short"/> I've only ever recorded one video before and erm I've never done it since</u>
<u n="866" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="867" who="S0084">I mean it just because you just don't know what might get sent out</u>
<u n="868" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> especially now with frickin YouTube</u>
<u n="869" who="S0084">yeah that's what they say to the teenagers isn't it <pause dur="short"/> don't do it <pause dur="short"/> just don't take photos because obviously <pause dur="short"/> I mean they're all messing around and at school then the photos get passed around <pause dur="short"/> the you know girls called slags <pause dur="short"/> boys are patted on the back you know</u>
<u n="870" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember when a photograph of me in my underwear got passed around the school</u>
<u n="871" who="S0084">oh horrendous <pause dur="short"/> I probably was still playing with my Sylvanian Families <pause dur="short"/> I was a bit of a slow starter so I don't think I've got that to worry about</u>
<u n="872" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> We were in college <pause dur="short"/> it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually and it was on his phone which was fine cos I trusted him <pause dur="short"/> I must admit I still trust him now</u>
<u n="873" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0041">and but my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had gone on his phone and had found it and he was like holy fuck <pause dur="short"/> had seen it <pause dur="short"/> sent it to his own phone and that was it</u>
<u n="875" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos that's it <pause dur="short"/> cos it's so easy now <pause dur="short"/> one touch of a button and it's on Facebook <pause dur="short"/> twitter <pause dur="short"/> you name it</u>
<u n="876" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and obviously this was the time before any of that <pause dur="short"/> thank frick</u>
<u n="877" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="878" who="S0041">but you just wouldn't do it now <pause dur="short"/> that's why I thought my phone had gone I thought oh shit <pause dur="short"/> there's some really bad on there <pause dur="short"/> really bad <pause dur="short"/> I'm totally never doing that again</u>
<u n="879" who="S0084">where? I mean I just can't believe it <pause dur="short"/> it must have been that boy</u>
<u n="880" who="S0041">must have been</u>
<u n="881" who="S0084">it must have been them that stole it mustn't it?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0041">it's got to have been</u>
<u n="883" who="S0084">Cos we've never found it in the house</u>
<u n="884" who="S0041">nope <pause dur="short"/> wherever the hell they are <pause dur="short"/> if they end up on the internet they will have be as bad as the girl <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's no video <pause dur="short"/> it's no movie but it's me <pause dur="short"/> without a shadow of a doubt it would be bad</u>
<u n="885" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="886" who="S0041">the type of stuff your family would disown you for</u>
<u n="887" who="S0084">oh man</u>
<u n="888" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0084">that's why I get freaked out because I always think like you know when people say oh when your nan and granddad when they're dead they'll be with you always <pause dur="short"/> and I think oh that will be nice</u>
<u n="890" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="891" who="S0084">every so often usually when I'm doing something naughty I think oh my god <pause dur="short"/> imagine if your nana all very lovely during the day they're with you <pause dur="short"/> looking after you <pause dur="short"/> but when you're doing naughty things</u>
<u n="892" who="S0041">do you think?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0084">well I'm hoping they're off sitting on a cloud somewhere having a much better time than watching their granddaughters carry on with any old man that strolls through the door</u>
<u n="894" who="S0041">yeah yes <pause dur="short"/> oh shudder <pause dur="short"/> never thought of that did I <pause dur="short"/> oh if we pop it and find out that that's the case I'm going to be so embarrassed</u>
<u n="895" who="S0084">well then cos you've got to come back and watch your kids carry it on with any man that walks through so yeah</u>
<u n="896" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="897" who="S0084">erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> I don't know if they do <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0041" trans="overlap">well let's hope not <pause dur="short"/> I apologise in advance</u>
<u n="899" who="S0084">oh nanas</u>
<u n="900" who="S0041">poor to all the nanas <pause dur="short"/> to all the nanas</u>
<u n="901" who="S0084" trans="overlap">to all the nanas <pause dur="short"/> we're really sorry <pause dur="short"/> we just want to have fun</u>
<u n="902" who="S0041">oh and the guy the Colchester guy was saying this is how I knew I was that I was a bit like dubious cos he was like <pause dur="short"/> so when are you next coming to Colchester? And I said er so when are you next coming to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> who the hell wants to go to Colchester?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0041">definitely not me <pause dur="short"/> and he said erm oh er if I come are you going to put me up for the night and look after me?</u>
<u n="905" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="906" who="S0041">and I said well I might <pause dur="short"/> cos I thought I'm not going to that <pause dur="short"/> and if he said well  if you can guarantee  if you can guarantee it then I'll come as in if if he's got a bed for the night then he'll come round</u>
<u n="907" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0041">and I said have you not thought about what will happen if we don't actually get on?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0084">yeah I know it's weird isn't it</u>
<u n="910" who="S0041">and he said oh we'll just have to make sure that we do <pause dur="short"/> and I thought ah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0084">rapey <pause dur="short"/> sounds quite rapey</u>
<u n="912" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sounds very rapey</u>
<u n="913" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0041">and I've just thought no <pause dur="short"/> no no no</u>
<u n="915" who="S0084">leave your Rohypnol at home please <pause dur="short"/> fucking</u>
<u n="916" who="S0041">leave all of you at home please</u>
<u n="917" who="S0084">please don't <pause dur="short"/> just actually just don't <pause dur="short"/> because at least that with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know for all his faults for which there are many</u>
<u n="918" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="919" who="S0084">primarily with being a psychopathic maniac</u>
<u n="920" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="921" who="S0084">erm he was you know right <pause dur="short"/> well I'll get a hotel <pause dur="short"/> you know I want to come and meet you and <pause dur="short"/> there was no expectation that he would stay here <pause dur="short"/> he was polite</u>
<u n="922" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yep it <unclear/> offered it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="924" who="S0041">just mm</u>
<u n="925" who="S0084">and that's what I don't like about the boy <pause dur="short"/> the boys</u>
<u n="926" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's about the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="927" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't gone out <pause dur="short"/> he's gone to bed</u>
<u n="928" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah no <pause dur="short"/> no no no <pause dur="short"/> so he was a he's a right off</u>
<u n="929" who="S0084">they've just all got to go</u>
<u n="930" who="S0041">they've all got to go <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> so quite a I quite trusted in the er the one in Afghanistan's quite funny but I think he's thick <pause dur="short"/> he's</u>
<u n="931" who="S0084" trans="overlap">probably but then that's you know it depends what you want <pause dur="short"/> I mean no one's looking for a boyfriend so</u>
<u n="932" who="S0041">he's lovely <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="933" who="S0084">you know for shits and giggles</u>
<u n="934" who="S0041">fun for shits and giggles</u>
<u n="935" who="S0084">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know he's not boyfriend material for me <pause dur="short"/> would be for some girl but not for me</u>
<u n="936" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fine for shits and giggles</u>
<u n="937" who="S0084">but he is hilarious</u>
<u n="938" who="S0041">he's really funny <pause dur="short"/> I even told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about him you know</u>
<u n="939" who="S0084">oh god <pause dur="short"/> he is mental</u>
<u n="940" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="941" who="S0084">he was really upset about the polar bear facts</u>
<u n="942" who="S0041">was he? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Was he?</u>
<u n="943" who="S0084">he really took it to heart yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was really funny <pause dur="short"/> I think cos he he he wanted to have a fact but there were no facts <pause dur="short"/> we were the ones giving the facts about the polar bears and I think he took it to heart</u>
<u n="944" who="S0041">I really wish we'd never had the polar bear ice cream</u>
<u n="945" who="S0084">oh I really want the polar bear ice cream</u>
<u n="946" who="S0041">yeah I wish we'd never tried it now cos now I know I really love it <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't even like ice cream before <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't even that fussed</u>
<u n="947" who="S0084">oh what have done to yourself?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0041">ruined it didn't I</u>
<u n="949" who="S0084">oh man</u>
<u n="950" who="S0041">ruined it</u>
<u n="951" who="S0084">that is a big big shame</u>
<u n="952" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="953" who="S0084">probably time to go to bed</u>
<u n="954" who="S0041">yeah I think I'm going to erm go and check my emails and go to the Bedfordshire</u>
<u n="955" who="S0084">I think it's time</u>
<u n="956" who="S0041">Cos I erm I want to get up before work tomorrow</u>
<u n="957" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> don't do it <pause dur="short"/> it's bad for you <pause dur="short"/> I told you</u>
<u n="958" who="S0041"><unclear/> at least I was going to get a washing my hair but if we're not going to go swimming tomorrow then</u>
<u n="959" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="960" who="S0041">not going to <pause dur="short"/> but I'll get up and just shower the rest <unclear/></u>
<u n="961" who="S0084">yeah do it <pause dur="short"/> just say no kids <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0041">thanks <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to take this with me <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> juice</u>
<u n="963" who="S0084">to to beddie</u>
<u n="964" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="965" who="S0084" trans="overlap">right let's turn you oh <pause dur="short"/> it's dark <pause dur="short"/> I'm scared <pause dur="short"/> is the grudge coming?</u>
<u n="966" who="S0041">oh my god I'd forgotten about The Grudge <pause dur="short"/> you had to put it back in my head</u>
<u n="967" who="S0084">the grudge is probably under your pillow</u>
<u n="968" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="969" who="S0084">I saw it</u>
<u n="970" who="S0041">you did not see it at all</u>
<u n="971" who="S0084">I didn't want to tell you cos I thought you might get scared</u>
<u n="972" who="S0041">about what?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0084">the grudge is in there</u>
<u n="974" who="S0041">look at that lot</u>
<u n="975" who="S0084">Grudge's little babies in there <pause dur="short"/> can you see his little fingers coming around the box?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0041">stop it <pause dur="short"/> stop this filth <pause dur="short"/> stop this filth</u>
<u n="977" who="S0084">it's it's funny <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="978" who="S0041">that flat one will go on top of my wardrobe</u>
<u n="979" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="980" who="S0041">those three</u>
<u n="981" who="S0084">but you've got a lot of space under your bed <pause dur="short"/> you just need to re-jig I think</u>
<u n="982" who="S0041">yeah I think I need to re-jig</u>
<u n="983" who="S0084">I might be worth this going <pause dur="short"/> erm and plus the books can go on the bookcase <pause dur="short"/> I know that's a renegade idea</u>
<u n="984" who="S0041">the books are not going to come out of there because  they're not  they're not book books <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> Men are from Mars and Women are from Venus is in there actually so I'll fish that out for you before I get it shipped away</u>
<u n="985" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="986" who="S0041">erm but the dictionaries</u>
<u n="987" who="S0084">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> it's not anything that you would actually want out</u>
<u n="988" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> so it they really need to be stored but I'll put them in the cupboard up there</u>
<u n="989" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> you need to get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on the case <pause dur="short"/> she could probably put you up at a picture hook or I'll get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to if you wanted it up</u>
<u n="990" who="S0041">no I don't want it up <pause dur="short"/> don't want it up <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>c</trunc> I could actually just run it over to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="991" who="S0084">just put put pack it all away to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> if it's all stuff that you want to keep but you don't need</u>
<u n="992" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> when I next go over there I'll take it over <pause dur="short"/> maybe for the next few weeks I'll shove it in the cupboard up there</u>
<u n="993" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> plan</u>
<u n="994" who="S0041">Cos like that's definitely a fire hazard going on <pause dur="short"/> just just there <pause dur="short"/> that's definitely <unclear/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0084" trans="overlap">all of that yeah <pause dur="short"/> and we won't be able to get to the fire panel wall if the fire alarm goes off and trust me when I say <unclear/> you're going to want to turn that bad boy off as soon as humanly possible cos it feels like you're brain is about to fall out</u>
<u n="996" who="S0041">yeah about that</u>
<u n="997" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0041">although I have acquired some tennis racquets and some badminton racquets so we can play</u>
<u n="999" who="S0084">is badminton with the shuttle cocks?</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0041">yes yes</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0084">cock</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah so</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0084">erm that sounds fun <pause dur="short"/> a bit of badminton action</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> don't really know how or when or where but you know</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0084">yes <pause dur="short"/> all of that <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="place"/> has got them outside</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0041">does it?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0041">could go play <pause dur="short"/> not that I'm any good at it but it will be fun</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0084">I haven't played since school but it's worth <unclear/></u>
<u n="1010" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no me neither</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0084">probably wait wait till your willy's gone down</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wait till me willy's less excited and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then get out the other cocks so</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> How appropriate</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0041"><event desc="sound of cymbal crashing"/> Yes</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0084">alright <pause dur="short"/> brush my teeth and then bed</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0041">bon soir my dear <pause dur="short"/> bon soir</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0084">thank you for the pancakes</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0041">you're welcome</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0084">night</u>
</body>
</text>
