<text id="S6Q6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>2:00:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-12-18</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>5</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0592 S0595 S0596 S0597 S0598</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s house, Surrey</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>TV series, university, work, apprenticeships, illness, Christmas, presents, friends, family.  </topics>
		<activity>Friends gathering for Christmas talking about university and general life. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0592">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Frimley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Camberley (home) Lancaster (uni)</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years / 3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0595">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Frimley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>British</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Ashville</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Care support worker</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0596">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aldershot, Hampshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Surrey</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Aldershot</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Trainee Accountant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0597">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Frimley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Frimley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Navel Combat Systems engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0598">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Frimley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Estuary English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Winchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student/ Retail Customer Assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0595">then you don't have to have erm adverts</u>
<u n="2" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0595">and I don't like Current Theory</u>
<u n="4" who="S0596">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0595">I'm watching Fringe at the moment</u>
<u n="6" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0596">which one's that?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0597">I tried watching that I've only watched the first episode</u>
<u n="9" who="S0595">it's good you have to watch like a few episodes now I'm in series three but like I've watched like ten episodes today</u>
<u n="10" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0595">and they're each like half an hour forty-five minutes long</u>
<u n="12" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0597">it's really hard not to binge watch it plays the next video for you</u>
<u n="15" who="S0595">it does</u>
<u n="16" who="S0597">it's like oh okay if I have to</u>
<u n="17" who="S0595" trans="overlap">okay ten ten's a a bit of an <trunc>ex</trunc>exaggeration I've watched probably about four or five episodes today though</u>
<u n="18" who="S0596">I used to do that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0592">I haven't done that in a while actually I don't really watch TV at the moment</u>
<u n="20" who="S0595">no I haven't either but I was like it was good cos this week I worked Sunday Monday Tuesday cos it's a Sunday to Saturday week</u>
<u n="21" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0596">we had the other week I had a day off work and I just watched like four episodes of I don't even know what and they were like an hour each</u>
<u n="24" who="S0597">you don't know what?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0596">I can't remember what it was but I watched like four in a row</u>
<u n="26" who="S0592">it must have been a really good show if you don't remember what it was</u>
<u n="27" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0597">yeah if you watched four hours of it but don't remember anything</u>
<u n="29" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah well I was I was ill</u>
<u n="30" who="S0592">you were ill oh</u>
<u n="31" who="S0597">oh was this last week Friday?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0596">erm I don't remember when</u>
<u n="33" who="S0597">Friday</u>
<u n="34" who="S0592">you don't remember anything do you?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0596">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0597">no</u>
<u n="37" who="S0596">I'm I'm I'm fine at work I like go to talk to my boss and he's like oh do you remember when you did this? no do you remember what this is? no</u>
<u n="38" who="S0597" trans="overlap">early onset dementia no</u>
<u n="39" who="S0595">how is your work?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0596">it's fine</u>
<u n="41" who="S0595">what are you actually doing there an apprenticeship?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0596" trans="overlap">it's all like yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0595">in?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0596">accounting</u>
<u n="45" who="S0595">I thought so I was just checking</u>
<u n="46" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0596">yeah it's kind of boring I don't have anything to do at the moment</u>
<u n="48" who="S0595">yeah what do you actually do?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0596">I erm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0595">and don't say accounting</u>
<u n="51" who="S0592" trans="overlap">numbers</u>
<u n="52" who="S0596">eh I do accounts erm no but clients all businesses have to produce a certain file of accounts are required to give us their records and we produce the accounts which say how much money you earned how much money spent</u>
<u n="53" who="S0595">I do that for my mum and she gave me all her receipts and there was two hundred receipts for the whole year</u>
<u n="54" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah our clients do that I do one one client I'm working on at the moment and they gave us five folders full of receipts most of which have been stood on</u>
<u n="55" who="S0592">stood on?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0596">yeah he's like he's like a mechanic and all his receipts have like footprints on them</u>
<u n="57" who="S0592">right that's weird</u>
<u n="58" who="S0595">no I sat down with mum and she said you have to put even the little things and like some things are like ninety-eight P and I was ah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0595">it was on my day off as well <vocal desc="laugh"/> I sat there cos you have to do the months as well like all in the same month I sat there for like three hours sorting out what which month cos you've got to like the date's not always on the same part of the receipt and I was like</u>
<u n="61" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0595">so bored doing this out of kindness</u>
<u n="63" who="S0597">it's a massive job</u>
<u n="64" who="S0596">yeah I do this for a living</u>
<u n="65" who="S0595">ah I'd hate to</u>
<u n="66" who="S0592">I wouldn't do it out of kindness I'd get mum to pay me if I was doing that</u>
<u n="67" who="S0595">you want to do it you want to do accounting</u>
<u n="68" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah I do <trunc>a</trunc> I do actually enjoy it so</u>
<u n="69" who="S0595">yeah I didn't</u>
<u n="70" who="S0596">maybe that makes me sad but</u>
<u n="71" who="S0595">no what do you do now?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0597">erm I have an apprenticeship as well first whole year's college though</u>
<u n="73" who="S0595">doing?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0597">erm called er</u>
<u n="75" who="S0596">oh that systems engineering</u>
<u n="76" who="S0597">yeah that</u>
<u n="77" who="S0595">exactly</u>
<u n="78" who="S0597">I'm working for BA</u>
<u n="79" who="S0596">that's my mum's steak knife</u>
<u n="80" who="S0595">bugger</u>
<u n="81" who="S0592">what?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0596">what?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0595">I left it on the table</u>
<u n="84" who="S0597">what the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0595">I have a card for your mum</u>
<u n="86" who="S0596">oh right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0595">erm I wrote and mum was like don't forget it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0592">oh you you put that on it</u>
<u n="89" who="S0595">I wrote it about three weeks ago and I just keep forgetting to come round and put it through the door and she was like you must take it you're actually going over there and I'm like but mum</u>
<u n="90" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0595">I'm really annoyed I've ordered <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a really cool present it didn't arrive</u>
<u n="92" who="S0592">ah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0597">erm sorry yours hasn't turned up yet</u>
<u n="94" who="S0592">no I got I I ordered some for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday cos he's really into this erm I don't know what it's called like a musical artist called Cry Wolf erm it it's just what he's into Cry Wolf but I ordered a T-shirt for him but it's from America and I'm not sure it's even going to come in time for his birthday let alone Christmas so</u>
<u n="95" who="S0597">yeah I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and she knows I won't get them till the second of January</u>
<u n="96" who="S0596">I got a bit over excited about Christmas so I had everyone's presents by November I think I can't remember what they are</u>
<u n="97" who="S0595" trans="overlap">so did I</u>
<u n="98" who="S0596">I can't remember what I got anyone but they're just over there so</u>
<u n="99" who="S0595" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="100" who="S0597">it's a surprise for you as well</u>
<u n="101" who="S0595">oh I haven't wrapped them all but I got all of my presents before the third of December</u>
<u n="102" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0595">and then I sat down today cos I had like this box in my room that I'd just filled</u>
<u n="104" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0595">and just kept putting a bag on top so you couldn't see in to it</u>
<u n="106" who="S0597"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0595">and I sat down and wrapped something I was like I I was finding stuff I was like oh cos my brother <unclear/> he's like what do you want for Christmas? I went oh I want a a hamper of joy being stupid and he's like I'll get you one if I get if I get him one so I'd bought him like this ridiculous erm I went into the <unclear/> I was like oh my god I bought him a fart whistle you know those fun snaps that you chuck at the ground and they like they exploding snap things</u>
<u n="108" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0595">bought him them I bought him a Lego digger to make I bought him a little bouncy frog you know the frogs that you flick and they bounce</u>
<u n="110" who="S0597">oh they got they little tack on the end and they</u>
<u n="111" who="S0595">I bought him bouncing balls and then I bought him edible floss I don't know</u>
<u n="112" who="S0596">sounds weird</u>
<u n="113" who="S0595">I know I bought him socks and everything and I was like going through all the stuff I was oh I know what this does</u>
<u n="114" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0595">loads of people like my sister I've bought her Busted are doing a reunited tour next year I've bought her tickets for me and her to go I bought them like two months ago and I so want to tell her but I can't I've kept it a secret for so long I've got a week to go it's getting so hard cos she keeps questioning saying what have I got? what have I got? and I was like I haven't bought it yet</u>
<u n="116" who="S0592">cos on Christmas Eve what have I got? I I haven't bought it yet</u>
<u n="117" who="S0597">I'm going out tonight at midnight to buy it</u>
<u n="118" who="S0595"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's been hard trying to keep it a secret</u>
<u n="119" who="S0597">is that the end of your base okay not quite</u>
<u n="120" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really annoyed me said he won't be here till like half seven seven o'clock and I have to leave cos I have to go with my sister somewhere at seven thirty I want to see his face when he opens his present it's from both me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we're being really stupid</u>
<u n="121" who="S0597">what is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doing?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0595">decorating his house</u>
<u n="123" who="S0597">right</u>
<u n="124" who="S0596">that can't wait</u>
<u n="125" who="S0595">apparently they started and his mum wants him to finish the wall before he comes</u>
<u n="126" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="127" who="S0595">or something which is fair enough he he can't just leave like a little bit of a wall not done</u>
<u n="128" who="S0596">he did <unclear/> though</u>
<u n="129" who="S0592">mm my mum did most of the decorating and I didn't really help I wish I did but I just sat there on my laptop</u>
<u n="130" who="S0597">we have too many decorations for our tree it's ridiculous and our tree is really big</u>
<u n="131" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I did I did most of the decorating but it's only that so</u>
<u n="132" who="S0597">yeah well you've seen our tree and how much stuff is on it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0592">our tree isn't up yet</u>
<u n="135" who="S0596">I did the Christmas tree at work as well</u>
<u n="136" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0597">yeah but you like decorating</u>
<u n="138" who="S0596">but yeah but I I didn't like ask to do it I just got kind of like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like oh who is going to put up the Christmas tree this year? and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s artistic isn't she? and <unclear>I kind of just thought</unclear></u>
<u n="139" who="S0597">mm  <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0596">well okay you can do it this year</u>
<u n="141" who="S0597" trans="overlap">that's what you get for giving out personal details</u>
<u n="142" who="S0592">is that a personal detail?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0596" trans="overlap">well I have talked about myself</u>
<u n="144" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0596">I have interests</u>
<u n="146" who="S0597">a personal <trunc>I</trunc> thingy</u>
<u n="147" who="S0596">I literally <trunc>ha</trunc> <trunc>say</trunc> it  says on my CV that I'm artistic so I kind of have to like</u>
<u n="148" who="S0592">oh I lied yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0597">who reads CVs any more?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0592">who what?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0596">Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> did when he</u>
<u n="152" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I said who reads CVs any more?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0596">apparently</u>
<u n="154" who="S0592">I I hope a lot of employers read CVs <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos</u>
<u n="155" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0597">well they don't like go through them thoroughly</u>
<u n="157" who="S0595">what's this?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0596" trans="overlap">Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> read my CV</u>
<u n="159" who="S0592">CVs</u>
<u n="160" who="S0595">ah I'm so happy I only sent off my UCAS and I never I only got the <unclear/> cos like last year I didn't get any till like February</u>
<u n="161" who="S0597">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0595">but each day I've been getting one I'm like oh oh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0597">oh oh</u>
<u n="164" who="S0595">but I have a like a mental log of it in my head of course I put it in like the <unclear/> it's like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0595">but like the one in Brighton starts at eight o'clock in the morning but my brother lives in <anon type="place"/> which is like a fifteen minute drive so I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can I come stay with you?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0595">I'll probably stay with him like for <anon type="place"/> never been to that uni <anon type="place"/> never been to that uni <anon type="place"/> I have but that starts at like nine so it's alright</u>
<u n="169" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0595">and the <anon type="place"/> one starts at one so</u>
<u n="171" who="S0597">have you spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at all? is she alright?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0595">mm she's happy she's not her job is very harder than she thought it was going to be</u>
<u n="173" who="S0597">what is she doing?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0595">care assistant but she's bank so she literally gets a text saying can you do this shift this shift this shift?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0596">oh yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0595">like the night before</u>
<u n="177" who="S0597">oh so she like zero hour contract</u>
<u n="178" who="S0595">mm like she didn't know she was like she she had training today which finished at five but then they asked her to work from five till like late on</u>
<u n="179" who="S0597">that's why zero hour contracts are abusive and the government considered getting rid of them</u>
<u n="180" who="S0596">well yeah but they're also really good for some people</u>
<u n="181" who="S0597">I'm not saying I'm not saying they're bad</u>
<u n="182" who="S0595" trans="overlap">yeah like she wants to do it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0597">yeah but</u>
<u n="185" who="S0595">cos she wasn't going to come anyway because of like she was going to come but later because of her training and stuff</u>
<u n="186" who="S0592">I dunno they're not for me sort of zero hour contracts just because I like to be prepared for if I need to go to work kind of thing</u>
<u n="187" who="S0597">it is nice to know cos then you could plan around it</u>
<u n="188" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0596">but then you can like organise yourself</u>
<u n="190" who="S0595" trans="overlap">that's why I have <trunc>Chris</trunc> that's why I have Christmas off cos I want to get flexi work but I <trunc>sho</trunc> cos of the <trunc>tr</trunc> I'm doing a training programme with the NHS professionals they should I should get my things a month in advance but I don't so I went to my boss I was like I went to my boss like can I can I? I <trunc>s</trunc> I don't know why I was so nervous I was like so what's happening over Christmas? cos this was like in the end of November I was like I want to organise Christmas but I can't cos like I can't give you days when you can work and stuff so I was like could I have this day? he said yeah this day off just ticked loads of days off and I was like thanks yeah those biscuits are too good</u>
<u n="191" who="S0592">they are aren't they? I bought them</u>
<u n="192" who="S0597"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just take credit I bought them</u>
<u n="193" who="S0592">yeah they are they're nice though</u>
<u n="194" who="S0597">you look like you have red in your hair it's from like the lamp on the back of it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0595">my hair's a really weird color at the moment</u>
<u n="196" who="S0596">it's nice</u>
<u n="197" who="S0595">I tried to dye it dark brown and it went black still trying to wash it out <pause dur="long"/> I just want to sit and eat these</u>
<u n="198" who="S0592">that's fine</u>
<u n="199" who="S0597">that's all we ever do at these parties</u>
<u n="200" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0595">yeah just sit around and eat food</u>
<u n="202" who="S0592">it's yeah it's just an excuse to eat eat bad things</u>
<u n="203" who="S0596">oh I I <trunc>ca</trunc> I can eat this bad thing cos I'm at a party it would be rude not to</u>
<u n="204" who="S0597">I have to tell this to the guys at work oh what do you do at parties? sit around and eat food</u>
<u n="205" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0597">you don't even go out? no I know cos none of my friends go out</u>
<u n="207" who="S0592">oh hello</u>
<u n="208" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0597">oh you're back <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s depressed at the moment</u>
<u n="212" who="S0592">why?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0596">I don't know he's a bit mental</u>
<u n="214" who="S0592">hello</u>
<u n="215" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looks nice</u>
<u n="216" who="S0596">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fine</u>
<u n="217" who="S0597">yeah that's cos he his bed was put back where it should be</u>
<u n="218" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s depressed so now he doesn't attack <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> any more so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s happy <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0597">feed me</u>
<u n="220" who="S0595">fine to meet you oi</u>
<u n="221" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0597">sorry dear <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="223" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0596">what?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0592">what do you want? <pause dur="long"/> oh there we go</u>
<u n="226" who="S0596">I don't think he's going to ea biscuits</u>
<u n="227" who="S0595">my cat does</u>
<u n="228" who="S0592">my cats have been erm stealing scones</u>
<u n="229" who="S0597">scones?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I <unclear/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0592">yeah I think cos erm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0595" trans="overlap">my cat really likes your bread</u>
<u n="233" who="S0592">I think cos they're cos they're butter scones</u>
<u n="234" who="S0597">okay</u>
<u n="235" who="S0592">but they've been licking the scones and eating them so they're weird but they've been doing it they've done it twice now apparently</u>
<u n="236" who="S0597">so the scones are a bit hit and miss then are they?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0592">yeah I think I think he was just</u>
<u n="238" who="S0595" trans="overlap">have you got cream and strawberries?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0597">I don't know</u>
<u n="240" who="S0596" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="241" who="S0592">I think he just</u>
<u n="242" who="S0596" trans="overlap">got some strawberries in the garden I think</u>
<u n="243" who="S0595">you shouldn't have them now</u>
<u n="244" who="S0596">they're still growing <pause dur="short"/> gimme one</u>
<u n="245" who="S0597">I like strawberry macaroons</u>
<u n="246" who="S0592">I like them as well can I have one?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0597">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er I have good taste</u>
<u n="248" who="S0592">thank you oh have you put one on a plate? oh oh</u>
<u n="249" who="S0595">that that put that <unclear/> on there <pause dur="long"/> macaroon party</u>
<u n="250" who="S0596">I think I might have some blueberries or raspberries maybe</u>
<u n="251" who="S0595">don't like blueberries and raspberries I just wanted the whipped cream part</u>
<u n="252" who="S0596">what about an orange? they go into that</u>
<u n="253" who="S0592">orange <unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0595" trans="overlap">there they go <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> I was petrified <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0597" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> I was petrified <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0596">I do apologise I've been having issues with my playlist I had to delete like ten songs off it <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't even know how they got on there</u>
<u n="257" who="S0598">what's the white one for?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0596">from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for me some scanners</u>
<u n="259" who="S0597">no it's not</u>
<u n="260" who="S0596">yeah it is I can feel it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0597">no it's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0596">it is</u>
<u n="263" who="S0592">you have to act surprised though</u>
<u n="264" who="S0596">or the one underneath</u>
<u n="265" who="S0595">that's my dad it's <trunc>no</trunc> erm er like heater for the wall</u>
<u n="266" who="S0596">I love Christmas</u>
<u n="267" who="S0595">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0596">it's even better now that I have money to spend</u>
<u n="269" who="S0595">uhu</u>
<u n="270" who="S0596">that's why I got like</u>
<u n="271" who="S0595">I get paid weekly as well</u>
<u n="272" who="S0597">oh lucky you</u>
<u n="273" who="S0595">it's useful</u>
<u n="274" who="S0597">why do go out and spend it all every week? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0595">no I said to myself that one week I'll spend it the next week I'll put it away</u>
<u n="276" who="S0592">is someone knocking?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0597">no that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> upstairs</u>
<u n="278" who="S0592">I was just hearing things</u>
<u n="279" who="S0595">good plan</u>
<u n="280" who="S0597">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0596" trans="overlap">shall I run out and buy some more?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0595">and when you do get cream</u>
<u n="284" who="S0596">I've got milk</u>
<u n="285" who="S0592">oh wow</u>
<u n="286" who="S0597">you could whip it really aggressively and hope something happens</u>
<u n="287" who="S0596">I got butter</u>
<u n="288" who="S0592">it's just yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0596">just put a hunk of butter in it</u>
<u n="290" who="S0592">if you beat up eggs I guess you can just like do it like that as well</u>
<u n="291" who="S0596">eggs?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0592">actually no I'm thinking of a different thing aren't I?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0596">I'm just going to go to my cow and just milk my cow and make some cream from it okay?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0592">I was thinking of erm I was actually thinking of making meringue not whipped cream it it is a bit like counterproductive isn't it?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0595" trans="overlap">we need more meringues</u>
<u n="296" who="S0592">just make more meringue</u>
<u n="297" who="S0596">is meringue healthy?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0595">and then meringues with er get a bowl of whipped cream put the meringue in it crush it</u>
<u n="299" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0597">could just eat them</u>
<u n="301" who="S0596">I don't like whipped cream or fruit</u>
<u n="302" who="S0592">I love whipped cream</u>
<u n="303" who="S0595">you're weird</u>
<u n="304" who="S0597">you could eat a banana with it</u>
<u n="305" who="S0595" trans="overlap">and then</u>
<u n="306" who="S0596">I don't like bananas</u>
<u n="307" who="S0592">do you like anything?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0597">grapes?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0596">no</u>
<u n="310" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="311" who="S0597">grapes</u>
<u n="312" who="S0596">no I I don't like anything except meringue</u>
<u n="313" who="S0595" trans="overlap">put grated chocolate in it that would be oh oh that would be quite nice actually</u>
<u n="314" who="S0596" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0597">do you like mince pies? no?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0596">er er I didn't buy any cos I didn't think anyone liked them apart from you</u>
<u n="317" who="S0597">yeah I I</u>
<u n="318" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I don't like them</u>
<u n="319" who="S0592"><trunc>mi</trunc><trunc>mi</trunc>mince pies are okay</u>
<u n="320" who="S0597">I forgot everyone doesn't like them</u>
<u n="321" who="S0592">I I haven't had them in a while though I feel like I can only eat half of a mince pie and then it's too much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0596">we should we should get some mini mince pies then</u>
<u n="323" who="S0592">maybe yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0596">I'm gonna eat that now</u>
<u n="325" who="S0597">bite size ones</u>
<u n="326" who="S0592">bite size mince pies <pause dur="short"/> that'd be good actually I'd eat those but</u>
<u n="327" who="S0595">what's the <unclear/> thing in the packet that erm behind the Sensations?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0597">what this?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0596">erm weird cinnamon-flavoured cake biscuit things</u>
<u n="331" who="S0597" trans="overlap">those those things?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0592">oh I had enough of those</u>
<u n="333" who="S0598">oh they've got haven't those oh I don't eat those oh they're <trunc>lu</trunc>luchen</u>
<u n="334" who="S0596">luchen</u>
<u n="335" who="S0595">gluten</u>
<u n="336" who="S0597">they just taste so weird</u>
<u n="337" who="S0592">no they're I quite like them actually</u>
<u n="338" who="S0596" trans="overlap">they're they're they're kind of weird but nice</u>
<u n="339" who="S0592">they've they've got a weird texture I think</u>
<u n="340" who="S0598">what flavours of dip?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0596">erm I don't know spicy</u>
<u n="342" who="S0595">don't say tomato because I know</u>
<u n="343" who="S0597">it's hot salsa</u>
<u n="344" who="S0596" trans="overlap">erm it's hot salsa</u>
<u n="345" who="S0597">this is a party song <pause dur="short"/> is this Christmassy?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0596">I don't know I don't remember what happened</u>
<u n="347" who="S0597">it doesn't feel like Christmas it's way too warm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0592">no it's much colder up in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0597">is it?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0597">what?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0592">it's always windy like</u>
<u n="353" who="S0595" trans="overlap">my dad's in Munich at the moment</u>
<u n="354" who="S0597">Munich <pause dur="short"/> any pictures going off?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0595">mm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0597">no one will get that</u>
<u n="357" who="S0596">I get it</u>
<u n="358" who="S0597" trans="overlap">do you get that? do you? what the Munich crunch?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0597">how do you know about that? did we do that in?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0596" trans="overlap">cos I did history</u>
<u n="363" who="S0592">she she she she was in she was in our class <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0597">I was I was thinking we did it at A level</u>
<u n="365" who="S0595" trans="overlap">his packing</u>
<u n="366" who="S0592">no no we did it at GCSE</u>
<u n="367" who="S0595">oh it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s class</u>
<u n="368" who="S0592">we didn't we didn't even do Germany at AS</u>
<u n="369" who="S0595" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0592">we we we we did Russia</u>
<u n="371" who="S0597">oh yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><unclear/> quite <unclear/> overnight</u>
<u n="373" who="S0597">it's been so long that</u>
<u n="374" who="S0596" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="375" who="S0592">this <trunc>sh</trunc>shows how much you er</u>
<u n="376" who="S0597">retained</u>
<u n="377" who="S0592">retained from that course to be honest I didn't retain much either so that's fine I hated it it sucked</u>
<u n="378" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I spoke to Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> the other day</u>
<u n="379" who="S0592">oh did you?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0597">on Facebook</u>
<u n="381" who="S0595">I saw Mrs <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> today</u>
<u n="382" who="S0597">did you?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0596">isn't she like really pregnant?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0595">no her baby's a week old</u>
<u n="385" who="S0596" trans="overlap">not any more okay</u>
<u n="386" who="S0595">it's the most adorable looking little baby I've</u>
<u n="387" who="S0597">ever seen</u>
<u n="388" who="S0595">no no</u>
<u n="389" who="S0597">they grow up quickly in the first week</u>
<u n="390" who="S0595">no oh my god it was the most cutest looking baby but she's still like got her little flobber belly</u>
<u n="391" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0595">I was like I don't think she recognised who I was <pause dur="short"/> I went hi</u>
<u n="393" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0597">random girls coming up to me and saying hi</u>
<u n="395" who="S0595">no she did after a while well not after a while after I said <pause dur="short"/> who I was</u>
<u n="396" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="397" who="S0595">and then I saw <pause dur="short"/> who's our <trunc>te</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0596">oh right</u>
<u n="399" who="S0595">the other day as well <pause dur="short"/> she's pregnant again <pause dur="short"/> she's now moved and lives now in <anon type="place"/> at some new new place that's opened <pause dur="short"/> which I think's better for her not teaching <pause dur="short"/> no offence to her</u>
<u n="400" who="S0597">who's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0595">our tutor</u>
<u n="402" who="S0596" trans="overlap">our form tutor</u>
<u n="403" who="S0592">yeah Miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0597">our Miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0595">computer <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> whatever you like to call her</u>
<u n="407" who="S0592">yeah what did Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> have to say?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0597">oh cos erm I haven't <unclear/> on my friends list of er <unclear/> and he like said he couldn't come</u>
<u n="409" who="S0595" trans="overlap">hey look <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you want some do you want some meringue?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="411" who="S0597">and that he'd try and come to the next one and we just I asked him if he was still teaching at the other school in <anon type="place"/> and he said he is but he's thinking of quitting or working at a private school instead</u>
<u n="412" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="413" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come here</u>
<u n="414" who="S0592">last time he spoke to me was</u>
<u n="415" who="S0596" trans="overlap">come here</u>
<u n="416" who="S0592">when I got my A level results and he was telling me don't be too disappointed it'll be fine I'm like okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0597">I keep forgetting I have him on Facebook</u>
<u n="418" who="S0592">I don't er I just kind of don't pay attention to to what he does I don't pay attention to what half my friends do on Facebook</u>
<u n="419" who="S0597" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0592">the only person <pause dur="short"/> I've only removed one person from my friends list because he his his posts and what he kept following just really annoyed me so I had to stop following him <pause dur="short"/> it was always Britain first and get these Muslims out of our country innit so er I kind of got sick of it</u>
<u n="421" who="S0595">and why am I eating so much?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0592">hello</u>
<u n="423" who="S0597">don't fill up too much we have pizza</u>
<u n="424" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s late</u>
<u n="425" who="S0597">what?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s officially late now</u>
<u n="427" who="S0597">later than late? or is it six already?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0595">yeah it's ten minutes past</u>
<u n="429" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="430" who="S0597">disappointment</u>
<u n="431" who="S0592">hello hello</u>
<u n="432" who="S0597">what do you want?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0596">I'm hungry</u>
<u n="434" who="S0597">ah would you like some Pringles?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0595">huh?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0597">they're salt and vinegar</u>
<u n="437" who="S0595">no no you're <unclear/> in your pile</u>
<u n="438" who="S0597">don't really want to do it</u>
<u n="439" who="S0595">they're <pause dur="short"/> really crunchy</u>
<u n="440" who="S0597">bit of a dance</u>
<u n="441" who="S0592">I dance with my cats they're not happy about it but I do it</u>
<u n="442" who="S0597"><vocal desc="laugh"/> put me down</u>
<u n="443" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I won't subject your I I won't subject your cat to it though no I I I I don't pick them up I kind of I half pick them up and <trunc>y</trunc> I'll I'll they'll be on the table so I'll half pick them up and then do this make them dance</u>
<u n="444" who="S0596" trans="overlap">he would let you though he's pretty like he'll just let you do whatever</u>
<u n="445" who="S0597" trans="overlap">he'll just like scratch your shoulder</u>
<u n="446" who="S0592" trans="overlap">my cats let me as well they're not happy but they let me</u>
<u n="447" who="S0596">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's like even don't jump up on the table good boy like even when you're trying to like <pause dur="short"/> put flea stuff on him or anything he'll just lie there</u>
<u n="448" who="S0592">oh no our cats hate it we have to wrap our cats in towels to do it and they'll just they won't do it I'm not I'm not erm actually no we do we have to wrap them in towels cos otherwise if we don't they'll feel it on the back of their necks or whatever their shoulders and they'll go crazy and they'll scratch us so</u>
<u n="449" who="S0596">well he actually freaks out if you try and pick him up</u>
<u n="450" who="S0595">our cat's just a fluff ball just sits there like this</u>
<u n="451" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0596">hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0597">so are you still going to dance with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0595">who?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0597">from like Kings</u>
<u n="456" who="S0595">I never did that</u>
<u n="457" who="S0597">like who <pause dur="short"/> who did you dance with?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0595">where I always dance in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> the lady I've danced with since I was two</u>
<u n="459" who="S0597" trans="overlap">no I thought <pause dur="short"/> no I thought you did the things with Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> or was that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0595" trans="overlap">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> that was him</u>
<u n="461" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what's wrong with you?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0592">he's just sitting there</u>
<u n="463" who="S0595">I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday and he was in the bathroom I was like okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0592">what? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0596"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you alright?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0592">meow</u>
<u n="467" who="S0595">I don't have any signal</u>
<u n="468" who="S0597">no one does except you do you have signal?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0595" trans="overlap">yeah this is my house</u>
<u n="470" who="S0597">that doesn't mean you get signal in your own house</u>
<u n="471" who="S0596">don't think about jumping on the table</u>
<u n="472" who="S0597">but no one's looking</u>
<u n="473" who="S0592">everyone is looking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0595">okay I won't don't worry</u>
<u n="475" who="S0597" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0595">I'll stay seated here I won't jump</u>
<u n="477" who="S0592">er</u>
<u n="478" who="S0596">oi oi</u>
<u n="479" who="S0597">hey</u>
<u n="480" who="S0596">he's he's been like really we we've been letting him on the table a little bit and now we're trying to discourage them so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps jumping off the table</u>
<u n="481" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="482" who="S0596">and he'll just look up like it's a really fun game</u>
<u n="483" who="S0592">it's it's too late to discourage your cats from doing anything they've had too many years of doing it</u>
<u n="484" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0592">cats are getting on <pause dur="short"/> they're twelve and thirteen now my cats</u>
<u n="486" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0592">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0597">that's pretty old for a cat isn't it?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0592">yeah I think they're <trunc>pre</trunc> they're really healthy though</u>
<u n="491" who="S0597">fifteen or sixteen is about the average age isn't it?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0597">or am I just saying it?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0592">no it is erm I think I I don't know I think they're probably going to live longer than average cos they're still really really healthy so <pause dur="short"/> I hope they do cos I'm going to miss my cats</u>
<u n="495" who="S0596">I think my cat is literally about</u>
<u n="496" who="S0597" trans="overlap">try really hard <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0596">thirteen or fifteen? I can't remember exactly</u>
<u n="498" who="S0592">wow</u>
<u n="499" who="S0597">is that these cats or your old cat?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0596">yeah these cats lived to be fifteen</u>
<u n="501" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0597">what?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0596">no my my old cat that I used to have</u>
<u n="504" who="S0597"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0597" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> no oi</u>
<u n="508" who="S0592"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0595">and then the other one which was the sister of that one died when she was like four or five I think</u>
<u n="510" who="S0592">ah that's sad how did?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0595">yeah they had a pair of them and they both died of throat cancer</u>
<u n="512" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="513" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I think we when we got them they were quite old already</u>
<u n="514" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0595">and then we had them for probably about ten five or ten years after that</u>
<u n="516" who="S0592">mm <pause dur="short"/> no my cats are pretty good the only thing they're having trouble with now is jumping up on things they they're having a bit of trouble one of them she will jump and then she'll fail she'll half jump instead she ended up breaking a glass yesterday because she jumped and she knocked it over so</u>
<u n="517" who="S0595">can you put that on the table please?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0592">I had to clean that up when I was trying to cook dinner so that was fun</u>
<u n="519" who="S0595">so how is uni?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0592">uni? yeah it's good erm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0595">where are you?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0592"><anon type="place"/> yeah erm we had to show up like a week early which I don't I I have no</u>
<u n="523" who="S0595">why's that?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0592">because erm there was floods in <anon type="place"/> and the substation got flooded and so there was a power cut so we couldn't do anything so we got told to go home erm I don't have any complaints personally because I had tests that week so</u>
<u n="525" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0592">no you know loads of people erm <trunc>lo</trunc>loads of people celebrating cos they had course work deadlines that are getting like postponed and things like cos they obviously they left it too late so yeah I guess it's worked out for people but yeah no it's it's good erm I have a lot of free time which I don't quite know what to do with sometimes I spend most of it in bed</u>
<u n="527" who="S0597">it's alright when you start working it will be the other way around you won't have any time</u>
<u n="528" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0597">you're like I have two days to do I don't want to do anything menial</u>
<u n="531" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0595">so what do you two work nine till five?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0596">nine till five thirty <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0597">but I travel to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0597">every day</u>
<u n="539" who="S0596">it only takes me half an hour to a hour to get to work</u>
<u n="540" who="S0597">it takes me an hour and a half if I'm lucky</u>
<u n="541" who="S0592">it takes me ten or fifteen minutes to walk to my lectures</u>
<u n="542" who="S0595">it's gonna to take me cos I'm going now going to <anon type="place"/> getting the train which is sixteen minutes long</u>
<u n="543" who="S0596">oh yeah I have to get the train to <trunc>wo</trunc> to work on Wednesday cos we're going out for a Christmas meal so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is giving me a lift home which is really annoying I don't want her to</u>
<u n="544" who="S0595">who?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0597">why don't you just say?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's a senior partner</u>
<u n="547" who="S0597">why don't you go just say?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0596">cos that would that would be rude</u>
<u n="549" who="S0597">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0596"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0595">if he's offered you're like yeah if she's offered I'd be like yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0592">she she was like really insistent like oh no it's alright it's alright I can do that</u>
<u n="553" who="S0597">maybe she thinks she's under the impression you're going someplace</u>
<u n="554" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I'm amazed you've still</u>
<u n="555" who="S0592">no I they know I don't drink</u>
<u n="556" who="S0597">right okay</u>
<u n="557" who="S0595">I do admit I'm amazed you've still got stuff at the bottom of your tree our cats has stripped the bottom of our tree of all the baubles</u>
<u n="558" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did climb up the tree a bit when we first put it up but</u>
<u n="559" who="S0595">he did no our cats didn't climb it we just have until see where they've put that I'd say about where that the person is there from about there downwards there was stuff and there isn't any more</u>
<u n="560" who="S0596">and he got he got into like that first layer of erm branches before we be fallen out he used to do that a lot more when he was little he used to actually like climb up the tree properly</u>
<u n="561" who="S0592">yeah our cats like to play with the decorations cos we put erm we put our tree on the table because there's not we don't have anywhere to put the table when there's a tree out and there's no space anywhere else so we put it on the table they always sit on the table and start batting the decorations around</u>
<u n="562" who="S0595">oh no our cat sits underneath and does this and then you knock off and then in the morning you're going cos he gets shut in there in the night cos otherwise he'll be on our beds and like purr so loudly erm we shut him in there you come in in the morning you have like this apple thing like a dangling apple that's made of like polystyrene foam and stuff and it'll just have loads of puncture hole marks <unclear>of some teeth</unclear></u>
<u n="563" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no our cats are kept out of the living room my mum bought new cushions and they keep trying to scratch them so they're not allowed in</u>
<u n="564" who="S0595">oh our sofa is awful we have blankets dangled down the sides now</u>
<u n="565" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="566" who="S0597">I have no animals to talk about so</u>
<u n="567" who="S0592">that's fun <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you should you should get an animal</u>
<u n="568" who="S0596">yeah maybe get a hairless cat</u>
<u n="569" who="S0595"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0597">they could not be uglier</u>
<u n="572" who="S0595">still still be a cat though</u>
<u n="573" who="S0596">doesn't doesn't mean they don't deserve love</u>
<u n="574" who="S0592">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're basing who you give love to based on appearances</u>
<u n="575" who="S0597">what a pink scrawny cat?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0592">well they could have a lovely personality</u>
<u n="577" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0595"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0592">I'm sure I'm sure there's people who absolutely love how they look you know? hence why they're pets</u>
<u n="580" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah hence why they exist</u>
<u n="581" who="S0592">well I mean they'd exist regardless but <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know there's a lot of things that are ugly that still exist</u>
<u n="582" who="S0595"><shift new="singing"/> er er er er er <shift new="normal"/> parent <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0592">what?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0595">I thought a parent <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was coming down the stairs</u>
<u n="585" who="S0596">they might be they're going out</u>
<u n="586" who="S0595">new <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's the friggin <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0596">I didn't say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said they might be</u>
<u n="588" who="S0595">oh I thought you said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might be and I was like who is have you got a long lost sister?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s my new mum <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0592">wait is is that why I had to stay out was that cos your parents were still downstairs?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0596">yeah cos my dad had been on the exercise bike so he was in er very attractive shorts</u>
<u n="592" who="S0592">oh right</u>
<u n="593" who="S0595">what Lycra shorts?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0592" trans="overlap">okay wouldn't okay</u>
<u n="595" who="S0595" trans="overlap">oh I'm used to that</u>
<u n="596" who="S0597">sorry if I just like closed it in your face</u>
<u n="597" who="S0592"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like get out and I was okay</u>
<u n="598" who="S0597">hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can't come in sorry</u>
<u n="599" who="S0592">I'm here on time and everything</u>
<u n="600" who="S0595">I get that at rowing old old men like seventy-five years old men</u>
<u n="601" who="S0597">I would never wear anything that tight</u>
<u n="602" who="S0595">night</u>
<u n="603" who="S0596" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oi I can see you</u>
<u n="604" who="S0595">mare</u>
<u n="605" who="S0597">oh</u>
<u n="606" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0597">he walked into my leg</u>
<u n="608" who="S0592">do your cats like being picked up?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0596">yeah that one does he's really happy about it</u>
<u n="610" who="S0597" trans="overlap">you can pick up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if you want he will go on the table</u>
<u n="611" who="S0592">ah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0595">pardon me</u>
<u n="613" who="S0592">I think no there's one one one of one of mine likes being picked up most of the time actually it depends if she's upstairs she likes being picked up if she's downstairs she hates it she'll growl at you</u>
<u n="614" who="S0595">mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0592">I don't know what it is about being downstairs she just doesn't like it</u>
<u n="616" who="S0595">mm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0597">too much <unclear/></u>
<u n="618" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> freaks out if you pick him up his tail starts to go round it's really funny why are you so heavy?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0592" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="620" who="S0597">cos you feed me so much</u>
<u n="621" who="S0596">he looks like a fat cat</u>
<u n="622" who="S0597">cos I complain so you feed me more give me biscuits</u>
<u n="623" who="S0596">I know</u>
<u n="624" who="S0592">oh I made a noise I'm so used to my cats making no noise when I put them down</u>
<u n="625" who="S0596">well they're pretty heavy so</u>
<u n="626" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0596">you're your cats are rather gentile they're just like</u>
<u n="628" who="S0592">my my cats are tiny tiny tiny <pause dur="long"/> don't know why they're so tiny they've always been tiny</u>
<u n="629" who="S0596">I think our cats are just really huge</u>
<u n="630" who="S0592">oh no no</u>
<u n="631" who="S0596">they seem much bigger</u>
<u n="632" who="S0595">oh our cats are huge my cat actually if I shaved it it'd be like the skinniest rat ever it's just he he has like the furs the furs?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0597">the hairs</u>
<u n="634" who="S0592">the furs</u>
<u n="635" who="S0595">the hairs are like this big</u>
<u n="636" who="S0597">oh my mum's friends had a rather large dog and literally the hair was that long on it</u>
<u n="637" who="S0595">the cat and the dog are about the same size</u>
<u n="638" who="S0597">biggest hairy tail</u>
<u n="639" who="S0592">wow hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I kind of want to pick him up</u>
<u n="640" who="S0596">pick him up</u>
<u n="641" who="S0597">does anyone know where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0596">she's probably dead</u>
<u n="643" who="S0592">oh okay I'll I'll</u>
<u n="644" who="S0595">I've just text her</u>
<u n="645" who="S0592">that's a nice thought she's probably dead</u>
<u n="646" who="S0596">well I was exaggerating</u>
<u n="647" who="S0597">what is tonsillitis? I know it's</u>
<u n="648" who="S0596">it's erm when your tonsils get inflamed</u>
<u n="649" who="S0592">I think I had it when I was at uni as well I don't know</u>
<u n="650" who="S0597">did you have swelling of the inner mouth?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0596">yes</u>
<u n="652" who="S0592">my tonsils are always huge though so sometimes it's hard to tell if they're if they're swollen or not the doctor said to me nice she was looking in my throat she said wow those are big I'm like thanks I'm like it's it's it's not even more than one doctor has been like that and okay I know you know I I I swear to god they get infected all the time it's really annoying I should just get them removed but</u>
<u n="653" who="S0596">when I dislocated my elbow the nurse the nurse was like oh let's have a look at your other elbow then she's like wow they're pointy yeah thanks okay</u>
<u n="654" who="S0597">that's what I said</u>
<u n="655" who="S0592">she's good at small talk wow that's a pointy elbow</u>
<u n="656" who="S0596" trans="overlap">okay I don't need you to judge my elbow</u>
<u n="657" who="S0597">you have really pointy elbows</u>
<u n="658" who="S0596">well I'm I can't help it</u>
<u n="659" who="S0597">if you if you played rugby you'd be great cos you'd just go in there like that</u>
<u n="660" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I have pointy shoulders</u>
<u n="661" who="S0592">are you allowed to do that?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I have really pointy shoulders someone asked me if you know when erm Lady Gaga did all her films and stuff and had the little implants put there</u>
<u n="663" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0597">no but okay</u>
<u n="665" who="S0596">she had little pointy things put on her clothes</u>
<u n="666" who="S0595" trans="overlap">things put on there someone asked me like have you had them put on and I was like no no they're natural</u>
<u n="667" who="S0597">oh no</u>
<u n="668" who="S0595">my shoulders go really pointy it's because you can see like after like the whole of my clavicle is that your clavicle?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0597">I couldn't tell you</u>
<u n="670" who="S0596">yes maybe</u>
<u n="671" who="S0595">I think that's your <trunc>cla</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0592" trans="overlap">collar bone</u>
<u n="673" who="S0595">yeah your clavicle</u>
<u n="674" who="S0592">is that what it's called?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0597">the collar bone we <unclear/> collar bone</u>
<u n="676" who="S0595">well yes <trunc>cla</trunc> your clavicle</u>
<u n="677" who="S0592">okay is that what it's called?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0597">been in hospital too much</u>
<u n="679" who="S0592">yeah I I I I don't know the fancy terms for them</u>
<u n="680" who="S0596">décolletage</u>
<u n="681" who="S0595">I had to do it for college but yeah my clavicle you can see it just from like right the way from here all like and then you can see the end of it as well like it points up</u>
<u n="682" who="S0597">nice</u>
<u n="683" who="S0592">stop eating so I can pick you up I won't I won't do it while you're eating that would be mean my mum</u>
<u n="684" who="S0597"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0592">always tells me off because I tend to erm pester the cats when they're sleeping but they just look so nice</u>
<u n="686" who="S0596">it's not like it's not like they're going to do anything else they sleep they sleep all day</u>
<u n="687" who="S0592" trans="overlap">no that's that's that's that's what I say it's like they can go to <trunc>s</trunc> back and they</u>
<u n="688" who="S0596">they can handle being woken up for a bit</u>
<u n="689" who="S0592">they go back to sleep so easily and they wake me up during the night anyway so this is kind of payback isn't it?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0595">they don't wake me up</u>
<u n="691" who="S0592">they do well it's only <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually that does it she can't make her mind up she she'll be in my room for a bit and then I'll move around too much in bed so she'll get too pissed off and leave and then she'll be back meowing at my door I'll be like</u>
<u n="692" who="S0596">I don't let the cats in when I'm asleep cos they chew my hair</u>
<u n="693" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="694" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0592">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't do that</u>
<u n="696" who="S0595">he likes to munch your hair</u>
<u n="697" who="S0596">yeah it was pretty weird</u>
<u n="698" who="S0592">it's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that do that no <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> chews your hair and she'll she'll start like going like this on your head and like clawing you erm she's she's she's not trying to be mean but she just likes it and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would just rub you and it's really nice</u>
<u n="699" who="S0595">yeah I can't <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> can't fold can't fold I've lost so much flexibility</u>
<u n="700" who="S0597">you're meant to be Miss flexible</u>
<u n="701" who="S0595">I've <trunc>lo</trunc> ah it's awful</u>
<u n="702" who="S0597">how's rowing going?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0595">er?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0597">how's rowing going?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0595">yeah I've now moved to the senior squad</u>
<u n="706" who="S0597">have you?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0595">and I hate it so much lack of organisation though like we're racing tomorrow and I don't even know where we're racing really like where we're boating from</u>
<u n="708" who="S0597">do you still do rowing with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you do rowing with?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0595">yeah yeah yeah erm she went to uni but now she's coming back and doing starting another course</u>
<u n="710" who="S0592">what does she do at uni? or what did she do?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0595">she was doing sport psychology</u>
<u n="712" who="S0592">alright</u>
<u n="713" who="S0595">but she wants to come to do therapy and stuff</u>
<u n="714" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="715" who="S0595">but cos she really likes the psychology part but then she did her course and everything she's done the first term but has not really enjoyed it</u>
<u n="716" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="717" who="S0595">doesn't like the course itself doesn't like the uni doesn't like the people she housed with</u>
<u n="718" who="S0592">where did she go to uni?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0595">she went to <trunc>co</trunc> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="721" who="S0595">so she's loving back she's moved back yesterday two days ago yesterday two days ago whatever this week</u>
<u n="722" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0595">and she's starting doing sport science degree at <anon type="place"/> college like <anon type="place"/> tech</u>
<u n="724" who="S0592">oh yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0595">so it's an actual degree and stuff</u>
<u n="726" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0595">so she's starting that but</u>
<u n="728" who="S0598">hey guys</u>
<u n="729" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">hello</u>
<u n="730" who="S0595">hey we've both got Boots bags snap</u>
<u n="731" who="S0598">I haven't been able to go shopping so</u>
<u n="732" who="S0597">it's fine we have</u>
<u n="733" who="S0598">it's like chocolate and then I'll post you your birthday present once I've bought it</u>
<u n="734" who="S0596">okay</u>
<u n="735" who="S0595">and yours once it arrives I was so annoyed it didn't arrive and it was next day delivery as well and I bought it like four days ago</u>
<u n="736" who="S0598">I haven't got my Boots discount card yet so I didn't want to buy anything then I went to get it on Thursday and then I didn't go into work so yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0597">ah you sound ill</u>
<u n="738" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="739" who="S0596">what do you want a drink as well?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0598">erm can I just have a glass of water and can I put my antibiotics in your fridge?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0596">yeah okay</u>
<u n="742" who="S0597">do you have to keep them cold?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0598">yeah cos it's penicillin it they're not erm liquid</u>
<u n="744" who="S0597" trans="overlap">there's some penicillin in the bread bin</u>
<u n="745" who="S0598">yeah cos cos my throat's like this small right now how am I I've still got to swallow them in the first place how am I going to deal with a swollen throat? where can I put my coat?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0597">anywhere</u>
<u n="747" who="S0595">I just chucked mine on there</u>
<u n="748" who="S0596">anywhere <trunc>so</trunc> there's not a cat or a person</u>
<u n="749" who="S0595">on my David <trunc>Wi</trunc>William who is David Williams?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0597">I think I just caught my leg in a kick it was up here</u>
<u n="751" who="S0592">oh what you're doing that reflex thing?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0597">I can't do it there is works I've never been able to do it before</u>
<u n="753" who="S0598">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming? cos he's he did a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and didn't reply to</u>
<u n="754" who="S0592">no</u>
<u n="755" who="S0598">even though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did reply this time</u>
<u n="756" who="S0595">I like your shoes</u>
<u n="757" who="S0598">thank you</u>
<u n="758" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I've never been able to do this before</u>
<u n="759" who="S0598">they're from Primark they were a fiver</u>
<u n="760" who="S0595">I know I I <unclear/> clearing out this cos we had we had to basically put everything that was in the hospital to <anon type="place"/> I signed about fourteen of the whacky things and I was walking round with them in my pocket and there was one of the patients who I know really well came up to it and said <unclear/> and I'm like oi</u>
<u n="761" who="S0597">I've never been able to do this oh that's great</u>
<u n="762" who="S0592">I don't think I I can do it I'm trying to figure out where you</u>
<u n="763" who="S0597">I went to the hospital by myself</u>
<u n="764" who="S0595">oh</u>
<u n="765" who="S0598">yeah it's really scary I got lost trying to find the X-ray unit or something</u>
<u n="766" who="S0595">why did you have to use the X-ray?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0598"><unclear/> ankle</u>
<u n="768" who="S0595">when did you do that?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0598">we have hills in <anon type="place"/> and I went over it twice and it went purple so I had to go to</u>
<u n="770" who="S0596" trans="overlap">and you fell on them</u>
<u n="771" who="S0595" trans="overlap">what did they say?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0598">erm they said there's nothing majorly wrong on the X-ray but they're going to give me physio anyway cos it's like really it's a really terrible ankle at like being an ankle it's just not strong I can't really walk on it properly it's just not</u>
<u n="773" who="S0597">physio will sort it</u>
<u n="774" who="S0598">yeah hopefully so yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0595">are we waiting for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to open presents or shall we just go ahead without him?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0598">oh and I can't eat anything until half eight</u>
<u n="777" who="S0595">okay</u>
<u n="778" who="S0598">because I have to take my antibiotics at eight and they're annoying ones where you have to either take it half an hour before food or three hours after food so</u>
<u n="779" who="S0596">oh right</u>
<u n="780" who="S0597">we can save you a pizza</u>
<u n="781" who="S0598">thanks</u>
<u n="782" who="S0597">we'll do ours and then you can have yours</u>
<u n="783" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0598">erm but it's annoying because during the night I have to get up at 2 AM and then 8 AM to have my antibiotics and I then <unclear>I</unclear> go back to sleep cos every six hours you have to</u>
<u n="785" who="S0592">oh yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0595">so how do you organise tomorrow?  I'm racing at erm eight o'clock in the morning tomorrow in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0596">you erm well go for one of <trunc>cha</trunc> armchairs cos</u>
<u n="788" who="S0598" trans="overlap">this is new</u>
<u n="789" who="S0592" trans="overlap">is this my one down here? I think this is my glass isn't it?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0597">I left my glass here so</u>
<u n="791" who="S0596" trans="overlap">we got it last year</u>
<u n="792" who="S0592">probably</u>
<u n="793" who="S0598" trans="overlap">is it <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0597">is that thing mine</u>
<u n="796" who="S0592">this is got that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s one and this is mine</u>
<u n="797" who="S0598" trans="overlap">well it's easier to sit down with a skirt on isn't it?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah and it reclines as well</u>
<u n="799" who="S0598">nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0596"><unclear/> me I'm joking don't don't hold my hand</u>
<u n="801" who="S0598">you know it's it's panic Saturday tomorrow it's because it's the last Saturday before Christmas and I'm working at Boots on <anon type="place"/> high street open till eight o'clock in the evening</u>
<u n="802" who="S0597">you work at Boots?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0598">yeah temp job cos I'm broke</u>
<u n="804" who="S0597">oh</u>
<u n="805" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I'm in to my overdraft at the minute cos I had to buy a new pair of shoes for my job because I wore a pair my first day and they basically tore my feet to shreds so I was like limping like</u>
<u n="806" who="S0597">well if you've got a bad ankle you should probably wear good shoes</u>
<u n="807" who="S0598">yeah so I had to go into Clarks and buy a pair of school shoes like proper leather school shoes that cost me forty-five pounds which is erm so I had to er pay with my Santander student account with my overdraft nearly crying as I typed typed it in</u>
<u n="808" who="S0596" trans="overlap">oh I went into my overdraft a little while ago and that was</u>
<u n="809" who="S0598">but you have a job</u>
<u n="810" who="S0596">yeah I know but I spent all my money on Christmas presents</u>
<u n="811" who="S0597">I did as well</u>
<u n="812" who="S0596">really?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0596">it was only like ten pounds but still <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has gone into to overdraft as well</u>
<u n="815" who="S0592">I haven't I've been responsible with my student loan</u>
<u n="816" who="S0595">oh I've spent mine</u>
<u n="817" who="S0597">it's not like I've spent that much money I think it's just the way they came out my bank</u>
<u n="818" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I got paid today first day but I only get paid for my nights and a Saturday</u>
<u n="819" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="820" who="S0597">cos like I transferred over some money so I should have been fine but I think it came in like a week late or something</u>
<u n="821" who="S0596">oh right okay</u>
<u n="822" who="S0597">just the way it all processed</u>
<u n="823" who="S0598" trans="overlap">do you want to open them now or later?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0597">mm</u>
<u n="825" who="S0596">I'm excited for everyone to open their presents cos they're cool</u>
<u n="826" who="S0595">yeah you're yours hasn't turned up yet</u>
<u n="827" who="S0598">okay that's fine</u>
<u n="828" who="S0597">I've only got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yours you haven't turned up yet I'm sorry</u>
<u n="829" who="S0598">that's fine</u>
<u n="830" who="S0597">you'll get them at some point</u>
<u n="831" who="S0595">but the thing is it's really annoying I ordered two things from the same place and they said they'd be together so the calendar arrived to my mum cos it's a really pretty one</u>
<u n="832" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0595">and then yours didn't arrive and I was like what the hell? where is it?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0598">no I know</u>
<u n="835" who="S0595">this chair's really annoying it doesn't say reclined</u>
<u n="836" who="S0598" trans="overlap">yeah I just like I just have sweets</u>
<u n="837" who="S0596" trans="overlap">well there's a a glitch on the side that you can press</u>
<u n="838" who="S0597">the back thing</u>
<u n="839" who="S0598">I just have sweets but you'll get like really good birthday presents this year because I'll have money when everyone's birthdays are so <vocal desc="laugh"/>  like I'll get paid  at the end of December so like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s presents are going to be like amazing and then like</u>
<u n="840" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0598">so it will I just when I get money I just put it at everything you know</u>
<u n="842" who="S0592">I want to try and get a job but I think I'm trying to</u>
<u n="843" who="S0598">yeah yours isn't wrapped</u>
<u n="844" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I'm trying to focus more on getting erm</u>
<u n="845" who="S0595">I love it</u>
<u n="846" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="847" who="S0592">like a volunteer placement <unclear/></u>
<u n="848" who="S0598" trans="overlap">oh I so want <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be here</u>
<u n="849" who="S0597">what did you get him?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0598">I just found it was going to be really hard to get a job at uni because a lot of them if especially like where I am if a college student who like lives in <anon type="place"/> all the time applies for the same job as me they're always going to go for the college student because they're there during the holidays I was like okay well I have to go home at this time of year and at this time of year and then I can't do these dates and then they're like so you can only do like twelve you can only do like twelve weeks or twenty-four weeks a year and I was like yeah they're like oh so they didn't give me the job</u>
<u n="851" who="S0592" trans="overlap">is there is is there not like?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0595">okay that was meant to erm you need to shout hurry up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="853" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0592">erm do you do you like have any shops on campus? I don't know what <anon type="place"/> is like is it is it is a campus uni or is it like?</u>
<u n="855" who="S0597" trans="overlap">hurry up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0598">we're we're sort of a campus uni but we're a very small uni we only have four thousand students</u>
<u n="858" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0598">so we have two on site shops but the jobs get taken quickly</u>
<u n="860" who="S0597" trans="overlap">mm are you snapchatting me? hurry up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0598">and I don't really fancy doing like bar work but I</u>
<u n="862" who="S0595">he said I don't know how to tell me mum</u>
<u n="863" who="S0598" trans="overlap">but the temp job's good I'm doing thirty-seven and a half hours a week</u>
<u n="864" who="S0597">that's not a temp job</u>
<u n="865" who="S0598">erm for three weeks</u>
<u n="866" who="S0596">that's what I do</u>
<u n="867" who="S0598">yeah so it's full time for three weeks and I finish on the second of January and I get seven pound fifty-six an hour</u>
<u n="868" who="S0596">that's pretty good</u>
<u n="869" who="S0595" trans="overlap">that's pretty good</u>
<u n="870" who="S0596">that's more than I get</u>
<u n="871" who="S0598" trans="overlap">yeah yeah erm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0596">you're going to be rich</u>
<u n="873" who="S0598">erm and then I go back to Lego I finish uni on the first of April like I'm done for the year on the first of April</u>
<u n="874" who="S0595" trans="overlap">really? what?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0596">what do you not have exams or anything?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0592">no</u>
<u n="878" who="S0597">that's a joke</u>
<u n="879" who="S0595">why so early?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0598">so so I do erm you know you know Easter</u>
<u n="881" who="S0597">April Fool's you still have two months left</u>
<u n="882" who="S0595">whoo</u>
<u n="883" who="S0598">you know Easter erm so I go back and I do twelve weeks straight through erm and then when Easter is I get the Friday and then the Monday off but then I have four more days and then I'm done for the year so our well and then we have four weeks off then there's a set-up week but I don't go back for that cos I don't have exams er but the annoying thing is I'm paying for accommodation till end of May</u>
<u n="884" who="S0595">so stay there</u>
<u n="885" who="S0598">no cos I'm going to working at Legoland to actually get some money so that I can pay for rent over the summer at my second year house cos the contracts start in July</u>
<u n="886" who="S0592">yeah so do mine like we pay half rent though over the summer</u>
<u n="887" who="S0598">what?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0595">that's cool</u>
<u n="889" who="S0598">have you found a house already then?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0592">yeah cos er it I was I wasn't <trunc>go</trunc> I wasn't going to so early but one of my flatmates was like erm all the houses are going really quickly erm and</u>
<u n="891" who="S0595">we normally get them around now</u>
<u n="892" who="S0592">yeah so we got the we got it a few a few weeks ago there was a bit of a kerfuffle with my flatmates</u>
<u n="893" who="S0595" trans="overlap">have you put the pizza in?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="895" who="S0592"><unclear/> things so</u>
<u n="896" who="S0596" trans="overlap">do you want? who who wants</u>
<u n="897" who="S0595">I will have pepper</u>
<u n="898" who="S0596">do you want pepperoni?</u>
<u n="899" who="S0598" trans="overlap">are you living with all your flatmates next year?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0592">erm I'm living sorry</u>
<u n="901" who="S0596">who wants pizza with pepperoni and who doesn't want pizza with pepperoni?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0598">well can I have one without pepperoni but like not now</u>
<u n="903" who="S0595" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0597" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0596">yeah that's fine yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0597">there are three pizzas in there so</u>
<u n="907" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0597">you can like</u>
<u n="909" who="S0596">so who votes pepperoni?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0597">yeah that's fine did you want pepperoni <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0592">no</u>
<u n="912" who="S0597">no</u>
<u n="913" who="S0596">what?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0595">no</u>
<u n="915" who="S0596">you don't want pepperoni?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0592" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="917" who="S0597">do one with and one without</u>
<u n="918" who="S0596" trans="overlap">okay I can do it half and half I'm sure I can handle it</u>
<u n="919" who="S0597">can you handle the heat?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0592" trans="overlap">you you you guys know I haven't been eating meat for like a year yeah?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0597">haven't you?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="923" who="S0598">no</u>
<u n="924" who="S0597">no are you a vegan?</u>
<u n="925" who="S0595">oh why why's that?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0592" trans="overlap">no I'm not a vegan</u>
<u n="927" who="S0597">vegetarian?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0597">how long have you been no when have you been?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0598" trans="overlap">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="931" who="S0592"><trunc>l</trunc>like a couple of times I've liked slipped up but I've been trying to be a vegetarian</u>
<u n="932" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0596">you've tried you've tried</u>
<u n="934" who="S0592">no no I've been good I've been good actually</u>
<u n="935" who="S0598">is it for like health reasons or the sort of belief behind it?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0595">or just to do it</u>
<u n="937" who="S0592">yeah just to do it erm</u>
<u n="938" who="S0595">no</u>
<u n="939" who="S0592">erm a bit of both to be honest</u>
<u n="940" who="S0598">and also cheaper</u>
<u n="941" who="S0595" trans="overlap">so <trunc>fi</trunc>first of January I'm going to cut out everything with wheat and gluten in my diet because</u>
<u n="942" who="S0596">are we waiting for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="943" who="S0595">because I find like yesterday I went and ate garlic bread biggest mistake of my life I was bloated and I actually looked like I was about fully like third semester pregnant like third trimester trimester not semester you know what I mean</u>
<u n="944" who="S0597">are you erm intolerant then?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0595">well I'm guessing I am</u>
<u n="946" who="S0597">you must be if you're getting that</u>
<u n="947" who="S0598">I don't eat white bread any more and I don't eat many like sweet stuff because I can't afford it</u>
<u n="948" who="S0597" trans="overlap">thank you what is it?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0596" trans="overlap">oh thank you</u>
<u n="950" who="S0595">random stuff</u>
<u n="951" who="S0596">thank you oh it's two ah thank you</u>
<u n="952" who="S0597" trans="overlap">thank you oh it's two even more chocolate</u>
<u n="953" who="S0596" trans="overlap">this is like the it's it's the best Christmas present</u>
<u n="954" who="S0595">I really didn't know what to get you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="955" who="S0596">it's like this is just what I wanted literally</u>
<u n="956" who="S0597">you're not allowed to top me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="957" who="S0595">so what did you get three? you only got one</u>
<u n="958" who="S0597">I I need to get three now</u>
<u n="959" who="S0598">ah I've got out of buying my brother a Christmas present this year cos I spent ninety-five pounds on him for his birthday</u>
<u n="960" who="S0596">nine oh my god</u>
<u n="961" who="S0598">yeah I bought him the</u>
<u n="962" who="S0597">you bought him tickets for something</u>
<u n="963" who="S0598">no I bought him the Batman thingy</u>
<u n="964" who="S0597">batman</u>
<u n="965" who="S0598">the erm Lego Batman that's like a hundred and seventy pounds like forty per cent off</u>
<u n="966" who="S0595">oh they're pretty</u>
<u n="967" who="S0596">I almost kept them</u>
<u n="968" who="S0597">you say that every year about someone's present</u>
<u n="969" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah because I buy people things when that's what I want</u>
<u n="970" who="S0595" trans="overlap">yeah I've nearly run out of my ones so I don't need to go buy another one</u>
<u n="971" who="S0596">you have one?</u>
<u n="972" who="S0598">well not this exact but I mean like my fave wash scrub thing</u>
<u n="973" who="S0597" trans="overlap">thank you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0598">so thank you</u>
<u n="975" who="S0595">I really didn't know what to get I felt really bad that was really fun funny stuff though</u>
<u n="976" who="S0597">your present's quite random</u>
<u n="977" who="S0596" trans="overlap">oh should I should I give people their cards now?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0595">best for you</u>
<u n="979" who="S0592">ah I'll give people their cards now as well</u>
<u n="980" who="S0597">okay</u>
<u n="981" who="S0592">I <trunc>ga</trunc> I gave you guys like two chocolates because</u>
<u n="982" who="S0595">oh Fiji green tea</u>
<u n="983" who="S0596">it's kind of weird but it smells nice</u>
<u n="984" who="S0595">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0592">that is nice</u>
<u n="986" who="S0595">I have boobs on mine</u>
<u n="987" who="S0592">everyone has boobs on theirs it's really good</u>
<u n="988" who="S0595">thank you</u>
<u n="989" who="S0597">we didn't draw anything inappropriate around the chocolates</u>
<u n="990" who="S0592">and then yours is if you want your card now</u>
<u n="991" who="S0596">excuse me</u>
<u n="992" who="S0595">kick her when she's down</u>
<u n="993" who="S0597">why why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0592">it's always Kylie <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc>every single year it's Kylie I don't know what you were expecting</u>
<u n="995" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I know it always is</u>
<u n="996" who="S0595">is that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0592">they're meant to be I don't know baubles or something</u>
<u n="998" who="S0595">oh okay sorry</u>
<u n="999" who="S0592">for someone with a dirty mind</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0598">thank you</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0596">hopefully it's helpful</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0595">really great present</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0598">I don't actually get hung over though</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0592"><trunc>ev</trunc><trunc>ev</trunc>everyone's got different ones it's fine</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0598">I just sort of sleep</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0596" trans="overlap">well it's got a good recipe like recipes in it</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0598" trans="overlap">I just sort of sleep all day because I can because I have the day off on Wednesday so I just</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0595">really? really?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0598">what what what?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0595">thanks for gracing us with your presence presents presents and gracing</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0592" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought that was pretty clever</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0598">oh is it like?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0595">did you spell your name are you going to write your name capital and then changed your mind?</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0592">I I I I I I did like all different levels of like being hung over</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0595">I do that I always I always write my name in capitals in work then I went to go sign in <unclear/> stuff and I was like oh no</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0596" trans="overlap">and I think they're just good recipes anyway</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0596">cos like it's actually ways of cooking eggs</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0598">a hangover is an opportunity</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0597">yeah we we saw it in the bookshop and we thought of you so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1021" who="S0598">I don't actually drink that much since fresher's I mean I haven't really like like my <trunc>p</trunc> my mum and my gran came down for the weekend</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0595" trans="overlap">now I'm not I'm not <unclear/> booze now</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/> my mum and my gran came down for the weekend and they were like oh have we got a bottle of Prosecco? you know well done for finishing your first semester</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0597" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants <unclear/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0598">and</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0596">sorry</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0592">ruler</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0597"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> want me Moolam</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0592">I I said I was joking though the cat the cat said I was joking</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0598" trans="overlap">and my mum and gran were like here's some Prosecco and they were like drinking it all and like kept like topping me up and I was like no I'm fine I don't want any more please stop giving me alcohol I don't I don't want like</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0596">are you getting into that alright?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0592">yeah no it's fine I'm just being slow <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0598">that's the name of my Tumblr blog now shanananana batman</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0597">it's been that for years</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0598">yeah my my <unclear/> is now eighteen and still hungry cos it was seventeen and hungry and</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0592">do you change it every year then as you get older?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0598">I think I'll probably change it next year</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0595">nineteen now starving</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0598" trans="overlap">nineteen yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1040" who="S0596">twenty almost dead</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0595">twenty-one gone</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0596">twenty-two shrivelled away to nothing</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0595">twenty-five completely <trunc>ma</trunc> now mal <trunc>nu</trunc> oh I can't say it</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0597">mal <trunc>nutr</trunc> mal nurtised? mal nutritionised</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0598" trans="overlap">thank you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'll eat these once I've had my antibiotics thank you</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0595">oh that went a lot better than I thought</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0592" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0596">I don't know if it's any good I didn't read it first <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0592">I'll <trunc>re</trunc> I'll read it at uni when I've got too much free time I'm pretty sure this is a mug but</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0597">oh I was wondering what that was</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0596" trans="overlap">did you not?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0592">it it feels like a mug</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0596">if it's not a mug I'd be pretty impressed</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I didn't see the I didn't see the weird bit I just saw the like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0595">it's not a mug it's a hat whoo</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0592">thank you I need I need another mug cos like one</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0595">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as you're up can you pass me my bag?</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0592" trans="overlap">mine was new I got it from Tescos and I put water I put erm I just put water in it</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0595" trans="overlap">as as as and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0598">oh thank you</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0595">as yours didn't turn up I made you a little bag too</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0598">oh thank you</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0592">I <unclear/> tonight</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0598">you can it's a generic birthday card you'll get you know the things that you wanted me to get you from Amazon don't arrive on Amazon Prime so they're going to take forever to come but right that's for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0598">and that's for you</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0592">thank you</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0598">and just a lucky dip <unclear/></u>
<u n="1073" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I know I know I saw I almost kept them I got my ears pierced cos I wanted to buy my own ones</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0595">mm wait you got your ears pierced again?</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0596">yeah cos they both got swollen and horrible</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0595" trans="overlap">but look look look look</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0596">it's okay this one's bad</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0598">ah</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0595"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> that feels different than this one oh</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm feels different it's the exact same thing</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0592">I did it felt different</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0597">feels different can you feel colours now?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0592">it was on a different plane okay it was like this way and the other one was this way</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0598"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1086" who="S0595">you're too high you're too high</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0598">I didn't have time to go to a shop</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0592">I've just thrown your present on the floor sorry</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1090" who="S0598">where is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is she just not here yet?</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0595">working</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0596">she's not coming</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0595" trans="overlap">she's working</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0598">oh she said she was coming</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0595">yeah but she didn't know she was working</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0598">oh</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0597">oh she's coming on no wait what? I'm confused</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0596">she's coming for the birthday thing</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0597">oh right oh thank you I'm <unclear/> what I am doing? is this like lucky dip?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I didn't do Christmas cards</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0595">I didn't do Christmas cards because the Christmas cards I did have I</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0597" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0598">what sweets do you like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0596">chocolate</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0597"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <unclear/></u>
<u n="1107" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0595">can I can I <unclear/> swap lucky dip?</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0598" trans="overlap">she's going with the Haribo</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0595" trans="overlap">can I <trunc>lo</trunc> can I <trunc>li</trunc> swap lucky dip? cos I</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0598">everybody can <unclear/></u>
<u n="1112" who="S0596">where did the glitter in this come from?</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0598">huh?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0596">it's got glitter on the inside</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0597" trans="overlap">the nose the nose</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0598">yeah it just came from it</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0596">it's coming off</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0595" trans="overlap">sorry I'm not really a fan of <unclear/></u>
<u n="1119" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I love you too <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1120" who="S0598" trans="overlap">that's alright</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0595">I wrote them like ten minutes ago</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0596">erm do you have any chocolaty things still in the thing can I swap one of these?</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0598">yeah there's Smarties</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0596">yeah? oh I actually would prefer this</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0592">not only do not only do we do Christmas presents at work apparently we also do Christmas cards as well so now I've got to give everyone at work Christmas cards</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0597">you work with three people</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0596">four people</u>
<u n="1128" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">whoa</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0597">oh four people</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0595">whoa pushing the boat out I'm gonna I'm gonna</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0597">how many people do you work with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? like twenty?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0598">well in the whole of the NHS</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0595">no no no in my ward there's probably about twenty-one different people</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0595">colleagues and then twenty-four patients</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0598">I work with a team of fifty plus at</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0597">to be fair well I work with three people</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0595" trans="overlap">they're really random I literally went in you know you can get like the little little bag things with like loads of little things I went in and I went to the till I forgot what it was and I was like carrying them all these little things I don't know what they are I just thought they</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0598" trans="overlap">they're they're sour</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0595">here's the other one</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0598">thank you</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0595">hello</u>
<u n="1143" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello alright?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0595">how are you?</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0596">hi dad</u>
<u n="1146" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">good thank you</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0598">hiya you alright?</u>
<u n="1148" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello yes you?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0598">yeah good good well I've got tonsillitis so</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0596" trans="overlap">well thank you for having us</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0592">oh thank you</u>
<u n="1152" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">have you?</u>
<u n="1153" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello how are you?</u>
<u n="1154" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello sorry to intrude</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I have a card for you which I which I wrote about three weeks ago and I keep forgetting</u>
<u n="1156" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah how's it at the hospital?</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0595">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="1158" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">what what you doing?</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0595">er being a care support worker for mental health patients</u>
<u n="1160" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">bet you've seen some things already</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0595">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I have <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just the naked men that walk around as well</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0598">good to see you</u>
<u n="1163" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">and you how are you?</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0598">good good yeah I've got er I was just saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I've got tonsillitis just in time for Christmas but yeah apart from that I'm good yeah</u>
<u n="1165" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah enjoy the uni?</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0598">yeah it's good yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1168" who="S0598">it's fun</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0597">I have to tidy up here now</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0598">it's hard work but I enjoy it</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0596">you live for tidiness</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0598">it's nice to be home though</u>
<u n="1173" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah bet your mum's pleased to see you</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0597" trans="overlap">it wasn't annoying me but I feel better now</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0598">well I've been home quite a few times during the term but it's nice to be sort of home for longer I've always <unclear/></u>
<u n="1176" who="S0592" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0597" trans="overlap">the mess on the floor</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0595">for some reason I keep my room at uni clean but then my room at home is quite a lot more</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0597">yeah that I think that's like a</u>
<u n="1180" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1181" who="S0592">hi</u>
<u n="1182" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hi how are you doing?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0592">I'm doing alright how about you?</u>
<u n="1184" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah alright thank you anybody else here?</u>
<u n="1185" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0597">no just me</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0596"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1188" who="S0595">yeah just <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0597">yeah no apparently if you keep work clean you keep your house dirty and visa versa apparently</u>
<u n="1190" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">uni alright?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0597">so like if you're clean at work you're messy at home or if you're clean at home you're messy at work I don't think this applies I'm clean everywhere</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0595" trans="overlap">er a pre-school teacher so reception year one</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I I I like to keep my uni room clean I guess cos there's more people who are potentially going to be coming into my room so seeing seeing it</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0598" trans="overlap">I am the messy one</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0597">organised chaos</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0592">I like to keep my desk clean as well cos I actually use my desk</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0598">like if I make breakfast and I'm in a rush to get to a lecture I leave my stuff on the side like my plate on the side and like one knife I come back in</u>
<u n="1199" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I bet she's got some stories to tell</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0598">and then like <unclear/> so you left your plate on the side this morning I'm like yeah and I try and save water by building up plates and then washing them all in one go instead of like washing them after every meal</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0596">good plan</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0598">yeah well I do it as if I had a dishwasher cos you wouldn't put a whole dishwasher load in for like just one plate would you?</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0595">I'm pestering <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't worry hello <unclear/></u>
<u n="1204" who="S0598">is he at work?</u>
<u n="1205" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you waiting for anyone?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0595">no he's decorating part of his house</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0596">well there's only <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and no one else is coming so</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0597" trans="overlap">what's up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did I just let you out? why is your tail really fluffy?</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0598">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still actually at uni?</u>
<u n="1210" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">right we'll leave you to it we're <unclear/></u>
<u n="1211" who="S0597" trans="overlap">his tail is massive</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0596">he probably got scared by another cat</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0592">I want I want to pick him up now he's in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1214" who="S0596" trans="overlap">pick him up he'll be really cold though</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0597" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0592">oh god you are really</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0598">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still at uni?</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0592">yeah he's erm</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0597">he comes back today doesn't he?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0592">no</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0595">where is he at uni in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0592">no no <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1223" who="S0595">right I dunno how I had <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1224" who="S0592">no he's in he's in <anon type="place"/> and he's got to he's got to he's got to work tomorrow and he</u>
<u n="1225" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">bye</u>
<u n="1226" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">bye</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0598">panic Saturday</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0592">yeah he couldn't get a transfer early enough so you have to I'm sorry you're not liking this are you? I'm going to put you down</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0598">I haven't yet decided whether I'm going into work or not</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0592">yeah I I like caught myself on the chair no erm he's got to work tomorrow and he couldn't get a transfer so he's working tomorrow and then he's getting the train back on the twentieth so</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0598">mm yeah I haven't yet decided whether I'm going into work or not</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0597">well you work at a semi pharmacy so</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0598">no I work at like Boots sell a whole lot more I do it's a</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0597">well they sell like health products and</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0598" trans="overlap">eight hours and fifteen minute shift just standing behind a till</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0597">oh so you not like go round and stock stuff up?</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0598">no cos I don't know how to do that cos I'm a Christmas temp</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0597">oh new</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0595">when I was a Christmas temp at Primark I didn't even know how to use the tills and I got in front of the till so that's what it felt like</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0597">just put it money swipe stuff</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0592">the amount the amount of people who ask me can you do returns and exchanges here? no I can't you have to go to the till that says returns and exchanges on the top of it it's like can't you do it here? I've been waiting in line it's not my fault you can't read</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> the biscuits</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0597">what the?</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0595">oh I was trying to make a <unclear/> to get up pretty early</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0597">so I don't have to get up</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0598">I'm so hungry</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0595">I'm going to nurse them next thing your cat is eyeing my coat</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0592">not that I would want to <unclear/> anyway but that's what I have</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah he might sit on it</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0595">my cat loves it</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0598">and I have like a two week course</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0597">has it made you feel ill or anything yet?</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0598">what do you mean? like side effects?</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0597" trans="overlap">the antibiotics</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0598">well I feel like I have a head cold like I feel like my head's been stuffed full of cotton wool and they give me headaches and stuff</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0595">what's that?</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0597">how long have you got them for a week? two weeks?</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0598">two week course</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0595">what's that for? the antibiotics yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0598">so Christmas</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0595">eat loads of cheese</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0596">is that supposed to help?</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0595">penicillin yeah like blue cheese</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0597">or eat <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bread</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0595">but I erm</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0592">what's wrong with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bread? it's mouldy?</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0597" trans="overlap">it's mouldy</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0598">oh I'm working Christmas Eve Boxing Day New Year's Eve New Year's Day and the second</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0597">there'd be no one there for those days will they though?</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0595">Boxing Day day sales</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0597">oh that counts but like Christmas Eve no one will be there</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0595">no no no</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0598" trans="overlap">yes there will</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0597">really?</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0595">last minute shopping</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0597">people go shopping?</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0598">mm</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0596" trans="overlap">when I when I was at when I worked at the coffee shop <trunc>e</trunc> they were like oh you have to come in for Christmas Eve and Boxing Day cos there's going to be loads and loads of people here there was no one</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0595" trans="overlap">my dad won't my dad won't probably shop until the twenty-third twenty-fourth</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0598">but we get paid for Christmas Day so I get still I get Monday Tuesday off which is my two days off and obviously I get Christmas Day off but I get it paid but then yeah then my dad made me take Monday bank holiday Monday and Tuesday off cos we're going to see family if you work bank holiday Monday you get double pay which for me is like fifteen pounds an hour and my dad made me take it off</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0597">I'm not letting you on the table</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he's like no</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0597">you keep looking up at the table there</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0596">cos he wants to go on the table cos he thinks it's okay but it's not</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0597">there there's no room</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0596">he especially likes standing on things you don't want him to stand on</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0595">I don't even remember what this is now</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0592">I like the wrapping paper</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0598">we have one present under our tree so far</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0592">we don't have a tree yet</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0595">we can't put wrapped presents under there cos the cat and the dog the cat will probably pull on it rip it and the dog will probably move it are you having fun there? you've been trying to open that for the past like</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0592">the the actual erm lid thing is not</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0597">have you pulled the entire lid out?</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0592">yeah no the whole lid the whole thing keeps coming out this bit's not coming off it's being a bit</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0597">is there a little like tab that you have to pull all the way round?</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0595">chuck it chuck it like a baton</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0592">erm no I don't think so this doesn't look like you can pull any tabs</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0595">let's chuck it</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0592">I'm I'm afraid the lid's going to come off and it's going to go everywhere okay he's interested</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0597">I have no nails so</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0595">what have you done?</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0592">I haven't done anything <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1305" who="S0597"><vocal desc="laugh"/> now just don't close it you have you have to eat them all now</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0592">okay fair enough <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1307" who="S0598">oh yeah I've lost my phone so I don't think I have people's numbers</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0597">you lost it</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0598">yeah it was stolen in <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0597">oh I thought you got that sorted by now</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just text me saying</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0598">no I have my dad's old phone</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just text saying where's mum? I think she's still at work <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1314" who="S0597">is it just like one big packet like?</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0595">no that's three little ones normally</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0597">oh right</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0592">four I think</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0598">or four I don't really know</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0597">you didn't write the to and from</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0598">no my no my mum bought them in Tesco's for me</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0597">I thought you got it from Boots</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0598">I haven't left the house no I haven't got my discount card yet so I haven't bought stuff</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0597">oh it was in a Boots bag I presumed</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0598">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0595">oi cat</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0597">don't do it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there is no room</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0592">it was fine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her cat <pause dur="long"/> ah ah</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0595">I tried</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0592">he really is heavy though I wasn't expecting him to be that heavy</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0595">you carried that like a person who doesn't like cats</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0597">I don't like I just I've never picked up cats I've liked picked up him twice including just now</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0595" trans="overlap">oh look I got a wrapping paper thing <unclear/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0598">whose phone is that? Samsung Galaxy?</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0597">that's er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1335" who="S0592">oh is some going off?</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0598">no it's just I didn't know you had the erm curved one</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0592">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0598">I'm jealous</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0597">is like the screen actually curved round the side?</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0597">oh yeah does it make a difference?</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0592">not really</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0597">to your life?</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0592">I I I just think it looks quite nice</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0598">apparently they break easier because the screen is more vulnerable</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0595">same with mine apparently</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0592">that makes sense but</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0595" trans="overlap">like if I take the case off</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0597">I've dropped mine loads this year</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0598">so have I</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0592">I haven't dropped my phone yet</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0597">yet</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0592">I fell I fell asleep on it though last night</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0595">like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1356" who="S0598"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have you got a Boots healthcare professional discount card? you can get one gives you a discount in Boots</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0595">that would be quite useful I go in there quite a lot</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0597">what do you go in there for? what what do they?</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0595">like everything</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0596">well <trunc>ma</trunc> makeup mostly</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0598" trans="overlap">erm makeup wipes toiletries</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0595" trans="overlap">and erm the food the food there is quite good</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0598">wash <unclear/></u>
<u n="1364" who="S0595">toiletry yeah</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0598">their their their meal deal is quite good <pause dur="short"/> yeah they do electrical good good gift sets</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I I never use Boots</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah they sell like razors and stuff like electrical kind of</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0595">that's what I mostly get</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0598" trans="overlap">and they do they do three for two on everything like literally everything at the minute is three for two</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0595">nail varnishes mostly I normally get my <trunc>hai</trunc> like shampoo and stuff from there</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0598">hair dye loads of hair dye</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I know I knew they did hair dyes I don't know why they</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0596" trans="overlap">they do like perfume and stuff as well</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0597" trans="overlap">it's much cheaper</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0598">they do deals on perfume</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0596">like baby stuff and medicine</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0598">med yeah pharmaceuticals sun scream</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0595" trans="overlap">anything like</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0596" trans="overlap">anything you can think of they sell that basically</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0595">below your knee</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0597">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0595">oh okay</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0597">it made my like leg go tingly</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0592">he's just</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0597">I'm just whacking it</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0598">and Christmas gifts lots of Christmas gifts like <unclear/> and everything</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><unclear/> tapping that bit there</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0597">what does that do?</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0595">makes your hand go up like you know where your knuckle is so if you do that you know where your two knuckles are</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0595">if you go in in a with your last knuckle and go across to the middle where the your vein is if you whack there it should make your whole hand go</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0596">no but you're not doing it right</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0597">I'm I'm dead no</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0598">are those Pringles salt and vinegar Pringles? I'm like torture</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0597">yeah I got these I thought you liked the sour cream ones no you don't</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0596">I like the sour cream ones</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0597">god</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0598">I had porridge at like two o'clock</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0597">oh porridge</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0598">yeah well it's easy to eat right now</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0595">I bought this new thing called protein porridge nicest tasting thing ever it's it's good for you</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I dislike the <unclear/> of porridge porridge with golden syrup in it's nice</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0595">no protein porridge</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0598" trans="overlap">I have porridge with Nutella cos someone at uni ate my Nutella</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I have that whey powder in there</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0592">I haven't had porridge in ages</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0598" trans="overlap">and I haven't worked out who it is yet they ate like a kilo <trunc>de</trunc> jar of French Nutella</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0595">who?</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0597">next time buy Nutella and put loads of laxatives in it and then you'll know who did it</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0598">no no because then I can't eat it someone at my flat</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0597">yeah but it's not there for you to eat it's there for you to punish the person who eats your food</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0596" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0595" trans="overlap">yeah have your own thing just take it with it but pretend the one in there is the one you always eat</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0598">but I just cos it was a gift from my mother from France</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0597">how dare you eat my Nutella from France</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0598">it tastes different</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0597">does it? how does it?</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0595">it does</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0598">it does and it was a kilo jar that's a lot so someone deliberately tried to like eat it like if you were just going to use a little bit every now and then once it got to a certain point you'd be like okay she's going to start to notice I'll stop using it</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0598">and they obviously were trying to</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0596" trans="overlap">they had like the whole thing</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0598">I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came in completely drunk like late one night and just sat there with this like massive spoon</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0597">it's the problem with university is that all obviously all the students have just come from living in their own house</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0598">mm</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0597">they haven't realised that it's different can't just like go in the fridge</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0598">well quite a lot of us share our food like the four of us girls in our flat who get on really well we erm we share</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0597">there's a real weird thing coming in</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0595" trans="overlap">no come in do do it get your two knuckles get your two knuckles and like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0598">we share like milk and eggs and erm like and everything</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I don't know if I'd be able to like share food cos I I'm really like really obsessive with my <unclear/> like if I like if I bought something I would want it like for me I wouldn't like anyone else to have it</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no oh there we go it's it's more of a sensitive one if you take like your fingers</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0598" trans="overlap">well we only share the stuff that like it would be silly like cos you know cos first week of uni we had six bottles of milk in the fridge</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0596" trans="overlap">just like the plain things and stuff</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0597">cos everyone bought milk</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0598">yeah and what's the point? you know and everyone has their like own bread but like eggs we'll just get a set of like twelve <trunc>e</trunc>eggs toilet roll everyone buys together like cleaning supplies washing up liquid erm foil like cling film and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0596">yeah I guess I guess those things</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0598">cos it just doesn't make sense and and cos we're all quite close if someone's like oh can I I've erm run out of bread can I just borrow a slice of your bread we'd be like yeah that's fine but we always ask each other we don't just like yeah</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0597"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> jumped up on the table again</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0596">mm?</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0597"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> jumped on the table</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0596">oh</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0598">so did I</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0597">I picked him up you're getting old <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1447" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0597">you're losing it completely oh yey a black dog</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0596">I don't I something is really up with my playlist</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0597">it's meant to be Christmas</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0596" trans="overlap">it's supposed to be a Christmas playlist but it's got loads of random songs on it and I don't know how</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0597" trans="overlap">this song is Led Zeppelin</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0598">I've got a Christmas playlist on my Spotify</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0596">but we don't really <unclear/> music</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0598">this has erm Beats audio</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0597">oh quality of the semi <unclear/> loads of people at college have Beats it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0595">I hate Beats</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0597">they're not even that good</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0595">they're so over yeah so over</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0597">they're just over branded and over priced because people buy them</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0595">it's because of will.i.am</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0596">oh the <trunc>p</trunc> no it's cos of Dr Dre</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0597">yeah I mean they they're probably already but the frequency response won't be great so</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0598">I erm my uncle bought me and my brother those fake Beats</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0597">fake Beats</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0598">from China and the you know you could tell that they were fake cos if you looked in the small print on the box there are all like spelling and grammar mistakes because that's what they do to warn like copyright</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0595" trans="overlap">oh they're not open oh it's not <unclear/> I don't have I'm not blessed with Pringle hands through my hand doesn't fit so once it gets to like here</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0597">mine mine only just does</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0595">so we always the other day</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0597">how big is your hand <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? yeah mine's slightly wider</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0595">I have really fat wide knuckles so I'm not blessed with a Pringle hand</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0597">they are only just big enough</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0595">and I said that the other day to and I said that to my sister cos my sister has a Pringle hand and I say so it's skinny enough and it slips down and my auntie cos my auntie's back from <anon type="place"/> she was like don't be so rude so she was feeling my sister's little hand and I was like no no that's horrible it was funny</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0592">hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> but he's so heavy</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0595" trans="overlap">doesn't he look sad?</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0597">just like</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0592">no he just looks a bit like</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0596">he's kind of depressed at the moment</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0592">he he he he's really heavy</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0596">yeah he is</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0592">I didn't expect the like I picked him up and I was expecting something much lighter I was like oh god</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0597">do you not remember from last year?</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0592">I don't <trunc>remem</trunc>remember picking him up last year</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0596" trans="overlap">he's probably heavier he's probably heavier than he was last year</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0597" trans="overlap">you were you were out last year I don't know</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0592">I don't know maybe maybe</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0597">you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always come over like oh cats I want to pick you up</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0592">it's just anywhere there's cats you just go to just got to just got to pay attention to them <pause dur="short"/> look it's cleaning himself isn't that cute?</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0598">oh I spent erm</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0595">your lava lamp is working again</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0598">you know like last week of uni you probably wouldn't have been the same cos of the whole like flood and power cut and stuff but I was I was I was panicking a bit cos I had a three thousand word assignment due for one module and a two and a half thousand word due for another and the a four thousand word group assignment for another and I had a hundred words written for one so I basically lived in the library and I managed to write nearly nine thousand words in two days</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0596" trans="overlap">there's something up with the</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0597">right</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0596" trans="overlap">it's like inflated</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0598">and I did a thirteen well I did a fifteen hour stint at my campus so we all left like accommodation we left our flat at like seven</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0595">what the evening or morning?</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0598">in the evening and then it got to about five in the morning in the study room and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we live in the same flat and do the same course she was like I've got a seminar at nine erm at nine o'clock on the main campus and I was like well is there any point in us going back to our flat? we might as well just stay here so</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0597">you were sitting in the library all night?</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0598">so we left the library at erm <pause dur="short"/> at eight so that was er thirteen hours after we'd got to the the library and then we had breakfast on main campus in the food hall and we went to our seminar we got to our flat at half ten there was no one in <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was so dead so I went to bed for like four hours and I got up and went to the library again</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0595" trans="overlap">that's probably why you've got tonsillitis</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0598">what <pause dur="short"/> what from studying?</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0597" trans="overlap">what from?</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0592">by <trunc>we</trunc><trunc>we</trunc><trunc>we</trunc>wearing yourself out</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0595">no no no from doing like not <unclear/> yourself like not having</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0598">I know because I slept slept a lot after it like I slept for like two days straight after I'd finished</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0596">yeah but still that messes up your shift patterns and stuff</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0598">mm I've done that like all year really I've done that all semester I don't know I think it's just I'm very prone to it I'm not contagious any more though according to the NHS you're not contagious after you've taken antibiotics for twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0595">oh okay and then as you're up</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0597">what is that?</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0595">see the <unclear/> ah I don't know where my glass is gone</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0596">put it into</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0595">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0598">ah that pizza smells so good</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0592">don't worry there are two more</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0598">I know but it's just I'm like I've still got an hour and I'm really hungry</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0595"><shift new="singing"/> do do do <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1517" who="S0597">is that what song's playing?</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0592">what song is it?</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0596">cancan</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0597">why do you have this song on your Ipod?</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0596">I don't know</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0597">where did it come from?</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0596">I don't know</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0597">are you sure this isn't your mum's one?</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0596">no it's on here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1527" who="S0598">hello <pause dur="short"/> did you do presents from you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0595">only to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1529" who="S0598">oh okay</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0595"><unclear/> stupid yesterday <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1531" who="S0596">pizza</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0592">yey don't mind me</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0596">I'll just take I'll just have this</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0595"><unclear/> oh what can we get him? we really want to <unclear/> <shift new="singing"/> de de de de de de de <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1535" who="S0598">do you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ever have the same days off?</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0595"><unclear/> shift</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0596">I just moved <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thing</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0595">I've got him look I got him a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1539" who="S0598">it's just the getting there</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0596">I know</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0598">it's it's annoying cos it's actually cheaper to get a train to <anon type="place"/> and then a coach no it's actually cheaper to get a coach from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> and a train from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> than it is to go direct from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1542" who="S0592">I'll just steal this part here</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0598">but if you do come down Tuesday nights are like you can go out for like a tenner because it's two pound entry and then drinks are Jaegers are like one pound</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0595">oh I'm never doing Jaeger bombs again</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0598">ah I love them</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0595">last <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took me out never again I literally</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0598">they they're one pound on <unclear/> night so if you get erm er <unclear/> to get Jaegers</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0595">no <trunc>li</trunc><trunc>li</trunc>literally I went out I'm going to take these two erm and oh my god my head the next day</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0598">no I love them</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0595">I just drank no I drank them and I probably had in total about ten of them and ah I didn't I wasn't <trunc>dru</trunc> you know when you're tipsy but you can fully function and everything and I can remember the whole night</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0597">yeah I know that feeling</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0595" trans="overlap">but my goodness my head in the morning jesus christ I'm never doing it again and then I had to go out and play the drum in a marching band with my mum</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0597" trans="overlap">sarcasm</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0598">white wine is I can't do that</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0595">I don't like wine</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0598">cos I had</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0595">I got a really expensive one from Marks and Spencer's</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0598">but I had a bottle of white wine before I went to <anon type="place"/> and we played ring of fire so I had a bottle of white wine as my drink in ring of fire erm so that's drinking a whole bottle in like half an hour so I was like fucked before I got in the taxi</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0595">like white wine I</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0598">and that was the night I got stranded in <anon type="place"/> and my dad had to come and pick me up</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0597">dad you know you love me and it's two o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0598">no cos cos the thing was he did say if you're ever trapped somewhere and you know stuck somewhere and you need me just call me</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0597">oh so you're blaming your father</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0598">and I'll come and get you and then I was like well you did say and I don't have any money to get home but I don't I don't really talk the the people that I was like friends with at the beginning of the semester in the hotel I don't really talk to them any more cos I went out with them a couple of weeks ago</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0597">is <anon type="place"/> closer?</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0598">it's like twenty minutes and then I went out with them like half way through the semester and it was so boring cos they're really like the girls they'll like have a drink then they'll go on to the dance floor and then five minutes later they'll be like I want to go outside and I have you follow them because if I get left by myself then I'm left by myself and I can't find anyone and then they get like really pissed at me and they're like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you were so drunk last night I couldn't find you you know you just you deserted us</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0597" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you put the second one on?</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0598">and then they're like outside for a bit and then they're back on the dance floor and then they're outside again then they're back on the dance floor and I know it's nice to cool down a bit cos it gets like really hot in the club but you know every five minutes in and out in and out in and out you don't get a chance to meet anyone so</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how do you spell Munich?</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0597" trans="overlap">M U N I C H</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0598" trans="overlap">I don't really talk to them anymore cos they're a bit they're like the typical bitchy girls that I wouldn't have really hung out at school and I was like why am I hanging out with them now? so</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0595" trans="overlap">my dad's back so he was like how is it going? I'm back and I was like how was <trunc>mu</trunc><trunc>mu</trunc><trunc>mu</trunc>? I couldn't think how to spell it</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0598">er she had erm type one diabetes and one night erm I got like separated from them so I just found some other people that I knew and was dancing with them and then I saw them and I thought they were leaving so I left the club so I stood outside the club by myself for like half an hour cos I couldn't find them anywhere then they finally came out and she was like where have you been all night? like I've been feeling really sick all night and I couldn't find anyone and I need to go home and you weren't there and you were so drunk and going off with these random people blah blah blah and then so I just walked home by myself and bought well not by myself they were like the next day they were like we have to get one of the guys to walk you home cos you were so drunk and I was like you didn't have to carry me home we walked home side-by-side talking to each other like you know? and the next day we were like oh you were you know you were really terrible to deal with and all this stuff and I was like actually no I was just having a good time they weren't random people they were friends of mine and how am I supposed to know that you were feeling like low sugared like I know my brother has diabetes but I know what he's like when he goes low I have I've just met you I have no idea like am I meant to be able to like read your blood like just with by looking at you? don't get mad at me for that</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0595" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like we have our coach at rowing he has like he's type two but it's still you know when he hasn't eaten and stuff like oh</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0598" trans="overlap">cos that's what you get to know when you know someone</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0595">oh Wednesday oh my god he was in the foulest mood and I went with my aunty who's back from the <anon type="place"/> and she came to circuits with us and I was like oh he hasn't eaten he just needs to <unclear/> he isn't normally like this and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other coach said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't eaten today and it just really <unclear/> so I just said it was like it's so bad though but he's with kids and he can't act like that</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I don't mind is that yours? is that the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0597" trans="overlap">mine's er that's the clean one</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I keep forgetting <unclear/></u>
<u n="1580" who="S0597" trans="overlap">just like leave it on there or something</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0598">it's just it's they're the sort of people that like you know when you do get a bit tipsy you laugh and you smile and you're happy and you're having a good time and they think that is like smashed and I'm like you haven't seen me smashed like that's not that's just me being happy</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0597" trans="overlap">could I try some of your <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1584" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1585" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1586" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> or a bit more</u>
<u n="1587" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>bit more</unclear></u>
<u n="1588" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">thank you</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0598">I I'm like that's my exaggerated personality when I'm tipsy you may turn into like a conceited bitch when you're drunk doesn't mean I have to</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0597">apple and watermelon</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0598">yeah safe to to say we don't talk <unclear>enough</unclear></u>
<u n="1592" who="S0592" trans="overlap">well I've <trunc>al</trunc>almost drank all this by myself</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0597">that's why I'm helping they're strange watermelon's alright</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0598">but uni uni is fun</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0592">two of erm two of my I say my people er someone</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0598" trans="overlap">your people <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1597" who="S0592">my peeps</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0598">my peeps</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0597">you have a crew now? you have a gang?</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0592">no no cos erm during freshers' week we erm cos we had freshers' reps sort of er helping us out and erm taking us to clubs and things erm we went with the flat next door as well so we were one big group and on the first day I didn't go erm one second I've got feel like I've got something in my throat er excuse me</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0598">totally relate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1602" who="S0597" trans="overlap">is it your tonsils?</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1604" who="S0592">erm what was I saying? yeah erm I didn't go on the first night erm because I wasn't feeling up to it but they went to erm they went to a nightclub I think called <anon type="place"/> rooms it was a UV paint party erm apparently two of them got so drunk from the flat next door that they threw up and they had to get sent home</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0598">I've never done that</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0592">and then and then the what? the the girl learnt her lesson and she didn't do it again but then the guy did it again later on in the week and then I think also another guy also did it and he got they got sent home before they even reached the club that's how drunk they got themselves</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0598">do you do you have a chunder chart?</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0592">no</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0595">I haven't got chender</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0598">chunder</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0595">I thought you said chender</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0598">no chunder chart I haven't been sick since I've been there and I got out the most out of the girls in my flat and this one girl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's lovely but she makes out that she's not a lightweight but she's been out twice and she's thrown up both times so I was like okay <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm we I've been thrown out of a club because I fell asleep on one of the sofas</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0592">I think you told us about this when you went back for that that weekend</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0598">yeah yeah that was when I was still like with these people the hotel crew</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0595"><unclear/> down the side</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0598">and the night I got like really upset</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0597">is it working?</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0595">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0597">I I don't know why I got up</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0595"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1622" who="S0598">but I haven't been thrown out since so</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0592">I haven't really been out that much I went out for Halloween erm</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0595">okay Halloween this year next year we we can meet up and we can do the best thing ever so we were clearing out the sort of my the old hospital hospital ward I have the scrubs the shoe covers face mask and plastic surgeon masks it's going to be a laugh</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0598"><anon type="place"/> meant to be really good at Halloween we have one club in <anon type="place"/> and it's called <anon type="place"/> it's like the only place we can go out apart from the SU</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0592">we have we have loads of different clubs but erm there's we have a students' club erm called <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0595">do you have any tissues?</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0598">what's your student union called?</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0592">just <anon type="place"/> student union</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0598">oh ours is called the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1632" who="S0592">it it's called I think it's abbreviated <anon type="place"/> I think people just refer to it as <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> university students' union cos we're creative</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0598">erm <anon type="place"/> university is erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1634" who="S0595" trans="overlap">what have you done with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0596">Disney man</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0595">a what?</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0596">Disney man</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0595">of what?</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0598">and then erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1640" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1641" who="S0597">oh yeah that</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0595">what have you got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0597">mm?</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0595">what have you got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0592">I know <anon type="place"/> is <anon type="place"/> I think</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0597">er a camera stat</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0595">I was going to say what have you got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s sat right there what did you get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0592" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> are rivals <unclear/> I tried <unclear/> didn't realise they were rivals</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0596"><unclear/> colouring book</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0595">she wants one as well</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0598">we we call it <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> life <anon type="place"/> uni</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0597"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1653" who="S0598">yeah we do we say the SU or</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0597">we can call you <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1655" who="S0595">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0598">oh ha I <trunc>reg</trunc> reregistered for the doctors</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0597">did you?</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0598">er a couple of year yeah in <anon type="place"/> and like a couple of months ago my mum changed my name on the NHS register to be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know my actual name</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0597">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0598">I registered for the doctors in <anon type="place"/> and someone was obviously reading my form and was like oh that's wrong and some bag had <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> again</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0595" trans="overlap">what do you mean? what what do you mean your name's?</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0598">so my name on the official NHS register I am <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1663" who="S0595">oh</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0598">and my mum changed it because it was wrong and then when I reregistered they changed it back so now I'm back as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I just can't be bothered to change it</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0597">you'd have to legally change your name to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1666" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0597">just cos everyone else calls you</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0598">and I get free prescriptions until I turn nineteen</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0597">celebration</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0598">mm?</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0597">celebration <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1672" who="S0592">actually it's an appropriate song isn't it</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0596">if I get erm with my prescription right the erm I got I have to pay eight pound twenty for the NHS prescription or I can buy the</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0595">for what?</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0596">iron tablets but I can actually buy them non prescription for six pounds and I can get more</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0595">yeah just do that</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0596">yeah I do but I don't get I don't get it</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> good times come on do do do <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1679" who="S0592">I'm not sure I think I'm under my dad's insurance or something cos I'm a full time student so I think I'm under it till I'm like twenty-five</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0595">you don't have to pay if you're a full time student</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0598">no only once you're <trunc>ei</trunc> erm nineteen</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0595">no</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0598">yeah read the back of the</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0595">we I have a form at home</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0598">read the back of the erm prescriptions you can claim it back but like you actually have to like pay up front</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0595">well I filled out a form to say that I'm going to university</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0598">no I don't</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0597">I don't know about me</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0592">I don't I don't think I have to pay for things like that</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0598">I don't yeah I don't have health insurance either</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0595">I don't now I have to pay for it now like I was ill they thought I had and like my head was like was funny again like I was on so many antibiotics it cost me so much it was like worth it it was like an extra like thirty pounds and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="1692" who="S0592" trans="overlap">as <trunc>lo</trunc> as long as I'm a student I'm okay so</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0598" trans="overlap">is it like supreme health of something?</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0598">that's what my parents were on and it just wasn't worth it cos it's an extra four pounds a month but I mean honestly it just wasn't worth it</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0597">thirty?</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0595">about thirty forty</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I don't I don't know actually like how much it actually costs and which one it is but my older brother's offered now cos he's just finished uni so</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0598">okay well</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0595">which one's that? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0596">I get erm that's okay well I have no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1703" who="S0595">didn't he do a masters?</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0598">I would do if I was</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0597" trans="overlap">how often do you get erm?</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0592" trans="overlap">no he just did erm</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0598">permanent at Boots</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0595">it was something with history or something?</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0597" trans="overlap">a work based health check as in eye tests back tests?</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0595">you get a free eye test won't you? cos you're working</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0597">yeah cos you work in front of a computer</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I think he just he just I think he did I don't want what it's called in history I I'd call it a bachelors I don't know if it is a bachelor's</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0597" trans="overlap">you actually pay for eyes tests I assume you do?</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0597">yeah well now you can get them for free it's required like I don't know how often every six months every year</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0598" trans="overlap">bachelor of science or is it a bachelor of history?</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I don't know if it would be bachelor of arts for history</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0597">maybe</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0592">I don't know</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0598">my brother gets everything free</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0592">I don't know but he he completed it this year so</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0597">damn wish I had diabetes</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0598">ha no it's <trunc>s</trunc> it's erm cos you can erm you're more likely to get gum disease lose teeth go blind or lose a limb if you have type one diabetes so you get everything free</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0595">it's it's when he gets older</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0598">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0595">then his cos he'll get like a oedema and stuff in his legs</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0598">that's why he's doing a lot of sport he he broke his toe playing rugby his second</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0595">breaking your toe is really easy but it hurts so much</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0598" trans="overlap">but they can't he said erm the doctors can't do anything about it</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0595">no you can't it's a toe</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0598" trans="overlap">they just left</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0595">you just strap it</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0598">but he can't now like bend it this way he like he can do it that way he can't do that way</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0597"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at work said he dislocates his knee really easily he's dislocated it like eight times in his life</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0598">fifty minutes until I can take my antibiotic</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I can dislocate my knee quite</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0598">but then I still have to wait half an hour to eat after that</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0595">why don't you just take them now?</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0598">because you have to leave six hours in between</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0595">it's only <trunc>ha</trunc> it's only half an hour</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0598">no you have to leave six hours in between</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0595">I would take them now</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0597">you work in a hospital is this the kind of advice you give to your patients?</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0598">is it okay to take my antibiotics now I'm not going to die from an overdose?</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I would say no no</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0596">but you won't be able to take them for</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0598">ah I never put them in your fridge oops</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0595">no it's not if you take it now it's fine like with the patients if they have medication or anything there's a leeway of an hour where they do medication so it should be fine like there's morning medication lunch time and and tea time medication and the medication will take within an hour and a half like the actual</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0598" trans="overlap">it's like the colour of a food dye</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0596">oh</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0598">it's really red</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0595" trans="overlap">so you'll be fine what flavour did you get the banana flavour?</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0598">no it's strawberry flavour but it <trunc>does</trunc> it smells like strawberry like really pungent and the actual like taste of it tastes like nothing</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0595" trans="overlap">oh it tastes like just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1756" who="S0598" trans="overlap">it tastes like it tastes like chemicals that shouldn't</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1758" who="S0597">at least it doesn't taste like mould</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0598">like what?</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0596">mould</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0598">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is ignoring me</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0598">but the banana one was actually nice</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0597"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1765" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>ig</trunc> oh that's probably why</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0596">what?</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0595">hey why is my internet now <trunc>disloca</trunc> disconnecting?</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0597">you were going to say dislocated then weren't you?</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0592">my my internet's dislocated</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0595">why is it not? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1771" who="S0596">what?</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0595">it's working now don't worry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is ignoring me look look</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0597" trans="overlap">the signal here is</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0598">well how did he go in and get er erm a certificate for exams?</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0592">you go into registry</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0595" trans="overlap">I think you just go in</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0596">yeah just go to reception and just say I want my certificates</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0595" trans="overlap">you have to normally take it cos when I did mine at college cos we didn't have a certificate either you have to take a form of ID with you as well</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0596">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0595">so like your driving licence</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0592">take take take some ID and just go to registry I think</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0597">when do they start doing that fourth?</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0595">fourth?</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0592">fourth yeah</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0597">just the day I get back</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0596">yeah me too</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0592">I need to pick up my erm yeah I'm probably just going to leave mine in my drawer or something cos I'm not happy but</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0595">what did you get?</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0598" trans="overlap">it's like the consistency of erm</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0592">A N U</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0598">it's like the consistency of like jelly you know like before it's set set</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0595">but you're meant to leave that in the</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0596">I know I know you're meant to leave it in the fridge</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0598">well I have got another bottle</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0595">I made jelly I left it in the fridge though I tried to make it really cool cos it's Christmas so right I did painting green jelly tastes like strawberry so it was like red so I when you make jelly I <trunc>a</trunc> instead of putting I put half hot water which melts it and instead of putting cold water in I put ice cubes and then it melts so it like set itself half already like sets quicker</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0598">mm</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0595">so it goes like really gloopy put the red one in the dish put that in the fridge for like half an hour and it was really gloopy still and then I did the same with the green and then I popped them together in one see because they're part set it should marble hopefully if it works it's going to look amazing when you cut into it but if it doesn't it's going to look absolutely foul and disgusting it will taste fine still but <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1798" who="S0598">oh I made a <unclear/> for my Christmas dinner I I cooked Christmas dinner for the flat me slaving away in the kitchen all day erm and it was so good</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0595" trans="overlap">you're just looking at me trying to open this it's almost</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0592"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1801" who="S0595">she will do this</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0598">apart from the fact that I burned the pigs in blankets I left them in the oven like forgot about them</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0592">almost there don't worry about me it's okay</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0595">sorry I love looking at stuff</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0598">it was so cool the icing tastes like tasted like Bourneville</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0595">is that the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0597">dunno</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0595">no it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1810" who="S0598">and that was the Christmas dinner I made</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0595">cute <pause dur="long"/> where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? I want him to open this present</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0596">what did you get him? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1813" who="S0595">I want it to be a surprise to you lot too cos it's actually really funny in a weird way</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0592">I know what it is</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0595"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1816" who="S0597">what did you get him?</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0595">I'm not telling you <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's funny but he may be funny about it <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think it'll make him laugh about it me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> refused to go and buy them</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0597">them?</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0597">them</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0597">them</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0596" trans="overlap">there's two they're they're right there they look like soap to me</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0598">it was funny because</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0597">where are they? oh these</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0598" trans="overlap">when people bring those to the erm till and just you're in autopilot and so you scan them through and then once you've done the transaction you say enjoy the rest of your evening and they go will do</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0596">I know what they are</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0597">yeah I know what they are</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0596">I've done that in Sainsbury's once the guy I was on the till and a guy came up to me and he was like just these please and then gave me this really weird look</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0595" trans="overlap">in Sainsbury's when have you ever worked in Sainsbury's?</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I worked in Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0597">last year</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0596">ages ago</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0595">oh</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0596">during summer</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0597" trans="overlap">last year</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0596">and he he was like being really weird about it</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0598">and you go enjoy the rest of your evening on autopilot and they're like I will</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0595" trans="overlap">no she she we basically bought king size ones and then flavoured ones just to be stupid and erm she was like I'm not going up there with you I'm not I refuse and she was you know how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is she went bright red and I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just go away and I'll go and get them so I did</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0596">but did you buy the JLS ones?</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0595">no no no they they were like ten quid these were like two quid</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0597">I'm sure they'd be rubbish</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0595">for packs of fifteen</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0598">you get given them by the SU and</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0597" trans="overlap">that's like twenty P per</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0598">and erm so you get them in like a pack when you start uni</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0595">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0598">erm and so just and them in my room</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0597" trans="overlap">you get them in a pack when you start uni?</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0595">yeah like on your freshers' week I got one</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0598" trans="overlap">yeah they give them to you</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0597">you got one</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0598">I got four</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0597">well that's that's what they think about you</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0598">no they actually give them to no they actually</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0597">oh that girl looks like she needs four <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1857" who="S0598" trans="overlap">everyone everyone gets them</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0595">we got one on Valentine's Day</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0598">I put them in my erm <trunc>pu</trunc> just put them in my room and I forgot about them and then I was thinking wait my mum and gran are coming down I have no idea where I put them like I can't remember and they're going to help me pack I don't want them to like pick something up and they just fall out</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0597">oh what's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> been doing?</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0595" trans="overlap">why? you're practising's safety</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0598">it would just be like a really awkward conversation</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0597" trans="overlap">practising like for the real thing?</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0598">or like an awkward like an awkward encounter</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0595">practise safe safe practise</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0598" trans="overlap">to have so I spent ages like searching my room and I managed to find them and now I know exactly where they are but I was like</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0597">good thing well if that ever happens stick it in your bra someone told me that the other day and I was like no</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0596">what if you're wearing like a really thin shirt and they can like see the shape of it?</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0595" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0597" trans="overlap">just have like a little square on the boob</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0595" trans="overlap">a patch over each boob</u>
<u n="1872" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1873" who="S0595">sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1874" who="S0597"><trunc>st</trunc><trunc>st</trunc>staying extra safe</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1876" who="S0595">nipple condoms</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0595"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have you seen the condom challenges?</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0597">no</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0595">oh it's</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0597">is that the one where you fill it with water and then drop it on someone's head?</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0595">yeah oh my god that's why we were going to buy them cos that's why we were going to buy them and we were like ah we have to do this and then we were like actually no it's funny</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0597">that's really weird</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0595">ah no it's so <trunc>we</trunc> it feels I've done it it feels so weird cos it goes like it goes over your head but the water stays in it but then it's not touching you and it just feels really odd</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0596">er</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0595">like the little just dance because like you can't breathe cos it's like on your face but then the water is like you feel like a bull frog and like and then it burst and ah</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0598"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh no I don't want to do that</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0595">yeah this song's been on twice now three times I mean</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0597">has it? is it like a playlist of five songs?</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0596">I don't know I don't even know any more</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0597">to be fair the</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0595" trans="overlap">no she's just munching</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0596">I am yeah</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0597">the shuffle on <unclear/> is a bit rubbish it's like you play two of the songs and it's like</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0595" trans="overlap">do you have a <trunc>cha</trunc>? ah actually I'll get it</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0596">would you like some more pizza before you leave?</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0595">okay that pizza was really good though</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0597">really? I thought it was a bit er</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0595">I like doughy pizza</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0596">I have that song on my playlist</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0595"><shift new="singing"/> a Christmas <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1901" who="S0596">isn't that just the most like miserable Christmas song?</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0597">it's meant to be a prep or hymn you know</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0596">it's meant to be what?</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0597">a hymn you sing it in the church</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0596">er no it's not</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0592" trans="overlap">what that song that just?</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0597">oh Christmas tree</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0596">that's not what was playing</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0592">it it was erm</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0597" trans="overlap">wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0596">no it was Fairy Tale of New York</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0597">was it? oh</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0592">my mum doesn't like that song</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0598">it's got a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1916" who="S0595" trans="overlap">can you imagine in a church song? <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1917" who="S0597">I don't know what I thought it was</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0592"><unclear/> faggot like</u>
<u n="1919" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1920" who="S0598">the priest all the little kids on the front row</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0597" trans="overlap">well this is my <unclear/></u>
<u n="1922" who="S0596">did you turn it off?</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0595">I paused it</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0596">what is this?</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0598">this actually has <unclear/></u>
<u n="1926" who="S0595">Glee why are we listening to Glee?</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0596">we don't want we don't want to listen to Glee</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0598" trans="overlap">it's just it's a Christmas song</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0597">I thought you you used to watch Glee</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0596">yeah but not not for the singing I used to fast forward through it</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0597">what so you watched it for the reality?</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0596">yeah I watched it for the acting</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0597">wow</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0596">what acting?</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0597">what have I got myself into?</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0596">the the the story was like really bad but I couldn't stop watching it</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0595"><shift new="singing"/> wager for happiness wager for happiness <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1939" who="S0598">if you follow my blog I posted a new weekly series of my top five and I did top five Christmas songs</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0596">I follow your blog and I didn't see that</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0598">yeah cos I literally updated <trunc>ye</trunc> on Monday <shift new="singing"/> let's December it <shift new="normal"/> let's December it I think</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0595">no</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> once upon time in a tunnel like this <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1944" who="S0595">oh oh my thumb went through hello ah best song ever</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0598">oh this is this is Glee again</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0595"><shift new="singing"/> de de de de <shift new="normal"/> <shift new="singing"/> cos an extraordinary happy Christmas <shift new="normal"/> it totally sounds like that as well <shift new="singing"/> he told me that it's gonna be a special year for you and me <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1947" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> that it's gonna be a special year for you and me <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1948" who="S0597"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what time are you going?</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0595">around half past</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> underneath the mistletoe hold me tight and kiss me so <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1951" who="S0597">okay</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just leaving</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0597">yes I'm leaving with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm sorry</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> I want to hear you say to me have a merry merry merry merry Christmas <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1955" who="S0592">don't mind me I'm just sitting down here with the cat</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0596">oh this is a good one</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0595">hey <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1958" who="S0598">ten minutes yeah</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0596">better put the pizza on then</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0592">I want I want to try and pick him up again but I'll be more prepared this time</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0596">we had a <unclear/> cat on <unclear/> it's a cat that lives in the States and they go to</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0598">oh my god</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0595"><unclear/> and it always is in my <unclear/> and it <unclear/> and it's so fat</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0596">what's going on?</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0595">do you see in the living room like that was me ah ah actually what actually happened?</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0596">that actually really scared me</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0595">I'm just gonna have a just gonna have a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1969" who="S0596">oh that actually really like my heart I put it back on</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0598">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1971" who="S0596">oh my god sorry <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1972" who="S0598">do you have chores?</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0596">do we have what?</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0598">do you have a chores list?</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0596">yes</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0598">I never know when whenever I come back to the house I'm just whenever like my parents are like oh can you do this? I kick up a fuss and I'm like no I'm a guest in this house now I don't live here any more <unclear/> stop it and then it's just like erm when you erm come home to come home too early for Christmas and your parents try and tell you to do something and you're just like Dobby has no master Dobby is a free elf</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0596"><unclear/> like but I I do it anyway because I'm a nice person</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0595">I'm purple</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0592">nothing purple what is what is going on really?</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0598">oh I guessed</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0596">I've guessed</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0597">we're having an affair</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0598">I've guessed</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> your phone is flashing</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0592">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0596"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1987" who="S0592">erm cos I'm recording</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0598">oh I like the hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s psychology people</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0592">well <trunc>ac</trunc><trunc>a</trunc>actually it's for it's for a project that <anon type="place"/> is doing for linguistics</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0598">hello to <anon type="place"/> I wasn't clever enough to <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0595">did you even apply to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0598">no I didn't even I remember being on the website I was like this is not for me oh he looks green</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0596">yeah I like it as well</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0598">are you going to analyse our conversation about condoms?</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0592">no it's it's it's it's not analysing it it's the erm people at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1996" who="S0598">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1997" who="S0592">so they're they're they're they're going to transcribe the conversation</u>
<u n="1998" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh <unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="1999" who="S0592">no if there's <trunc>a</trunc> if there's any</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0596">how long has that been recording?</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0592">yeah it's been a while</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0598">how much stuff are you recording?</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0592">erm an hour and almost forty minutes</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0596">how much do you you get quite a bit of money for that though don't you?</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0592">eighteen pound an hour so I need to end it I think at two hours though because they don't accept longer than <unclear>three ones</unclear>  at a time so I'll just put it back over here <unclear/> about it now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2006" who="S0596">it'd be interesting though <unclear/></u>
<u n="2007" who="S0598">is it meant to be like we're not meant to know?</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0592">no you you are meant to know that's why I told you that I'd be recording but erm there's meant to be like an actual conversation that's you know</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0598">not a fake conversation</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0592">no not not not fake or like well hello there</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0598"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hi how are was your day?</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0592">it's been alright my dear friend that's great</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0598">thumbs up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2014" who="S0596">maybe it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="2015" who="S0598">I know what it is</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0596">well I mean it's pretty obvious I'm not <unclear/></u>
<u n="2017" who="S0595"><unclear/> I'm just giving birth to my weird <unclear/></u>
<u n="2018" who="S0598">let's turn off the lights for no reason</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0597">no don't do it yet</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0596">it's not it's not my birthday</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0598">you now have working light switched</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0596">what what did you say?</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0598">I like that you now have like a proper light switch</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0596">we've literally had that for five years now</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0598">no you haven't</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0596">yeah we have</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0598">no you haven't</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0596">we have</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0598">I refuse to believe that and this though this is still</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0596">yeah but can't it's a dimmer switch</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0598">I can't use them</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0596">they don't let you <unclear/></u>
<u n="2033" who="S0598">I've never understood <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s light switches</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0592">are they the ones that push?</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0596">you you press it and the light goes off you press it and it comes back on you turn it and the light changes</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0592">I I had those in my lounge</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0596">we've got on in there but it doesn't work</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0595">oh</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0596">it always turns off</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0592">we had this annoying thing that in our rooms whenever you turn the lights on that's gonna be right in the sorry</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0598">yeah you probably shouldn't like leave it so close to the</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0592" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know I just I just realised</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0598">the whole of the last forty minutes</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0592">I just I just realisd that's going to be doing that</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0598">erm the our light so you turn it on it would be normal for like three seconds and then it switches off again and if you stand really still and you don't move it doesn't switch on cos it's on a censor so you just and then you like move and the light turns off</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0596">you alright</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="2048" who="S0596"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> your singing is being recorded</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> angel voices <shift new="normal"/> these are cute</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0596">which ones? oh the snowballs yeah</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0598">they're a lot lighter than I thought</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0592">they're probably just polystyrene</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0596">well yeah probably</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0592">polystyrene should things</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0596">quality</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0598">quality it's Christmas who cares?</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0596">if you're looking for matches you're not going to find them in there</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0598">I like these erm birds we bought some Christmas decorations at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2059" who="S0596">well I don't think they might not be in there</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0592">oh there's a coca cola polar bear</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0598"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what did you buy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0595">it's because I've now started smoking</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0596">erm it's a <unclear/> band</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0598">really?</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0595">I now smoke <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I need a lighter</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0596">okay well we don't have one so</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0595">erm that's the kind of thing I actually always normally have one my back pocket cos I have to for work cos patients are</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0596" trans="overlap">light a candle on the erm on the stove</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0595">what candle?</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0596">one of these</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0595">I need I need a cigarette</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0596">one of these</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0598">four minutes</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0596">oh I haven't put any pizza in</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0598">oh it'll fine</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0596">put the oven on it's not even heated up yet</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0598"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="2078" who="S0595">have a look <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2079" who="S0592">they're a bit stale</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0596">well they shouldn't be they've just been opened</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0592">I've no idea how loud that music's gonna be on the recording but oh well yeah</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0596">well I'm sure they can handle it</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0596">maybe you should turn it down a bit?</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0592">they asked for not too much background noise but as long as they can hear what people are saying I'm sure it'll be fine</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0596">they're a bit weird they're kind of like cinnamon flavored biscuit cake things</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0592">yeah I found the texture of them weird I quite like how the taste but</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0598">I didn't eat crisps the whole time that I was at uni</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0595">the light out so I'm in the oh sorry</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0596"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2093" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><shift new="singing"/> happy birthday to you happy birthday to you <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="2094" who="S0595">sorry I broke your name</u>
<u n="2095" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><shift new="singing"/> happy birthday dear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> happy birthday to you <shift new="normal"/> hip hip hooray</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0597">they look like side eyes</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0596">mm</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0595">really really</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0595">here you can have your E cos that broke off separately</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0596">wow thank you wow that's a fantastic E</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0595" trans="overlap">and and the tick of your N and then you're and then you're A it all broke in my hand</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0597">your mum made your name and it broke</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0595">and then the T and the A and then I'm going to have the O and the R</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0596">thank you even though it wasn't you</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I know I know it's not your birthday but your parents were like the cake's really big and your friends and here so you should really eat the cake</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0596" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0598">and it is your birthday tomorrow so</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0596">er?</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0598">it is our birthday tomorrow</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0595">does anyone want cake?</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0592">I think I'm alright for now</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0598">pizza first</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0596">we don't have any more plates so I don't know what you're going to do</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0597">there are a couple of plates</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0596">there's like two</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0597">er yeah there's two</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0595">where's the? oh I was using your plates</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0597">there's a bowl</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0595">here give her a <unclear>lime</unclear> to suck on</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0597">okay</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0595">oh</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0596">I need to stop eating it</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0595">oh oh it's sticky</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0597">that might be the candle wax</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0595">no it's like where I stuck it in the cake <pause dur="short"/> oh it's only a bit of pizza juice</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0596">the good thing about it being your birthday is that you don't have to awkwardly sing happy birthday to someone else</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0597">yeah you have to sit there</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0595">I never <trunc>sa</trunc> sung awkwardly what are you on about?</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0597">your mum made you four I guess for the front and back of the gate</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0595">but then I stuck it on back to front</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0596">my mum made these?</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0597">er think so I don't know you can ask her she made the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2135" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2136" who="S0596">mm?</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0595">would you like cake?</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0596">yes please</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0597">I suppose you have to does a bear wear a funny hat?</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0595">it's not that you're wearing the wrong way round</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0597">I know but cos then you say just approach it in the woods</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0595">where's your plate you had?</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0596">I don't know I think you got it no <pause dur="short"/> can I have the bowl actually I want a bowl <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> thank you that's a rather big slice of cake</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0597">it's like another candle</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0595">yeah</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0597">sorry <unclear/></u>
<u n="2147" who="S0595">don't come between me and my cake it's oh smaller</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0598">is the pizza in?</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0596">mm the oven need to heat up</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0592">oh no thanks</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0596">can you help put the pizza in? I'll help you do the <unclear/></u>
<u n="2153" who="S0597">yeah I'll do it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2154" who="S0595">do you like chocolate?</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0596">yeah are you are you going to put the pizza in then? do you have pepperoni on it? half pepperoni on it at least</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0597">I'll only make is this the pepperoni?</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0595">when was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> meant to come?</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0592">now around now</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0596">around now</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0596">ah</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0595"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just said where can he park?</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0596">anywhere he can find a space</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0592">in the car park</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0598">there was a space in the self he drives past where the layby and there's a little car park there was a space in there when my mum dropped me off</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0595">no he's driving <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="2167" who="S0598">yeah I'm saying there was actually a parking space there it will be gone by now</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0595">oh <pause dur="long"/> I wouldn't move this if I were you it may lose its signal okay how is that ever going to <unclear/> is it ringing?</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0596">do you want me to deliver is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just trying to find a place to park?</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0595">no he said where what's your address as well?</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0596">okay give me that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2172" who="S0595">say what you want me to type</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0596">what?</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0595">just speak <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2175" who="S0597">want to cut the cake?</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0598">lovely pepperoni cake</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0595"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> speak</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0596">no</u>
<u n="2179" who="S0598">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0597">I don't know</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0596">hello</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0595">stop just saying hello and tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> where to park</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0596">do you know round here?</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0597">does he need <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to hold his hand?</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0596">it's <anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="2186" who="S0597">which means you won't find it cos you live in an estate state like this</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0596">okay well it's number fifty-two erm have you have you left yet?</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0597">would you say that's about half <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0596">there there should be spaces to park erm you know erm</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0598" trans="overlap">mm very good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2191" who="S0596">erm no yeah should do if if not just like give <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a call and then I'll tell you</u>
<u n="2192" who="S0598">not on the cardboard</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0597">no I'm going to take the bard board off</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0598">okay fire</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0596" trans="overlap">there there is two car parks but you might just like leave the car somewhere on the road okay <anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="2196" who="S0595" trans="overlap">in the slap bang middle of the road</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0597" trans="overlap">okay what?</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0598">it's just your hand just went yeah it's just you went stop yeah just stop in the middle of the road</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0595">this cake's really good</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0596">okay see you</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0592">is it rich the cake?</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0595">mm</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0596">I got so much cake why did I why did you give me such a <trunc>bi</trunc>big bit of cake?</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0595">cos it's your birthday</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0596">look look look look what I can make do do it again</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0597">this is why we're going cake now</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0598">does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> know how to get to your house from the start of the estate?</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0596" trans="overlap">he's got sat nav</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0598">okay</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0592">that's how your verbalise cats is do that it works in all of them I swear okay look at me okay fair enough</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0596">don't let him lick you cos he'll bite your fingers</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0595">thank you</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0597">you're one</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0596">I'm one</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0597">or ninety-one or nineteen and now I'm just taking the piss you're a hundred and ninety</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0596">nine hundred and eleven</u>
<u n="2218" who="S0595">yesterday I was ninety-one <unclear/></u>
<u n="2219" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0596"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2221" who="S0597">is it twelve minutes or ten minutes?</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0595" trans="overlap">why does she always ask me this she always asks me the date I'm staying here?</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0596" trans="overlap">ten</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0597">oh well</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0596">although I only did it for eight cos it was looking a bit cooked</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0592">are you going to bite me? <pause dur="short"/> I'm such a loser <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2227" who="S0597">here <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> look</u>
<u n="2228" who="S0592">hello</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0597">smell the cake</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0592">am I supposed to keep the stick things? did mum tell you that?</u>
<u n="2231" who="S0595">no you have to eat them</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0597" trans="overlap">no where did he go?</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0595">don't know</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0596">hello I have this for you as well come on hi</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0595">six per cent battery have to charge it on the way to <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2236" who="S0597">is that where you're going now?</u>
<u n="2237" who="S0595">mm</u>
<u n="2238" who="S0597">what for?</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0598">where are you going?</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0595">I'm going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2241" who="S0598">oh nice what are you doing?</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0595">to another gathering for I double booked myself really badly but I'd said yes to the person who I'm going to next like three months ago</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0596">oh</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0595">but then I wanted to come here too so I was like</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0598">are you going M3?</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0595">mm mm</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0597">no <anon type="place"/> no the back way</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I cannot eat any more</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0595">no I'm going through <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2250" who="S0597">it didn't look that big but it was actually quite a big chunky</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0596" trans="overlap">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that was an enormous piece of cake</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0595">oh was it?</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0597">turning down chocolate</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0595">I've nearly finished mine</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0596">I don't know I got a my bit was really really big</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0595">so was mine</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0592">okay I'll leave the cat alone now</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0596">I'm sure they don't mind the attention</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0597">it's fine they will not</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0596">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might be depressed cos he's lonely no one wants to play with him any more</u>
<u n="2261" who="S0592">I love playing with my cats</u>
<u n="2262" who="S0597">yeah that's cos he's mean</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0596">yeah the only person who wants to play with him he beats up</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0592">maybe that it his way of playing I don't know</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0595"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2266" who="S0592">it's like oh my god like I want to lick you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="2267" who="S0595">like no let me lick you okay I agree with the cake now it's taking its toll</u>
<u n="2268" who="S0597">that's why I got you to half mine</u>
<u n="2269" who="S0595">I think it's quicker though you know sometimes when you put icing and it's really really like disgusting this icing is actually really good</u>
<u n="2270" who="S0597">I don't really like icing and I agree</u>
<u n="2271" who="S0595">no me neither but this is really good I don't I normally take the icing I'd normally take the icing off</u>
<u n="2272" who="S0596" trans="overlap">I'm not mad on icing</u>
<u n="2273" who="S0597">this icing isn't that bad</u>
<u n="2274" who="S0592">is it not?  I I find it too much</u>
<u n="2275" who="S0597">it's not this one though</u>
<u n="2276" who="S0595">I normally take the icing off and this this is alright</u>
<u n="2277" who="S0592">I just I just I like the cake part of cake the best I don't really like</u>
<u n="2278" who="S0595">yeah same</u>
<u n="2279" who="S0592">I'm not really kind of all like the butter cream and the icing</u>
<u n="2280" who="S0596">I like the icing part of the cake but I have to eat cake with it cos it's too rich otherwise</u>
<u n="2281" who="S0597">would you describe this icing as different?</u>
<u n="2282" who="S0596">no well it's nice it's not like sickly or anything no the the cake's a bit it's not I don't know it tastes different</u>
<u n="2283" who="S0597">might be the wax <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2284" who="S0596">what did you do with that candle?</u>
<u n="2285" who="S0597">it's upstairs I need to sort that</u>
<u n="2286" who="S0592">still burning no I'm joking</u>
<u n="2287" who="S0597">yeah I just when you hear the fire alarm</u>
<u n="2288" who="S0595" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we left it on the floor in your room <pause dur="short"/> do you want a hand?</u>
<u n="2289" who="S0597">no it's fine thank you for the help though</u>
<u n="2290" who="S0595">no worries</u>
<u n="2291" who="S0596">I need to <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2292" who="S0595">okay</u>
<u n="2293" who="S0592">we're upsetting the cats</u>
<u n="2294" who="S0595">I will always get the last clap</u>
<u n="2295" who="S0596">want to go outside? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2296" who="S0595"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="2297" who="S0597">your mum was like I got a cake for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like no don't give me the responsibility I don't want to do it</u>
<u n="2298" who="S0592">I love how it says extremely chocolatey party</u>
<u n="2299" who="S0596">what did what did you put the timer on for?</u>
<u n="2300" who="S0597">cos I <unclear/> and then I said oh two and a half minutes okay</u>
<u n="2301" who="S0598">do you have any orange juice?</u>
<u n="2302" who="S0596">yes you may have half a glass</u>
<u n="2303" who="S0598">no I don't even need half a glass</u>
<u n="2304" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="2305" who="S0598">thank you</u>
<u n="2306" who="S0597"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2307" who="S0596"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2308" who="S0597">oh no you have to <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2309" who="S0595">do you mind if I put these back?</u>
<u n="2310" who="S0596">that's fine I <trunc>wa</trunc> I wasn't expecting anyone to leave the food here that they bought</u>
<u n="2311" who="S0595">I'll <trunc>lea</trunc> I've left one can</u>
<u n="2312" who="S0597">the mince pies aren't great again I haven't found yours is like the best I've had this year and</u>
<u n="2313" who="S0596">you haven't had any this year</u>
<u n="2314" who="S0597">like was wasn't even the best</u>
<u n="2315" who="S0596">oh that one</u>
<u n="2316" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="2317" who="S0596">the one that you had that was really dry</u>
<u n="2318" who="S0597">yeah like that's the best one I've had though are you going?</u>
<u n="2319" who="S0596">okay</u>
<u n="2320" who="S0595">I feel like I've got to run now</u>
<u n="2321" who="S0598">bye you have to come see me because <anon type="place"/>'s fun</u>
<u n="2322" who="S0595">it smelt really nice oh <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="2323" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2324" who="S0598">yeah <unclear/> it's Calvin Klein <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2325" who="S0597">it's Calvin Klein?</u>
<u n="2326" who="S0598">yeah</u>
<u n="2327" who="S0597">isn't that just like men's stuff though?</u>
<u n="2328" who="S0598">no it's not</u>
<u n="2329" who="S0595" trans="overlap">Calvin Klein like we I played this it's really fun</u>
<u n="2330" who="S0597" trans="overlap">okay cos I only ever see Calvin <trunc>Kli</trunc> I only ever seen Calvin Klein on men's underwear</u>
<u n="2331" who="S0595" trans="overlap">did you spend over two hundred pounds?</u>
<u n="2332" who="S0596">I don't know my dad bought it</u>
<u n="2333" who="S0595">if it you spend over two hundred pounds he got it for free</u>
<u n="2334" who="S0596">he probably did then those things are actually I don't know</u>
<u n="2335" who="S0595">is it Star Wars stuff?</u>
<u n="2336" who="S0596">no it's a house</u>
<u n="2337" who="S0597">yeah it's boring</u>
<u n="2338" who="S0595" trans="overlap">which one? no because my friend the person who erm he gave us this the little gingerbread house he went he's really into Star Wars and there's like limited edition</u>
<u n="2339" who="S0597">yeah</u>
<u n="2340" who="S0595">Lego stuff</u>
<u n="2341" who="S0598" trans="overlap">ah <unclear/> restaurant</u>
<u n="2342" who="S0595">there's like limited edition stuff at the moment and he was like it's</u>
<u n="2343" who="S0598">but you probably paid full price for it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2344" who="S0597">you probably paid full price for it whereas you could probably get it at Legoland</u>
<u n="2345" who="S0596">yeah but parents bought it not me</u>
<u n="2346" who="S0595">yeah but I'm saying you'll get <trunc>for</trunc>forty</u>
<u n="2347" who="S0596">yeah but I didn't even know they were</u>
<u n="2348" who="S0595" trans="overlap">is there one Snapchat do you have Snapchat on your phone?</u>
<u n="2349" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="2350" who="S0595">can you snapchat David's reaction to him opening the present for me please?</u>
<u n="2351" who="S0592">I don't have you on Snapchat</u>
<u n="2352" who="S0595">I've been messaging you today <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> or get or get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s phone to send me one then</u>
<u n="2353" who="S0592">I sent you one to the <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear></u>
<u n="2354" who="S0595">that's now</u>
<u n="2355" who="S0592">so you've been messaging me and I haven't got anything <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2356" who="S0595">where?</u>
<u n="2357" who="S0592">take it back</u>
<u n="2358" who="S0595"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can click on my phone bye</u>
<u n="2359" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">bye</u>
<u n="2360" who="S0595">love you lots like <unclear/> what's?</u>
<u n="2361" who="S0598">have a good Christmas see you after it</u>
<u n="2362" who="S0597">it was nice to see you again since like six months half a year half a year</u>
<u n="2363" who="S0595">bye</u>
<u n="2364" who="S0598">bye</u>
<u n="2365" who="S0592">six months?</u>
<u n="2366" who="S0596">well yeah college I don't remember the last time I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2367" who="S0598"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday</u>
<u n="2368" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="2369" who="S0597">when was your birthday?</u>
<u n="2370" who="S0592">in August</u>
<u n="2371" who="S0598">is that <unclear/> the end of August?</u>
<u n="2372" who="S0597">obviously it wasn't that exciting</u>
<u n="2373" who="S0592">that's that's mean man</u>
<u n="2374" who="S0597">oh no I remember it</u>
<u n="2375" who="S0598">well yeah because everyone drove so I was like the only one who drinks and like</u>
<u n="2376" who="S0596" trans="overlap">oh yeah you drove and I got I had like one thing of vodka and then I got kind of</u>
<u n="2377" who="S0597" trans="overlap">cos you were working</u>
<u n="2378" who="S0592">was that with the jelly? the jelly?</u>
<u n="2379" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="2380" who="S0597">yeah it was you going like</u>
<u n="2381" who="S0598">it's cos you were working the next day</u>
<u n="2382" who="S0596">yeah</u>
<u n="2383" who="S0598">and then everyone else drove so it was just me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that got</u>
<u n="2384" who="S0597">why was I driving?</u>
<u n="2385" who="S0596">I don't know cos you offered</u>
<u n="2386" who="S0598">and I remember cos you told me and I was annoyed I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> why did you drive? <vocal desc="laugh"/> but oh well and then I had my actual birthday</u>
<u n="2387" who="S0597">I I have completely lost track of time since I started working four months have gone</u>
<u n="2388" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="2389" who="S0596">they can't fire me now</u>
<u n="2390" who="S0592">why not?</u>
<u n="2391" who="S0596">cos I'm out of the probationary period</u>
<u n="2392" who="S0592">they can still fire you</u>
<u n="2393" who="S0597" trans="overlap">I think it might be</u>
<u n="2394" who="S0596">well they can still they can still fire me but it's harder for starters</u>
<u n="2395" who="S0592">they need a reason yeah</u>
<u n="2396" who="S0597">they have to give you a reason that's the only difference  then you get notice</u>
<u n="2397" who="S0592" trans="overlap">oh well I'll need a reason yeah</u>
<u n="2398" who="S0596">erm my erm my boss on like this review thing they have at the college</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
