<text id="S6R4">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:04:27</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0092</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Education, family, hobbies, work, crime, health, politics</topics>
		<activity>Neighbours having a chat over a cup of tea.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, inviting, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0092">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>50 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Norwegian -- Intermediate; French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0092">although people say I'm fibbing  I don't know</u>
<u n="2" who="S0018">and so do you speak French and German when you go when you travel?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0092">I don't the thing is I've only been to Germany on at an airport Hamburg I think <pause dur="short"/> I went I've been on to school trips as a teacher</u>
<u n="4" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="5" who="S0092">I went to Dijon in Paris and so and I went with my mate to Paris and although he's got better qualifications than me he couldn't speak any French <pause dur="short"/> so when we went on the metro and stuff I did all the  all the  conversation for him and eh he eh <pause dur="short"/> you know on this do I have to tick all of them if I've done all of them?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0018">em or just tick the the most recent</u>
<u n="7" who="S0092">post graduate <pause dur="short"/> and should I put retired?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why not? Retired teacher <pause dur="short"/> mm hm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0092">retired</u>
<u n="10" who="S0018">that's</u>
<u n="11" who="S0092">topic <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what that means</u>
<u n="12" who="S0018">I don't know what we'll talk about yet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0092">how many years have you lived here? Eh well I've lived here since I was I've been away but only for not to live anywhere else</u>
<u n="14" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0092">so I'll just</u>
<u n="16" who="S0018">were you born in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0092">I was born at <anon type="place"/> Hospital yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0092">mm <pause dur="short"/> nineteen fifty-three</u>
<u n="20" who="S0018">uh-huh and both of your parents were from?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0092">no my mum's from Norway</u>
<u n="22" who="S0018">ah oh really?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0092">she's Norwegian</u>
<u n="24" who="S0018">oh okay that's why you speak Norwegian</u>
<u n="25" who="S0092">they were pen  They were pen  friends</u>
<u n="26" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="27" who="S0092">then she came over <pause dur="short"/> he was a lad he was <pause dur="short"/> he used to <pause dur="short"/> he had loads of girlfriends <pause dur="short"/> he was all over the place and as soon as he met her and she was the opposite</u>
<u n="28" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="29" who="S0092">she was middle <trunc>cla</trunc> he was working class <pause dur="short"/> she was middle class <pause dur="short"/> eh he just that was it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0018">how did?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0092">oh god</u>
<u n="32" who="S0018">how did they become pen friends?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0092">she was a nurse and he was in the army</u>
<u n="34" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0092">during the war they used to do that</u>
<u n="36" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0092">so that you know you'll meet I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what he was</u>
<u n="38" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What a lovely story</u>
<u n="39" who="S0092">well I'm glad they met <vocal desc="laugh"/> Gordon Bennett <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't been here <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't be here otherwise <pause dur="short"/> how many years have have you lived here? Well I'd put over fifty</u>
<u n="40" who="S0018">whatever you like <pause dur="short"/> and so did you speak Norwegian at home? When you were growing up?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0092">no no no no no <pause dur="short"/> cos I did French and German at school</u>
<u n="42" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0092">and it was my dad working class and all his family <pause dur="short"/> he's one of seventeen</u>
<u n="44" who="S0018">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> blimey</u>
<u n="45" who="S0092">Great at Christmas <pause dur="short"/> presents</u>
<u n="46" who="S0018">ooh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0092">Great Christmas and</u>
<u n="48" who="S0018">it must eat up most of your salary no? Presents for the family?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0092">I don't know I mean eh they didn't have salaries <pause dur="short"/> they used cos four or five of them they used to sleep in the shed in the garden there wasn't enough room in the house</u>
<u n="50" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0092">and they had boot clogs or something they oh eh they're poor</u>
<u n="52" who="S0018">where was this round here?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0092">yeah I mean my dad my granddad was born in Bromsgrove but they lived in Birmingham <pause dur="short"/> yeah this was he was brought up born in in nineteen twenty-six with my dad <pause dur="short"/> eh he didn't he died when he was forty-eight  forty-eight  So em so I remember it cos it's the same day my finals started at university</u>
<u n="54" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="55" who="S0092">yes <pause dur="short"/> so the family came I thought they were coming to see me and they said so I had to go back <pause dur="short"/> and I had two of my final exams <pause dur="short"/> they came up <pause dur="short"/> I had a week I was going to do revision had to go back and had to do the other seven exams after coming back from my dad's funeral</u>
<u n="56" who="S0018">oh my no</u>
<u n="57" who="S0092">I know <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't  You couldn't  eh it you couldn't plan it or write about it you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0018">gosh</u>
<u n="59" who="S0092">and I was the one cracking jokes on the in the kind of cos I it didn't sink in to me till about six months later</u>
<u n="60" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0092">then it hits you <pause dur="short"/> poomff</u>
<u n="62" who="S0018">gosh</u>
<u n="63" who="S0092">it was a sort of delayed reaction</u>
<u n="64" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="65" who="S0092">but these things are for everybody though <pause dur="short"/> it happens to everybody</u>
<u n="66" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0092">and eh it's like a lot of things until you've had things happen you can't really empathise with anybody else</u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0092">you can talk in a certain way but unless you've been in a relationship that's died or you've had relatives or you've messed up this that and the other</u>
<u n="70" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0092">unless you've done that</u>
<u n="72" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0092">you don't you can't empathise</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0092">people say you just normally <trunc>emp</trunc> I don't know maybe you can but I think if you have things similar happen to you</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0092">you're more likely to</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">yeah to be able to understand what that person's going through</u>
<u n="79" who="S0092" trans="overlap">so linguistic origin now <pause dur="short"/> eh I think it's I'll put England there shall I?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018">yeah and so <trunc>y</trunc> how did your mum cope with that cos?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0092">she's a well my mum's a brick <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't say anything <pause dur="short"/> she won't say anything</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0092">she just keeps it all in <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm like me mum and my brother and my sister are like me dad <pause dur="short"/> to look at they're like my dad but em I get I mean I've got a lot of habits I I I'll I haven't analyzed it really <pause dur="short"/> but if you look at <trunc>m</trunc> my brother and sister have brown eyes so has my dad <pause dur="short"/> I've got green eyes so has my mum <pause dur="short"/> I've got freckles so has my mum</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0092">they're slightly tanned without going in the  in the  eh sun <pause dur="short"/> so they just like darker complexion <pause dur="short"/> but we're definitely related <pause dur="short"/> but eh so at certain facets I get off my mum I mean she's like when she was in hospital we were clearing the house out we found like bean bags hundreds of them all under the cupboards <pause dur="short"/> we found loads of stuff stuff books</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">she's a hoarder <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0092">paper <pause dur="short"/> money in envelopes all over the place</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/><unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0092">em things and you know and I think and I look at some of the things and I thought blimey this I know where I get all these things <pause dur="short"/> I'm not gonna stick money in envelopes all over the place but no I mean em <pause dur="short"/> and so I work out if there's something she doesn't say I thought well would I do in that situation? Maybe if I'm like her you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0092">and I'm usually right</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0092">but she doesn't she only tells you what she wants to tell you <pause dur="short"/> and in a way that some people don't realise it <pause dur="short"/> the best way <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people tell me things and I don't know why and it's because I'm not asking</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> are you a good listener?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0092">and if people some people are always asking and prodding and they never get anywhere because people and I'm not saying anything to him he's got a big mouth and the gossip <pause dur="short"/> so I never I'm not curious if people want to tell me something they can and if they don't it's fine I'm not gonna <pause dur="short"/> cos some people seem it's like when I go on my walks <pause dur="short"/> some people always wanna know what's going on <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking and they can't help it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0092">so I don't know it's not a big deal really</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">so where do you normally go walking?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0092">well I'm I'm the team leader I organise all the walks</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="101" who="S0092">so I I organise two walking groups</u>
<u n="102" who="S0018">is it an <trunc>org</trunc> oh it's an organisation?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0092">not a big organisation now <pause dur="short"/> one was from school and it just developed friends and friends and friends</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0092">and the other one we retired when I retired every Tuesday second week during the day we go on a ramble and they could invite their friends relatives neighbours whatever</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">super</u>
<u n="107" who="S0092">there's more women on the one on Tuesday and on Sunday it's about fifty fifty</u>
<u n="108" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0092">eh sometimes it's a small number like five or six sometimes it's twelve thirteen fourteen</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0092">eh but it's good because there's no and the reason they like it is because there's no eh obligation if you don't want to turn up for one two or whatever you can turn up out of the blue that's fine <pause dur="short"/> I'll just give you the walks and you turn up when you like</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0092">there's no eh it's totally unconditional</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">where is your favourite place to go walking?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0092">well weather makes a difference</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0092">but em I like em I went to the peak cos the Peak District isn't too far away</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0092">Cos once you hit Litchfield which is only twenty-five miles away then it's just about another half an hour</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0092">from there and you're at <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/>'s on the edge of the <trunc>pe</trunc> sort of you know the <trunc>d</trunc> lake Peak District and you've got lovely roaming hills valleys you've got farms and camping sites</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0092">lovely river <pause dur="short"/> I mean what we did when I say we depending on who I'm going with it's either friends or whatever you know it's always different people <pause dur="short"/> eh and I love churches</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0092">that's why I mean bell ringing just happened just because I like <trunc>arc</trunc> I like architecture</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">oh do you do bell ringing?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0092">I do bell ringing</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="129" who="S0092">Cos em what's her name?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0092"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she get  <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me today she said I'd like to go bell ringing <pause dur="short"/> I said are you sure? Cos I <trunc>sho</trunc> I showed her my shirt with the bell ringers</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="133" who="S0092">logo and stuff</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="135" who="S0092">and I do that on <trunc>Wed</trunc> it's usually Wednesdays and Fridays <pause dur="short"/> I started at <anon type="place"/> this is when I just retired when I was fifty-five <pause dur="short"/> and I stuck it till about just under a year</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="137" who="S0092">but the thing is I used to get a bus to Kings <trunc>N</trunc> I still had a car but I didn't I thought well no I can get a bus there but the problem at <anon type="place"/> is when you get there you have to wait for everybody then you have to go up this massive spiral staircase to the top and then when you finish and you're knackered you have to come all the way down and there's no banister</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="139" who="S0092">it's just a piece of string you hold onto as you go down</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> is it it steep?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0092">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I went up into the bell tower and it's massive massive bell tower <pause dur="short"/> but I was watching these old people like I mean I know I'm getting on a bit now <pause dur="short"/> I'm sixty next year <pause dur="short"/> but these people you're talking are seventy plus eighty and they're ringing miles better than me <pause dur="short"/> it's not about how you much power you've got it's all about technique</u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">so you're actually ringing the bells in the churches or are they hand bells?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0092">no they're church bells</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018">fantastic <pause dur="short"/> oh can I come?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0092">ay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018">can I come?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0092">yeah if you want to come along <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">Cos I used to where I used to live in Spain</u>
<u n="149" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">a place called Murcia it had a cathedral and loads of different churches</u>
<u n="151" who="S0092">if you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> want to come along</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> that would be great</u>
<u n="153" who="S0092">that way you'll feel better then</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that would be super</u>
<u n="155" who="S0092">Cos but you're right cos usually it's beginners on a Friday</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0092">eh there's two blokes that are learning at the moment and one guy nearly packed up because what they think they think it's just pulling a rope</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0092">and it just all it won't <pause dur="short"/> you pull a rope then it will go back the other side <pause dur="short"/> if you don't do it properly it's all about controlling it</u>
<u n="160" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0092">and I'd I'd done it for a year then I stopped because the people that helped me one guy Ray he <trunc>wa</trunc> his family had all died <pause dur="short"/> he was never married he was a bachelor</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0092">but the thing is close family and stuff sisters and stuff</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0092">and the nearest ones are in Winchester that's got a cathedral down there and he had no reasons to stay except for the bell and so I went down there he moved down there and he was really helpful to me <pause dur="short"/> and another guy he was a fireman and he had three jobs but he wasn't always there and the other person was eh <trunc>Me</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his name was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>but the woman who was in my maths department she retired the year before me that was her doctor <pause dur="short"/> and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who comes on the walks I said when I retire I want to do something really different and I wanna do it <pause dur="short"/> because there's nothing worse than thinking you'll go down the pub or you'll you watch a</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0092">because you might as well be dead</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0092">so I mean I stuck with my chess I kinda played chess for Warwickshire county player</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0092">and I like chess but I don't like the people I'm with</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0092">because they're they're I mean as I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said that I used to think I was weird but whenever I go to the chess club I realise I'm normal <vocal desc="laugh"/> You know eh so but <pause dur="short"/> I stopped playing this year because I wanted to spend more time doing something else</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0092">eh <pause dur="short"/> not too much cos if you do too much you're not really doing anything you're just not <pause dur="short"/> so what I did what I em I started the bell ringing at <anon type="place"/> and then these people left and I used to turn up and I didn't they don't give you a chance unless you're if they want to ring in a group and you're not able you can't you'll mess it all up for them</u>
<u n="176" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0092">so you're watching and they'll say come along we'll just help you a bit <pause dur="short"/> but I was staying there for two hours and getting like five minutes</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0092">and sometimes I get there it was raining and I get soaked <pause dur="short"/> so I just thought no <pause dur="short"/> so I decided I've got to do what else did I want to do? I wanted to do Norwegian <pause dur="short"/> so the next year I signed up to do Norwegian at the Brasshouse on the Tuesday nights</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0092">and I did that for a year <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was my tutor <pause dur="short"/> she's lovely <pause dur="short"/> she's about the same age as you too and she's got a little baby</u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0092">and she's a laugh</u>
<u n="184" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0092">and I used to like going there and eh she used to bring in cakes and bake cakes and everything and she was like it was more like a social club</u>
<u n="186" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="187" who="S0092">more than anything else</u>
<u n="188" who="S0018">did you learn any Norwegian? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0092">oh yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0018">were you speaking Norwegian in the class? Was it?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0092">yeah and then I stayed another year but the thing <pause dur="short"/> the then the third year eh we got this guy <trunc>wh</trunc> who would <trunc>supp</trunc> who'd I'd had before when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was ill and I didn't like him called em <pause dur="short"/> but I'm not a good judge of character initially cos I'm always I <trunc>d</trunc> if I say something I just judge it on what I see straight away</u>
<u n="192" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0092">but em they all all the people in the group said you've got to go in the high group you can't stay in this <pause dur="short"/> so I went to the high highest group cos everybody I started with just fell by the wayside</u>
<u n="194" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0092">or left or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and eh this higher group eh there wasn't enough there was only six and we needed eight so <pause dur="short"/> the reason we were at the university's cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's one of them has been doing it for about for nine years <pause dur="short"/> he works at the university in security and</u>
<u n="196" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0092">so under the great hall there's a whole office with lecture theatres and he said we can get this room for X cheap amount of money and the most of the money will go <pause dur="short"/> so I said alright so we go there now every Tuesday</u>
<u n="198" who="S0018">is it run by the university?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0092">no it isn't</u>
<u n="200" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="201" who="S0092">it's run by em we just pay this guy who'd eh who gets it all tax free</u>
<u n="202" who="S0018">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="203" who="S0092">well that's not gonna</u>
<u n="204" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh don't worry <pause dur="short"/> they won't know you're saying it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0092">but he <trunc>lec</trunc> he lectures he's a very academic guy <pause dur="short"/> eh <trunc>Pe</trunc> is it Peter or something? But the thing is I didn't like him at first when he covered the lessons cos he was too pushy but now I can see a different side to him</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0092">but you know what it is when you see you just see one aspect of something and</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0092">sometimes people do take eh oh I don't like that</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0092">so em</u>
<u n="212" who="S0018">but pushy in what way? That he was pushing you to speak more and learn more or?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0092">well eh when he'd covered everybody was away except me and this other woman so it was nonstop asking questions</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0092">and stuff and I and he's he's a very academic sort of guy who he he was brought up in Norway eh and he's married to I don't know he's <pause dur="short"/> I think might might must be Norwegian but he says he's totally English and he's laid back but he's everything his jokes and everything are all very academic sort of jokes and I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> you know so eh <pause dur="short"/> not that there's anything wrong with that it's just that eh sometimes it takes you a while to work out what's going on</u>
<u n="216" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0092">there's nothing worse than when you're in the group and everybody's laughing and you're thinking what the? You know and you can't look like you don't know what's going on <pause dur="short"/> so I'm thinking you know what's going on here? So I'm I'm blank to it all so eh</u>
<u n="218" who="S0018">do you feel you've improved a lot since you?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0092">ah my Norwegian's better but it's I'm doing a level in a way I it's too difficult for me</u>
<u n="220" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="221" who="S0092">but the others said to me so what you're learning because you're not realising it there's certain things that are sinking in even though you're not aware of it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0092">because because eh <pause dur="short"/> and also he realises I don't do all my homework all the time <pause dur="short"/> so he said you better do your homework</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">naughty boy</u>
<u n="225" who="S0092">but sometimes I mean like anything I thought if I get if I'm stuck I'll go to ask my mum to help me because she's eighty <pause dur="short"/> but she did my homework anyway and she got it all wrong <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't tell my mum because it's all cos she's the old Norwegian</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="227" who="S0092">does the old Norwegian</u>
<u n="228" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="229" who="S0092">so eh</u>
<u n="230" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0092">you know and she's eighty-nine and I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> you know I mean <pause dur="short"/> she <trunc>c</trunc> I mean she can read stuff but she's slow anyway <pause dur="short"/> but I forget that cos I just say you know if it's your own mother you just don't take that into if it was somebody else eighty-nine you'd think blimey</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0092">but you don't do that on your own time you just expect I mean she still thinks I'm a <trunc>fi</trunc> fifteen to twenty-five year old kid <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You know she just I go I went over there today and she goes here's an Easter egg for you</u>
<u n="234" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="235" who="S0092">here's your card</u>
<u n="236" who="S0018">that's a mum's prerogative though</u>
<u n="237" who="S0092">you know and I'm thinking if I'm sixty next year and she's treating me like I'm a so but that's that's <vocal desc="laugh"/> That is that isn't it? So</u>
<u n="238" who="S0018">but going back to you being in a higher class than maybe your level is that's actually quite good if you're  if you're  if you feel confident in that class</u>
<u n="239" who="S0092">well I'm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">as as opposed to just learning the language you're actually acquiring it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0092">when I'm in a group situation if I'm not confident with the topic I'll I'll I'll compensate by being more myself like I am now</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0092">and I'll interrupt and say <pause dur="short"/> I'm a strategist I mean cos you're a teacher you can tell the strategy like you make out can you say that again or something? Even though you haven't got a clue what they're on about <pause dur="short"/> cos I'll think you're <pause dur="short"/> you know or you haven't done any questions except two so you make sure they know you've done these two or pretend you've done some other one</u>
<u n="244" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You know all the tricks don't you? Being a teacher</u>
<u n="245" who="S0092">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I mean <pause dur="short"/> when you look at other kids cos when you're teaching a class and they're stuck you've got to work out why they're stuck</u>
<u n="246" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0092">and if you don't want to bollock them you've got to work out how to get the best out of them without making them feel that they're being sort of marginalised cos if you marginalise kids or people</u>
<u n="248" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0092">it's obvious if you've got any common sense what their reaction's gonna be they're just gonna get more marginalised and they're not gonna get involved</u>
<u n="250" who="S0018">yeah they'll be demotivated</u>
<u n="251" who="S0092">so eh I would work out strategies that eh blur the actual reality</u>
<u n="252" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="253" who="S0092">so that they feel part of it <pause dur="short"/> cos you're never taught that at <trunc>coll</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> when I went to em cos I taught for a year before I went to <trunc>un</trunc> my postgraduate education</u>
<u n="254" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0092">when I left Sheffield and got me I got my degree in chemical engineering and field technology and not maths <pause dur="short"/> but it was all physics maths chemistry and other things</u>
<u n="256" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0092">em then I left cos I cos my dad had just died <pause dur="short"/> I did cos I got my degree when I I'm a July baby so I actually did my degree when I was twenty</u>
<u n="258" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0092">I didn't I graduated when I was twenty and I didn't sort of <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't want to do a job straight away so I got a job in a factory in SelIy Oak I was working on a lathe cutting metal <pause dur="short"/> I worked in the post office I worked in the railways flogged tellys</u>
<u n="260" who="S0018">Butlins?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0092">Butlins <pause dur="short"/> and then I wrote to four different jobs <pause dur="short"/> I wrote to laboratory <pause dur="short"/> I wrote to a education authority I wrote eh to the police and I wrote I don't know if it was the army or something else I wrote to places where <pause dur="short"/> and I got a job teaching</u>
<u n="262" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0092">at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I hadn't got a teaching degree and it was I got eaten alive there</u>
<u n="264" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="265" who="S0092">but that was the best way to learn</u>
<u n="266" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0092">because then I went to <anon type="place"/> University and got my PGCE and all these other people I was with had just finished their degrees in <anon type="place"/> or nice universities</u>
<u n="268" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0092">and had just started when you're going to do teacher training and stuff</u>
<u n="270" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0092">I me I had come from a I had just been eaten alive in an inner city Birmingham school <pause dur="short"/> and I was listening to these lecturers talking about discipline and behaviour and I was listening and I thought these people haven't got a clue</u>
<u n="272" who="S0018">clue <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0092">about anything <pause dur="short"/> and these are telling me what to do</u>
<u n="274" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you'd had the baptism of fire hadn't you?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0092">so what happened was I ended up at eh I the schools I ended up <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>hi</trunc> there was <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> a really rough area</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018">oh <anon type="place"/>'s yeah they're they're <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0092">mega rough <pause dur="short"/> and I got a job at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0092">and the kids were all disturbed there and strangely enough they had Maths there you're doing alright here? I said yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> and then my tutor came in and they didn't like him and then I said <pause dur="short"/> and then I haven't got a car so what do they do? It's a terrible winter where did they send me on my main secondary practice they sent me to Derby <pause dur="short"/> I'm in Nottingham in a bedsit <pause dur="short"/> they send me to Derby when other people have got cars can teach in Nottingham <pause dur="short"/> so I have to get a bus in the morning to Derby then a bus out in to to <trunc>Mick</trunc> Mickleover</u>
<u n="280" who="S0018">how long did that take?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0092">bloody ages</u>
<u n="282" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0092">and then the head of the school at Mickleover where I was he ran a chess team and he found out I could play chess and I won all my games for him <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And suddenly he if I had any discipline problems he used to sort it all out for me</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0092">and eh it was amazing really that eh you know <pause dur="short"/> my tutor came and watched me in one lesson and this kid called me a bastard <pause dur="short"/> and he he looked at me after he said that's terrible isn't it? I thought my god this guy is nuts</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's quite polite from what I heard in the classroom</u>
<u n="287" who="S0092">but I know but the thing is what I  what I  realised when I left there was that the people running it aren't haven't got their finger on the pulse and even now</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0092">if you're in the certain management situation you just want to maintain your job you don't want to ruin your job your immediate high people so you just pretend <pause dur="short"/> it's all let's pretend</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0092">and the ones at the bottom are being eaten alive</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0092">so what? It's their problem they're the ones that haven't got a proper strategy</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">well I I just felt that eh the tutors in university knew that it was a completely unrealistic situation</u>
<u n="295" who="S0092">oh yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">but they were pretending that it wasn't just because</u>
<u n="297" who="S0092">okay <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">otherwise everything just breaks down I mean <pause dur="short"/> all the the classes that I was teaching I had a for example just for one class I had four visually impaired children four hearing impaired children <pause dur="short"/> about ten children with anger management issues who as soon as they felt angry they had a leave of absence to go and talk to someone about how to deal with their anger on the moment and then in during that time you have to have lessons aims for three different levels of the within each lesson <pause dur="short"/> so you're trying to teach three different classes at the same time</u>
<u n="299" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">while you've got all you've got to cater to the visually impaired students you've got to cater to the hearing impaired students <pause dur="short"/> and then all the anger management the eh these students that don't deal with their anger very well <pause dur="short"/> you've got all this to manage and then on top of that I don't know what it was like for maths but for teaching languages you have to prepare so much material <pause dur="short"/> and it's the fashion nowadays <trunc>n</trunc> not to rely on course books <pause dur="short"/> all the teachers that I saw in about three or four different schools that I visited they</u>
<u n="301" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">generate their own materials <pause dur="short"/> I mean you know probably from your Norwegian classes that in an hour you can get through about four or five bits of material</u>
<u n="303" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">that will stimulate conversation</u>
<u n="305" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">or stimulate you know reading skill or level</u>
<u n="307" who="S0092">Cos what he does cos it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we used the textbooks and she used to digress if we talked about making cake or something</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0092">or a walk or something <pause dur="short"/> cos she used to she was one of these she was very funny <pause dur="short"/> she was wacky <pause dur="short"/> she had a hobby it was called <trunc>plan</trunc> I don't know was it planking or plaining? She used to get on places and</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">oh planking yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0092" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she used to bring pictures on her phone and anywhere on a mountain and</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> A few people have died doing that haven't they? Trying to plank on bridges or cliffs</u>
<u n="313" who="S0092">and then this other one which something ironing where you have to put an ironing board</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">on a motorway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0092">or on the top of a hill or on a bloody <vocal desc="laugh"/> rock in the middle of nowhere I mean for god's sake but she was funny <pause dur="short"/> she was wacky but she was funny</u>
<u n="316" who="S0092">very crazy <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0018">yeah but I mean you know at least you know where you're coming from <pause dur="short"/> I well I I I felt sort of felt more and I don't know why I should feel more relaxed with people like that but I did <pause dur="short"/> sometimes if people are too serious and stuffy and stuff I don't feel relaxed with them</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0092">I don't know why but em no I mean you've got to have a bit of eh you've got to have an edge somehow</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0092">just to give some momentum in a situation</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0092">otherwise and I mean that's the trouble and a lot of the people I work with <pause dur="short"/> eh I used to do crazy things all the time <pause dur="short"/> well crazy relative to what they'd say was crazy and I mean</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018">what in the classroom?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0092" trans="overlap">I got oh my god I've got pictures of me em when I was at <trunc>Swan</trunc> you know the girls school?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="327" who="S0092">I was there for two years <pause dur="short"/> I got <trunc>thr</trunc> oh we had a blind date competition and I dressed up as this woman <pause dur="short"/> I had three balloons in here I had a pair of wellys I had an apron <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I had my hair all done properly <vocal desc="laugh"/> I had a mop eh and I was one of the eh the girls went absolutely bananas when I came into the room <pause dur="short"/> but the the scheme of things I they always gave me the bottom forms and my form and you know I had the bottom form <pause dur="short"/> they'd run after me with compasses trying to break my balloons <vocal desc="laugh"/> And I thought bloody be careful <pause dur="short"/> you know what girls are like together they're worse than boys <pause dur="short"/> they were scary I tell you</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">very scary</u>
<u n="329" who="S0092">I know <pause dur="short"/> the only time I've ever been hit is trying to stop girls fighting</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0092">stop boys fighting they'll stop</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0092">you get in the way of two girls they won't stop trying to hit each other</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">passion involved in a girl fight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0092">oh <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>kn</trunc> oh girls together wow</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018">so how did you cos one of the biggest problems I found in the classroom was I mean obviously your Norwegian class everyone who goes there is motivated</u>
<u n="337" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">they've got their internal motivation reasons that they want to learn</u>
<u n="339" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">so they come and they're happy to be there and they're happy to</u>
<u n="341" who="S0092">well</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">participate <pause dur="short"/> but obviously as you know in classrooms in secondary schools</u>
<u n="343" who="S0092">well</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">and also kids don't  kids don't  want to learn a foreign language <pause dur="short"/> they don't see the benefit of it</u>
<u n="345" who="S0092">I know that's I mean I know with maths <pause dur="short"/> but if I was doing <pause dur="short"/> as I said to you the other day you've got to have a combination I know it's difficult for women I mean I'm a big bloke and when you dress really smartly</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0092">and you look after you make your hair all <unclear/> and you're clean shaven and you your voice projects a manner of eh I'm not gonna be messed about but you're not nasty with it</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0092">so I have a mixture of fear they have a mixture of fear and <unclear/> Cos some teachers though they do not play up it's if it's more fear than anything else</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0092">given an opportunity they'll like if they're away to cover <pause dur="short"/> but like with my form I had the same form five years and then I was another form I kept <pause dur="short"/> they used to em if I was away nobody played up they all did they everybody shut up because they were used to it</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0092">and all the kids associated with the room that day my room as a place where nobody played up</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">mm that's good</u>
<u n="355" who="S0092">and it's strange how you do <trunc>ass</trunc> associate a certain building or something <pause dur="short"/> or they won't play up as much they might play up a bit if I'm not there</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0092">but em and also I never used to send the kids to the management <pause dur="short"/> I never used to sent them to heads of year</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0092">ever <pause dur="short"/> I used to sort all my own problems out</u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">that's good</u>
<u n="361" who="S0092">and I never made threats <pause dur="short"/> I said I used to say to them if you do that now I'm gonna do something <pause dur="short"/> I won't tell you what I'll do but I'll do something <pause dur="short"/> cos if you let them know what you're gonna do</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0092">you have had it</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0092">Cos they'll push it so I never and I said <pause dur="short"/> that I used to do at the first start I used to make like my first lesson after I've thrown the books at them and told them just and told them a load of rubbish and so they worked <pause dur="short"/> well basically they didn't know if they were coming or going with me because they didn't know how what I was like and cos all their mates used to say <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is a laugh he's funny</u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0092">and then they were thinking no he isn't <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos I the new kids</u>
<u n="368" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0092">and then I used to say well I'm gonna have the first week I'm not gonna do any maths we're just gonna learn what you've got to do to be behave for me <pause dur="short"/> I said and I used to say I've got no control about what goes on with the rest of the school so if you doss around and mess about in somebody else's classes that's not my problem <pause dur="short"/> but I I looked at this nice top set of first years that came in and then I said I just stared I said everybody in here knows how to behave <pause dur="short"/> but you also know how to play up now don't you? And I pointed to this nice well you know girl sitting there <pause dur="short"/> and yes sir then I also who else knows how to play up? Put your hand up they all put their hand up I said see but you're not going to do that with me are you? No sir <pause dur="short"/> and you do that for the first week <pause dur="short"/> they'll not forget that that's there for the whole five years</u>
<u n="370" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0092">and then  And then  I said rules like you don't come late and then I used to say I don't want you to go on <unclear/> Why not? Can somebody tell me <pause dur="short"/> I want five reasons so I used to reinforce them from them</u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0092">I never used to eh go on and just say and what about your books? And I said here's a book and I said one and here's another one <pause dur="short"/> which one do you think if you were a teacher you'd tell a person off <pause dur="short"/> I'm getting them reinforcing what I want</u>
<u n="374" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0092">by getting them why? Somebody's put some graffiti on it <pause dur="short"/> what's what's that mean? And then they were telling me <pause dur="short"/> why isn't that a good idea? And then I set them a ruler <pause dur="short"/> what's that? It's a ruler <pause dur="short"/> now somebody told me that I should use that to hit people over the head with but and I <trunc>s</trunc> and they think  they think  is he a nasty so and so or what? And just try and smoulder about it thinking let me think about it</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="377" who="S0092">but I only thought of a nail a drawing pin at one end <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah they're really scared then <pause dur="short"/> and then I'd go on to say well who can tell me what a ruler is for? Drawing lines sir <pause dur="short"/> but what does he mean by that? I <trunc>mar</trunc> what a margin? And then I'd get them so I'd spend ages</u>
<u n="378" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0092">I don't just do it quickly so it all sinks in because the teachers worry about the bright children in class</u>
<u n="380" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0092">they're going to follow it anyway <pause dur="short"/> it's the ones that are going to give you trouble later on</u>
<u n="382" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0092">if you let that sink in big time at the start</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0092">later on they might be they doing it with other and when they do start getting away with things with other people unless you've made a big deal about it you're going to be on the receiving end <pause dur="short"/> cos it's like a virus</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018">yeah yeah definitely</u>
<u n="387" who="S0092">but</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018">I think that's what had happened in my in the school that I was in that basically senior management</u>
<u n="389" who="S0092">what school was it?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">em the one I told you about last last week in Bournville?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0092">oh Bournville</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">and I think senior management hadn't got just at the top-down discipline and so the <trunc>te</trunc> the teachers basically didn't have the support behind them to be able to to use discipline themselves</u>
<u n="393" who="S0092">was Nick Osbourne still there in PE?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0018">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="395" who="S0092">we used to go there and play basketball <pause dur="short"/> I remember we went to Bournville <pause dur="short"/> I'll tell you why I remember Bournville cos we used to go to the pub afterwards</u>
<u n="396" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0092">and we went to the Country Girl and I had my car nicked from the car park there</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">oh doesn't surprise me that area is was a bit dodgy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0092">and do you know me mates asked when he give a little <vocal desc="sneeze"/> I said eh  I said eh  I can't find my car <pause dur="short"/> and eh he said and I was looking under I was looking you know what you do you look over the fence you look in the most <trunc>stu</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> as if the car's gonna jump out over the fence <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know so eh and this bloke he just buggered off <pause dur="short"/> he said oh well I better catch the bus then <pause dur="short"/> I was going to take him home <pause dur="short"/> he didn't no I'll stay with you and stuff</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">didn't help you or anything</u>
<u n="401" who="S0092">no no no</u>
<u n="402" who="S0018">nice bloke</u>
<u n="403" who="S0092">I went to King's Heath police station to report him and you know what the policeman said to his mate? Thank god that's not on our patch</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018">oh god</u>
<u n="405" who="S0092">in Bournville <pause dur="short"/> so really when you're looking for sympathy the worst thing is the shock is when you don't get it when you <pause dur="short"/> and so sometimes when you want to lean on somebody you can't and so you've gotta</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0092">and that in a way you get inured in and hardened to <pause dur="short"/> it makes you stronger but at the time you feel really vulnerable I <trunc>fo</trunc> I found it or the police phoned me up five days later <pause dur="short"/> I was in Spark Hill in the inner city</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0092">eh I had to start it with a screwdriver somebody had all my marking my tapes my books everything CDs they nicked</u>
<u n="410" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="411" who="S0092">yeah they they'd screwed the doors with a screwdriver the coursework nicked I was gonna mark</u>
<u n="412" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="413" who="S0092">yeah I got in trouble over that</u>
<u n="414" who="S0018">you got in trouble?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0092">yeah initially I did till I told them <pause dur="short"/> eh and also the fact that I couldn't go anywhere without you know and I just felt bloody hell it's just gone where has it all gone to?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="417" who="S0092">you know</u>
<u n="418" who="S0018">why would they steal coursework?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0092">they didn't know what was in it</u>
<u n="420" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="421" who="S0092">they just took everything and then just like what they do when they burgle a house <pause dur="short"/> if something looks and then they'll dump it later on won't they?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0092">so that was that</u>
<u n="424" who="S0018">and what did the kids have to do? Do the coursework again?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0092">no <pause dur="short"/> but in a way I thought that's good but some of them were crap they'll probably get an average mark now <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know what I mean? But these are things that happen to you and you just don't want them to happen again <pause dur="short"/> it's like a lot of things you know</u>
<u n="426" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0092">what people don't realise when they're younger anything you see somebody who's a lot older than them the things that happen to them the chances are fifty or sixty percent of the things happening to them you're gonna have</u>
<u n="428" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0092">or maybe more <pause dur="short"/> because part of living is not just having fantastic things happen to you</u>
<u n="430" who="S0018">yeah it's getting through the</u>
<u n="431" who="S0092">but things like</u>
<u n="432" who="S0018">awful things</u>
<u n="433" who="S0092">either meeting having a nasty experience with people or in that or a health scare</u>
<u n="434" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0092">or a job it may be losing a job or getting demoted</u>
<u n="436" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0092">or not keeping whatever or if you've got family split up or your kids are in trouble</u>
<u n="438" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0092">I'm not saying it's but it's a combination of them or</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0092">even families that are sort of stable you know like <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean it's a tough time for middle classes now really</u>
<u n="442" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0092">because they they say they work hard and they've got all this and then all of a sudden they realise things have got to they've got to sacrifice things</u>
<u n="444" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0092">you know I mean my sister I mean my nephew is at <anon type="place"/> it's ten grand a term but I said may my wife's husband's on two hundred grand a year</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018">wow what does he do?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0092">he's a big chief exec for an induction company</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0092">but it's <unclear/> it owns eh race horses and he's like mega mega mega bucks he's boss he's just a minion he is he's just lucky he's impressed <pause dur="short"/> and I mean he only got the job because he was going to be made redundant <pause dur="short"/> he's on thirty grand a year at Birmingham city council</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0092">and he got so he had to find somewhere and then this he got rapid promotion</u>
<u n="452" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0092">so it's just luck really</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018">it is <pause dur="short"/> I'm waiting for a bit of luck <pause dur="short"/> I've had nothing but bad luck for the past ten years or so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0092">but I mean you know I mean <pause dur="short"/> you might think you've had bad luck but you might meet other people who've had a lot worse</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">yeah I know it's true <pause dur="short"/> that's when</u>
<u n="457" who="S0092">it's all</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I went I got mugged when I was thirty and they broke my jaw I broke all my bones down my arm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0092">was this in Birmingham?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018">no that was in Barcelona when I lived there</u>
<u n="461" who="S0092">Cos Barcelona I mean my my friends went there and em they got robbed</u>
<u n="462" who="S0018">oh it's yeah I was teaching I was training teachers to be English teachers and we'd have like thirty students every month and at least two of them would get mugged on a it was a monthly thing</u>
<u n="463" who="S0092">but then you didn't know that you'd been robbed till you got back to your?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="465" who="S0092">they were really sophisticated</u>
<u n="466" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah they they've got so many methods of doing it <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately well I was mugged about six times eh what robbed but the last time was a violent mugging cos they were on a motorcycle and they came up onto the pavement behind me and grabbed my bag off my arm but it had short straps so I ended up getting dragged behind the motorbike that was going about fifty kilometres an hour</u>
<u n="467" who="S0092">so they didn't intend to break your arm?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> they didn't do it like</u>
<u n="469" who="S0092">I thought they were just gonna broke your arm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">no they didn't do it like</u>
<u n="471" who="S0092">oh</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018">here take this bang bang bang</u>
<u n="473" who="S0092">no I mean</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018">but still</u>
<u n="475" who="S0092">I know if it's the case it's the big place for robbery in the whole of Europe</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0092">and Rome is not too good either they say</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0092">but I mean you know when things like that happen it does make you well it takes a while to sort of feel confident to go out again</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">definitely but I I would have got over that fine but the problem was that the consequences of me being ill I got sacked from my job for while I was off sick and I had to take them to court</u>
<u n="481" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">cos it was illegal what they'd done <pause dur="short"/> and then I hadn't had <trunc>d</trunc> the doctors hadn't diagnosed me properly <pause dur="short"/> I was complaining about my neck cos every week or so I'd get a bolt of lightning in my neck</u>
<u n="483" who="S0092">and what did they do?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">they just sent me to a lot of different specialists that told me</u>
<u n="485" who="S0092">is it sorted now?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018" trans="overlap">kind of I still have problems <pause dur="short"/> it was a herniated disc in my neck</u>
<u n="487" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">and so I had to take so much time off on my next job</u>
<u n="489" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">because sometimes I couldn't even hold my head up eh or breathe properly <pause dur="short"/> that I lost that job as well and then the next job that I got teaching at Murcia University <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="491" who="S0092">which university?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">in Murcia in Spain</u>
<u n="493" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">and cos they did dodgy work contracts over there because they don't want to make you permanent because they have to</u>
<u n="495" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">pay more social security for you</u>
<u n="497" who="S0092">right</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">and so Murcia University were illegally employing us and one of teachers complained to the department of employment who came and did a big inspection and and said <trunc>we</trunc> we're fining you half a million Euros and you're no longer allowed to employ people on these contracts <pause dur="short"/> so they just terminated everybody's contract and only took on teachers who had the civil service em</u>
<u n="499" who="S0092">so anyway you got punished for?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah it was just being bang bang bang and that's</u>
<u n="501" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018">in the end the reason why I moved back to England and thought I'll carry on being a teacher I'll do a PGCE</u>
<u n="503" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">and then it was the difference it was just such a shock to get into</u>
<u n="505" who="S0092">behaviour</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018" trans="overlap">the behaviour was a nightmare I mean I've taught all ages and levels of kids in Spain and yeah there's you know they are they're kids aren't they?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0018">they're gonna play out they're gonna misbehave but there was no hostility there was no violence</u>
<u n="509" who="S0092">how many schools have you taught in here then? Was it all secondary schools?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0092">if you get have you ever thought of private schools?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0092">I mean you could still get them playing up but they play up in a totally different way</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0092">eh I don't know I mean it's <trunc>la</trunc> the good thing is I think language you're at an advantage now because some of the news headlines the other day about they haven't got enough interpreters</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0092">for criminals <pause dur="short"/> there's a massive problem now with recruitment getting people to do languages so I think if if someone changes</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0092">in your I mean what language would you be able to teach just Spanish or?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">french and Spanish yeah and because of the EBac that is in at the moment is being brought in</u>
<u n="521" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">you know a language for a lot of people is gonna be essential</u>
<u n="523" who="S0092">oh you?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">to get their EBac so I think there's going to be quite a lot of teaching jobs</u>
<u n="525" who="S0092">it's just that I</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">but I just don't know whether I'll be able to cope I mean you say that all teachers and are so stressed and don't get to enjoy their holidays cos they're always working</u>
<u n="527" who="S0092">well the thing is I mean it might sound bad in one way but because I wasn't married or had kids myself</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0092">in a way it was a benefit in one way because some of them used to go home and I'm not saying their marriages were on the rocks but to have their strong marriage you're got to put a lot in to it</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0092">and so that means you've got to be eh either understanding or say you have eh not in the right frame of mind one way and you've got to do A B C D and you if I come home I don't want to do anything I just used to do what I liked</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0092">which is basically either soak in the bath or go to bed eh or just chill out</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0092">and I mean I I I I didn't know I had diabetes for a while so I'd end up going on that <pause dur="short"/> I used to get my blood pressure checked regularly and then it wasn't that long cos if it was too long it would cause all the damage but eh <pause dur="short"/> so I must have been at school working and I was wondering why I was tired and stuff</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0092">but there must be other teachers going in and having other things going on with them <pause dur="short"/> but partly I think some of the stress must affect create a situation where it makes you ill</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure of it</u>
<u n="539" who="S0092">so you know and it is a stressful job <pause dur="short"/> I mean I eh I started teaching in nineteen seventy-five</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0092">I stopped I retired in two thousand and eight <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not long in compared to some but it is long enough when think about the intensity of the job you're on your feet all day <pause dur="short"/> I used to get in I used to leave the house at about <trunc>tw</trunc> quarter past seven</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0092">so I could get on the photocopier and then chill before we started</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0092">so is it was only the last fifteen years at Hall Green <pause dur="short"/> it isn't that far but there's nothing worse if you've got a long train journey or traffic</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">it was taking me two hours to get to the other side of Birmingham</u>
<u n="547" who="S0092">what side did you live then?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">em Solihull</u>
<u n="549" who="S0092">you live in Solihull and you had to get to Bournville?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">yeah public transport</u>
<u n="551" who="S0092">what time what route did you go?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">I'd catch the thirty-seven down to Acocks Green</u>
<u n="553" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">and then get the eleven around to the Bristol Road</u>
<u n="555" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">and then get the eh sixty-two</u>
<u n="557" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">down the Bristol Road which would have been fine if there hadn't been in traffic eh</u>
<u n="559" who="S0092">were there teacher that worked lived near?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> there weren't any that lived by me</u>
<u n="561" who="S0092">oh</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">it was such a shame but yeah I was spending four hours a day travelling <pause dur="short"/> and then getting home at night and then you've got to plan your lessons for the next time and</u>
<u n="563" who="S0092">so how long were you at Bournville for?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018" trans="overlap">eh four months <pause dur="short"/> it was my first</u>
<u n="565" who="S0092">I bet you weren't upset when you didn't stay any longer</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">well it was my first placement <pause dur="short"/> it was only for</u>
<u n="567" who="S0092">where have you been doing since then?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018" trans="overlap">well that's the thing I deferred  I deferred  it in January because</u>
<u n="569" who="S0092">was that with the university?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0092">which Birmingham or?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">yeah Birmingham</u>
<u n="573" who="S0092">okay</u>
<u n="574" who="S0018">Cos I put I've done the five five months the four months before Christmas</u>
<u n="575" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018">literally every day all my waking hours was working and then at the weekend I'd be writing the research projects</u>
<u n="577" who="S0092">mm hm</u>
<u n="578" who="S0018">for the university so I had no free time to relax</u>
<u n="579" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0018">and I sustained that for four months and then I had the Christmas break and then I went back in January and I just couldn't concentrate and my brain just broke <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I thought there's no way that I could continue</u>
<u n="581" who="S0092">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0018">I'm gonna defer <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether I want to to be a teacher in in this environment and I'm gonna take the year</u>
<u n="583" who="S0092">but what what options have you got now?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0018">well I'm looking into em publishing cos the English as a foreign language</u>
<u n="585" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0018">there's such a big big market worldwide there's quite eh a few big publishing companies that em publish materials for</u>
<u n="587" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0018">different markets within the English as a foreign language market <pause dur="short"/> so I've applied for a few jobs em in Oxford working to promote</u>
<u n="589" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0018">primary resources and that would seem natural for me to go into</u>
<u n="591" who="S0092">oh yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0018">for me to take advantage of the experience that I've got <pause dur="short"/> cos I've got fourteen years experience</u>
<u n="593" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0018">in teaching English <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="595" who="S0092">yeah you've got to do something like that</u>
<u n="596" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0092">it's just unfortunate the job situation</u>
<u n="598" who="S0018">exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's just not the right time to well be making a career move <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0092">but it's the same for everybody and I mean</u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0092">you know you need but I mean <pause dur="short"/> I never think about what other people's problems are I just think well I'm out of it now</u>
<u n="602" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0092">I mean</u>
<u n="604" who="S0018">thank your lucky stars <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0092">well I'm lucky in one way it's no good <pause dur="short"/> I give it I <pause dur="short"/> somebody told me a joke the other day that made me really think about a lot of things <pause dur="short"/> they said this was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who came on the walk she's a very interesting woman she said there were these two two blokes in an old people's home <pause dur="short"/> they're about ninety-five years old each sitting there staring at the wallpaper just like that <vocal desc="laugh"/> And one said to the other aren't you glad we stopped smoking? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Basically they probably lived eh not doing anything</u>
<u n="606" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0092">so they'd live a long life but they're just living like morons</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0092">and yet some people don't live so long because they're taking risks</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0092">and doing this that and the other <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking yeah I know it's it's terrible in a way but it's far better than I I think <pause dur="short"/> you don't think though that if you're ill or something but to do lots</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0092">I'm not saying it's cramming so it's unbearable cos some people do have a life where they're doing a lot more</u>
<u n="614" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0092">and I'm not saying that they're going to die young but other people don't do anything</u>
<u n="616" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0092">and that's not a life is it?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0018">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's just an existence</u>
<u n="619" who="S0092">so so you know I mean <pause dur="short"/> some of your experiences and I know they were unpleasant <pause dur="short"/> they might hold you in good stead later on</u>
<u n="620" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0092">because at least you're aware of what's there</u>
<u n="622" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0092">then you're aware you know some people are totally naive and didn't like</u>
<u n="624" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="625" who="S0092">you know and go through life and they think that everything is all just going to be alright it isn't <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>educa</trunc> education <trunc>edu</trunc> people in charge as you said they know they're playing let's pretend</u>
<u n="626" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> totally <pause dur="short"/> would you go back into teaching? Well if you had to do a career start a career now would you go into teaching?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0092">no</u>
<u n="628" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0092">well it's sad <pause dur="short"/> one thing I the scary thing at Hall Green one thing was it was too many women <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't hate women but there's ninety percent women</u>
<u n="630" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0092">and some of these aging lads cos I said the culture and although women can do the job just as well as men in a lot ways that when you get a certain number of women together other things kick off <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what it is but I mean they go to extremes <pause dur="short"/> men will say no I mean</u>
<u n="632" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0092">but if you got women together they'll go to extremes to do something</u>
<u n="634" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0092">men will think oh no I don't  I don't  that's a good idea <pause dur="short"/> we should stop there and if you've worked for a boss that's totally determined they're scary some of them that eh <pause dur="short"/> and the way they bully each other as well <pause dur="short"/> when women bully women it's a lot worse than men bullying men <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean I saw it when I <unclear/> with girls just over the interview and some woman was ranting down some other woman's earhole and the woman getting bullied was this head of department <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking Jesus Christ what kind of people are they?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="637" who="S0092">you know so em I worked there for a while <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's an eye opener</u>
<u n="638" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="639" who="S0092">but em mind you I've worked in all bloke environments <pause dur="short"/> that's not nice either but for a different reason</u>
<u n="640" who="S0018">A bit smellier <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0092">well I it's I don't know I mean my I'll tell you something really weird at <anon type="place"/> this is really weird <pause dur="short"/> most schools I've been at you get in the gents there's about three cubicles and then a load of urinals about five or six <pause dur="short"/> and I thought you know you got to <anon type="place"/> which is a girls school right? You go in the blokes urinals there you saw about five thousand urinals it's got the biggest gents toilet I've ever been in and I'm thinking this is a girls school they don't have as many men anyway <pause dur="short"/> it's got the biggest amount of toilets you could have a bloody three classrooms in there <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just couldn't get my head around it I thought what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> You know how things strike you and you just want to know why and I couldn't I still can't for the life of me understand why you know and people say and I said well</u>
<u n="642" who="S0018">it sounds quite <trunc>ty</trunc> typical of the logic that is in operation in a lot of schools <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0092">oh tell me about it <pause dur="short"/> but em there were the reason I like teaching for me personally it's nothing <pause dur="short"/> no matter what system's in operation I still do me own thing</u>
<u n="644" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0092">and eh and if they don't like it they'll try and sort of some of the bully types will make some threats but with me it won't work because I'll just play the game and then if they start getting nasty I'll just I won't it's like what people do they just pretend nothing is there and I mean I've been threatened by her management</u>
<u n="646" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0092"><trunc>To</trunc> the tough guys in management</u>
<u n="648" who="S0018">why what was it that they didn't like that you were doing?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0092">well I was union rep in two schools</u>
<u n="650" who="S0018">oh really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0092">you know <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is once they'd guarantee me is just digging my heels in</u>
<u n="652" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0092">is somebody coming around it's like you know actually I mean I'm not a tough hard guy but if people start doing that I'll I'll I won't act hard to them but I won't back off</u>
<u n="654" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0092">so I know what I was saying  But eh because you can see that now with em well with this government really <pause dur="short"/> things are gonna get nasty soon</u>
<u n="656" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="657" who="S0092">and cos I'm I mean I'm I'm really left wing I am very <pause dur="short"/> people I bell ring with don't there they're all fascists they're all I mean they're all sort of bankers</u>
<u n="658" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0092">they're alright</u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0092">but they're in a nice rich area</u>
<u n="662" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0092">and I never talk politics with them <pause dur="short"/> and I daren't bring my copy of Socialist Worker in <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean I've got it in the house <pause dur="short"/> you know but I mean you know I just want to get on with them I don't start mouthing about things I'm thinking just don't say anything <pause dur="short"/> so I keep me mouth shut</u>
<u n="664" who="S0018">that's a good plan</u>
<u n="665" who="S0092">and I go there the the rotor club they're all there you know</u>
<u n="666" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0092">and they're talking about scroungers and all that or whatever <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is when you think about it it makes sense because it's all this country there's a lot of a little different many worlds</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0092">everywhere</u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">exactly</u>
<u n="671" who="S0092">I mean I go to  there's you don't see any ethnic minorities there</u>
<u n="672" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0092">you see big houses and they're nice people I mix with because that's the environment they live in</u>
<u n="674" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="675" who="S0092">but people might say well this that they might be but you know <pause dur="short"/> I still want to ring bells in churches and if I  if I  start upsetting people I won't be able to do that</u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="677" who="S0092">so I've got to play a game as well I play let's pretend just like everybody else <pause dur="short"/> but certain things like the health bill I might go on a march on that if I have to cos I went on the  abortion bill in London that's where I was marching at Hyde Park then <pause dur="short"/> I hope the police didn't have me on film anywhere</u>
<u n="678" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0092">but em my brother is a <trunc>rav</trunc> raving <pause dur="short"/> all my family are Tories</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0092">yeah me brother ex-policeman what do you expect?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0092">eh my dad was a Tory <pause dur="short"/> they're the worst a working class Tory</u>
<u n="684" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0092">because the they're <unclear/> You know it's like voting for the person who is going to be beating you up</u>
<u n="686" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0092">but you can't tell him <vocal desc="laugh"/> All my dad's side of the family they're all Tory all of them and yet <pause dur="short"/> who is going to suffer with all these cuts it's going to be the working class</u>
<u n="688" who="S0018">yeah and they're all it all it is all they are already <pause dur="short"/> I mean the amount of</u>
<u n="689" who="S0092">they are already and <trunc>Sp</trunc> I mean you talk about unemployment here <pause dur="short"/> look at Spain fifty percent youth unemployment</u>
<u n="690" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0092">fifty percent</u>
<u n="692" who="S0018">and it's quite interesting actually to see cos see normally in Spain people don't really challenge the establishment that much but the young generation nowadays they're really organising themselves</u>
<u n="693" who="S0092">you know why don't you?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0092">Cos Franco did so much</u>
<u n="696" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="697" who="S0092">psychological damage to everybody</u>
<u n="698" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0092">I mean even when he took power he's still killing people years and years and years afterwards with his cohorts <pause dur="short"/> anybody that was on the side if they find out they just arranged something</u>
<u n="700" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0092">I've heard stories of people hiding in buildings for ten fifteen years</u>
<u n="702" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0092">you know and I mean something kicked up the other way we had some French lawyer who got in trouble over something <pause dur="short"/> and I mean what they did there was awful <pause dur="short"/> I mean the only reason Franco <trunc>actu</trunc> he was going to be beaten but apparently Hitler eh</u>
<u n="704" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="705" who="S0092">went to North Africa where all the Spanish colonies were and brought all the Spanish soldiers that were in the colonies back to the mainland Spain and when <trunc>Fran</trunc> to reinforce Franco's army</u>
<u n="706" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0092">and it was that that swung it otherwise and it was just the army he had at the time</u>
<u n="708" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0092">they'd have been overwhelmed but they got the actual forces back from North Africa</u>
<u n="710" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0092">and that swung it and then <pause dur="short"/> then and then you have all this eh all this genocide really</u>
<u n="712" who="S0018">completely and the people still don't like talking about it</u>
<u n="713" who="S0092">well they don't cos some of them are <trunc>com</trunc></u>
<u n="714" who="S0018">it's like thirty thirty years later and it's still they just don't talk about it</u>
<u n="715" who="S0092">because they were <trunc>com</trunc> yeah cos some of these people are murderers they were complicit in it</u>
<u n="716" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0092">well it's like a lot of things just like all this abuse in the Catholic church and stuff</u>
<u n="718" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="719" who="S0092">people are still getting you know</u>
<u n="720" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> have you heard about the judge <trunc>Gar</trunc> Garzon? Em</u>
<u n="721" who="S0092">the one in Spain who's?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he was trying to</u>
<u n="723" who="S0092">that's the one I was on about</u>
<u n="724" who="S0018">oh right yeah cos he's trying to bring to justice a lot of the the war crimes they not even war crimes they were just crimes against humanity <pause dur="short"/> he was the one that tried to bring Pinochet to justice</u>
<u n="725" who="S0092">I know <pause dur="short"/> I've read about that</u>
<u n="726" who="S0018">and Maggie Thatcher helped helped him escape</u>
<u n="727" who="S0092">well I mean you know <pause dur="short"/> when you think about a lot of  a lot of  the problems now Thatcher eh you know this like the big banking crisis?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0092">banks weren't allowed to do what they did and then Thatcher and Regan</u>
<u n="730" who="S0018">they deregulated everything</u>
<u n="731" who="S0092">and then eh Clinton didn't help signing some bill a as well but everything kicked off like <pause dur="short"/> we've got problems with housing now who decided to sell council houses? Thatcher</u>
<u n="732" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0092">because everybody should have a right to buy but the thing is council houses were built for people who couldn't afford</u>
<u n="734" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0092">housing</u>
<u n="736" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0092">and eh it's obvious the when you look at the the different amounts of money people earn some people like <pause dur="short"/> and in Germany most people don't own their property</u>
<u n="738" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0092">and look at their economy they haven't got a problem with it</u>
<u n="740" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="741" who="S0092">I mean I didn't buy that house next door till when I was twenty-<trunc>sev</trunc> and it's only cos I thought I was going to settle down <pause dur="short"/> so I ended up buying a house a good job I did think I was going to settle down otherwise I probably would never have bought a house but it didn't work out so I ended up but the thing is <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad I bought it <pause dur="short"/> I bought that house next door in nineteen eighty-one</u>
<u n="742" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="743" who="S0092">guess how much I paid for it?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0018">eh in nineteen eighty-one gosh thirty thousand? Forty thousand? More or less?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0092">fourteen</u>
<u n="746" who="S0018">fourteen thousand? Blimey <pause dur="short"/> and was that like a year's salary two year's salary back then?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0092">eh I've got me payslips from when I em when I started teaching <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember how much I earned though I didn't earn a lot but it was a hell of a lot of money then</u>
<u n="748" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="749" who="S0092">A hell of a lot of money and eh <pause dur="short"/> I thought no I thought it was too much cos it had gone up a lot in a short period of time anyway</u>
<u n="750" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="751" who="S0092">but I didn't buy it to make money cos I've lived I I mean people say oh how much is this? But I didn't buy it to make money</u>
<u n="752" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="753" who="S0092">Cos I haven't sold it <pause dur="short"/> I don't need <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to sell it and if I I have any intention to sell it I have to do so much work on it <pause dur="short"/> I mean because I've lived there and I just let I haven't needed to I've had things done but I'm not a DIY expert I get people in like I had the roof done when the next door on the other side had theirs done <pause dur="short"/> I had double glazing done when my brother's mate he said double glazing I'll do it <pause dur="short"/> I had the floorboards done when I had a problem with them I had to get all that sorted <pause dur="short"/> I had a new wall outside when some bloke came round had a chimney <pause dur="short"/> when these things happen <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is there's only so much you can do</u>
<u n="754" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="755" who="S0092">and then you think why keep it up to date immaculately? It's like you know <trunc>go</trunc> every day going to the bars or having your hair cut you know why? What for? You're not going on a date every day <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know what I mean? So and also but it's not sensible because at the end of the day you want to feel comfortable in your house</u>
<u n="756" who="S0018">yeah exactly it needs to be your home your castle</u>
<u n="757" who="S0092">you know it's just when someone else sees what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> But so you know depends what people are <trunc>cu</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I don't see things other people do</u>
<u n="758" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="759" who="S0092">which is good really <pause dur="short"/> but em no <pause dur="short"/> and then each to their own <pause dur="short"/> everybody's got their own way of doing or coping with things</u>
<u n="760" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know I think your <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't think that nowadays a teacher on a teacher's salary you can buy a house can you?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0092">I don't know I mean I was never promoted <pause dur="short"/> I well I was but I didn't  I didn't  I mean I didn't creep around people for promotion <pause dur="short"/> I just was happy with what I got and I just budgeted within that</u>
<u n="762" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="763" who="S0092">and I mean I didn't learn to drive till I was thirty</u>
<u n="764" who="S0018">I'm learning how to drive right now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0092">and eh I still got me bus I go to town I don't drive there</u>
<u n="766" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0092">I pay fifty-five quid a month and I can drive on any not I can <trunc>s</trunc> get on a bus anywhere in the West Midlands so that's</u>
<u n="768" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="769" who="S0092">so but I don't like <pause dur="short"/> I mean driving into town you got to park and you got to worry about being late and you've got all the traffic</u>
<u n="770" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="771" who="S0092">and I don't like that <pause dur="short"/> I don't like hassle like that <pause dur="short"/> I hate hustle no matter what it is</u>
<u n="772" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="773" who="S0092">I just like a nice easy I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said what do I want out of life? I want peace and quiet <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0018">I agree with you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0092">peace and quiet that's all I want <pause dur="short"/> I don't and people don't understand this <pause dur="short"/> they say don't you want anything else? Well other things come anyway</u>
<u n="776" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0092">if you're not looking for things they'll come along anyway</u>
<u n="778" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0092">because they do</u>
<u n="780" who="S0018">Strange that you <trunc>c</trunc> chose to be a teacher then if your life <trunc>ga</trunc> goal was to</u>
<u n="781" who="S0092">well I know I'll tell you how it started <pause dur="short"/> eh I taught at Stockland Green for a year and at the end of the year the guy said eh we think you should em go to <trunc>ri</trunc> go do research <pause dur="short"/> I went at Nottingham got me and then I eh <pause dur="short"/> the first job that they offered me I went around the country I ended up in Thetford in Norfolk</u>
<u n="782" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="783" who="S0092">A nice little country village <pause dur="short"/> I got the interview in the summer and I said oh lovely and what I didn't realise a lot of the houses there were it was a London overspill</u>
<u n="784" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="785" who="S0092">so I had all these psychos <vocal desc="laugh"/> So I taught there for two years and then I came back to Birmingham stayed at my mum's and I got a job at and this is really funny <pause dur="short"/> cos I was a big football fan Birmingham City fan <pause dur="short"/> I was at my mum's had my blue scarf on and went to Preston <pause dur="short"/> I'd written to the eh Birmingham educational authority a few weeks before <pause dur="short"/> I hadn't come back from Norfolk then and I was only about another three weeks <pause dur="short"/> and eh this phone rang and it was Don Persie from Turs Green Boys he said em you eh <pause dur="short"/> the authorities said you're eh you're looking for a job? This is out of the blue on a Saturday morning and I said well I'm going to a football game now in an hour <pause dur="short"/> he said can I come along and eh pick you up and take you to the eh school and have a quick look around? So I had me blue scarf on <vocal desc="laugh"/> He he picked me up took me to the school and I said I'm going down the <pause dur="short"/> he said well you've got the job <pause dur="short"/> I didn't I said yeah?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0092">yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0018">oh blimey cos nowadays you have spend a whole day in the school and they grill you you have to do a</u>
<u n="789" who="S0092">it depends on what they want though because</u>
<u n="790" who="S0018">an observed lesson and</u>
<u n="791" who="S0092">but I never had any trouble with the kids because basically I was <trunc>com</trunc> I was a bit of a pyscho as well <vocal desc="laugh"/> But not in a  not in a  a terrible way</u>
<u n="792" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="793" who="S0092">but I wouldn't take any crap <pause dur="short"/> and eh not I mean you know there was a big like kid a <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> he used to play for Birmingham a big West Indian kid he played for them in the final of the em the Johnson's Plate Trophy at Wembley <pause dur="short"/> massive I he was in my class and I I whacked him a few times <pause dur="short"/> he played I said right well I probably said bend over and wham <pause dur="short"/> you could say it was illegal did it you know? And eh don't hit me don't hit me don't hit me <pause dur="short"/> but I wasn't like somebody going around beating people up <pause dur="short"/> eh and one teacher said that's illegal and I said alright grass me up <pause dur="short"/> so em</u>
<u n="794" who="S0018">you wouldn't be able to get away with that nowadays would you? The kids have got so many</u>
<u n="795" who="S0092">well I sorted one kid out when I was at <anon type="place"/> and he said you can't do that that's legal <pause dur="short"/> I said grass me up <pause dur="short"/> cos I these are tough kids and so I said grass me up <pause dur="short"/> they liked me cos I was fair with them</u>
<u n="796" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="797" who="S0092">and I had a laugh and I didn't grass them up or anything and I <pause dur="short"/> I said go go and grass me up to the head and they said no <pause dur="short"/> and then I covered one of their lesson with their mates <unclear/> and I went in the room and this big kid says don't mess with him <vocal desc="laugh"/> He'll knock you out <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="798" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The fear</u>
<u n="799" who="S0092">and he  And he  stayed over a pub in Aston and he went alright sir we think you're really alright <pause dur="short"/> that's all they said and I got it and they were really badly behaved with other people</u>
<u n="800" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="801" who="S0092">and I sat down and then they will have a chat with me <pause dur="short"/> they said eh you're a bit over the top there <pause dur="short"/> I said I didn't I said that it just happened and I'm sorry I said I'm just a bit eh I said I'm sorry sir it's alright I understand <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking and I agree with you I mean he wasn't I mean I would probably get sacked now</u>
<u n="802" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="803" who="S0092">I but I don't know I think it depends with what kids you deal with</u>
<u n="804" who="S0018">yeah true</u>
<u n="805" who="S0092">but the thing is I've em kids are more violent now not less violent</u>
<u n="806" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="807" who="S0092">when there's no discipline</u>
<u n="808" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="809" who="S0092">there's more and I'm not just saying weapon I'm saying beating up gangs and everything</u>
<u n="810" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0092">and kids respect knowing where they stand <pause dur="short"/> I never used to go around em <pause dur="short"/> you only have to do it once and what I used to do is you do one thing once and if you're in school for ten fifteen twenty years that incident will be passed on through mates and stuff and whatever</u>
<u n="812" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="813" who="S0092">and eh they'll <trunc>mak</trunc> and they'll sort of ornate it and make it bigger and <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know Chinese whispers thing?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0092">the kids will do that with a story where you push somebody you know as if threw them out a window or whatever so you don't have to do anything <vocal desc="laugh"/> And eh if it's and also it's not what you do it's the way you do it</u>
<u n="816" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="817" who="S0092">it's like when you talk to somebody some kids will react to <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've got I've sworn at kids I've called my kid a a wanker in front of the whole class and he's never grassed me up <pause dur="short"/> other teachers say something like you're a slime a git or something like that <pause dur="short"/> they'll go and complain</u>
<u n="818" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="819" who="S0092">because it's the way  the way  you say it and who you are</u>
<u n="820" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0092">and you can't I mean you know but then also at the end of the day if I do things wrong then I'll say I'll face the music <pause dur="short"/> if you're prepared to face the music</u>
<u n="822" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="823" who="S0092">but if you're a valuable asset to the school and you don't have trouble or anything and you don't <pause dur="short"/> they're going to think twice before they try and get rid of you</u>
<u n="824" who="S0018">yeah yeah they're gonna want to keep you</u>
<u n="825" who="S0092">you know</u>
<u n="826" who="S0018">especially nowadays with the</u>
<u n="827" who="S0092">the only time when I was away was the last year I was away a bit <pause dur="short"/> because I was hardly ever away</u>
<u n="828" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0092">I was never away and I did my first year of over <pause dur="short"/> and when I covered that in that class classes rioting <pause dur="short"/> like sometimes you get a supply in</u>
<u n="830" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0092">you know <pause dur="short"/> I remember once I was at <unclear/> god I must have had a good reputation then but I some of these classes there were shit scared of me <pause dur="short"/> and they used to come in and behave and one day I had a  I had a  cover for music and this woman was really played up alot <pause dur="short"/> she was neurotic and she was do you know what I mean? And I thought oh I went  I went  to her room before the bell rang and I hid behind the door <vocal desc="laugh"/> and they all came in this is the class I have dead quiet <pause dur="short"/> and they were screaming and yelling and the and then the door's closed and I was standing there and I had a smiled <vocal desc="laugh"/> And all of a sudden suddenly they all went quiet and they all sat down and I said hello</u>
<u n="832" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="833" who="S0092">and I did it all like it was a little play and it was lovely <vocal desc="laugh"/> And it was I was like an actor in a play and I used to love all of this thinking you couldn't do this better if you tried <pause dur="short"/> and I said eh is this a drama lesson? I said I was just taking the piss out of them all the time <pause dur="short"/> and in a way I've always used that because if you do it like that it's even more effective</u>
<u n="834" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="835" who="S0092">because they do that with each other</u>
<u n="836" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="837" who="S0092">so you're just doing what they do so they know exactly what they sort of <unclear/> And also their put-downs and you know <pause dur="short"/> and they don't want you to think they're naughty and so they suddenly you know <pause dur="short"/> especially if it's a nice quiet little girl who's always well behaved and she thinks you've sussed out she's not <pause dur="short"/> they don't like that <pause dur="short"/> so eh</u>
<u n="838" who="S0018">it's like</u>
<u n="839" who="S0092">so you've got to be careful you don't</u>
<u n="840" who="S0018">but it surprised me the amount of kids that just don't care <pause dur="short"/> that they'll just push the boundaries and push the boundaries and they've just got no <pause dur="short"/> I think maybe cos at home they don't have any boundaries or anything</u>
<u n="841" who="S0092">well the thing is like in a way <pause dur="short"/> they're the kids that are losing and not the teachers because it</u>
<u n="842" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="843" who="S0092">in their whole life if that's gonna be what their life's like that means they're never going to have a situation they're going to have a situation in respect or intimacy</u>
<u n="844" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0092">or being able to relate to people in a sensible</u>
</body>
</text>
