<text id="S6YA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:37:16</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-05-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013 S0152</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>trip to London, horses, school, Youth hostel in Cornwall, selling houses, cars, TV, travelling, buying houses, election, eBay, football, health, money</topics>
		<activity>Talking about allsorts</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, buying/selling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0152">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Birmingham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>w_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="2" who="S0152">so yeah so I met them back and I said thanks for doing the <pause dur="short"/> you know and I was a bit concerned about well I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and er what are they wanting to do? are they gonna be happy</u>
<u n="3" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0152">doing it? they so I said do you fancy doing a little bit of sightseeing? and they went <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay alright so I took them up to the BBC <pause dur="short"/> the Broadcasting House</u>
<u n="5" who="S0012" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0152">cos that's the top of Regent Street</u>
<u n="7" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="9" who="S0152">and then we walked back down Regent Street <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I was winding <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up I was said oh we'll go to the statue of love shall we?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0152">what do you mean the statue of love? I says Eros</u>
<u n="13" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0152">where is that? I said that's Piccadilly Circus</u>
<u n="15" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so walked to Piccadilly Circus and <pause dur="short"/> took she took some pictures and I'd taken some pictures prior to that cos I when I'd walked that way earlier the Horse Guards Parade there was a guard on a horse</u>
<u n="17" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0152">and everything</u>
<u n="19" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0152">in a box but that that kind of so so this is Piccadilly Circus explain <pause dur="short"/> what it was then we walked down to The Mall and I said look if you look that way</u>
<u n="21" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0152">you or I there was this column and I said do you know who that is? and it was like yeah that's Nelson's Column I went no <pause dur="short"/> no I said cos we're not in Trafalgar Square at the moment</u>
<u n="23" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="24" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no that's not is it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0152">and I said that's Duke of York that is I said if you look down there there's Buckingham Palace Buckingham Palace yeah and then Regent's Park and whatever</u>
<u n="26" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0152">I said and we'll walk across here and we walked across to Horse Guards Parade and they could see the London Eye in the background and everything</u>
<u n="29" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0152">and so they were fascinated by walking across Horse Guards Parade underneath the arch and they saw the two soldiers in uniform</u>
<u n="31" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0152">and it was like is that real? and the the police were there with guns and everything</u>
<u n="33" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah they yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0152" trans="overlap">the police erm like you know they've got guns I went yeah yeah they've got guns type of thing</u>
<u n="35" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0013">did they have their photo taken next to the</u>
<u n="37" who="S0152" trans="overlap">they had they did have their <trunc>pho</trunc> pictures taken next to the</u>
<u n="38" who="S0013" trans="overlap">what do they charge now? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0152">no they don't charge no</u>
<u n="40" who="S0013">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0152" trans="overlap">they still don't so then we I said then what's this? and we walked I says what's this down here? don't know don't know that's the Cenotaph there the Cenotaph? I explained it and I said look you've you've seen it on telly you've watched</u>
<u n="42" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0152">the poppy procession this is where it happens</u>
<u n="44" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0152">I said and this is where the queen comes out and all the it's and the I said and then we'll just walk down a little bit and look what's down there that's number that's where the prime minister lives and all the other bits</u>
<u n="46" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0152">I said yeah yeah so er so that was quite</u>
<u n="48" who="S0012" trans="overlap">is that still gated though?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0152">it's all gated yeah oh heavily gated</u>
<u n="50" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0152">heavily gated</u>
<u n="52" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it's really really really thick steel gates and</u>
<u n="54" who="S0152" trans="overlap">oh it's <trunc>stee</trunc> and there's a ramp in the road that comes up</u>
<u n="55" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0152">and we every before we got to Horse Guards Parade it was <trunc>k</trunc> open <pause dur="short"/> and then as we were walking towards it all these bars <vocal desc="laugh"/> came up out the ground like this</u>
<u n="58" who="S0013">oh really?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0152">it was it was though you could still walk across it but</u>
<u n="61" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="62" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it's just on the edge of the road type of thing</u>
<u n="63" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0152">wow we're gonna so that was like I said now <pause dur="short"/> I said and if we walk further down so we walked further down and we <pause dur="short"/> and we Big Ben and I said yeah that's Big Ben I said but it's not actually the Big Ben I said that's Elizabeth Tower I said it's Big Ben that the <trunc>chi</trunc></u>
<u n="65" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that chimes the bell</u>
<u n="66" who="S0152">the bell</u>
<u n="67" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0152">has oh so they stood there and had the pictures taken type of thing</u>
<u n="69" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="70" who="S0152">then we walked across the bridge just there <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="71" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0152">I said er we'll walk along <trunc>th</trunc> the Embankment there past the old council offices which is now an aquarium and past the the Eye and we watched a bit of street art that was</u>
<u n="73" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0152" trans="overlap">going on I said and then if we walk across the bridge here I says we'll <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>wa</trunc> we'll walk up Northumberland Street I said and we'll get to Trafalgar Square</u>
<u n="75" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="76" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so it was <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="78" who="S0012">oh they enjoyed it then</u>
<u n="79" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> so we did that we walked up and it was cos I was going oh I've stayed in a hotel there and oh I've stayed in that hotel over there</u>
<u n="80" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0013">oh dear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0152">and walked walked across <pause dur="short"/> stayed in Trafalgar Square for a little bit of time <pause dur="short"/> I said now and it was getting around about five o'clock now I think like it was getting towards five o'clock or half five and I said do you fancy something to eat? you know I know I knew <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would need to have something to eat</u>
<u n="83" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0152">and my concern was the other two</u>
<u n="85" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0152">so I said well do you <trunc>fa</trunc> I said do you fancy like Pizza Hut or something like that? knowing well you know it's relatively cheap in Pizza Hut</u>
<u n="87" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0152">we'll go in there and er <pause dur="short"/> they went yeah okay so we didn't we didn't go to <trunc>Pizz</trunc> we went we went to a an Italian place</u>
<u n="90" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0152">and they had pizzas and everything</u>
<u n="92" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0152">so that wasn't that was alright and I had a couple of beers while I was in there</u>
<u n="94" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0152">I thought well I'll I I've walked all this way and I'm gonna have</u>
<u n="98" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0152" trans="overlap">something to eat</u>
<u n="100" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and I'm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0152">and it was the first drink I'd had since my breakfast I think no I'd had a coffee <pause dur="short"/> so I had that and then <pause dur="short"/> I said if I said I know what we can do now I said if we walk back to Oxford Street I said you can go in any shops that you might wanna that you haven't been in I said then what we'll do is we'll catch the train back to St Paul's</u>
<u n="104" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0152">I said and we'll get off at St Paul's and we'll go and look at St Paul's Cathedral and we'll walk down to the Millennium Bridge <pause dur="short"/> and then we'll walk across the Millennium Bridge</u>
<u n="107" who="S0012">yeah we did that one didn't we? the Menali Millennium Bridge</u>
<u n="108" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0012">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0013">no we didn't walk across it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0012">we didn't walk across it but we went on it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0152">yeah er so where the Tate Modern is so you could on the Millennium Bridge you could see Tower Bridge</u>
<u n="113" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0152">and you could see you could see the Eye on the</u>
<u n="115" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0152">on the bend at St Paul's and then you could see <pause dur="short"/> the Shard and everything so</u>
<u n="117" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it was all</u>
<u n="119" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0152">that was that was quite that was quite nice so we did that but we <vocal desc="laugh"/> had a problem getting out of St Paul's in the sense that we used our Underground tickets when I purchased the Underground tickets I said I want a you know I want a day rover zone one</u>
<u n="121" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0152">for five people <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> and I said and I and I want to come back to Liverpool Street <pause dur="short"/> well I goes to <pause dur="short"/> go through it won't accept my card</u>
<u n="124" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="125" who="S0152">it won't accept it just keeps coming through</u>
<u n="126" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="127" who="S0152">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> put hers in and it kept it</u>
<u n="128" who="S0012">it kept it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> put hers in and it kept it</u>
<u n="130" who="S0012">oh what?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0152">and I thought oh so I went to the guard I said look I said <pause dur="short"/> trying to get out I said it's kept two tickets cos I've got three tickets here cos I've not put them in I said I <pause dur="short"/> I bought an all we bought I bought tickets for all day so that I could use the Underground</u>
<u n="133" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0152">all day and he looked and he went <pause dur="short"/> it's a return ticket to Liverpool Street <pause dur="short"/> and I went yeah but I asked I had and when I paid for it I asked for a and he went don't worry about it he said I'll let you through he says and he said are you coming back this way? and I went yeah he says if I'm on come and see me and I'll let you through <pause dur="short"/> if not I'll go and tell my colleague over there and he went and told him and he pointed to us</u>
<u n="135" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0152">about it he said and I'll let you through</u>
<u n="137" who="S0012">oh that was nice of him</u>
<u n="138" who="S0152">so I thought well I er and he was nice you know I thought okay and</u>
<u n="139" who="S0012">and you could have</u>
<u n="140" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0012">and you could have had</u>
<u n="142" who="S0013" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> what</u>
<u n="143" who="S0152" trans="overlap">well he <unclear>could have sure</unclear></u>
<u n="144" who="S0013" trans="overlap">why did they take</u>
<u n="145" who="S0013">because it was a one way <trunc>ti</trunc> it was a return ticket</u>
<u n="146" who="S0012">to Liverpool <trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="147" who="S0152" trans="overlap">to Liverpool Street <pause dur="short"/> to from Oxford</u>
<u n="148" who="S0013" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="149" who="S0152" trans="overlap">to Oxford Circus to Liverpool Street</u>
<u n="150" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0152">that's all it was supposed to be</u>
<u n="152" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="153" who="S0152">it wasn't a <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="154" who="S0013">it wasn't a rover?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0012" trans="overlap">and you couldn't</u>
<u n="156" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it wasn't a rover</u>
<u n="157" who="S0012" trans="overlap">get on in the middle</u>
<u n="158" who="S0152">you couldn't get on in the middle now we were fortunate</u>
<u n="159" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="160" who="S0152">cos we walked through barriers on a couple of the others</u>
<u n="161" who="S0013">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0152">where the barriers were open</u>
<u n="164" who="S0013" trans="overlap">cos you could have gone</u>
<u n="165" who="S0152">could have <trunc>lo</trunc></u>
<u n="166" who="S0013" trans="overlap">could</u>
<u n="167" who="S0152">lost it earlier you see</u>
<u n="168" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0152">so when we came so we did that and walked across and we got back to the bridge we got back to St Paul's <pause dur="short"/> saw the guy and he went yeah no problem he said you'll have no problem at Liverpool Street cos there was no barriers at Liverpool Street at the moment</u>
<u n="171" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0152">cos they're something's they were doing something and I went okay <pause dur="short"/> and er <vocal desc="laugh"/> we gets on the <trunc>trai</trunc> we gets on the tube gets <pause dur="short"/> gets to Liverpool Street there's barriers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0152">the one we wanted so I was back to the guard and the guard said yeah you can just <unclear/> and we can see you <trunc>ye</trunc> I've got my ticket which says</u>
<u n="175" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0152">you know? so he said yeah no problem and let us through</u>
<u n="177" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="178" who="S0152">and we were back at our train wasn't until half past nine <pause dur="short"/> and we want and we <pause dur="short"/> erm there's nowhere to sit at Liverpool Street <pause dur="short"/> there's no seats or anything</u>
<u n="179" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="180" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="181" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="182" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0152">erm so we we went in Costa Coffee <pause dur="short"/> which just which is just at the top it was it was empty so we had a drink in there</u>
<u n="184" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0152">and sat there until ten past nine</u>
<u n="186" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0152">erm came out looked on the board the platform wasn't up which train <pause dur="short"/> back to <anon type="place"/> but then at twenty-five past <pause dur="short"/> the platform and we were on the train and we were off at half nine</u>
<u n="188" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="189" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0152">and we <pause dur="short"/> there was five of us so <pause dur="short"/> so going <pause dur="short"/> we had a <pause dur="short"/> a table of <trunc>thr</trunc> a table of four but only three of us sat there</u>
<u n="192" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0152">and two sat by themselves <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sat together</u>
<u n="194" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I sat together</u>
<u n="196" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="197" who="S0152" trans="overlap">coming back we sat in rows so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sat together <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <unclear>thingy</unclear> sat together and</u>
<u n="198" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I sat</u>
<u n="200" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0152" trans="overlap">by myself</u>
<u n="203" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0152">mm and that was alright we got back here at got back here at <pause dur="short"/> half eleven? got in the car drove to <anon type="place"/> took <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> home took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> home first then took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> home and then got</u>
<u n="205" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="206" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0152">so it was a</u>
<u n="208" who="S0013">sound a</u>
<u n="209" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it was a busy day</u>
<u n="210" who="S0013" trans="overlap">a brilliant day</u>
<u n="211" who="S0152">it was a it was a <trunc>g</trunc> it was a good day yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it was it was good in in lots of ways it was good in lots of ways</u>
<u n="214" who="S0013">you must have done loads of things it's lovely</u>
<u n="215" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0012">you didn't go to Tate Modern then?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="219" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="220" who="S0152">I I've already I did that <pause dur="short"/> a couple of years ago but it it was too late er you know</u>
<u n="221" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it was like seven o'clock</u>
<u n="223" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0152">type of thing</u>
<u n="225" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and the restaurant we went in was alright except for <pause dur="short"/> er <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> the bill was eighty pound</u>
<u n="227" who="S0012">was it? yeah?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0012" trans="overlap">what in the restaurant?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="232" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that was for five of you?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0012">fifteen pound each</u>
<u n="237" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I've forgotten the</u>
<u n="238" who="S0012" trans="overlap">or thereabouts innit? for five</u>
<u n="239" who="S0152">yeah well the problem the problem was <pause dur="long"/> they paid they paid for their pizzas</u>
<u n="240" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0152">erm <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had tap water <pause dur="short"/> so you don't pay for tap water</u>
<u n="242" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0152">erm <pause dur="short"/> mm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had tap water <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a lemonade <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had lemonade and I <trunc>ha</trunc> I had well originally I asked for just a beer</u>
<u n="244" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0152">and and some bread <pause dur="short"/> and I did ask for two lots of bread <pause dur="short"/> because there was five of us</u>
<u n="246" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0152" trans="overlap">just because it's a bit of a starter type of thing and they only brought one lot</u>
<u n="248" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="249" who="S0152">so then I went can I have another one please? and he bought me another beer</u>
<u n="250" who="S0012">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0152">alright so</u>
<u n="253" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0152">and it was already open and I thought oh I'm gonna have some more I'll <trunc>dri</trunc> not a problem I'll drink it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0152">I know and I'll have another beer <pause dur="short"/> and then when the bill came that was that was fine <pause dur="short"/> that was alright but they'd put twelve pound on <pause dur="short"/> for the tip</u>
<u n="257" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0012" trans="overlap">what service charge they call it now don't they yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0013">extra twelve pound?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="263" who="S0012">don't they trust you to give a tip?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0152">so I and you you can say no but it was already calculated on the bill and the bill comes and oh</u>
<u n="265" who="S0013">well it's in most places they include it in in the meal don't they? the service charge in</u>
<u n="266" who="S0152">no it's</u>
<u n="267" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><trunc>usua</trunc> usually it will say <pause dur="short"/> it it will either say</u>
<u n="269" who="S0012" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="270" who="S0152">service charge included</u>
<u n="271" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="272" who="S0152" trans="overlap">or gratitude at your discretion or something</u>
<u n="273" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0152" trans="overlap">like that but you know for five people a pound per person is fine but not two pound per person</u>
<u n="275" who="S0012">no that was a bit</u>
<u n="276" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0012" trans="overlap">too much innit?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0152">you know erm so</u>
<u n="279" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0152" trans="overlap">that was <pause dur="short"/> well apart from that and of course</u>
<u n="281" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0152">you can't say to I can't say to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I can't say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well I need an extra</u>
<u n="283" who="S0013">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="285" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="286" who="S0012">so it should be around about ten percent I thought</u>
<u n="287" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0012" trans="overlap">service charge innit?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0012">it should be</u>
<u n="291" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it was twelve twelve and a half</u>
<u n="292" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0012">yeah that's quite a bit innit?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so quite a bit</u>
<u n="295" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0152">but it it didn't spoil the day so</u>
<u n="298" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="299" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0013" trans="overlap">you sound like you had a brilliant day</u>
<u n="301" who="S0152">so we</u>
<u n="302" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so that was so that was it we had you know we had a really nice day we had <pause dur="short"/> erm the weather was good it wasn't like Friday where it was all smoggy and everything</u>
<u n="304" who="S0012">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0152">erm and it all and it all fell into place so I can't you know can't grumble with</u>
<u n="306" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0152">can't grumble with the day</u>
<u n="308" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="309" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0152">it's just that it was that couple of hours that like three hours where I was walking by yourself</u>
<u n="311" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you could have done with someone</u>
<u n="314" who="S0013" trans="overlap">whereas they'd have been quite happy to be with you really wouldn't they all the time wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0152">I think if</u>
<u n="316" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no they wouldn't</u>
<u n="317" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I think if they'd I think if I'd have walked with them to the shops somewhere well they'd have been happy but</u>
<u n="318" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0152">I didn't wanna go out shopping because</u>
<u n="320" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I just couldn't they'd got they'd got money and bits and pieces</u>
<u n="322" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they have fun when I mean</u>
<u n="326" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0152">it's that it's that learning experience isn't it?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0012">it is course it is</u>
<u n="329" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it's that growing up thing</u>
<u n="330" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0152">you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s what? only done it <pause dur="short"/> how many times have I taken <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to London? it's only been once</u>
<u n="332" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0152">I think she's only been once</u>
<u n="334" who="S0012">when ours were were little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said they could go on holiday down there didn't they?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0013">yeah yeah we just put them on a train <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we put them on the train</u>
<u n="337" who="S0013">we saw them off</u>
<u n="338" who="S0012">and we</u>
<u n="339" who="S0013" trans="overlap">and the guard</u>
<u n="340" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I mean they weren't very old</u>
<u n="341" who="S0013">kept</u>
<u n="342" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="343" who="S0013">looking</u>
<u n="344" who="S0012">and the guard looked after them</u>
<u n="345" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0012">on the train they don't have guards any more</u>
<u n="347" who="S0013" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was quite old</u>
<u n="348" who="S0152">yeah they yeah they still have</u>
<u n="349" who="S0012" trans="overlap">do they?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0152" trans="overlap">guards yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was about ten weren't she? twelve?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0013">she must have been yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you <trunc>ha</trunc> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er</u>
<u n="354" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0012">and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> met them the other end <vocal desc="laugh"/> and er</u>
<u n="356" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0012" trans="overlap">they had a wonderful time didn't they down there?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah he did all the sightseeing with them and</u>
<u n="359" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0013">they</u>
<u n="361" who="S0152" trans="overlap">you know there's lots to do down there</u>
<u n="362" who="S0013" trans="overlap">had to keep a diary <vocal desc="laugh"/> of what they'd done</u>
<u n="363" who="S0012">yeah they had to keep the diary</u>
<u n="364" who="S0013" trans="overlap">so we knew exactly where they'd been and <trunc>every</trunc></u>
<u n="365" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> made them keep a diary <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0013">he's like that</u>
<u n="367" who="S0152">we'll do it I mean we'll do it <trunc>ag</trunc> you know I'll</u>
<u n="368" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0152">do it again with them I mean the ticket I mean <pause dur="long"/> for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> return ticket was thirteen pound</u>
<u n="370" who="S0012">yeah well that's nothing is it? all the way to London and back</u>
<u n="371" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0152">you know mine was twenty-three</u>
<u n="373" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0152">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s was twenty-three</u>
<u n="377" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0152" trans="overlap">mine was for twenty-three</u>
<u n="379" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0013">but the girls were thirteen pound well <pause dur="short"/> six pound fifty?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0152">to London and back a coach the coach is more expensive</u>
<u n="385" who="S0012">yeah coaches are</u>
<u n="386" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0012">and if you book it in advance <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="388" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0012">and a coach ain't quite so nice is it?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0152">no no then you you can so that was that was alright <pause dur="short"/> so I mean I'll we'll do it again erm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0152">but it was it was just an it was a nice it was a nice day</u>
<u n="393" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0012">good</u>
<u n="396" who="S0152">it was a nice day and then <pause dur="short"/> and as I say this week has this week really has been a week where <pause dur="short"/> I've taken <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> riding <pause dur="short"/> and I haven't I seen you know considering I haven't seen her</u>
<u n="397" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="398" who="S0152">haven't seen her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> six o'clock <pause dur="short"/> I think Monday was was it Monday? <pause dur="short"/> when did I cook? <pause dur="short"/> you came on Sunday <pause dur="short"/> and Monday I cooked <pause dur="long"/> and <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know what time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was coming back <pause dur="short"/> so I got a text at four o'clock <pause dur="short"/> then I got a text pick her up at five o'clock</u>
<u n="399" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0152">then I got a text to pick me up at six o'clock</u>
<u n="401" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="402" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="403" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0152">which wasn't which wasn't a problem but when I got there <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> called me over cos I thought something had happened in the sense of the horse had given birth</u>
<u n="405" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had given birth but it wasn't she just wanted me to go over <pause dur="short"/> and then she started showing me some bits and pieces <pause dur="short"/> and I <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I just went <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I would like to go really now I've been I've been up she'd been up since six o'clock</u>
<u n="407" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0152" trans="overlap">that morning</u>
<u n="409" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0152" trans="overlap">cos she had to be there at quarter past six</u>
<u n="411" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0152">but</u>
<u n="413" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0152">at half <trunc>si</trunc> no she had to be there at quarter to <trunc>sev</trunc> half six you have to be there cos they we're going down to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and they went to <anon type="place"/> to pick up</u>
<u n="415" who="S0012"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0152">to pick up two horses</u>
<u n="417" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="418" who="S0152">so you know it wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thing but I you know I just wanted</u>
<u n="419" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0152">well so I said come on and cos that she was a bit upset about that</u>
<u n="421" who="S0012">was she? oh okay</u>
<u n="422" who="S0152">a bit upset about it</u>
<u n="423" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0152">well I didn't say anything and then Tuesday she had another good day riding and then I picked her up at six o'clock on Tuesday and that was <pause dur="short"/> wednesday erm got there at half got there at half nine on Wednesday and picked up at five <vocal desc="laugh"/> five o'clock</u>
<u n="425" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="426" who="S0152">erm she didn't ride on Friday <pause dur="short"/> but her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went into <anon type="place"/> on Friday</u>
<u n="427" who="S0012">did they? yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0152">and they came back <pause dur="short"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went round to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s on Friday night <pause dur="short"/> so I haven't seen oh the yeah then I <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says I need to get my school <pause dur="short"/> polo shirts so I</u>
<u n="430" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0152">oh yeah you do so I had to go and buy her six polo shirts</u>
<u n="433" who="S0012">six? <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="434" who="S0152">well there is there is a problem if don't get six cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> won't wash</u>
<u n="435" who="S0012">won't she?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0152">she won't wash them</u>
<u n="437" who="S0012">won't she?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0152">or well she will but they won't be dry for the next day</u>
<u n="439" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="440" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="441" who="S0152">and they smell</u>
<u n="442" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0152">so she needs one a day because I know the way <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does her washing and other bits and pieces</u>
<u n="444" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0152">so I got six in the end and I said right <trunc>wha</trunc> whatever happens <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> two stay here all the time <pause dur="short"/> because when you come on a Wednesday you will come in one</u>
<u n="446" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0152">but you'll have your Thursday and your Friday one</u>
<u n="448" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0152">and then the following week when you when you come on a Thursday you need one for the Friday but you will always have</u>
<u n="450" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0012">something there</u>
<u n="452" who="S0152" trans="overlap">two here</u>
<u n="453" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0152">cos I it just it's the only way to do it with the way it is</u>
<u n="455" who="S0013">yeah I see yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear>it's all good</unclear> innit?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I forget you have to split things up like that mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0152">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me this morning she says did you get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> polo shirts this week? and I went <pause dur="short"/> yeah how much? I said er <trunc>twen</trunc> er fifty-two pound</u>
<u n="459" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0152">I said I got six oh so the <unclear>one is twenty</unclear> she says and I'll give you the other five for <unclear/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh well</u>
<u n="462" who="S0152">so that was alright</u>
<u n="463" who="S0012">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="464" who="S0152">that was alright <pause dur="short"/> so so that was so that was <pause dur="short"/> that was that I went out on Friday and met up with <pause dur="short"/> some people I used to work with I met up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0012">did you? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did you?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0012">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right</u>
<u n="468" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I hadn't seen I hadn't seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I'd seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in September <pause dur="short"/> I hadn't seen him at Christmas and it was May time <pause dur="short"/> last May when I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0152">so it's like been twelve months <pause dur="short"/> and just a <trunc>ca</trunc> a catch up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was looking well still having</u>
<u n="471" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0152">er still having her <pause dur="short"/> treatment for her cancer or whatever</u>
<u n="473" who="S0012">is she?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="475" who="S0152">so it's in remission but she's on a she's on a special they're trying something new with her so she has to go to <anon type="place"/> every Wednesday for a dose</u>
<u n="476" who="S0012">does she?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0152">of</u>
<u n="478" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="479" who="S0152" trans="overlap">steroids and chemo and</u>
<u n="480" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="481" who="S0152" trans="overlap">as he</u>
<u n="482" who="S0012" trans="overlap">is it breast cancer she's got?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0152">no ovarian cancer</u>
<u n="484" who="S0012" trans="overlap">ovarian cancer?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0152" trans="overlap">erm yeah I think it's not ovarian the other one in that area</u>
<u n="486" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0152">erm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0152">and <pause dur="short"/> she <pause dur="short"/> I mean she looks she looks well I mean she I know she wears a wig or whatever</u>
<u n="490" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0152" trans="overlap">is the other thing but she does look well</u>
<u n="492" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="493" who="S0152">and it's in and the blood count seems to be all okay and</u>
<u n="494" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="496" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so it seems that they they give her the dose on a Wednesday they fill her up with steroids and antihistamine on the <trunc>Th</trunc> for the Thursday so she can't drive back <pause dur="short"/> so she drives there then</u>
<u n="497" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="498" who="S0152">her husband gets a train</u>
<u n="499" who="S0012">I see yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0152" trans="overlap">to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0152">and then he drives back so they do it that way</u>
<u n="503" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="504" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0152">erm <pause dur="short"/> thursday she's really really</u>
<u n="506" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="507" who="S0152">buzzing because it's got all this</u>
<u n="508" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="509" who="S0152" trans="overlap">steroids and antihistamine</u>
<u n="510" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0152">it's er inside her Friday tends to drop off <pause dur="short"/> a little bit at Saturday she's just like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0012">she's knackered</u>
<u n="513" who="S0152">and then she's back to</u>
<u n="514" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="515" who="S0152">really you know and then it's back</u>
<u n="516" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0152">for the</u>
<u n="518" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0152">next couple of <trunc>sess</trunc> which is better than if she'd had the chemo which really did</u>
<u n="520" who="S0012">oh right that take it out of you</u>
<u n="521" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it takes it out of you type of thing erm she was supposed to have an Ofsted inspection two weeks ago but they phoned to go in on the Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> and she said I I'm sorry I would like to defer it because I'm er I'm having this treatment and they went yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="522" who="S0012">yeah? good</u>
<u n="523" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and they <trunc>sai</trunc> and they said yeah we're fine about it they explained</u>
<u n="524" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0152" trans="overlap">the situation so so <trunc>talk</trunc> so so talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I said he said how did the inspection go? and I went we haven't been told I said we've not been told a thing</u>
<u n="527" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="528" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0152">I said you know we haven't you know they were in for the two days I says we were told on the <pause dur="long"/> on the I think it was the Thursday that they wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> they wouldn't be able to give us the they wouldn't give us the results till the thirteenth of April and he look <unclear>he</unclear> says well I know what they are <unclear>he</unclear> said we've been told we they're not gonna give them</u>
<u n="530" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="531" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><unclear>he</unclear> said because they've gotta be externally verified <pause dur="short"/> er for quality assurance and he went <vocal desc="sigh"/> it means two <trunc>thi</trunc> it means two things then don't it? you've got a category you've either got a three or a four and if they're wanting verification on it</u>
<u n="532" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0012">you'll be in special</u>
<u n="534" who="S0152" trans="overlap">could be special measures</u>
<u n="535" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="536" who="S0152">but I don't think I just said I <trunc>d</trunc> but I said I think I I said but <pause dur="short"/> I said <pause dur="short"/> it's more likely to be a three and he went <pause dur="short"/> it shouldn't be a three</u>
<u n="537" who="S0012">did he?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0152">mm that it shouldn't be a three</u>
<u n="539" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="540" who="S0152" trans="overlap">looking at all the data and whatever cos they get to look at the data and stuff</u>
<u n="541" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0152">and if you're an Ofsted inspector you're <pause dur="short"/> you have the password to <vocal desc="cough"/> to get online to see where it is</u>
<u n="543" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0152">online and stuff like that to see</u>
<u n="545" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0152" trans="overlap">data and stuff so we I know for a fact he would have looked at</u>
<u n="547" who="S0012">yeah cos he would the</u>
<u n="548" who="S0152" trans="overlap">the data of</u>
<u n="549" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0152">the school or whatever I said but you know</u>
<u n="551" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0152">so <trunc>w</trunc> Thursday well Tuesday we'll be able to you know see what happens on Tuesday cos that's when supposedly we're gonna be told</u>
<u n="553" who="S0012">what this Tuesday?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="555" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="558" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="559" who="S0152">and then with that and then this is the week where the consultation period finishes job wise so</u>
<u n="560" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0152">we'll know a little bit more on Tuesday</u>
<u n="562" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="563" who="S0152">so it's gonna be a</u>
<u n="564" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0152" trans="overlap">an interesting week</u>
<u n="566" who="S0012">that will be won't it? oh dear</u>
<u n="567" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0152">it's gonna be an interesting week</u>
<u n="569" who="S0012">and we're off to the Lizard Wednesday</u>
<u n="570" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0012">that'll be nice <pause dur="short"/> and they reckon it's gonna be good weather don't they?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0152">do they?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0152">yeah it should be <pause dur="short"/> should be good you're away</u>
<u n="578" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0152" trans="overlap">aren't you so</u>
<u n="580" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0152">it'll be</u>
<u n="582" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well we're going where are we going first to the</u>
<u n="583" who="S0152">er Wye Valley first</u>
<u n="584" who="S0012">Wye Valley first</u>
<u n="585" who="S0152">Herefordshire?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0012">yeah that's</u>
<u n="587" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear>before ours</unclear> and then it's four hours to the Lizard from there</u>
<u n="589" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0012">so we stay overnight at Wye Valley <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> off we go to the Lizard the next day and we've gotta be there by about two haven't we?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0012">cos she has to do a changeover</u>
<u n="595" who="S0013">and they just tell you where the</u>
<u n="596" who="S0012">where the <unclear/> are</u>
<u n="597" who="S0013" trans="overlap">files are and things</u>
<u n="598" who="S0012" trans="overlap">and the files are and how to fill them in and what to do</u>
<u n="599" who="S0013">what the code for the fire alarms</u>
<u n="600" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's like those</u>
<u n="602" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and now they're trying to make us all <pause dur="short"/> volunteers to do make the beds</u>
<u n="603" who="S0152" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0012">which is a ridiculous thing <pause dur="short"/> I mean every youth hostel if you go in you make your own bed</u>
<u n="605" who="S0152">that was all that was always part of it wasn't it?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0152">you sorted all that out and whatever</u>
<u n="609" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0013">must be cos they only stay one night or lots of people do don't they?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0013">that's quite a lot of</u>
<u n="613" who="S0152">that's a lot of bed making</u>
<u n="614" who="S0013">it's a lot</u>
<u n="615" who="S0012">it's a lot of bed making</u>
<u n="616" who="S0013" trans="overlap">we usually have about</u>
<u n="617" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0013">well at least twenty beds to you know to</u>
<u n="619" who="S0012">to change yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that's a lot of your time mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0012">and er the top bunks they're they're the hardest to do</u>
<u n="622" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0012">so we'll see what happens</u>
<u n="625" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well we haven't got to do it in this one</u>
<u n="626" who="S0012">we ain't gotta do it in this one</u>
<u n="627" who="S0013" trans="overlap">next year they're bringing that in</u>
<u n="628" who="S0012">or trying to</u>
<u n="629" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> trying to</u>
<u n="630" who="S0012">I mean most people voted against it <pause dur="short"/> and we didn't get to go to the meeting this year did we?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0012">but er there you go</u>
<u n="633" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="634" who="S0012">we don't wanna do it <pause dur="short"/> make all them beds I mean we don't get done till well sometimes after</u>
<u n="635" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's a lot a lot a lot</u>
<u n="636" who="S0012" trans="overlap">after twelve</u>
<u n="637" who="S0013" trans="overlap">to expect volunteers to do cos there's a lot of <pause dur="short"/> responsibility there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0013">I mean we have to do all the paperwork and everything else</u>
<u n="641" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0013">you know it's not just <pause dur="short"/> it's not just</u>
<u n="643" who="S0012" trans="overlap">take their money</u>
<u n="644" who="S0013" trans="overlap">looking after people you just have</u>
<u n="645" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0013">it's a lot to do</u>
<u n="648" who="S0012">and some of them come look at that squirrel on there <pause dur="short"/> he's run</u>
<u n="649" who="S0013">I've got to go look</u>
<u n="650" who="S0012"><vocal desc="misc"/> <event desc="sound of clapping"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0012">oh you have you've gotta go <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="652" who="S0152">zumbaing</u>
<u n="653" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll probably see you before we go erm er</u>
<u n="654" who="S0152">yeah I hope</u>
<u n="655" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0013">yeah yeah good luck with next week</u>
<u n="659" who="S0152">yeah okay take care</u>
<u n="660" who="S0013">right just gotta get things ready</u>
<u n="661" who="S0152">so yeah so so my leg hurt on Friday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0012">I bet it did</u>
<u n="663" who="S0152">my leg really did hurt on Friday <pause dur="short"/> it was a</u>
<u n="664" who="S0012">well you done a lot of walking didn't you?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I did do a lot of walking</u>
<u n="666" who="S0012">and that's not good walking that's walking on all that</u>
<u n="667" who="S0152">it was</u>
<u n="668" who="S0012" trans="overlap">hard surfaces</u>
<u n="669" who="S0152">it was it was it was pleasant walking because it was all flat</u>
<u n="670" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0152">and I got my trainers on so that <trunc>wou</trunc> made a difference</u>
<u n="672" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0152" trans="overlap">but if I've have got those shoes on that I've got on at the moment oh I'd have been crippled</u>
<u n="674" who="S0012">you would <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0152">although I did take two tablets before I went</u>
<u n="676" who="S0012">did you? yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0152">I took so I did take two tablets</u>
<u n="678" who="S0012">are you gonna have it done or not?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0152">can't have it done yet</u>
<u n="680" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> not until it wear right up I suppose <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0152">I can't <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I just can't you know?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> well you do get leave don't you?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0152"><vocal desc="sigh"/> well the way circumstances are at the moment</u>
<u n="684" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0152">you know it's not a good time to have it done</u>
<u n="686" who="S0012">no it's not is it?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0152">erm <pause dur="short"/> it will have to be done</u>
<u n="688" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0152">and I have thought about going back to the doctors and <pause dur="short"/> saying</u>
<u n="690" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0152">you know look I'd like another X-ray cos I think it is getting</u>
<u n="692" who="S0012">worse</u>
<u n="693" who="S0152">it is getting worse <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0012">they'll start giving you cortisone injections won't they shortly?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0152">somebody I know has just had some I think I mentioned it</u>
<u n="696" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0152">erm <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> they only last six months</u>
<u n="698" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0152" trans="overlap">twelve months</u>
<u n="700" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0152">somebody at work's had them done and it's not made it any it's worse now because</u>
<u n="702" who="S0012">it er yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0152">it you've you've <trunc>u</trunc> you <vocal desc="sigh"/> she says it's worse now because she can't have any more</u>
<u n="704" who="S0012">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> weird innit?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="706" who="S0012">but that's like buying extra time though innit you know?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="708" who="S0012">if er if you get an appointment for the operation and you have to get cortisone injections and they have to wait five six months that would be that wouldn't be so bad would it?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="710" who="S0012">but er I don't know what the waiting list is up up at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0152">it's it's er it's all this ifs and buts at the moment with me isn't it?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what's gonna happen still no news on the house and whatever</u>
<u n="714" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="715" who="S0152">no news on the house</u>
<u n="716" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you'd have thought there'd have been more interest wouldn't you at this time of the year?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0152">you know there've been nothing since the two in the first week of the holidays</u>
<u n="718" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0152">erm just just nothing</u>
<u n="720" who="S0012">and they don't they haven't come back at all?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0152" trans="overlap">they haven't come back</u>
<u n="722" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="723" who="S0152" trans="overlap">or whatever erm <pause dur="short"/> you know you <vocal desc="sigh"/> the thing is when you look around <pause dur="short"/> and you see what you know there's there's lots of houses which are not selling</u>
<u n="724" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0152">I have no idea why mine is mine <trunc>i</trunc> is not selling</u>
<u n="726" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="727" who="S0152">and the only thing I can put it down to is things like it's got carpet in the dining room</u>
<u n="728" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0152">now it's got a carpet in there not a wooden floor</u>
<u n="730" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0152">you know erm <pause dur="short"/> the kitchen the kitchen isn't isn't the kitchen's not bad</u>
<u n="732" who="S0012">no no that's not bad at all</u>
<u n="733" who="S0152">the kitchen is is fine you know if I changed the works if I put a new work surface in</u>
<u n="734" who="S0013">okay bye</u>
<u n="735" who="S0152">bye</u>
<u n="736" who="S0012">bye</u>
<u n="737" who="S0152">would</u>
<u n="738" who="S0012" trans="overlap">bye</u>
<u n="739" who="S0152">would that make a difference?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0012" trans="overlap">mind how you go</u>
<u n="741" who="S0013">bye</u>
<event desc="0013 leaves"/>
<u n="742" who="S0152">would that make a difference if I put a new work surface in?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0012">I doubt it cos what <trunc>h</trunc> what happen when people come in or buy a house <pause dur="short"/> they do their own thing to it don't they?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="745" who="S0012">if they want a new kitchen done or change the <trunc>kitche</trunc> change this and put their mark on it</u>
<u n="746" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0012">that's what they do</u>
<u n="748" who="S0152">yeah I don't know whether I dunno I I genuinely don't know whether to put a new floor down in the kitchen</u>
<u n="749" who="S0012">what a wood floor?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0152">a wood floor down in the kitchen</u>
<u n="751" who="S0012">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I mean when when they come in they'll they'll pull up everything out and change it all anyway and then of course the wood floor wouldn't be</u>
<u n="752" who="S0152">yeah the only the only reason that I say that it now is because that couple that came last week he went the floor's a bit uneven isn't it?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0012">did he? oh <pause dur="short"/> he's up there again look <pause dur="short"/> he's nicked the apples oh <event desc="sound of knocking"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="755" who="S0152">he's taken both of them</u>
<u n="756" who="S0012">he's took both of them <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="757" who="S0152">no he's taken <pause dur="short"/> he's no he's erm three by the looks of it</u>
<u n="758" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0152">they're a nuisance at the moment</u>
<u n="760" who="S0012">they are a nuisance <pause dur="short"/> the if I put any seed on the top of course they <trunc>lo</trunc> lots of birds like to eat from the top of the table if I put any seed on it he'll clear it right up</u>
<u n="761" who="S0152">yeah he's over here now</u>
<u n="762" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know and I have thought about just seeing if I can get <pause dur="short"/> some way just go and put some fascia on the back</u>
<u n="764" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0152">some plastic fascia on the back</u>
<u n="766" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0152">so I don't have to paint it</u>
<u n="768" who="S0012">that's right yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="769" who="S0152" trans="overlap">cos that because that looks</u>
<u n="770" who="S0012">yeah? <pause dur="long"/> and you're what about the moss on the roof do they ever say anything about that?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0152" trans="overlap">no they never say anything about the moss on the roof</u>
<u n="772" who="S0012" trans="overlap">don't they? oh</u>
<u n="773" who="S0152" trans="overlap">no it doesn't anything it insulates it really</u>
<u n="774" who="S0012">well it does really don't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0152">it doesn't</u>
<u n="776" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0152">you know it's a</u>
<u n="778" who="S0012" trans="overlap">and it ain't blocked up the gutters have it cos it don't</u>
<u n="779" who="S0152" trans="overlap">no cos I got I got a wire mesh in it and</u>
<u n="780" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you got a wire mesh in the gutters yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> I mean the you know the woodwork outside does need a paint you know I've been saying it for ages haven't I?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0152">and the only person really who can do it is me</u>
<u n="784" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="785" who="S0152">you know? <pause dur="short"/> and I haven't I haven't been in touch with the building society</u>
<u n="786" who="S0012">you haven't?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0152">and I should have done but I haven't because I don't want I don't I feel I'd get that it'll be that rejection and it'll be like</u>
<u n="788" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="790" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="791" who="S0152">when really they could make such a difference by saying yeah okay we'll do it for three years</u>
<u n="792" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0152">we'll give you that time to</u>
<u n="794" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> to get it sorted</u>
<u n="795" who="S0152">to to to sell type of thing</u>
<u n="796" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0012" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0152">I mean if I can get well if it all turns out the way that I'm hoping it will turn out <pause dur="short"/> with the job and with the other bits and pieces</u>
<u n="800" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="long"/> you got</u>
<u n="801" who="S0152">forgot her stuff</u>
<u n="802" who="S0012">are you alright <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0013">yeah forgot my water</u>
<u n="804" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="805" who="S0013">bye</u>
<u n="806" who="S0012">bye</u>
<u n="807" who="S0152" trans="overlap">bye so then I will then I'll be able to say look this is what I'm on</u>
<u n="808" who="S0012">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="809" who="S0152">and I can do it you know</u>
<u n="810" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0152">and I</u>
<u n="812" who="S0012" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="813" who="S0152">I'm <vocal desc="sigh"/> you know I have thought about going to the bank and say look how can you help me?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0152">you know what can <trunc>y</trunc> you know how can you help me?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> if I pay this off can you help me with the rest so I don't have such a large bill?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0152">you know</u>
<u n="820" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot of hoops to run jump through though ain't there?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> er you know I've not booked a holiday yet</u>
<u n="822" who="S0012">ain't you? no?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0152">I've not booked a holiday yet and I'm thinking mm that's not like me not to have a holiday booked for the summer</u>
<u n="824" who="S0012">no that ain't you cos getting a bit late now innit?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0152">well there'll be there'll be things about there'll always be a cottage about but</u>
<u n="826" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="827" who="S0152">whether it will be that price that you wanna pay</u>
<u n="828" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="829" who="S0152">which is the er <pause dur="short"/> which is the er thing you have to consider <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really needs to be having a car <pause dur="short"/> to <trunc>dri</trunc> to drive around in</u>
<u n="830" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0152">and she's waste er er she's wasting her money really</u>
<u n="832" who="S0012">she is she is</u>
<u n="833" who="S0152">she's having the driving lessons and isn't backing it up by practicing</u>
<u n="834" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0152">and she practices in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s car</u>
<u n="836" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0152">but <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's not the same</u>
<u n="838" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="839" who="S0152">it's not the same and <trunc>ca</trunc> certainly can't drive mine</u>
<u n="840" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="841" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is small I looked she's got she's got enough money <pause dur="short"/> that she saved to buy <pause dur="short"/> a car that is like twelve hundred pound</u>
<u n="842" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0152">but there ain't many about</u>
<u n="844" who="S0012">there ain't many about no</u>
<u n="845" who="S0152">not that are <trunc>n</trunc> are decent I looked at one yesterday which was five hundred <pause dur="short"/> a little Ka red Ka</u>
<u n="846" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0152">looked alright from from a distance</u>
<u n="848" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0152">looked at it <pause dur="short"/> the door doesn't close on the <unclear/> on the driver side cos it's got a dent in it so you can see</u>
<u n="850" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh crikey</u>
<u n="851" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="852" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0152">you know? erm it's got a dent on the other other side backs alright front's all the front was alright it just had a little bit of a dent on the side so the door's not fitting properly <pause dur="short"/> for a fact it would a hundred and fifty-six thousand miles on the clock</u>
<u n="854" who="S0012">oh wow</u>
<u n="855" who="S0152" trans="overlap">not not fifty-six thousand miles on the clock</u>
<u n="856" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="857" who="S0152">and that was five hundred pound</u>
<u n="858" who="S0012">was it? yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0152">there was a nice Peugeot two 0 six which was twelve twelve fifty at a garage which we pass every day when I take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to riding and he's got some decent cars but <trunc>th</trunc> an extra thousand pound makes a difference in the quality of car you get</u>
<u n="860" who="S0012">it does yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0152">you know? so</u>
<u n="862" who="S0012" trans="overlap">have you looked in Auto Trader?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0152">yeah not much on there</u>
<u n="864" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="865" who="S0152">not on the website</u>
<u n="866" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="867" who="S0152" trans="overlap">not on their website <trunc>any</trunc></u>
<u n="868" who="S0012" trans="overlap">there don't seem to be much do there no</u>
<u n="869" who="S0152">seem you know whether you <trunc>kn</trunc> whether you go Gumtree and look on Gumtree or things like that</u>
<u n="870" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0152">they got a <trunc>Fie</trunc> they got a Fiesta <pause dur="short"/> which looked alright well it looked alright but it was</u>
<u n="872" who="S0012" trans="overlap">trouble is you know <pause dur="short"/> they're all over the place you got to go and see it you've got to look at it you've got to test drive it if they come from a dealer they done something with it haven't they <trunc>lo</trunc> they've er and you've probably got a guarantee</u>
<u n="873" who="S0152" trans="overlap">you got a three month warranty on it and</u>
<u n="874" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0152" trans="overlap">stuff like that</u>
<u n="876" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="877" who="S0152">you know this garage at <anon type="place"/> that I've looked at it's got some really nice cars up you know</u>
<u n="878" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0152" trans="overlap">he's got some nice cars on there <pause dur="short"/> erm alright a lot of them are a lot have high mileage some aren't some are <trunc>o</trunc> some of just one owner cars</u>
<u n="880" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="881" who="S0152">but you know the there was a nice <trunc>Toyo</trunc> Toyota Corolla I think it was <pause dur="short"/> or Avensis which has only had one owner <pause dur="short"/> you know and if you were buying a car say for yourself</u>
<u n="882" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="883" who="S0152">and it was in that four thousand <pause dur="short"/> one owner</u>
<u n="884" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="885" who="S0152">full service history</u>
<u n="886" who="S0012">well that's it yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0152">it's something to go with you know if know what it's</u>
<u n="888" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> but er that was one of the things I said to her this week about come with me and we'll go and have a look and she wasn't wasn't very <pause dur="short"/> wasn't you know</u>
<u n="890" who="S0012">she wasn't too interested</u>
<u n="891" who="S0152" trans="overlap">she wasn't too keen <pause dur="short"/> and she doesn't want I don't want anything you know it's like when you're doing it yourself it's not a problem is it?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="893" who="S0152" trans="overlap">cos you and but when you know something about cars and you know</u>
<u n="894" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="895" who="S0152" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I have thought about asking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I've not spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in twelve months</u>
<u n="896" who="S0012">ain't you?</u>
<u n="897" who="S0152">I passed him one one morning and he said something he said oh we must go for a drink and I went yeah and <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>th</trunc> nothing</u>
<u n="898" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="899" who="S0152">he's too busy with his his hunting and his</u>
<u n="900" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> does he still do flying?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0152">no it's all hunting</u>
<u n="902" who="S0012">he's hunting now is he?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0152">it all for the last couple of years it's always been hunting Germany and places like that</u>
<u n="904" who="S0012">does he? yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0152">Prague boar hunting and stuff like that</u>
<u n="906" who="S0012">does he? <pause dur="short"/> how the other half live eh?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> and he and the garage is always busy though</u>
<u n="908" who="S0012">yeah it's always busy</u>
<u n="909" who="S0152"><vocal desc="cough"/> it's always busy</u>
<u n="910" who="S0012">some</u>
<u n="911" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and sometimes the garage that's down here has a a car or a</u>
<u n="912" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0152">for sale</u>
<u n="914" who="S0012">yeah he does yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0152">sometimes</u>
<u n="916" who="S0012"><anon type="place"/> autos yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="918" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he has some nice stuff</u>
<u n="919" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0012">and he's a nice bloke</u>
<u n="921" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="922" who="S0012">at <anon type="place"/> autos he he is really accommodating and and he's really nice <pause dur="short"/> I mean he come up here helped us with that with that car</u>
<u n="923" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0012">he is a very nice bloke but there you go <pause dur="long"/> well the we went to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> last night</u>
<u n="925" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0012">for Wednesday afternoon for dinner</u>
<u n="927" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0012">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and they they moved from er <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> no yeah <anon type="place"/> they they lived in <anon type="place"/> and we used to meet them down <anon type="place"/> when we went to <pause dur="short"/> and they asked us up for <pause dur="short"/> then he was it was three o'clock they asked us up for and we had snacks lovely it was prawns and stuff as snacks and cor it was really nice <pause dur="short"/> and then they did dinner around about eight o'clock I think <pause dur="short"/> and er we had er chicken and medallions of pork</u>
<u n="929" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="930" who="S0012">cor that was nice <pause dur="short"/> she's a vegetarian she doesn't touch meat she doesn't eat meat and yet she'll cook it for her husband and what have you</u>
<u n="931" who="S0152">that's good of her</u>
<u n="932" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0152">that's very</u>
<u n="934" who="S0012">they're a very nice couple too they're really nice <pause dur="short"/> and trouble is I had a skinful <trunc>di</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> well <pause dur="short"/> stella you're drinking your Stella and <pause dur="short"/> that bottle's gone cos they're only little bottles ain't they Stellas? but they're fairly strong aren't they?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0152">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0012">I think I had <pause dur="short"/> three Stellas and then two glasses of wine well that's enough for me I tell you</u>
<u n="937" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> stella's Stella Stella is strong</u>
<u n="938" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that was very nice we had a lovely dinner <pause dur="short"/> we got home about twelve o'clock <pause dur="short"/> and then we went to kip we still got up a six so</u>
<u n="939" who="S0152">yeah oh I was <pause dur="short"/> what time? I went I watched the football</u>
<u n="940" who="S0012">oh I watched that this morning</u>
<u n="941" who="S0152">and I watched the football last night and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we we watched Britain's Got Talent</u>
<u n="942" who="S0012">oh did you? yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0152">which was good it was alright</u>
<u n="944" who="S0012">well that was still on when we got home</u>
<u n="945" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0012">on ITV two</u>
<u n="947" who="S0152">yeah but it was so that was that was that was good</u>
<u n="948" who="S0012">that was good as it? yeah?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0152">they had some good stuff on there erm <pause dur="short"/> we so then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to bed and I <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was doing some work some artwork on the floor</u>
<u n="950" who="S0012">was she? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="951" who="S0152">doing this four foot by two foot board</u>
<u n="952" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="953" who="S0152">and the teacher said you need to do it larger and I said your teacher I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> look tell your teacher that there is no way that you can do it any larger because A you can't transport it on the bus easily</u>
<u n="954" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="955" who="S0152">I said and <pause dur="short"/> because the way that you have to transport the cars aren't large enough to put anything large in because you can't get much in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s car if you</u>
<u n="956" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="957" who="S0152">have a piece of board so I said four foot by two foot is is the maximum size</u>
<u n="958" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0152">and when I you know and when I consider that piece of board that I bought her two pieces of board a piece of MDF which was two foot by four foot and a piece of plywood two foot by four foot that was that was nearly thirty quid</u>
<u n="960" who="S0012">was it? crikey <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> what they cut it for you or</u>
<u n="961" who="S0152" trans="overlap">no it was already cut</u>
<u n="962" who="S0012">it was already cut was it?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0152">at Homebase</u>
<u n="964" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0152">and now it looks like they're not doing their sheet material any more Homebase</u>
<u n="966" who="S0012">aren't they?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0152">they've had the saw taken out the big saw taken out</u>
<u n="968" who="S0012">have they? <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="969" who="S0152">and you're thinking well I <trunc>ca</trunc> so I said you know and if there's a problem your teacher can speak to me about it</u>
<u n="970" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0152">you know if they want you want if they want you to do something larger then they provide you with the like cos they all have it easier to get move it about</u>
<u n="972" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they should supply it you buy it off them don't you?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0152">and it'll be a lot cheaper</u>
<u n="976" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0152">so she went oh okay so she was doing that she was doing that and I I watched the the Villa game <pause dur="short"/> and then I went to <pause dur="short"/> I think it must have been around eleven o'clock and then I went to bed and well <pause dur="short"/> I started just checking some things out when I was at the station on er <pause dur="short"/> thursday morning <pause dur="short"/> the on the notifications it says Liverpool <pause dur="short"/> lime Street <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went the train's in and I went is it? I says that's not our train I said that's Liverpool Lime Street that's at Liverpool</u>
<u n="978" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="979" who="S0152">right? that's not Liverpool Station London that is Liverpool Lime Street Station Liverpool I says but which makes me think if you can get a direct change from <anon type="place"/> to Liverpool that would be quite a nice journey</u>
<u n="980" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0152">because er and I said and I had the <trunc>si</trunc> when I went to Liverpool I did have a good time no matter what happened I had a good time in Liverpool</u>
<u n="982" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="983" who="S0152">I enjoyed it so maybe we could go on the train to Liverpool <pause dur="short"/> she went mm I said it's a long journey said how long do you reckon it will take us I said oh I would say probably around about four to five hours <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0152">oh really? and I went yeah so I I checked it out on the thing <pause dur="short"/> I think it was forty-six pound to go</u>
<u n="986" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0152">and eighteen pound return</u>
<u n="988" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="989" who="S0152">it depends on when you of <trunc>cour</trunc> it depends on</u>
<u n="990" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0152" trans="overlap">when you go</u>
<u n="992" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="993" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and when you book but the problem being is you can have a direct only one train</u>
<u n="994" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0152">five hours thirty minutes</u>
<u n="996" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="997" who="S0152">or you can have a train where you swap twice <vocal desc="laugh"/> so you go to Peterborough</u>
<u n="998" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="999" who="S0152">Leeds Liverpool <pause dur="short"/> still the same price</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0152">still the same <trunc>pri</trunc> still five and a half hours</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh and you gotta get off and on another one</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0012">in the hope that they're actually</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0152" trans="overlap">connected</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0012" trans="overlap">on time or</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0012">whatever</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0012">I can just imagine you getting off a train and the other one is pulling out</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0012">that often happen don't it?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0152">so I suppose if it's a little bit late and whatever</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0152" trans="overlap">so so it's like <vocal desc="cough"/> oh okay so I like and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says well how long does it take in the car? five hours?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0152">but in the car <pause dur="short"/> with the way the car is at the moment <pause dur="short"/> I can get there and back <pause dur="short"/> from here to to Liverpool and back</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0152">on a tank of petrol easily</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0152">and that's like sixty quid</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0152">so forty let's <trunc>c</trunc> call let's call it forty-five fifty-sixty pound per person that's a hundred and eighty pound</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0152">you drive don't you?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0012">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> weird innit? cor</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0152">you drive so</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0012">the only problem with driving is is parking up you know?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0152">yeah I mean the the hotel that we stayed in you got free parking with that</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh did you? yeah <pause dur="short"/> when we went down to Bournemouth you had to pay for their hotel parking or that was free just down the road so of course everyone went down the road but you had to pay for the parking in the hotel you could have gone and unload there</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0012">and lots of people were paying that was only a that was only a Premier Inn and it was very nice it were a <trunc>ni</trunc> a nice hotel but paying for your parking that's much innit when you're when you're paying for</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0152" trans="overlap">when you're sleeping there</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0152">they might as well put the price on the hotel room that's the way they do it</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0012">well of course it is yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they didn't own the car park that was the problem</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0152">yeah well see well this hotel well I a lot of hotels that are in like in the city centre don't like the Premier like the Premier in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0152">which is next door to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1040" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0152">you use <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0012">do you? yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0152">and you get a ticket</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0012">oh you get a ticket do you? it's like <anon type="place"/> oh that used to no no John Lewis now innit? you can park in or could park in John Lewis car park <pause dur="short"/> as long as you shopped there you got a ticket</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0012">and you got your free</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0012">but if you if you parked there and then went walking out and</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0012">but you gotta shop there and well <pause dur="short"/> bit expensive that place and you <trunc>c</trunc> if you need something that's fine but just to have a walk round <anon type="place"/> that really ain't work four and a half quid is it?</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0152">the cheapest the cheapest place really after four o'clock or after is it two o'clock? is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1052" who="S0012">is it? yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0152">yeah <anon type="place"/> is relatively cheap</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0152"><anon type="place"/> car park is mega expensive</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that is mega expensive yeah</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0152">mega expensive <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0012">you'd have thought these car parks had been run by the council so they could make the money and not these big car park people wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0152">oh it's like all council things isn't it?</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0012">it's all</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0152">the reason they don't do</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0012" trans="overlap">shipped out innit? yeah</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0152">the reason they don't cos they've gotta keep upkeep them haven't they?</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0012">yeah they have yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0152">you know why aren't there any council houses any more as such?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0012">well that's true yeah</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0152">why is it all private?</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0152">or going in that direction</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0012">well that is innit? yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a shame cos you know a council house for for local people should be for for them shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0012">but they sold off all the council houses didn't they?</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0152">well they gave you that right see that's where <pause dur="short"/> thatcher's government got you didn't they?</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0012">that was</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0152" trans="overlap">cos they allowed you to buy your council house</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0152">which was fine</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0152">because it meant that people the working class got their foot on the ladder</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0012">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0152">who were</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0152">for for the majority and knew they would have to continue working then</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0152">cos they they've got a mortgage so</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0152">going on strike and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0012">was yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's true yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> anyway when I got a change of government <trunc>wha</trunc> how they think or what they do are we even er whoever get in really</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0152">it's gonna be a strange election</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0012">it's gonna be a weird one innit?</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0152">it is gonna be a strange election</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0012">I mean they're all worried now it case the <trunc>l</trunc> UKIP get in <pause dur="short"/> well apparently <anon type="place"/> is changing over to UKIP <pause dur="short"/> and er lots of them are going this is what they the the polls say you know <pause dur="short"/> but that he's he's sick though isn't he? he want to be one of the boys don't he? a fag a pint of beer ha ha ha oh</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0152">you could see him doing it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1094" who="S0012">well I think a I think a lot a lot of er but I mean that used to be true blue <anon type="place"/> because the farms and the farmers <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="place"/> might some of <anon type="place"/> might go I I I can't see <anon type="place"/> going UKIP <pause dur="short"/> I mean people say I'm gonna vote for him well they don't in the end <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> I mean he's he's alienating people anyway by the way he just <unclear>ramble on</unclear></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah but he's only but he's a he isn't <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's alienating people <pause dur="short"/> that are relatively educated</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0152">or are not bias</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0012">yeah or aren't racist <pause dur="short"/> well cos I mean they reckon he's not they're not racist but</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0152">oh <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="1100" who="S0012">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> if he ain't racist I dunno what is</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0152">there is some there is something about there is something about I think see I <pause dur="long"/> they're they're talking about I think I <trunc>c</trunc> I caught it this morning they're talking about if the if Labour get in it'll be splitting up the country into all its different parts</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0152" trans="overlap">because you'll have the <trunc>l</trunc> you'll have Plaid Cymru and you'll have the SNP</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0152">backing Labour et cetera</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0152">so therefore you've got Labour will owe them something</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0152">so they might give them the <pause dur="short"/> referendum on</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0152" trans="overlap">Scotland again or <trunc>s</trunc> referendum on Wales Wales won't wanna join <trunc>b</trunc> by themselves</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0152">because they get too much and the and apparently there was some <pause dur="short"/> there was something like the pensions are gonna if you're if you've got pensions in and you're in Scotland you're gonna be better off in Scotland</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0152">because the deal that they did</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0012">yeah that's right and education in Scotland</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0152">you know</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0012">you can go to university in Scotland for nothing if you live up there</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0012">and you have to pay for it here</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0012">er who's who's going to get married? someone's come coming over er one of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends are coming over here <pause dur="short"/> to have their baby up I Edinburgh so they have rights <pause dur="short"/> to have free education in Scotland mind you that's a long while ahead now but that's what they think they're do going to do because really I mean all that money these people have to pay</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0012" trans="overlap">to be education and they call them you know it's a lot of people are paying nine thousand quid innit now? three thousand a year?</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0152">no it's nine thousand a year</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0012">nine thousand a year is it? that's a lot of money innit? who's got that?</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0152">no but you just have a student loan</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0012">yeah and then you have to pay it back er talking student loans erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is now got to pay a lot more because she's living abroad <pause dur="short"/> and they want to know every ins and outs of what what she's earning abroad you know <pause dur="short"/> but she is a affiliated to er <anon type="place"/> university so <pause dur="short"/> they know anyway</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0012">but we now got this application form <pause dur="short"/> and she's been paying from China she pays er every month or every six months or whatever she's been keeping up with the repayments now they want even more</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0152"><unclear>higher</unclear> tax</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just because she's living in <pause dur="short"/> china earning more money I expect than they do over here <pause dur="short"/> but you don't have to pay a student loan off if you earn under twenty thousand is it?</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0152">I don't know don't know</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0012">under twenty thousand a year something like that you don't have to pay it off soon as they get over that then you have to start paying it off <pause dur="short"/> I don't know exactly how much it is but I know you don't have to pay it at all if you are under and then you got thirty years and after thirty years you owe nothing <pause dur="short"/> it's a long time innit? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1135" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0012">but that's a shame cos I mean all these people are in debt after getting educated and if they can't get a job well <pause dur="short"/> if they get a job they gotta pay all this money back and if they can't</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0152" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0152" trans="overlap">get a job</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0012">well most <trunc>gradua</trunc></u>
<u n="1140" who="S0152" trans="overlap">they're no better off</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0012">a lot of graduates cos there there was an article <trunc>la</trunc> a lot of graduates now their starting salary is over thirty grand</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0012">is it? yeah? yeah if they can get a job</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0152">if you go and work for the likes of Lidl and Aldi as a graduate you're on forty grand</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0012">are you? wow</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0152">but they expect you to you're there all the time and</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0152">they're expecting you to do everything in the store</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0012">yeah yeah but they've</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0152" trans="overlap">you know you do</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0012">only got a few jobs they've only got an X amount of jobs them sort of people and there's loads and loads of graduates without one</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah it I mean that that is the problem that is the problem <pause dur="short"/> that is the problem <pause dur="short"/> mm that is the problem</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0012">mm oh it sounds <trunc>some</trunc> someone's hammering down there</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0152">wind's picking up</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0012">the wind's getting up but that's was lovely yesterday after the rain</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0152">oh it chucked it down didn't it?</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that chucked it down we got down to er <anon type="place"/> and that was that was like this but they they were going to have a barbeque you see</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0012">so like of course that got washed out in the afternoon er during the morning <pause dur="short"/> but er that was like this in the afternoon but the</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah which</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0012" trans="overlap">wind is very cold</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0152">yeah the wind is picking up yeah it's supposed to be windy this afternoon</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0152">which way did you go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0012">I can't remember we come back <anon type="place"/> way <pause dur="short"/> I think we went <anon type="place"/> way the first time <pause dur="short"/> when we went <pause dur="short"/> and then we come back through <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1165" who="S0152">so you come <trunc>thro</trunc> via <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0152">came via</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0012">but there was a better a better ride going <anon type="place"/> and up that way than it was coming back through <anon type="place"/> a better road a better ride altogether <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1169" who="S0152">A47 was blocked last night</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0012">what happened?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0152"><trunc>betwee</trunc> er it was blocked between <anon type="place"/> roundabout and the <anon type="place"/> turning</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0012">was it?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0152">erm a lorry had er something had happened with a lorry so when I went to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up there was nothing on the west carriageway</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0152">nothing and I thought oh I'd better not come back that way then</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0152">so I came back via <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0152">and then when I got to the <anon type="place"/> turning the traffic was running so they'd opened it up</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's amazing innit? I mean these er motorway accidents they block the motorway off for ages don't they? the M6 I think was <pause dur="short"/> there was a big smack up on the M6 er a couple of days ago saw it come over on the traffic news and they'd blocked the whole motorway off and they were waiting for the air ambulance <pause dur="short"/> so that weren't very good was it? but they have to block it off don't they for for the an air ambulance to land</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0152" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="long"/> no it's <pause dur="short"/> you kind of listen out to routes that you know I tend to listen out to routes that I know</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0012">do you?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1184" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0152">tend to listen so is it Wednesday you're going Wednesday morning?</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0012">yeah we're going early Wednesday <pause dur="long"/> and er well as I say we've gotta be there at two o'clock er the next day cos we're stopping over <pause dur="short"/> so it won't be too bad <pause dur="short"/> hopefully it's a long old journey down to Lizard though innit? <vocal desc="laugh"/> couldn't be any further</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0152">no Lizard is er not the best of journeys cos the if you're going M5 Taunton way</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0152">which is the way you tend to go unless you're going M4 <pause dur="short"/> if you're going Herefordshire Wye Valley</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0152">Herefordshire so that does sound like the M4</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0012">well whichever you've gotta get back onto that <anon type="place"/> road anyway so and that's the only one that lead down there</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0152" trans="overlap">there's the M5 goes all the way down there doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah just nip to the loo</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0152">the M5 goes all the way down there</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="1197" who="S0012">all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s tomato plants out there</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0152">they're coming on <trunc>lo</trunc> quite nicely aren't they?</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0012">yeah they're doing well really well</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0152">well the er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is away at the moment</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0012">is she?</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0012">where's she gone?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0152">she's down in Hertfordshire</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0012">oh she could go and see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1206" who="S0152">no not Hertfordshire what am I saying? <pause dur="short"/> berkshire</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0012">Berkshire?</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0152">oh I don't I dunno</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0012">so you ain't seen her lately?</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0152">I haven't seen her since <trunc>Sun</trunc> I haven't seen her since Saturday</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0012">haven't you?</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> no cos the girls came back and then her daughter went and stayed there till Monday</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0152">and then she went <pause dur="short"/> down to where she was going on Thursday on the train and she's staying there till Monday cos they don't go back to work until next weekend private school on on the holidays <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1215" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0152">on holiday erm which is <vocal desc="yawn"/> she's a nice person but <pause dur="short"/> finds I think finds me sometimes irritating</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that what she told you?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0152">oh I just get this impression I was I mean she phoned last night I've not spoken to her since erm Wednesday I think it was</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0152">I spoke to her on Wednesday erm she phoned last night <vocal desc="yawn"/> cos <vocal desc="yawn"/> where she was staying they'd gone out and it was a wrong call and I and er so I saw the number come up and I went so I answered it hello?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you rotter</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0152">so I was having this conversation and she went will you stop being silly now please?</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh did she oh dear</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0152">and then she said something and I went said have you missed me? I have yeah I missed your smile I missed tormenting you</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1228" who="S0152">and it and she didn't like that</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0012">didn't she?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0152">no no I just and I thought oh</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0012">she's got no sense of humour then</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0152">and I <trunc>sai</trunc> you know and I said well and she says second thing that comes out of when you were asked <trunc>i</trunc> is you missed tormenting me? I said yeah but I said it's tormenting you in a nice way not in a horrible way <pause dur="short"/> then I just thought oh well if you if you can't you know</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> weird innit?</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think maybe a bit too posh for me</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0012">she's too posh?</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1237" who="S0012">oh right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1238" who="S0152">quiet spoken or something dunno and then there was there was some she said something I said oh something about the north and she says about oh it's all flat caps and everything and then I</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0152">and I text back oh that reminds me I must get my flat cap out</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0152">so dunno did you see erm Escape to the Country?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0012">yes that was <anon type="place"/> weren't it?</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0152">there was there was a <anon type="place"/> one there was one from Yorkshire this week</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0012">oh I didn't seen that one I mean</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0152">where there's a couple where they've been looking they've been together fifteen years <pause dur="long"/> she stays with him six nights a week but stays one night a week in her own place <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1247" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0152">she's just retired she just retired from the job she was doing and and er was hating it because she wasn't seeing anybody</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0152">well you have to go if you you have to go out to see people</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0012">well of course you do</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0152">if you're retired and you know you're retired then you find things to do</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> and it <vocal desc="laugh"/> and so they had been looking for this house and they'd put an offer in on a house it nearly when through but she got cold feet</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0012">did she? oh</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0152">right? and they have a budget or something like six hundred thousand</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0012">oh wow</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0152">so you get plenty you know and like</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0152">they want certain things in the house et cetera and er <pause dur="short"/> I mean they spent an evening looking at properties up in Yorkshire</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0152">and they must he said we counted over a thousand houses that we looked at and didn't like any of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1263" who="S0012">what?</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0012">well what do they live in now then? er?</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0152" trans="overlap">and it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> a thousand houses you will find a house you know I could go on the web tomorrow I could go on the web now and find a house that I would love to have</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah we you know that Rightmove place on on the net? we I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> put in er interested in this area and they keep sending us of of er unsubscribed now but they kept sending us all these houses in Derbyshire and they're <pause dur="short"/> stone houses and er <pause dur="short"/> they're around about five hundred thousand you know and they're only three bedrooms very small rooms stone built houses and they got er the cos I always look at the <pause dur="short"/> heating thing what's that called? you know the</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0152">the EPC</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0012">the EPC and all got between between er D and F they're not every efficient at all because they're okay in the in the summer when it's hot outside cos they're nice and cool but you can't heat them up so good until or everything get hot</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0152">is that the is that reason? because mine's a D</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0012">yours is a D?</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0152">alright mine's a D</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I thought yours was</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0152">mine's a D</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0012">I think ours is D too innit? we got the same as you we got the same EPC as you</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0152">and the reason mine is at that level is because of my boiler even though my boiler is</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0152" trans="overlap">brand new</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0152">it's because Calor Gas is not</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it's expensive</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0152">it no it's not <trunc>an</trunc> expense it's it's calorific value that it burns at</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0152">if it was oil <pause dur="short"/> it would be a better</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it would have a better reading it's that calorific</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0012">yeah well they don't like that they don't like the the coal burner or the wood burner and they put our I mean they said if you had underfloor er insulation that</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0012" trans="overlap">would be okay we have got underfloor insulation</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0012">total idiots and that's there for ten years innit you can't change it</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0012">this bloke come round and he walk walked around every wall is insulated in this house</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0012">every single wall</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0152">it's never a cold house</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> and he he give us a <trunc>s</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0152">all down to it's all down to that that cos</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah it's all down to that</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0152" trans="overlap">you know when you consider that all my walls are <trunc>ins</trunc> it's got foam insulation</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0152">the new build has got the right thickness and thin</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0152">the loft has got vermiculate in although it's not the thickness but vermiculite is as good</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0012">yeah it is yeah</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0152" trans="overlap">as the stuff</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no he looked up in the loft and he said oh it's gotta be double this thickness <pause dur="short"/> cos there's four inches at the moment and you gotta put it across that's in between the</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0152" trans="overlap">but you can buy you can get insulation that isn't that thick that is only that thick which is just as good</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0012">yeah you can yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0152">half the thickness therefore innit?</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0152">right</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0012">well I I think I think the bloke was absolutely mental he didn't know what he was talking about he was there for about three minutes and that was it you know? then he gave you a <trunc>stu</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> result like that and we er complained to the <pause dur="short"/> to the er <pause dur="short"/> what was it Abbots? we complained to them he says er oh we'll like get him back in then <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1314" who="S0152">yeah but it'll be double it cost you though didn't it sixty quid or something like that</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0152">no I I don't know what I'm gonna do <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1317" who="S0012">no you're in a quandary really ain't you? <pause dur="short"/> I mean you dropped the price of the house didn't you?</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0152">I'm not dropping it any more</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0152">it it's got a range that if anybody wants it there is a range there that people can come in at</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0152">and when you see what's on the market</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0152">it's where it should be</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think it's a very good price for your house</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0152">I bumped into a <trunc>cou</trunc> last I think it was last Saturday <pause dur="short"/> I think it was last Saturday when I went to get the Lottery tickets erm <pause dur="short"/> I bumped into a couple on their bikes who had come to look at the house</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0152">in the village</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0012">oh did you? yeah</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0152">cos they live in the village they're renting in the village</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0152">and I <trunc>thou</trunc> I <trunc>f</trunc> really feel like saying well you know <pause dur="short"/> what was the <trunc>prob</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0152" trans="overlap">needed too much doing to it that's only what you wanted to do to it</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0012">yeah of course that is yeah</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0152">and you do it in time don't you?</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0152">you know you do it in time so</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0012">stupid innit?</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> so when you're when you're back I wanna put some stuff on Ebay</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0152">I wanna put that projector onto Ebay</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0152">and the organ and whatever</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0152">there's no point in me doing it now because you're gonna be away and</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0012">well that's right we <pause dur="short"/> we've gotta do do the same but there's no point in we've gotta put a few bits and pieces that I got collected up</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0152">I might sell my band saw as well</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0012">are you?</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0152">sell my band saw</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0152">my little band saw <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0012">what sort of cut is it? is it a thin blade or</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0152" trans="overlap">they have you can have different blades on it</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0152">you can change the blade</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0152">so you can do scrolling with it if you put a thin blade in it</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0152">or you can cut it chops like that</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0012">yeah it's good yeah</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0152">so might sell that I mean they're not that expensive to buy brand new <vocal desc="cough"/> I think they're something like a hundred and forty a hundred and fifty pound to buy brand new</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0012">are they? yeah</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0152">it's only I think I've only used it four times</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's a shame when you got all the gear innit?</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0152">well</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0012">and you don't use it any more <pause dur="short"/> just lay there don't it? I mean I suppose I got a load of stuff laying laying around</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0152">it's a case of just well</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0012">when we moved from fro <anon type="place"/> up to here we stuck everything up in that loft out there and we've only just got around to chucking it all out cos if you don't use it</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0152">you don't <pause dur="short"/> you just don't bother looking for it</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0012">you don't no and you think oh well I I haven't used it for ten years</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0012">get rid of it</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0152">thinking about there's a couple of computers in the loft I'm gonna take the hard drive out but I'm just gonna take it to the tip</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0152">take the hard drive out and smash the hard drive</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0152">cos there's no cos the hard drive's no good at the end of the day</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah stick a hammer through that cos people er get lots of information from hard drives don't they?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0152">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was erm <vocal desc="cough"/> it was a long while ago <pause dur="short"/> he wanted to start up a business of er cos people were changing computers left willy-nilly you know like mad cos they they kept upgrading didn't they? I mean the first computers were pretty useless weren't they? didn't have any memory or anything</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0152" trans="overlap">when you look back to how they were yeah</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah and er he had this business idea and he'd got it all drawn out all the <pause dur="short"/> and it was erm something to do with smashing the you know and you can witness it being done and all this that and the other you can witness the hard drive being made made <trunc>irre</trunc> <trunc>irr</trunc> unusable and er he was <vocal desc="laugh"/> he had it all graphic all these graphics to put up on <trunc>hi</trunc> on the website you know <pause dur="short"/> and then he felt oh I can't be arsed he couldn't be bothered <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and when you think about it you know okay you'd get a few but that wouldn't be worth doing would it?</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> right let's go and do some jobs</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what jobs have you gotta do?</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0152">well I've gotta do some <trunc>wash</trunc></u>
<u n="1387" who="S0012" trans="overlap">paint?</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0152">some painting no</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1390" who="S0152">I've got some washing to do I need to put the vacuum <unclear>round</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> try and might do a bit of ironing get some shirts ironed for the week so that I don't have to do them</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0152">there's <pause dur="short"/> fA cup day next week <trunc>fi</trunc> er semi-final next week so</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0012">yeah I shan't be seeing that though <vocal desc="sigh"/> phew</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0152">Arsenal have got an easy one</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0012">Aston Villa who have they got?</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0152">Liverpool</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0012">Liverpool yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0152" trans="overlap">although saying that the way they're playing at the moment</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah they had a good win didn't they?</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0152">beat Tottenham</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah broke my heart that did</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0152">beat Tottenham</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> only one nil</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0152">don't matter it's three points</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0152">three points should have three points on Tuesday night as well</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0012">they done well though to get out of where they were <pause dur="short"/> I thought they were gonna go down</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0152">well we need another <trunc>tw</trunc> we need another two wins</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0012">Leicester are going to go down ain't they?</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0152">well I dunno</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0012">well they're still at the bottom there</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0152">they're still at the bottom but they've still they've still got two games in hand you see</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0152">see Villa have got a they Villa have played an extra game</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0152">but er six points clear at the bottom</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0012">that's it Norwich are doing well</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0152">they were lucky yesterday</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0012">well they won</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0152">yeah well it's what it's about I mean he he's he put three strikers on</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0152">to go for that win</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0152">he changed the formation</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0152">brave</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0012">that was brave that was brave cos <pause dur="short"/> they were in a quandary at the <trunc>ti</trunc> er when they they scored first didn't they?</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0152">well well <trunc>ge</trunc></u>
<u n="1429" who="S0012" trans="overlap">did they? I they could have felt a bit <unclear>screwed</unclear></u>
<u n="1430" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah what gets me with like well Norwich should go up really but I got an idea it could be a Norwich Ipswich <trunc>fi</trunc> play off final</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0012">do you reckon? oh god <pause dur="short"/> well we always beat Ipswich anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0152" trans="overlap">could you <trunc>imagi</trunc> could you imagine that?</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0012">oh god</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0152">but I</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0012">there'd be riots</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0152">you know Benteke for Villa has scored</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0012">he's brilliant ain't he?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0152">eight goals</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0152" trans="overlap">in the last six games</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0012">he's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> and that and the goals he scored yesterday</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0152">why <pause dur="short"/> why is he sort of scoring now and he wasn't scoring before and everybody was on his case?</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0012">I don't know</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0152">because he's getting the service</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0012"><trunc>ye</trunc> well he <trunc>wa</trunc> he was he <trunc>wa</trunc> yeah and soon I mean right from the goal line up to him and he run through there like hell there</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0152" trans="overlap">he he's getting the service you know I always rated Lambert as a decent manager but</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0152">what something went wrong</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0152">something went wrong</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0152">you know if you consider what he did for Norwich took them from the first division</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0152">up into the championship then straight up into the Premiership</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0012">that's right he did yeah</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0152">why the why the change?</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0012">I don't know what's happened to Lambert he's <pause dur="short"/> he's weird ain't he?</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0152">you know he's gotta rebuild his career a bit like erm David Moyes has had to do</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah cor he went downhill didn't he? and then <pause dur="short"/> he's he's</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0152">they want him but they West Ham want him</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0012">yeah oh what's that? that was like a Hummingbird flying up <trunc>again</trunc> the window don't know what he was oh there he go again what's that?</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0152">little Finch</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0152">a little Finch he was</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0012" trans="overlap">cos he's nicking the cobwebs there</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0152" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0152">little finch</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0012">here he come again <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1470" who="S0152">so but no I was well I <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who <pause dur="short"/> is a Tottenham supporter I've not heard from him in <pause dur="short"/> I've been in touch with him but I've not heard from him</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0152" trans="overlap">if you know what I mean erm he <pause dur="short"/> two years ago I helped him move him to where he is</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0012">yeah you did yeah</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0152" trans="overlap">last it was last <trunc>Fe</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> february time was the last time I saw him last year</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0152">and I I've text him and I message him bits and pieces and he's a Tottenham supporter and I was expecting him yesterday that he would have got in touch to say oh you beat us type of thing but nothing</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0152">and I now I know he gets he's getting married in September time <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but I've not heard anything now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who <pause dur="short"/> I used to work with who's the Arsenal supporter almost well contact every other every week really</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0152">a message just how things are going and whatever</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0152">couple of messages in the week cos he's just come back from Budapest so talking about Budapest he wanted my address cos I've got a wedding to go to I've got his wedding to go to but I'm going I'm being invited for the whole day</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0012">are you? oh</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0152">church and</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0012">oh church and reception?</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0152" trans="overlap">er and reception and evening everything I've been</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0152">invited that's that you know erm <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0012">oh another present</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0152">so and suits as well</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0012">and a suit yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1492" who="S0152">I need to lose some weight I forgot I need to lose some weight</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0012">how you gonna do that?</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0152">dunno <pause dur="short"/> dunno cut all the biscuits out cut all the crisps out</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0012">I've cut all the biscuits out <pause dur="short"/> won't have any biscuits any more I went to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and had a blood test and he reckon they reckon when the when the results come back pre-diabetic</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0012">so I cut all sugars out</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0152">what stage two?</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0012">I don't know what that this is</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0152" trans="overlap">type two?</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0012">yeah pre-diabetic yeah I've gotta go up <pause dur="short"/> tuesday to get all the information from the nurse and all that sort of business <pause dur="short"/> and what diet you gotta go on <pause dur="short"/> and I know it's carbohydrates mostly cos carbohydrates actually turn to sugar <pause dur="short"/> and reading about it it says <vocal desc="cough"/> obese people and people who don't do any exercise get it well</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0152">you're always doing stuff</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0012">I do enough exercise tearing about like mad yeah</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0152">but your cholesterol level's high isn't it?</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0012">it well it's yeah no I I'm on statins now</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0152">what? okay what's your cholesterol level now?</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0012">it was six I don't know what it is now it was six <pause dur="short"/> supposed to be about four</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0152">four five</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0152">you're not stressed or anything like</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0152">your blood pressure's alright?</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0012">blood pressure's fine yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just probably too much cheese and milk and potatoes and bread and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0152" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0012">friend our friend down er Suffolk he had the same thing and he's cut out all <trunc>carbo</trunc> most carbohydrates right? and he's gone like a skeleton <pause dur="short"/> there's a programme on television You Are What You Eat or whatever it's called it was just on the other day this bloke come on he cut out carbohydrates altogether no he didn't this woman he was experimenting with she did she had to and er and finished up with no energy tired always wanting to go to sleep you gotta have the balance that's the trouble you gotta have the balance <pause dur="long"/> but er well I mean you can't give up everything can you? I had a load of <vocal desc="laugh"/> alcohol last night <vocal desc="laugh"/> sure that didn't help a lot but</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0152">you see I I'm when I was walking round London and we went for that meal I wanted a drink and I thought well I'm gonna have a I'm gonna have a beer and I had a bottled beer</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0152">and it was nice and I I ended up having two but and then Friday I went shopping <pause dur="short"/> and I thought <pause dur="short"/> I'll get a bottle I'll get a bottle of beer</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0152" trans="overlap">for the night and then I <trunc>p</trunc> picked it up</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0152" trans="overlap">it was only one bottle and then realised that I had to go and get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1523" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0152">and I just put it back on the shelf and thought what's the point?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0152">there's no there's no point</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0152">there's no point at all</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0012">and that's really strange you can have <pause dur="short"/> if you have beer it's bad for you it's bad for the cholesterol and everything and the sugar content and <trunc>what</trunc> but you can have wine</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0152">you'd think it would be the opposite wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0012">you'd think that would be totally opposite wouldn't you but you can have wine <pause dur="short"/> so there you go I'll have to just make my own wine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1532" who="S0152">make your own wine</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0012">instead of my beer <pause dur="short"/> I've still gotta make beer</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0152">yeah but you have to do something</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0012">course you do oh it's it's ridiculous I mean my my gran my great aunt smoked like a trooper I mean really smoked went through the First World War and the Second World War with all the stress and everything</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0012">and lived to ninety-three</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0012">weird innit?</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0152">well they put people on statins straight away don't they now?</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0012">they do</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0152">if they've got erm</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> and you have porridge don't you?</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0012">every morning</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0152">but you have full-fat milk</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0012">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> well you can't have the other stuff can you? you might just as well have water</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0152">you can have semi-skimmed</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0012">no you might as well have water</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0152">but there isn't much difference</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0012">and there's nothing like a lump of toast with a nice big thick</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0152" trans="overlap">butter's <trunc>al</trunc></u>
<u n="1553" who="S0012" trans="overlap">load of</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0152" trans="overlap">butter's</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0012" trans="overlap">butter on it and Marmite</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0152">butter's alright but you have all</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0012">and then finish off with a great big lump of cheese <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1558" who="S0152">you should have semi-skimmed not skimmed cos skimmed milk is horrible cos that's just like whitewash</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I'm I'm I'm not I'm not going to have semi-skimmed milk this big fat nurse told me last time I mean she was massive she says you have to go on this diet and there she is sitting there blubber all over the place</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0152">well it's like <pause dur="short"/> when I went for mine down there weren't it <pause dur="short"/> because he couldn't get any blood out of my finger to do the cholesterol reading he looked at me and went well you need to cut down this this and this and pardon?</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0152">and he went and I went no and it's cos my cholesterol level will be round about four point five no it won't no it won't so my cholesterol level will be round about four point five</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0152">I said <pause dur="short"/> and you and you're looking on the check sheet there because I'm a little bit overweight and because of this that I've got a high cholesterol level no <pause dur="short"/> he went and then cos he couldn't get anything out he went you're gonna have to have a proper blood test well that's alright I'll have the proper blood test</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I don't have a problem it's always good to have your blood done and see where you are and see if</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0012" trans="overlap">course it is yeah</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0152">everything's functioning properly which it was and it was four point six</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0012">ah right well you're alright then yeah</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0152">you know and if I don't have porridge like at this time of the year it will go to four point eight</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0152">and if it's stress levels stress doesn't help</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0012">no stress is bad <pause dur="short"/> bad for you stress <pause dur="short"/> you'll have to de-stress</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0152">how am I gonna de-stress come on?</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0012">get your <trunc>hou</trunc> house sold <vocal desc="laugh"/> pay off your debts there would be no stress would there?</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0152">no there wouldn't</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0012">so there there's the answer</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1579" who="S0012">and this coming spring <pause dur="short"/> this spring that'll all work out guaranteed <pause dur="short"/> you'll be <trunc>liv</trunc> living in a nice three bedroom rented property for six hundred pound a month and you'll have all that money</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0152">no I'll have money that I can do things with or not do things with and save because I've just would have wasted the last twenty-one years</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1582" who="S0152">of paying my mortgage</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah well <pause dur="short"/> it's all these women that was the problem <pause dur="short"/> spending it on all these women weren't it?</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0152">a lot of it</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0012">putting on new bits to the house <pause dur="short"/> so you can accommodate their kids</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> everything you can work out in hindsight but that <vocal desc="laugh"/> that don't work out for the future does it?</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0152">yeah I mean at the end of the day would I would I have done anything different? the answer is</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0152">am I doing things differently now? yes so I've learnt</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0152">if I could if I could just clear the the debts then there wouldn't be a problem that's the thing</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0152">and if I hadn't have lost that if I hadn't have lost the salary that I was on</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0012">that's right you'd have been fine wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0152" trans="overlap">I'd have been fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1599" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0152">but to take a fifty percent drop in salary</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0012">that's a lot of money innit? <pause dur="short"/> phew a lot of money <pause dur="short"/> these places have got no conscience they still want you money don't they?</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0152">that's right I mean that's that's the thing and I you know to be honest I've kept I've managed to keep up haven't I? so</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0012">of course you have yeah you</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0152">at the moment</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0012">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
