<text id="S72E">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:03:33</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0509 S0510</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON &amp; ANON's home, Hastings</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Car Accident, Alice in Wonderland, Scars, Music, Costume, the Internet, Presents, Seagulls, Reading, Theatre, Reading</topics>
		<activity>Mother and Daughter Catching Up</activity>
		<conv_type>Explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0509">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hastings</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0510">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Receptionist</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0509">so what's all this about uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his car?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0510">oh yeah well erm you know he normally drives erm to work with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they sort of take it in turns and</u>
<u n="3" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0510">drive in and everything and they have a very set route well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was off the other week and so when uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was coming back he kind of decided to go cross-country and do a slightly different route</u>
<u n="5" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="6" who="S0510">so he was erm coming through sort of <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> way which is where it's not that far from where auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives actually and erm it was getting <trunc>qui</trunc> er near to dark it was sort of dusk time you know</u>
<u n="7" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="8" who="S0510">so light wasn't brilliant but it was okay and erm he was just coming over the the brow of a hill</u>
<u n="9" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0510">when out of the corner of his eye he noticed something coming from the side and it was a deer</u>
<u n="11" who="S0509">I knew</u>
<u n="12" who="S0510" trans="overlap">about</u>
<u n="13" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it was gonna be a deer</u>
<u n="14" who="S0510">he knew those those deer they get everywhere don't they</u>
<u n="15" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0510" trans="overlap">in the country? so I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s had a few no two encounters with deer</u>
<u n="17" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="18" who="S0510">erm both of them have cost <vocal desc="laugh"/> luckily not her life but you know</u>
<u n="19" who="S0509">but money <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0510" trans="overlap">but cost her money cos they did quite a lot of damage cos they</u>
<u n="21" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0510">come at really come at speed and the worst thing for uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was was that you know he was sort of within the speed limit but he was probably at the maximum speed limit at sixty round there</u>
<u n="23" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="24" who="S0510">so you know he's just coming over the brow of a hill seen out of the corner of his eye a deer</u>
<u n="25" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0510">starting to you know launch itself and just does all he can to stop the car you know without</u>
<u n="27" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0510">spinning it like I did on that night coming home</u>
<u n="29" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0510">from <anon type="place"/> erm and so he's just braking and braking and just hoping for the best but it hits him <vocal desc="cough"/> hits the car</u>
<u n="31" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0510">but it's kind of like he clipped it almost on the on the side of the car</u>
<u n="33" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="34" who="S0510">and he's just sort of <trunc>g</trunc> after it's happened you know he it's <trunc>pr</trunc>pronged off somewhere and he's he's carried on slowing down so <trunc>n</trunc> he's sort of near the bottom of this hill and he pulls over to get out and have a look and</u>
<u n="35" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0510">dust himself down and as he gets out he looks up the hill and he can see that there's another car at the top of the hill that has also stopped and as it turns out what had happened was as he was coming over the brow of the hill to go down another guy was coming up the hill to go over</u>
<u n="37" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0510">and when uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> clipped the deer the other car collected it basically</u>
<u n="39" who="S0509"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh no</u>
<u n="40" who="S0510">well it hit the other car so the guy there's a guy up the top there waving down to uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so he kind of had a quick look at the side of his car and it's you know it's mashed up at the side but</u>
<u n="41" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="42" who="S0510">it's not you know it's not insurmountable as it were and he goes up to check this guy's okay and everything's alright up there and he goes up and this guy's got cuts to his head and</u>
<u n="43" who="S0509">oh my god</u>
<u n="44" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know to his arm not not really deep cuts but you know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0510" trans="overlap">he's bleeding a bit and everything but he seems pretty compos mentis and erm and you know they were chatting saying oh are you alright are you okay? oh gosh you know uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sees the front of his car and he definitely came off worse for it</u>
<u n="47" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="48" who="S0510">this this other guy</u>
<u n="49" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0510">because it's hit the top of the car in the middle</u>
<u n="51" who="S0509">what?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0510">and if you'd have seen a photo <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I in fact I said to uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> send me the photos <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos it's just unbelievable that this guy got out and he was walking and doing anything really</u>
<u n="53" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="54" who="S0510">because the whole of the middle of the car is kind of caved in</u>
<u n="55" who="S0509"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0510">erm and the windscreen is totally shattered and you know it's like this <pause dur="short"/> it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="58" who="S0510">in the middle so</u>
<u n="59" who="S0509" trans="overlap">caved in yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0510">yeah just completely caved in so the the deer's obviously hit the top you know near the windscreen anyway by this time another motorist or a couple of motorists actually I think had stopped and er this guy was sort of <trunc>y</trunc>you know saying to the the other driver you know are you sure you're alright? you know are you sure you don't want an ambulance? and he's like no no I'm fine you know I'm just sort of yeah I I've just got a few cuts but I'm absolutely fine but looking at the car you would never have believed it you know</u>
<u n="61" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0510">so no wonder the guy was sort of checking him out and everything anyway they went then went on their way although oh that was it this guy had a torch or something <unclear/> they were clearing away traffic that was sort of</u>
<u n="63" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="64" who="S0510">coming to and fro it just so reminded me of my crash in you know in <anon type="place"/> that evening</u>
<u n="65" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0510">oh my goodness erm and so uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then helped him sort of pull it off of the road into sort of like a layby area with a hedge and everything</u>
<u n="67" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="68" who="S0510">erm and then this other guy went and this lady went erm and they're they're kind of like oh the guy was going oh I don't you know I dunno what happened to the deer it just sort of it all happened so quick and</u>
<u n="69" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0510">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going well you know more often and not knowing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s experience as well</u>
<u n="71" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0510">erm what happens is they get hit but they just carry on because they almost they get kind of or they just get you know pranged over into the thicket or whatever</u>
<u n="73" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0510">but often when a deer gets <trunc>h</trunc>hit it keeps running you know</u>
<u n="75" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="76" who="S0510">and then it'll kind of just end up sort of you know going its sorry way really erm so er he says oh you know your <trunc>c</trunc> your car's <vocal desc="laugh"/> pretty bad what's it you know what's it like around the back? he said oh I don't even know I haven't even looked you know so</u>
<u n="77" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0510">uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just thought he's check his out and then go and check his out round the back as well</u>
<u n="79" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="80" who="S0510">and has he goes round he says oh he says er right so you've not seen the back then? he says no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0510">and he said oh you might wanna see this you've you've kind of got a visitor</u>
<u n="83" who="S0509">oh my god</u>
<u n="84" who="S0510">and it was unbelievable right? this deer what had actually happened was it had hit the centre of the the windscreen at the front it actually gone through the window right? over to the passenger side the passenger side you know the headrest was completely flattened down where the entry point had been the deer had come into the car passed the driver's head</u>
<u n="85" who="S0509">what?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0510">right? driver hadn't even been aware</u>
<u n="87" who="S0509">what?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0510">and deposited itself in the boot in the hatchback so as</u>
<u n="89" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0510">uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone round the back and there is literally a deer lying in the boot of his hatchback</u>
<u n="91" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="92" who="S0510">it looks just looks like it's resting it's just like you know bundled up</u>
<u n="93" who="S0509">jesus</u>
<u n="94" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it doesn't look as if it's got any mark on it on the side that you can see</u>
<u n="95" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0510">but clearly it has and and that's where it ended up in this guy's flipping <vocal desc="laugh"/> boot</u>
<u n="97" who="S0509">oh my god</u>
<u n="98" who="S0510">so er</u>
<u n="99" who="S0509">terrifying</u>
<u n="100" who="S0510">anyway as all this was happening the erm the police had arrived cos the one of the the other motorists had obviously called the police and an ambulance cos they'd while they'd been talking they'd seen their car go past but not with the sirens going but with flashing lights</u>
<u n="101" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0510">and an also an ambulance again flashing lights but no sirens and uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought oh yeah I wonder if that's for us <vocal desc="laugh"/> so then they started coming back up the other way slowing down and uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said er have <trunc>y</trunc> have you been called about a deer that jumped out? and they said yeah cos and by this point they'd pulled the car over into the side</u>
<u n="103" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0510">and you couldn't really see what you know what had happened so the police got out ambulance got out you know and er did their thing guy was insistent he was fine he wasn't</u>
<u n="105" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0510">you know gonna go to the <trunc>hosp</trunc>hospital but er they said well do you wanna call erm do you wanna call somebody to come and collect you?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0510">so that's what he did erm but yeah unbelievable the you know</u>
<u n="111" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0510">one that he'd got out with just a few scratches really</u>
<u n="113" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0510">and two what happened to the deer</u>
<u n="115" who="S0509">that is ridiculous isn't it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0510">it's crazy</u>
<u n="117" who="S0509">god</u>
<u n="118" who="S0510">and er thankfully as well you know so they were both okay poor deer</u>
<u n="119" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0510">dear dear the old deer but erm <pause dur="short"/> his uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s car is in at the garage at the moment thankfully he was fully comp and also he had no claims protection as well so that means that he used to pay an extra dividend if you like every or premium rather every year to protect his no claims so he could have up to three claims against it and still retain</u>
<u n="121" who="S0509" trans="overlap">retain the no claims bonus <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0510">yeah so he's</u>
<u n="123" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's a bit of a weird one isn't it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it is yeah I mean if you've got the money to do it you you know jolly dee and all that but most of us probably haven't erm but so he's getting all the work done and and that but you know I think the other guy from what he was saying as well was fully insured</u>
<u n="125" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="126" who="S0510">erm but if he'd have had third party fire and theft which a lot of people do</u>
<u n="127" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="128" who="S0510">it wouldn't have covered you and this guy's car obviously was a write-off a complete write-off</u>
<u n="129" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0510">er</u>
<u n="131" who="S0509">oh my god if it had come through yeah clearly <vocal desc="laugh"/> if it had come through</u>
<u n="132" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0509">the the screen</u>
<u n="134" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0509">and</u>
<u n="136" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0509" trans="overlap">all that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0510">yeah oh</u>
<u n="139" who="S0509" whoConfidence="low">sorry yeah I've managed</u>
<u n="140" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh that looks good</u>
<u n="141" who="S0509" trans="overlap">to thread it on now</u>
<u n="142" who="S0510">oh yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0509" trans="overlap">got all the cards on</u>
<u n="144" who="S0510">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="145" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="146" who="S0510">so you've got the erm the royal family on one side <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0509">yeah and then</u>
<u n="148" who="S0510" trans="overlap">king queen and jack</u>
<u n="149" who="S0509">and then you've got the spades cos in Alice in Wonderland the spades er they're they're characters in it so I <trunc>ch</trunc>chose ones that were characters</u>
<u n="150" who="S0510">oh superb yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0509">and erm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0510" trans="overlap">so the Queen of Hearts obviously does the croquet on the lawn doesn't she?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0509">yes she does</u>
<u n="154" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is it the Queen of Hearts isn't it?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0509" trans="overlap">she's scary</u>
<u n="156" who="S0510">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0509">yeah actually I'm not sure the oh it's cos it's the knave the jack is the knave isn't it?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0510">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="159" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0509">and then the knave is in trouble</u>
<u n="162" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="163" who="S0509">and then the king is just tries to calm down his wife and tells them to <trunc>s</trunc> not behead the people the queen says to behead basically</u>
<u n="164" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah cos she's</u>
<u n="165" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="166" who="S0510">having a hissy fit so yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0509">there's a lot of that going on but yeah so that's all good now</u>
<u n="170" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh they look really good so what have you what er chess pieces have you got in there? the queen</u>
<u n="171" who="S0509">the queen the king and the knight cos the knights are both characters they have a little fight in Alice in Wonderland</u>
<u n="172" who="S0510">oh excellent</u>
<u n="173" who="S0509">yeah so that's pretty much done now I've managed</u>
<u n="174" who="S0510">uhu</u>
<u n="175" who="S0509">to fix that king card which is good</u>
<u n="176" who="S0510">oh good</u>
<u n="177" who="S0509">and er yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0510">so are you just gonna thread them on to your costume?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0509">yes I am</u>
<u n="180" who="S0510">I like the way that idea you had with the chains is brilliant</u>
<u n="181" who="S0509">it <trunc>do</trunc> it looks quite good doesn't it?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0510">oh yeah it looks terrific</u>
<u n="183" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I need to pull them in a bit but we'll have to sort that out</u>
<u n="184" who="S0510" trans="overlap">pull pull them in a bit?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0509">oh shorten them</u>
<u n="186" who="S0510">oh yeah <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0509" trans="overlap">really gotta do it right as well so that it doesn't wanna go</u>
<u n="188" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="189" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0510">with the with the hoop on the end could you not</u>
<u n="191" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0510">just put the apron erm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0509">string?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0510">string through the loop?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0509">is that not what I'm doing?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0510">oh is it?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0509">the keyrings</u>
<u n="198" who="S0510">oh yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0509">that's that's what they're there to</u>
<u n="200" who="S0510">oh I see I couldn't see that right</u>
<u n="201" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0509">and then I'll tie them on but I I've gotta work on shortening them first cos they're too long at the moment</u>
<u n="204" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0509">so that's the next thing oh I haven't just knocked off a card I haven't that's good I thought I'd broken a card then</u>
<u n="206" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0509">but erm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0510">can you not <trunc>sh</trunc>shorten them by what you did last night? which was to hook up at</u>
<u n="209" who="S0509">er mm sort of</u>
<u n="210" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="211" who="S0509">basically when I was hooking it before I was hooking into the ring that one of the cards is on so</u>
<u n="212" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0509">so the card was then like flipping about and going in the wrong way</u>
<u n="214" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="215" who="S0509">so I've gotta just have a play with them now but that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="217" who="S0509">just do that</u>
<u n="218" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="219" who="S0509">but erm yeah so I had my singing lesson earlier</u>
<u n="220" who="S0510">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0509">yes</u>
<u n="222" who="S0510">mm sorry can I just not you know</u>
<u n="223" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0510">just take in the the brilliance</u>
<u n="225" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0510">of of these sort of chains that you're gonna have round your costume? that's so good do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to drill</u>
<u n="227" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="228" who="S0510" trans="overlap">erm the chess pieces?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0509">he's just got everything <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has</u>
<u n="230" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is he's</u>
<u n="231" who="S0509" trans="overlap">he's got</u>
<u n="232" who="S0510">he's steampunk <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah he's</u>
<u n="233" who="S0509">steampunk <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0510">oh I see I didn't notice that before on your cards what you hole-punch them with</u>
<u n="235" who="S0509">yeah the little</u>
<u n="236" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that was a good idea</u>
<u n="237" who="S0509" trans="overlap">butterfly hole-punch oh it was cos I couldn't find a normal hole-punch</u>
<u n="238" who="S0510">but do you know what? that probably works out better cos it gives you more room for manoeuvre with the keyrings going in doesn't it? if you'd have had</u>
<u n="239" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0510">a little hole there it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0509">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="242" who="S0510">it would have made it</u>
<u n="243" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I didn't think of that</u>
<u n="244" who="S0510">more tricky yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0509">alright that's shortened it a bit anyway erm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0510">yeah so the chess pieces how much were they? were</u>
<u n="247" who="S0509">oh it was like two pound from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0510">right and they're proper wooden ones aren't they?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0509">yeah they are</u>
<u n="250" who="S0510">that was cool in fact do you know what? they look a bit like the ones that I got from that charity shop don't they? that we use</u>
<u n="251" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0510">they're pretty similar aren't they?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0510">must be kind of like a bog-standard</u>
<u n="255" who="S0509">design</u>
<u n="256" who="S0510">design yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0509">yeah oh yeah this this clip just doesn't quite hook through but I have another idea</u>
<u n="258" who="S0510">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so we'll get to that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="261" who="S0509">yeah anyway costume</u>
<u n="262" who="S0510">costume yeah so it it's looking fab</u>
<u n="263" who="S0509">thank you</u>
<u n="264" who="S0510" trans="overlap">what about the hat? you have you finished with the hat?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh nearly I've just gotta stick the things with the buttons on in place</u>
<u n="266" who="S0510">oh have you stuck on the buttons? have you used er</u>
<u n="267" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0510">this glue gun?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0509">no I've just used normal PVA</u>
<u n="270" who="S0510">did you?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0509">and they they they've stuck that's what's</u>
<u n="272" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's amazing PVA isn't it?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it's a miracle</u>
<u n="274" who="S0510" trans="overlap">such a versatile glue</u>
<u n="275" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0510">and it's so cheap as well</u>
<u n="277" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0510">and it doesn't stick your fingers together like superglue</u>
<u n="279" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> quite</u>
<u n="280" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0509">indeed</u>
<u n="282" who="S0510">or burn you like a hot glue gun</u>
<u n="283" who="S0509">yeah oh when I was bringing that <unclear/> earlier</u>
<u n="284" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0509">I accidentally tapped some some hot ash onto my hand</u>
<u n="286" who="S0510">ouch oh dear oh</u>
<u n="287" who="S0509">do you know what else I burnt myself on the other day?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0510">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0509">I you know I've got my black trousers?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0509">the ones grandad got me?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0510" trans="overlap">the zippy ones yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0509">yeah and they've got like a button as well</u>
<u n="294" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0509">I took them out of the dryer</u>
<u n="296" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="297" who="S0509">and I touched a button by accident</u>
<u n="298" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="299" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and it was so hot that it burnt me</u>
<u n="300" who="S0510"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh my gosh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0509">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="302" who="S0510" trans="overlap">did you</u>
<u n="303" who="S0509" trans="overlap">if you can see it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0510">have are you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's just that little tiny mark there</u>
<u n="306" who="S0510" trans="overlap">as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0509">it's like a tiny one</u>
<u n="308" who="S0510" trans="overlap">only well tiny</u>
<u n="309" who="S0509">so that's okay</u>
<u n="310" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0510">how's the Bio-<trunc>Oi</trunc>oil going?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0509">I dunno</u>
<u n="314" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or your other one?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0509">I think it's alright</u>
<u n="316" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yeah it looks like it's faded</u>
<u n="317" who="S0509">do you think?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0509">I think it'll go with time hopefully <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah definitely</u>
<u n="321" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0510">so anyway sorry I cut you off earlier you were saying about you</u>
<u n="323" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh singing</u>
<u n="324" who="S0510">you had your singing lesson</u>
<u n="325" who="S0509">yes I did it was it it's hard but</u>
<u n="326" who="S0510">is it?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0509">it's good you know mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0509">I'm picking it up</u>
<u n="330" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0509">yeah she's she's a very nice teacher I think she's</u>
<u n="332" who="S0510" trans="overlap">what's her background do you know?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0509">er no I don't</u>
<u n="334" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0509">but she she says that she's taught quite a lot of opera singers</u>
<u n="336" who="S0510">oh really? well there's plenty round these parts what with <anon type="place"/> not being that far</u>
<u n="337" who="S0509"><anon type="place"/>? what's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0510" trans="overlap">have you heard of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="340" who="S0510">oh it's like a really famous erm you know operatic er well place where operas take place theatre <anon type="place"/> theatre</u>
<u n="341" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="342" who="S0510">it's not</u>
<u n="343" who="S0509" trans="overlap">is it <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0510">no it's further along from there it's nearer <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0509">okay</u>
<u n="346" who="S0510">erm and yeah but it's very well known in opera <trunc>c</trunc>circles so we're not</u>
<u n="347" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="348" who="S0510">that far from there really here</u>
<u n="349" who="S0509">right er</u>
<u n="350" who="S0510" trans="overlap">did you did you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to? that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="352" who="S0510">used to be involved with</u>
<u n="353" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I did know that</u>
<u n="354" who="S0510">oh you did?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0509">I think you told me</u>
<u n="358" who="S0510">uhu</u>
<u n="359" who="S0509">I remember</u>
<u n="360" who="S0510" trans="overlap">do you know what? she was saying last week when we were in rehearsals er I wonder oh actually we were doing a live point by that point erm just waiting for the play to open she was saying how much she missed her opera</u>
<u n="361" who="S0509">really?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0510">she's got she's got such a lovely music I did tell her about our Pale Shadows experience and</u>
<u n="365" who="S0509">oh yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0510" trans="overlap">sort of that's</u>
<u n="367" who="S0509" trans="overlap">is that what it was called?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0510">I'm sure it was Pale <trunc>Sha</trunc> Pale Shadows</u>
<u n="369" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I don't remember what it was called</u>
<u n="370" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or pale fire or something</u>
<u n="371" who="S0509">that was just awful wasn't it?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0510" trans="overlap">now what were the what were the name of the erm the Greek er <pause dur="short"/> oh it was it was all based around Greek mythology wasn't it? or am I getting that?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0509">oh I hope not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0510">well what what were the</u>
<u n="375" who="S0509" trans="overlap">dunno</u>
<u n="376" who="S0510">cos you knew the characters didn't you?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0509">oh they probably oh was it Shakespeare? no</u>
<u n="378" who="S0510">no</u>
<u n="379" who="S0509">unless it maybe it was</u>
<u n="380" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="381" who="S0509">Greek</u>
<u n="382" who="S0510" trans="overlap">the that that one</u>
<u n="383" who="S0509">I don't remember knowing the characters</u>
<u n="384" who="S0510">well you knew the story of the guy on when you know going to the island and the lover</u>
<u n="385" who="S0509">oh it was Greek myth cos it was Calypso</u>
<u n="386" who="S0510">Calypso okay</u>
<u n="387" who="S0509">I think it was Calypso</u>
<u n="388" who="S0510">uhu yeah that rings a bell well I'm amazed you'd forgotten I mean it was mind you was so far removed probably from anything</u>
<u n="389" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it was just so bad I've obviously</u>
<u n="390" who="S0510" trans="overlap">there was this</u>
<u n="391" who="S0509">blocked it out of my memory probably</u>
<u n="392" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah but I did say to her I you know <pause dur="short"/> I said you know we did try but it was</u>
<u n="393" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but we failed <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0510">it yeah we failed and they just seemed to take an inordinant amount of time really to just play out a story that seemed pretty basic</u>
<u n="395" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0510">er and just sort of really drag it out and it was the editing techniques as well wasn't it?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0509">oh yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0510" trans="overlap">using the film</u>
<u n="399" who="S0509">and it was all like weird</u>
<u n="400" who="S0510">it was very repetitive</u>
<u n="401" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's really descriptive isn't it? and it had that weird like background</u>
<u n="402" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0509">thing going on all the time</u>
<u n="404" who="S0510">yeah there was some really bad green screen stuff that</u>
<u n="405" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0510">they kind of</u>
<u n="407" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's it</u>
<u n="408" who="S0510">put on layered onto it but it it was just so unimaginative and</u>
<u n="409" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0510">and</u>
<u n="411" who="S0509">and it was supposed to be this like amazing thing</u>
<u n="412" who="S0510">mm mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but it wasn't</u>
<u n="414" who="S0510">yes yeah they did build it up in the the press didn't they? but they</u>
<u n="415" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0510">I guess that's what we're talking about really <vocal desc="laugh"/> isn't it? it's like with these things</u>
<u n="417" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's the whole point yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0510">but erm I can't say this is what I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know cos she's so passionate about opera and</u>
<u n="419" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know the all these er I I can't say that I've ever found myself getting really excited about you know an opera erm partly because or or just musically you know what it is it's just doesn't float my boat really</u>
<u n="421" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="422" who="S0510" trans="overlap">erm I said to her you know I'm probably a complete heathen and er you know I've got no cultural kind of kudos whatsoever but erm I just don't get it</u>
<u n="423" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0510">er er you know it doesn't help it's in another language clearly</u>
<u n="425" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0510">but even with subtitles you know</u>
<u n="427" who="S0509">I mean it's just I think it's</u>
<u n="428" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0509">it's a very specific thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0510">yeah but it just seems to be like oh just milking it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0509">melodrama darling</u>
<u n="432" who="S0510">yes darling totally <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm anyway your poor erm singing teacher maybe she can introduce us to some of the delights of</u>
<u n="433" who="S0509" trans="overlap">my poor singing teacher? why is she?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know she <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="435" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="436" who="S0510">if she could hear what I was saying</u>
<u n="437" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0510">now about opera I mean I'm probably maligning her you know and and everybody else that likes opera er by saying what I've just said but</u>
<u n="439" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0510">erm hey-ho that's life <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> deal with it</u>
<u n="442" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0509">tough</u>
<u n="444" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so yeah <trunc>th</trunc> your your you're you you're really enjoying it she's a good</u>
<u n="445" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0510">teacher is she?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah she is</u>
<u n="448" who="S0510">and how is she good? <trunc>h</trunc><trunc>h</trunc>how is she?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I'm not very good at this am I? er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> under the spotlight</u>
<u n="451" who="S0509">she just</u>
<u n="452" who="S0510" trans="overlap">she's no you I've obviously got my interview head on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she just sort of <pause dur="short"/> and she's like she's quite like determined about it but then she'll go oh if you don't if if I'm pushing you too hard or whatever or you just</u>
<u n="454" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0509">need to take a break just tell me just tell me and I I know I'm quite</u>
<u n="456" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0509">like a <vocal desc="laugh"/> she <trunc>sai</trunc> what did she say? she said slave driver today and I'm like</u>
<u n="458" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0509">no it's fine but</u>
<u n="460" who="S0510">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0509">she's just very sort of conscientious I suppose</u>
<u n="462" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0509">but at the same time quite sort of let's get this done</u>
<u n="464" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0509" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="466" who="S0510">yeah mm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0509">which is nice</u>
<u n="468" who="S0510">that's good that sounds just like you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0509">yeah the <pause dur="short"/> the did I say like the the pitching bits are harder? the</u>
<u n="472" who="S0510" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="473" who="S0509">the pitch that's that's the harder bit <trunc>m</trunc> trying to get the right notes I can kind of do the I've got some of the right technique I'm quite good at not using my throat which is very important cos otherwise</u>
<u n="474" who="S0510" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0509">you destroy your throat</u>
<u n="476" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and er yeah and like the exercises cos I've done them like quite a few times since I've seen her</u>
<u n="478" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0509">she was like really pleased with how I was doing them and it was like</u>
<u n="480" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="481" who="S0509">yeah okay they're really good</u>
<u n="482" who="S0510">oh excellent</u>
<u n="483" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but it's <vocal desc="laugh"/> just getting the right notes now</u>
<u n="484" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0509">but she seems quite confident that she can transform me into an excellent singer</u>
<u n="486" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="487" who="S0509">that's always nice</u>
<u n="488" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could be singing in</u>
<u n="489" who="S0509" trans="overlap">we have to do</u>
<u n="490" who="S0510">daddy's band before you know it</u>
<u n="491" who="S0509">oh no thank you</u>
<u n="492" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0509">what were we what are they called? I wanna say scales and they're not scales they're little</u>
<u n="494" who="S0510">no? you sure they're not scales?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0509" trans="overlap">bits on the piano they're not scales</u>
<u n="496" who="S0510">no?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0509">they're definitely not</u>
<u n="498" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="499" who="S0509">you do sort of</u>
<u n="500" who="S0510" trans="overlap">little stanzas?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="502" who="S0510">no?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0509">they're like gaps between the notes and there's like thirds and fifths</u>
<u n="504" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="505" who="S0509">and they have a name daddy'll know it</u>
<u n="506" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="507" who="S0509">I'm sure</u>
<u n="508" who="S0510">for sure yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0509">oh what are they called? oh it's gonna bug me now</u>
<u n="510" who="S0510">mm where's Mr Google when you need him?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0509">oh never mind <unclear/> erm what are they? I can't think of it</u>
<u n="512" who="S0510">keys?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="514" who="S0510">no? did we say that?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's like no it's <pause dur="short"/> it's like it would be like <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0510">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0509"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0509">they you go higher and higher and the little</u>
<u n="520" who="S0510">yes I know what you mean but can't for the life of me</u>
<u n="521" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="522" who="S0510">think what it's called yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right</u>
<u n="525" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah those they're harder it's always easier if you like sing some first though and then I can figure out</u>
<u n="526" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="527" who="S0509">erm yeah but</u>
<u n="528" who="S0510">the scale mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0509">it's not a scale</u>
<u n="530" who="S0510">but it's not a scale</u>
<u n="531" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0510">but mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0510">is it like the starting point it's the not most difficult bit? or</u>
<u n="535" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="536" who="S0510">no?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0509">it's just get it's actually the gaps that are the most difficult bit</u>
<u n="538" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="539" who="S0509">cos you have to figure out oh I nearly had the word then <pause dur="short"/> yeah anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0509">and lower notes cos like I I have quite a high pitched voice</u>
<u n="542" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0509">so lower notes I'm like wow okay like this <unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0509">and I can't find the note</u>
<u n="546" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="547" who="S0509">but erm yeah and then we were doing one of the songs that I'd sent to her so we were working on that and like</u>
<u n="548" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="549" who="S0509">going through a couple of verses of that</u>
<u n="550" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0509">and then we overran but like ten minutes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0510">oh that's why you were late</u>
<u n="553" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well at least you were having fun</u>
<u n="555" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0510">didn't charge you any extra?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="558" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0509">she was just like oh my god my boyfriend's picking me up I need to leave <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so do you think she might be an opera singer herself?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0509">no cos what she was saying was she used to teach a lot of opera singers because she had this technique that was helpful to them</u>
<u n="562" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="563" who="S0509">this particular technique</u>
<u n="564" who="S0510">right mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0509">she didn't say what it was</u>
<u n="566" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="567" who="S0509">but yeah god knows if this is gonna work yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="569" who="S0509">have I put it on the wrong side?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0510">no it looks like the right side well the end bit does</u>
<u n="571" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah it is</u>
<u n="572" who="S0510">anyway</u>
<u n="573" who="S0509">yeah it's fine</u>
<u n="574" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="576" who="S0510">mm so what's the song again that you're doing with her that's your song?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0509">er it is what's it called? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0509">erm Panic Cord by Gabrielle <trunc>Apli</trunc>Aplin that's it</u>
<u n="580" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="581" who="S0509">it's a good song</u>
<u n="582" who="S0510">and has she chosen one for you as well?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="584" who="S0510">or do you just oh?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0509">I just get to choose them</u>
<u n="586" who="S0510">it's it's not like the naked choir you know</u>
<u n="587" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="588" who="S0510" trans="overlap">where you choose one the teacher chooses one</u>
<u n="589" who="S0509">well and your rival chooses one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0509">no yeah so she's that that was good cos then she was like correcting the odd specific things so it was like oh</u>
<u n="594" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="595" who="S0509">and she was like you think it's higher than it is because</u>
<u n="596" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="597" who="S0509">the singer is doing this thing where she has like a really breathy voice</u>
<u n="598" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="599" who="S0509">and so it sounds more high pitched than it actually is so you're going higher than you need to</u>
<u n="600" who="S0510">oh interesting</u>
<u n="601" who="S0509">I know yeah yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="603" who="S0509">it was it's good</u>
<u n="604" who="S0510">so you're doing various breathing techniques as well then? is that</u>
<u n="605" who="S0509" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="606" who="S0510">part of your warmups and?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0509" trans="overlap">breathing wise yeah yeah it's <pause dur="short"/> with breathing it is a lot of breathing but it's all just to do with your diaphragm basically</u>
<u n="608" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm uhu</u>
<u n="609" who="S0509">and I'm quite good at using that now <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not actually that hard cos you just sort of if you just contract the muscle then you're using it so you can make yourself</u>
<u n="610" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="611" who="S0509">do it</u>
<u n="612" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="613" who="S0509">which is</u>
<u n="614" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="615" who="S0509">which is good oh there's the chains is that better?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0510">oh yeah yeah turn round let's have a look</u>
<u n="617" who="S0509">and you just tie them still but</u>
<u n="618" who="S0510">yeah and and the other side so it can see the other side yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0509">oh oh be careful</u>
<u n="620" who="S0510">sorry I was just sort of adjusting that</u>
<u n="621" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh yeah the apron</u>
<u n="622" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's not too tight is it? no no it's</u>
<u n="623" who="S0509">mm?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="625" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="626" who="S0510">I dunno I I I think they do better lower down have a look in the</u>
<u n="627" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="628" who="S0510">get the mirror</u>
<u n="629" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I don't like no it's fine I don't like them lower down</u>
<u n="630" who="S0510">well I'm not saying as low down as they were but I</u>
<u n="631" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I like them like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0510">oh you've got the mirror there haven't you?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0510">oh well it's your costume darling if you like them</u>
<u n="635" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh one of them's lower than the other one though that's significantly lower</u>
<u n="636" who="S0510">is it?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0509">yeah it's just cos it's is it caught? no oh oh</u>
<u n="638" who="S0510"><unclear/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0509">oh wait don't worry I'll sort it</u>
<u n="640" who="S0510">oh it's different yeah I see what you mean</u>
<u n="641" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they're probably on the wrong keyring that's why</u>
<u n="642" who="S0510">uhu</u>
<u n="643" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0510">all is revealed</u>
<u n="645" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's so complicated</u>
<u n="646" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0510">so I haven't got too much sewing to do on that it's just that little edge</u>
<u n="649" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no you've just got the little last bit to do</u>
<u n="650" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0509">and then it's done right</u>
<u n="652" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="653" who="S0509">is that right?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0510">oh yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0509">so that</u>
<u n="656" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that looks more like it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's more balanced</u>
<u n="657" who="S0509">yeah it's gone a bit off though</u>
<u n="658" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="659" who="S0509">I'll figure it out</u>
<u n="660" who="S0510">it's not the pockets giving the illusion of it being off is it?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="662" who="S0510">are the pockets a bit off or something?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no it's not that</u>
<u n="664" who="S0510">no?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0509">it's definitely it's all really off</u>
<u n="666" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's not my sewing work?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0509">no you you're all fine</u>
<u n="668" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0509">it's just me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's only my problem</u>
<u n="672" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0509">I'll figure it out why yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it doesn't look that</u>
<u n="675" who="S0509">it it is <vocal desc="laugh"/> anyway</u>
<u n="676" who="S0510">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> well you can work on it anyway can't you?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0509">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0510">okay so what am I doing now? I'm just sewing up that side</u>
<u n="679" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0510">and then you're getting</u>
<u n="681" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they do look the same length though</u>
<u n="682" who="S0510" trans="overlap">they do</u>
<u n="683" who="S0509">don't they?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0510">yeah they're the same</u>
<u n="685" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they're not</u>
<u n="686" who="S0510">you see</u>
<u n="687" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah that one is</u>
<u n="688" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> different</u>
<u n="689" who="S0509">that one's like that one's like two links longer or something</u>
<u n="690" who="S0510">ah right well it could be all the difference</u>
<u n="691" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0510">er I guess in terms of where you're putting it whether you're putting the longer one first behind as well you know if it's overlapping it might change the distance a bit</u>
<u n="693" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm trying to understand what you're saying</u>
<u n="694" who="S0510">yeah sorry</u>
<u n="695" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and failing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0510">I'm not explaining myself very well am I? erm so how are they coming together at the back there? let's have a look</u>
<u n="697" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that one threads that one threads on first then that one</u>
<u n="698" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0509">so it's like that</u>
<u n="700" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well it shouldn't make that much difference really should it?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="702" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's only a a little ring</u>
<u n="703" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0510" trans="overlap">above as it were</u>
<u n="705" who="S0509">I'll sort it out at a later date</u>
<u n="706" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="707" who="S0509">I'll probably sort my erm hat now</u>
<u n="708" who="S0510">oh that'll be good</u>
<u n="709" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0510">you've <trunc>u</trunc> you've used all your chess pieces there have you? have you not got any spare?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0509">oh I've got loads spare</u>
<u n="712" who="S0510">oh are you gonna put any in your hat?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="714" who="S0510">so you're just gonna have proper Mad Hatter</u>
<u n="715" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0510">sort of what what do you call those?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0509">top hat</u>
<u n="718" who="S0510">I know it's a top hat</u>
<u n="719" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0510">no you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0510">I know it's top hat <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="723" who="S0509">well <vocal desc="laugh"/> well what was this then?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I didn't think it was a bowler for goodness sake</u>
<u n="725" who="S0509" trans="overlap">what was the gesture?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or a witch's hat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0509">well what? come on then</u>
<u n="728" who="S0510">er the rods that come out</u>
<u n="729" who="S0509">oh <trunc>ha</trunc>hatpins</u>
<u n="730" who="S0510">oh hatpins thank you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0509">that's just as simple as <unclear>thinking of</unclear> top hat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="733" who="S0509">and totally <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't go giving yourself airs and graces mummy</u>
<u n="734" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="735" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0510">well it's not every day I wear a hatpin but there again it could be said it's not every day I wear a top hat either</u>
<u n="737" who="S0509">when have you ever? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="738" who="S0510">well quite <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0509">I thought you were gonna come out with some story then</u>
<u n="740" who="S0510">oh no well</u>
<u n="741" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh well when I used to go clubbing in London</u>
<u n="742" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no although having said that at the Camden Palace</u>
<u n="743" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0510">that wouldn't have surprised me if seeing somebody walk in in the eighties with a top hat</u>
<u n="745" who="S0509">cool</u>
<u n="746" who="S0510">erm you know rocking a top hat</u>
<u n="747" who="S0509">have you ever heard the song erm I Wish I was <trunc>pr</trunc> Punk Rocker?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0510">oh yeah that rings a bell</u>
<u n="749" who="S0509">it's a good song you sound you looked so disgusted by it</u>
<u n="750" who="S0510">er I'm no I'm I'm just</u>
<u n="751" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> I wish I was a punk rocker with flowers in my hair <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0510" trans="overlap">in my hair I think I've got it erm what's her name?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's really good</u>
<u n="754" who="S0510">it's</u>
<u n="755" who="S0509">I dunno what the name is</u>
<u n="756" who="S0510">I'm sure I've got her CD</u>
<u n="757" who="S0509">cos I I heard a cover of it and it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0510">yeah no it's it is good it is good it she's sort of almost like a folky singer isn't she?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0510">but she kind of has a different take on it a bit of a twist oh what was her name?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0509">the worst thing is listening to a cover before listening to the actual song and then the cover is better</u>
<u n="762" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0509">it's happened quite a few times to me</u>
<u n="764" who="S0510">really?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0509">oh yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0510">blimey <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0509">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it is a good song</u>
<u n="768" who="S0510">yeah I'm still struggling to think who it is but I'm just gonna have to let that one go</u>
<u n="769" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0510">sorry</u>
<u n="771" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I was thinking earlier when you were looking erm on Google I can't remember what oh you were looking up the Camden Palace and you were like oh I've gotta check whether it's the same place</u>
<u n="772" who="S0510">uhu</u>
<u n="773" who="S0509">er and I thought what would she be doing right now if you didn't have Google?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0510">I know well this is it you'd be <trunc>ri</trunc></u>
<u n="775" who="S0509" trans="overlap">well it was like would</u>
<u n="776" who="S0510">you'd be ringing up a friend</u>
<u n="777" who="S0509" trans="overlap">as</u>
<u n="778" who="S0510">or</u>
<u n="779" who="S0509">I was gonna say like would you ring up the what's it called now? the <trunc>Ko</trunc></u>
<u n="780" who="S0510">the Koko</u>
<u n="781" who="S0509" trans="overlap">Koko?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ring up the Koko and be like did you used to be called Camden Palace?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah or ringing up the place</u>
<u n="785" who="S0509" trans="overlap">go to the local library what would?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I know quite</u>
<u n="787" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and then you and then you but then it's like is it a good thing that you is it a bad thing because you remove that element of human interaction? or is it a good thing because it means like <trunc>i</trunc>if you had to go looking for that information would you bother</u>
<u n="788" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="789" who="S0509">to find it out?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0510">mm well you see the thing is</u>
<u n="791" who="S0509" trans="overlap">is it a good thing that you actually do?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0510">the the thing is at this point in time you're thinking about because you know it's quick to access er would you bother kind of thing but you've got to put it in the right context because in those days that was the only way so therefore the time factor you wouldn't really think of it as being necessarily elongated to find out because that was the way you had nothing</u>
<u n="793" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0510">to kind of you know compare it to in a shorter framework whereas now we do</u>
<u n="795" who="S0509">but do you think you would have bothered to like look that up if it hadn't been <trunc>easil</trunc> like easily</u>
<u n="796" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="797" who="S0509">accessible to you?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0510">yeah well yeah I <vocal desc="misc"/> I dunno mm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0509">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0510">I probably personally I probably would have tried <trunc>ri</trunc> you know just ringing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because I used to go and just asking her if she knew</u>
<u n="801" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0510">cos I was curious because you know it depends on on how badly you want to know isn't it?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0510">like when I saw them in that place and I thought</u>
<u n="805" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0510">god that's got to be the Camden Palace</u>
<u n="807" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0510">and bearing in mind that it was a significant period of my life</u>
<u n="809" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0510">where I used to go there so I was quite passionate about it</u>
<u n="811" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and really enjoyed it so therefore I probably would</u>
<u n="813" who="S0509">right yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I'm just thinking it through I <trunc>pro</trunc> I probably</u>
<u n="815" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0510" trans="overlap">would because I'd want</u>
<u n="817" who="S0509">but</u>
<u n="818" who="S0510" trans="overlap">to know cos it <trunc>ha</trunc> held so many great memories for me and exciting times and fun times it's like</u>
<u n="819" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0510">is that still <trunc>goi</trunc> is that place</u>
<u n="821" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0510" trans="overlap">still there? you know</u>
<u n="823" who="S0509">but then would you do it with other things I guess</u>
<u n="824" who="S0510">well exactly</u>
<u n="825" who="S0509" trans="overlap">is the question?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0510">you'd have to yeah it would all be in context really wouldn't it? as to</u>
<u n="827" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0510">how significant it was</u>
<u n="829" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="830" who="S0510">but it's an interesting point though</u>
<u n="831" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0510">you know and that whole thing about technology as well <pause dur="short"/> er about you know removing another layer of communication or interaction or</u>
<u n="833" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0510">the you know you know in some ways there are many there are many good things not in some ways but there are many good things about the access to information that we have now in terms of how it empowers us and kind of what what greater significance or what greater level of things we're able to do</u>
<u n="835" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0510" trans="overlap">because of it but also it does bring as you know its own drawbacks as well you know</u>
<u n="837" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh yeah I mean</u>
<u n="838" who="S0510" trans="overlap">kind of</u>
<u n="839" who="S0509">you you could debate that for ages the</u>
<u n="840" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well you</u>
<u n="841" who="S0509" trans="overlap">pros and cons of technology couldn't you?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0510">absolutely absolutely</u>
<u n="843" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="844" who="S0510">and I and I think erm something that's interesting for me actually is sort of when I was teaching IT erm and still to <trunc>th</trunc> to this present day really is how how little sometimes people check the veracity of the <trunc>informa</trunc> not the veracity</u>
<u n="845" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="846" who="S0510">you know er am I saying the right word? the <trunc>veraci</trunc></u>
<u n="847" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah the veracity</u>
<u n="848" who="S0510">of the information that they're looking at</u>
<u n="849" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0510">you know because so much of the stuff that you're looking at is self-published I mean Wikipedia being the greatest you know</u>
<u n="851" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0510">kind of example of that</u>
<u n="853" who="S0509" trans="overlap">the primary example</u>
<u n="854" who="S0510">and I can't tell you how many children you know and I mean and adults as well but when I was teaching</u>
<u n="855" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0510" trans="overlap">just take it as read that well if it's on Wiki it must be true you know</u>
<u n="857" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0510">and so I think er that's a dangerous thing as well you know</u>
<u n="859" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="860" who="S0510">that you aren't I mean l know like in history I remember primary sources and you know</u>
<u n="861" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0510">in research and that you I remember you coming home and sort of telling me about some of the research and methods that you were using so I guess in school there are other areas where people are questioning that and I certainly did in IT you know I'd ask</u>
<u n="863" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0510">the kids to well maybe you know think about the sources of information they're using for their own research for their projects</u>
<u n="865" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="866" who="S0510">and question that but I think we it's really easy to get lazy as well</u>
<u n="867" who="S0509">yeah definitely and yeah it <trunc>t</trunc> there was erm you know me and daddy have watched a few episodes of that David Gorman's Modern Life is Goodish?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0510">oh gosh no I didn't</u>
<u n="869" who="S0509">it's</u>
<u n="870" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is it it?</u>
<u n="871" who="S0509" trans="overlap">have you seen it?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0510">no I haven't</u>
<u n="873" who="S0509">it's if do you know what it's about?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0510">no I don't</u>
<u n="875" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0510">if it's Dave Gormon and anything where Dave Gormon's</u>
<u n="877" who="S0509" trans="overlap">Dave <trunc>Gor</trunc></u>
<u n="878" who="S0510" trans="overlap">gonna be good</u>
<u n="879" who="S0509">yeah and it's it's er he just goes on about all these different sort of things that are just not truthful online or just the weird things</u>
<u n="880" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0509">going on online and it's really interesting cos like he and and then he'll trick you as well</u>
<u n="882" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="883" who="S0509">and he'll go oh he he'll be talking <trunc>ab</trunc> he he kind of cos it's kind of comedy as well he'll be talking about</u>
<u n="884" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="885" who="S0509">oh there's all these names of celebrities where the domain names aren't taken and you can just like buy them and er and like they had some really weird ones well the weird ones like so there's like this Japanese punk band under some British celebrity minor celebrity's name</u>
<u n="886" who="S0510">uhu</u>
<u n="887" who="S0509">and then and then like everyone's laughing at it and then he goes through another couple and then he goes well actually none of this is true cos I've bought all these domain names and made them myself</u>
<u n="888" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0509">and we're all like</u>
<u n="890" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="891" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="892" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="893" who="S0509" trans="overlap">you know? you just can't</u>
<u n="894" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah right</u>
<u n="895" who="S0509">it makes you</u>
<u n="896" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="897" who="S0509">kind of go I can't trust anything</u>
<u n="898" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and he did this whole thing where he unravelled an entire sort of erm media campaign where it was this this story it was like a valentine story</u>
<u n="900" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="901" who="S0509">and it was about this woman dumping her boyfriend through like a you know in shops in like corner shops or garage stores you get the little</u>
<u n="902" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0509">advertising screens?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0509">er dumping her boyfriend through one of those on Valentine's Day</u>
<u n="906" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="907" who="S0509">and er he unravelled it all and it was actually just a media campaign like a marketing campaign</u>
<u n="908" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="909" who="S0509">done really <trunc>sa</trunc> subtly for Amstrad erm screens</u>
<u n="910" who="S0510">you're kidding?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0509">cos like he he was like looking at all these articles about it and like they'd all mentioned the price of the screens like twice</u>
<u n="912" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh ah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0509">and then he was going to the account of the person who originally tweeted it and he was like a CEO of a marketing company and then Alan Sugar had tweeted it</u>
<u n="914" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="915" who="S0509">and it was yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0510">and he <trunc>ac</trunc> managed to track it all back and</u>
<u n="917" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0510">uncover its real yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0509">yeah where it had come from and it was like oh yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0509">you just can't can't trust any of these stories</u>
<u n="922" who="S0510">yeah yeah but we do you know it's true we we kind of all fall into that trap of</u>
<u n="923" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0510" trans="overlap">just sort of taking things as read without</u>
<u n="925" who="S0509">without looking into it</u>
<u n="926" who="S0510" trans="overlap">questioning</u>
<u n="927" who="S0509">ourself</u>
<u n="928" who="S0510">yeah and <trunc>y</trunc> in more and more companies are getting you know more and more more and more erm looking at different ways via via social media via you know all these other digital means to get their</u>
<u n="929" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0510">message across</u>
<u n="931" who="S0509">oh yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="933" who="S0509">social media marketing</u>
<u n="934" who="S0510" trans="overlap">tagging or yeah</u>
<u n="935" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's massive</u>
<u n="936" who="S0510">yeah and make it you know viral in whatever way and <vocal desc="misc"/> yeah</u>
<u n="937" who="S0509">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0510">I'd love to see that programme so is it on the Iplayer?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0509">er it's on the Dave Iplayer thing</u>
<u n="940" who="S0510">I didn't even</u>
<u n="941" who="S0509" trans="overlap">Iplayer <unclear/></u>
<u n="942" who="S0510" trans="overlap">know we had the <trunc>d</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> Dave Iplayer</u>
<u n="943" who="S0509">we do</u>
<u n="944" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is that on that box that we got from Talktalk?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="947" who="S0509">it's sort of when you go to go to the Iplayer there's like <trunc>fi</trunc> there's like five or six other different players and Dave is one of them</u>
<u n="948" who="S0510">oh <trunc>go</trunc> well</u>
<u n="949" who="S0509">the selection I need to show you how to use this thing don't I? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> says a sixteen-year-old daughter to the former IT teacher</u>
<u n="951" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a bit worrying really</u>
<u n="953" who="S0509">well you you know you didn't you didn't do the TV managing</u>
<u n="954" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what remote controls?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0509" trans="overlap">department what am I even saying?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0510" trans="overlap">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="957" who="S0509">TV management department</u>
<u n="958" who="S0510">it's just you know</u>
<u n="959" who="S0509">you weren't a technician</u>
<u n="960" who="S0510">well actually I was cos that's what</u>
<u n="961" who="S0509" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0510">I went on to do after teaching I I was a technician wasn't I at the uni? an IT technician albeit in a</u>
<u n="963" who="S0509" trans="overlap">how did you do that?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="965" who="S0509">I remember when you were teaching saying how often you'd be going to the IT guys for help</u>
<u n="966" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but that's always the case though in any school erm the IT <trunc>depar</trunc> you know the IT technicians are are critical to oh gosh I anything running because often their networks are so poorly put together and patched together and there's so many different</u>
<u n="967" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="968" who="S0510"><trunc>varia</trunc>variables with student you know accounts and restrictions that they have on the network</u>
<u n="969" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="970" who="S0510">that that's why you end up going to the technicians half the time because either they haven't programmed something properly <vocal desc="laugh"/> or the user you know the the</u>
<u n="971" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="972" who="S0510">pupil or whatever has has got something major wrong erm in terms of their password or whatever so but</u>
<u n="973" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0510">yeah no I mean the the <trunc>I</trunc> to be honest the IT technician erm a job that I had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was a an agency job and it was very specific so I used to build erm computers</u>
<u n="975" who="S0509">yeah I remember</u>
<u n="976" who="S0510">yeah so it it wasn't you know you didn't need to know huge amounts about configurations and all the rest of it it was</u>
<u n="977" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="978" who="S0510">one specific set of rules if you like</u>
<u n="979" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="980" who="S0510">for setting up these computers building them installing drivers erm and then you know transferring the data from</u>
<u n="981" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="982" who="S0510" trans="overlap">one user's computer to another and just making sure it looked as it should do er and a lot of it also was to do with kind of customer interaction you know erm which is something that I've always enjoyed doing</u>
<u n="983" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0510">erm customer service because a lot of the people that you ended up doing their computers for didn't have a lot of IT knowledge so their starting point was really low down there so</u>
<u n="985" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0510">although they might have seen me as some kind of IT god guru</u>
<u n="987" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="988" who="S0510">I really only had a very specific set of</u>
<u n="989" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0510">information you know</u>
<u n="991" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that you needed to know to</u>
<u n="992" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and and but you know to them it was all smoke and mirrors you know it was kind of like wow you know this is amazing <vocal desc="laugh"/> but</u>
<u n="993" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="994" who="S0510">it is very limited but but it worked and you know the the</u>
<u n="995" who="S0509">yeah yeah it you did your job</u>
<u n="996" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I I did my job I got them what they wanted I rolled out you know a hundred and twenty different machines</u>
<u n="997" who="S0509"><trunc>jee</trunc></u>
<u n="998" who="S0510">for this the it was all just part of this specific contract so</u>
<u n="999" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0510">but yeah you know I mean when when you're you're at home and you've got a daughter that's willing to you know just sort of step in there and just go for it then you get a bit lazy don't you?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1004" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0509">okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0510" trans="overlap">cos like oh oh this isn't working oh</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1009" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1010" who="S0510">so really</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0509">you could do it</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0510">I well absolutely</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but it's just easier since I already know</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0510">mm and you're always very keen to jump in and help cos I think you see your parents as a bit you know IT degenerate <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0509">well I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh well that's good to know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1017" who="S0509">look you all have better phones than me</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0510">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1019" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so really</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh that looks good <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1021" who="S0509">well thank you yeah I've got the</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0509">the buttons in now and the er yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0510">oh look at that is that alright? I think</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0509">very slowly</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0510" trans="overlap">there we go pop it on can you move your top?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0509">er?</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0510">have you got your hair up?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0509">only half up</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0509">right <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1032" who="S0510">what are you doing to your?</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0509"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0510">how are you <vocal desc="laugh"/> how's it gonna stay? it looks fantastic</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's not gonna have to stay on all the time <trunc>hopeful</trunc> oh it does look good doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0509">do the button things look alright?</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0510">oh they look cool yeah you mean the hatpins <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1039" who="S0509">alright alright</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1041" who="S0509">I feel like they're a bit too straight up</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0510">well maybe they're a bit too evenly spaced or something you know</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0510" trans="overlap">a bit too symmetrical it's the Mad Hatter</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I've stuck them on with the tape now though so it's a bit late</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0510" trans="overlap">have you? oh</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0510">what sort of tape are we talking? gaffer or</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0509">Sellotape</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0510">oh well that's easy easily come off won't it?</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh but then it's then it's complicated</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0510">hey it's your hat do what you like</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0509">that's quite good isn't it with the feather?</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0510">yeah it looks good</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my god that looks awful <unclear/></u>
<u n="1056" who="S0510">put your pinny on</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0509">my pinafore yeah</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0509">also I need to get some tights from you <vocal desc="laugh"/> some tights</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh have you run out?</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0509">oh I might have some</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0510">I thought</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but they're they're not very wintery tights are they?</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0510">oh would you want some really dark ones?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0509">maybe</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0510" trans="overlap">do you do you want my</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah could you hold that a second please?</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0510" trans="overlap">patterned ones these ones?</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0509">yeah they would be fine could <trunc>y</trunc> take that?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah certainly madam</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0509">I know you're er you're a pro hat handler after your time at the stables</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah they were putting oh gosh yeah I used to have to do four hats a night didn't I?</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> four hats a night</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1075" who="S0509">sounds like some weird single by like</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1077" who="S0509">er</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0510">maybe <unclear/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0509" trans="overlap">a new start-ups band or something</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1081" who="S0509">there we go</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0510">there we go</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh that's good yeah I'm happy with that</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0510">yeah what footwear are you gonna have?</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0509">er I'm not sure I'm thinking of</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0509" trans="overlap">putting lots of polish on my old school shoes cos they're the most Alice in Wonderland <unclear/></u>
<u n="1088" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh that's true yeah you could do</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0509">I've got like double pockets</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1094" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you have indeed</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0509">I think it looks really good I'm really proud</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0510">oh yeah you certainly should be it's terrific</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1098" who="S0510">to think that you made that hat from scratch as well</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0509">I know</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0510">that is super-dupa</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0509">I'm in love with this feather</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0509">it's so massive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1104" who="S0510">that's yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0509">and it's kind of like if I take it off and it's all <unclear/> but if I put it on then</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0509">my costume is amazing</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0510">sure is are <trunc>ge</trunc> <trunc>wa</trunc>walk around a bit are you gonna be able to retain that hat? that's the only thing I'm worried about</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1112" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0509">just about I mean I'm probably not gonna keep it on most of the time but I can always sort of <pause dur="short"/> if I do that will anything fall off? no</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0510">no</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0509">that's amazing</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0510">superb</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0509">I feel like something'll probably fall off sooner or later though</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1119" who="S0509">but I can kind of walk around with it as long as I don't walk too fast is the thing or whack my head on the ceiling</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1122" who="S0510">er what about dancing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0509">I'm not gonna</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1125" who="S0509">I'm not gonna dance mummy I'm gonna sit there</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you're not gonna dance? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1127" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> maybe</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0510">it's it's an eighteenth birthday party for goodness' sake are you gonna wig out? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1129" who="S0509">wig out? wig out?</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1131" who="S0509">what is that?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1133" who="S0509">where does that come from? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1134" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well you don't use that vernacular</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1135" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1136" who="S0510">means like rock out really</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0509">wig out</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0510">wig out man</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1141" who="S0509">no I'm not planning on wigging out</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1143" who="S0509">maybe you could iron this for me at some point</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0510">yeah maybe yeah good</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0509" trans="overlap">cos it's quite it's quite un-ironed currently</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0510">oh it certainly is</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0509">you can see all the holes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1148" who="S0510">all the holes?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's quite bad isn't it? all the like the little creases like in lines going down</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0510">mind you it's had a lot of manhandling hasn't it?</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0509">yeah it's really good thank you</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0510">well you're welcome well it's a good starting point really you <trunc>ch</trunc> you know you that was a brilliant purchase</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0509">I'm so glad I found that cos I was like oh my god I'm <trunc>ne</trunc>never gonna find the pinafore</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0510">no I know</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and I did</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0510">and what was it? two pounds?</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0509" trans="overlap">two pounds yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0510" trans="overlap">crazy brand new</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0509">yeah sealed packet</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0509">I'll leave that with you to stitch the last couple of bits then</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah let me do that darling</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0509"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1166" who="S0510">see if I can find the old white cotton</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0509">oh I don't have any left</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0510">oh I think there was that little spool you know from the old from your sewing machine?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0509">okay you know what you can do for me on Friday?</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0510">what's that darling?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0509">you can tie this in a bow in my hair maybe</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yeah sure thing yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0509">yeah and how much will I need do you think? oh I haven't got scissors anyway so it doesn't matter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1174" who="S0510">there we <trunc>g</trunc> I might have some in my room</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh there's <trunc>s</trunc>some in here</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0510">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0509">there we go</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0510" trans="overlap">there we go <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0509" trans="overlap">how much ribbon?</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0510">er let's try it out</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0509" trans="overlap">do I okay</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0510" trans="overlap">so er try it out and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1183" who="S0509">okay I'll turn around</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0510">and oh push your your hair's gonna be much bunchier than that so if I get the whole</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0509" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0510">how are you doing it?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah I was gonna do it</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0510" trans="overlap">like it is there?</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0509" trans="overlap">in a style yeah</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0510">okay so alright then cool so do you want quite a big loop on it?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0509">I guess yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0510">yeah? okay</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0509">not like stupidly massive</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0510">right okay</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0509">but not tiny</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0510" trans="overlap">try not to be stupid</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1198" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1199" who="S0509">try not to be stupid</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0510">here we go whoop what about that ah?</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0509">that that feels about right yeah</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah? okay so I'll snip it if you</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0509">pass the scissors</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0510">off indeedy I'll snip it along there</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0509" trans="overlap">just don't chop my hair off instead</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0510">er no</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1208" who="S0510">there we go that's that done</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0509" trans="overlap">thank you I read my ten chapters of Jane Eyre today</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0510">oh well done you</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh but I've gotta write an eight hundred word essay on them</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0509">which is less good</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know you know how much you love writing once you get into the swing of it</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> eight hundred word what's that? er two A4 two sides of A4?</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0509">oh I don't know any more</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0510">do you not?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0509" trans="overlap">gotta be typed so</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0509">probably no more than that</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0510">do you think?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I'm like two hundred and fifty words a page so like three sides of <trunc>A</trunc></u>
<u n="1224" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh well yeah okay yeah</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0509">two</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0510">what?</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0509">four hundred words on a page is a lot isn't it?</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0510">well it depends how big the page is no I did say A4 didn't I?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah you did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0510">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was certainly</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I've got small handwriting</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0510">yeah it yeah I'd I'd be hard pressed with my the size of my writing actually</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0510">yeah how many lines are there? about twenty-three a sheet of A4?</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0509">I dunno I've got one with like thirty</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0510">have you?</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0509">and I write actually I probably do three hundred words a page but it</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0509">the thing is you've got spaces for paragraph breaks cos I'm like ten words a line basically</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0510">you are? okay</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0510">you're a ten words to a line girl</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0509">sometimes I'm a bit more</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I'm probably more like five <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1247" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> five words a line you're probably like seven</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or <vocal desc="laugh"/> when I'm doing the log at work you know the call log oh</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh it's just like</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0510" trans="overlap">gosh it's just a yeah five is cool really</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's that's what mine's like in some things</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0510">yeah?</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0510">but I do think you know when people come down to relieve me at lunchtime they must think my god she's</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0509" trans="overlap">what a mess</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0510" trans="overlap">illiterate what a mess because they can't read my writing not that they need to but you know</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0509">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1258" who="S0510">I I I was considering contemplating that today actually cos I had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the new lady come down</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0510">and and take over</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1262" who="S0510">and er when I came back I was struck by the difference in handwriting on the sheet you know between hers and mine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1263" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1264" who="S0510">it's like cor dear what a mess <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0509">oh no</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I really must take the time it's er I I just write so erm infrequently</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know a a letter</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or a you know a a proper</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0510">joined up</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I've written sorry carry on <unclear/></u>
<u n="1274" who="S0510" trans="overlap">paragraph you know I mean it</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0510">all I'm I'm I'm just taking notes from a call really</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0510">so yeah it would be nice to write a bit more actually</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0509">I've written a letter to auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I really need to send it now</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0510" trans="overlap">have you?</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well why don't I take it with me? <pause dur="short"/> you've written a letter to auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0509">no auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1284" who="S0510">oh auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0509" trans="overlap">the other one</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0509" trans="overlap">when I was in the chocolate shop today oh the lady's so nice in there</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0510">did you have the young girl or the lady?</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no older woman</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that owns it? the older lady</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I think yeah probably owns it</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0509">and she's so nice and she was like oh is it for you or is it for a</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0510" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0509">friend? cos it was like oh it's for my aunt and I just thought</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0510">yeah easier</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's my mum's best friend</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1299" who="S0509">was a bit more complicated</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0509">and she says oh that's nice and so I picked them all out and she was like oh you cos I'd written them all down on my phone I'd looked first and picked them out and like written the names of the chocolates I wanted on my phone</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0510">oh what? you mean you looked on the internet?</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0509" trans="overlap">when I went in no when I went into the shop I like wrote them all down</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0509">on my phone and then was like oh can I get these chocolates now?</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0509">and she was like and and then as I was doing them she kind of realised cos I was saying them so quickly she was like oh you you've got them written down on your phone I was like yeah</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0510">uhu</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0509">but I'd done five instead of six so that I had to pick one on the last minute I was like oh I got so close to doing this like perfect order</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0509">and then erm <pause dur="short"/> and then I got the white chocolate lollipop at the end and she was like oh something for yourself is it? and I was like no that's for my aunt too <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1312" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1313" who="S0509">and but she tied it all up really nicely didn't <trunc>y</trunc> didn't she?</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0509">did you see?</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it looked lovely it looked really nice</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah really nice</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0510">oh well that's great if you've got all the names of the chocolates are you gonna write them out on a little sheet for her?</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0509">I might have deleted them</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0509">er I'll write down the ones I can remember <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1322" who="S0510">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0510">yeah here have a selection of chocolates here are some of them the rest are a surprise</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1326" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1327" who="S0509">that's literally what I'm gonna do</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there's a surprise</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0509" trans="overlap">the rest are a mystery</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0510">yes</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1332" who="S0510">tell me what you think they are</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0509" trans="overlap">one of one of them is a passion fruit one</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's the one I chose at the last minute</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0510" trans="overlap">lovely mm</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0509">I think I might even be able to remember all of them but</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0510" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0509">I'm not saying that for definite yeah</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0510">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0509">that's that's that's er that's a long shot</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0510">yeah ah look you've got the cat are you gonna do anything with the cat?</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0510">or not? no</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0509">the cat is gonna stay away</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0510">if he was a proper just a head</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm yeah if it was a grin</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0510" trans="overlap">if it a grin yeah</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it would go it would be going somewhere but</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0509">no I've gotta write</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well he has if you have a look at him he has got a proper grin</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0509">yeah but it's not like a mouth it's gotta be like</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0510" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0509">it's like a crescent moon grin</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0510">yes</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0509">the Cheshire Cat has</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0510">yeah indeedy in fact</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0510">I've seen quite a few about for Halloween have you? <pause dur="short"/> just sort of</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0510">Cheshire yes but</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0509" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0510">spooky Cheshire Cats sort</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0509">spooky Cheshire Cat grins</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah oh well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1367" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh I've gotta sort out all the stuff for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s now <trunc>k</trunc> I keep getting getting these things in my head and I'm like I've gotta do this I've gotta do that</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0509">so I've gotta pack and I've gotta wrap things</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0510">do you know what? I haven't even threaded the needle let me</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1372" who="S0510">let me get one and do that</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0509" trans="overlap">how long have we been here? nearly an hour <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1374" who="S0510">have we?</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0509">and you haven't even threaded the needle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1376" who="S0510">oh that is shocking</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's alright I only gave it to you like ten minutes ago though so it's fine</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0510">did you find the little reel of white cotton?</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0509">no I didn't look</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0509">sorry</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0510">no that's okay I'm just wondering whether it's actually is it here?</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0509">there was one I'm sure at some point <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1386" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah ah here it is here it is</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0509">oh good</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0510">er finding a decent needle though this is the thing I think it might be in the settee downstairs <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1389" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1390" who="S0510">on the arm on the settee</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0509">oh wow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1392" who="S0510">whoops</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in the arm</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0510">oh dear</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0509" trans="overlap">did you just stab it in there?</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0510">yeah so whatever you do if you sit in my seat don't put your arm on the erm</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1398" who="S0510">arm</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0510">could have a nasty</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's not good is it?</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0509">oh dear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1404" who="S0510">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh I suppose that's one way of keeping people off my seat isn't it?</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1406" who="S0510">rather than putting barbed wire around</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0509" trans="overlap">you cruel woman <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1408" who="S0510">just you know</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1410" who="S0510">sticky out needles</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0509">wow that is that is like a <trunc>se</trunc>serious seagull deterrent isn't it?</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> seagull</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just the disgust when you</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0510" trans="overlap">why would we yeah?</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0509">when she said that one word seagulls</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0509">like bane of my life</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0510">yeah <pause dur="short"/> actually they haven't been too bothersome lately</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0509">no?</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0510">no</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0510">well maybe I'm just more used to them roll you know rolling things across</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0509" trans="overlap">rolling things across the roof</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0509">yeah that is it's just so strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0509">do you not find that strange?</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0510">it is I'd love to know what they roll</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1430" who="S0510">really or maybe I don't</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0510">maybe that would just be too much <trunc>inf</trunc> too much to handle</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0509">too much to handle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1434" who="S0510">kind of get the feeling sometimes though that they're playing you know bowls</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0509">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0510" trans="overlap">having a little competition up there to see who can roll</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0509">that's the seagull sport is it?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0510" trans="overlap">the most</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0509">the bowls?</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0510">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0509" trans="overlap">well yeah we were talking about the Olympics the other day not with you I was talking to <anon type="place"/> people</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and er</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0510"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1445" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah about how great it was</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0510">it was we were so lucky to kind of get to see some of it as well in London weren't we?</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah we were</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0510">it was a pretty pretty amazing experience</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0510">and and I mean the the event itself wasn't you know breathtaking</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1452" who="S0510">but erm</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0509">the walking race</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0510">the walking race but it was free and we</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah gotta</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0510">you know although we didn't win the lottery for any of the <trunc>othe</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0509">you've gotta look on the bright side</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0510" trans="overlap">all the other <trunc>s</trunc> yeah we actually got to see an event and it was the it was just a general sort of fever that there was you know the the everybody kind of just rooting for everybody you know</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0510">if and er</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it was nice</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that sense of sort of camaraderie really that everybody was there to just cheer people on and <pause dur="short"/> and know and also I think there was that thing about knowing that it was special you know it was a special time</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0510">and a special moment <pause dur="short"/> especially when we went to Hyde Park that was crazy</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I was talking to the <anon type="place"/> lot about</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0510">was it?</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0509">yeah just how great that was</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0510">oh and that wasn't even seeing it live that was just seeing it on a screen wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0510">as it was happening but</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0510">but erm well that's like saying in some sense it's actually it was live wasn't it? but not in person</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yes that's right there needs to be that distinction doesn't there between live and</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0509">live in person</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0509">what's the word? there must be a better word for that</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0510">I'm sure there is but my brain isn't really</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I don't know oh when I was <trunc>read</trunc></u>
<u n="1480" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's probably like blindingly obviously on a on</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1483" who="S0509">when I was reading through Jane Eyre earlier I was making <trunc>no</trunc> I've got a notebook <trunc>up</trunc> with my reading <unclear>nook</unclear> now and I was</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0509" trans="overlap">writing down all these words that I didn't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1486" who="S0510">ah really?</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0510">but there are many you see some of them</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh you know what Jane Eyre's like</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0510" trans="overlap">are probably just out of circulation now</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0510">you know it's like when</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no it was</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0509">fine it was just like this is weird</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0510">so give give us some words</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0509">alright let me get my notebook then I'll tell you</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1499" who="S0509">if I can find it there it is</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0510">before you do that actually what were you saying to your erm you know your <anon type="place"/> chums about?</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0509">just how nice it was and how exciting we all found it</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0509">you know?</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0510">yeah did any of them get to you know</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0510">experience any?</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0509">no although somebody was saying someone they knew went to see the swimming</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0510">uhu <pause dur="short"/> so they lived it vicariously through them?</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0509">er yes yeah</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0509">oh the words sorry the words</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0509">ignominious</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0510">oh yeah so don't tell me but it's</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I don't know I haven't looked them up yet</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0510">like oh right <trunc>i</trunc>isn't it sort of something to do er the root of it isn't it to do with like ignore erm ignominious so somebody who's sort of <pause dur="short"/> not got that much presence or? I don't know yeah we're gonna have to look this up</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0509">yeah penurious</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0510">no idea penurious?</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0509">moiety</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0510"><vocal desc="sigh"/> your guess is as good as mine</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0509">I think you'll know the next one though repast</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0510">oh repast yeah er go on</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0509">well no I don't know it but I thought you probably will</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><trunc>repo</trunc> do you mean repost? so it's er to <trunc>re</trunc> a repost er R E</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0509" trans="overlap">repast</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0510">it's when you kind of like bat <trunc>awa</trunc> you know bat away somebody or isn't it?</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0509">probably</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0510">erm you know not ignore them but you know oh I've probably got right we're gonna have to look at these now</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1532" who="S0510">have you got a device?</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0509">no we'll do I'll do it later though</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0509">I'll do it later and I'll tell you and I'll keep you informed</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0510" trans="overlap">tell me how wrong I was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1537" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1538" who="S0510">it's like erm in the Victorian plays</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0510">did I tell you what my two favourite words were?</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0510">oh my two favourite words were sagacity</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0509"><trunc>sagas</trunc> what's that?</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0510">ah it's like the sharpness really the the kind of you know the presence the <vocal desc="sigh"/> not the presence of mind but you know sagacity they were really oh I can't think of anything yeah the sharpness the they were on it you know</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0510">erm</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0509">on the ball</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0510">on the ball sagacity and that was used funnily enough in both plays they're completely different plays but</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0510">you know they were of the time and I</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I can't say I have ever heard that word used outside of those plays but</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1554" who="S0510">but then of course when you look at a a when I looked at it in a dictionary oh it was so funny cos part of the play had that dictionary didn't it? Mrs Bouncer's you know where he says Mrs Bouncer have you ever do you know what the word grudge actually means? and</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I don't remember that</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0510">and and he's going that's not I don't have a grudge and do you own a dictionary? and she says no and he says well here you are and he hands her this great big tome do you not remember that? from the top of the chest of drawers</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0509">oh yeah I do now</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0510">I mean it's only a small part play and I know it wasn't your favourite play erm</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the other one was better <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1560" who="S0510">yeah yeah so erm that word <trunc>saga</trunc>sagacity erm</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0510">I thought well I'll look up in this dictionary cos it's sort of not quite of the period it wasn't quite a Victorian dictionary but</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0510">it was sort of early nineteen hundreds</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0509" trans="overlap">not long after</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0510">so and I couldn't find it and then the other word that I really liked in the play was where <unclear>Box</unclear> says tell the gentleman if he doesn't like the effluvia of my tobacco smoke then he can jolly well whatever and I just and it was partly the way he said that</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> effluvia</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><trunc>effluv</trunc> yeah er <vocal desc="laugh"/> and again it was like what does that actually mean?</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0510">erm and that looked that up in the dictionary and I couldn't find it and I said to the director I said do you know I said I think it's</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0509" trans="overlap">are these words just made it up? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1572" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's it's really you know</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1574" who="S0510">you would have thought that if it they were gonna be anywhere they would be in there because</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0510">they were obviously you know topical words for the day and he was going really? I said yeah and he went well I am surprised and then a horrible thought struck me</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0510">do I actually know how to spell sagacity?</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1580" who="S0510">am I actually spelling it right?</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1582" who="S0510">no I wasn't</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1584" who="S0510">so then I thought mm yeah it does seem just too weird that both of the words aren't in there when it was</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0510">you know contemporary pretty much with the dictionary maybe I was spelling sagacity wrong so how do you think I might have spelt sagacity?</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0509">with an S?</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0509">and is it with a C?</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0510">er no it's still with an S so <trunc>ha</trunc> what?</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0509" trans="overlap">was it did you do it like S E?</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0509">and it's S I?</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0510">er no</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0509">S A?</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1597" who="S0509">sagacity</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0510">and then when I found the word it was like ah there's sagacity and there's sagacious to be</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0510" trans="overlap">sagacious you see so oh wow so I felt a right silly nana</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1602" who="S0510">and then I though</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a right silly nana</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and I thought right well er let's just try another derivative of of <trunc>efflu</trunc>effluvia</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0509">effluvia</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><trunc>efflux</trunc> I can't even say it properly</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0509" trans="overlap">effluvia</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0510">effluvia and I was spelling it oh dear I I'm ashamed now I was spelling it E double F</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0509">A?</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0510">it was A but it was something this is my excuse anyway there was something in the way with Mr <unclear/> said said it that made me think it was an E it's not that I'm silly or anything</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1612" who="S0510">erm and yes of course it was A double F so then I had to go back to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the director and say ha-ha-ha-ha</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll never guess what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1614" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1615" who="S0509">I spelt them both wrong</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1617" who="S0509">but not just one of them</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0510">both of them</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0509" trans="overlap">both of them</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0510">yes how silly am I? yeah but er yeah they're they're kind of out of currency nowadays but</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0510">there are so many good words so you're gonna start</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0510">are you gonna start dropping in some of these Jane Eyre words in your?</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh I'll probably forget them all but that's why I'm writing them down so I don't just look them up and then forget them</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0510" trans="overlap">fab fab yes</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0509">yeah that's the aim anyway</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0510">oh look <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I I've kind of done it</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0509">oh well done</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0510">look it's all stitched up</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0509" trans="overlap">thank you thank you very much</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0510">all done oh do I need to pay attention to? that's a little bit slack but</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0509">I'm sure it will fine</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it will be fine once I've ironed it</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0509">I'm sure it'll be fine</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
