<text id="S7DT">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0003 S0113 S0130 S0159</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Garden of student accomodation, Salford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Mobile phones</topics>
		<activity>Housemates talking about mobile phones</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0003">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Royal Leamington Spa, Warwickshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0113">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Salford, Greater Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0130">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sheffield, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Salford, Greater Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0159">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Salford, Greater Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year, 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0003">okay <pause dur="short"/> what what phone do you have?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0130">well I've got an iPhone three GS</u>
<u n="3" who="S0003">I've got an iPhone four which is the second newest one <pause dur="short"/> pretty good</u>
<u n="4" who="S0130">I have the four S the newest one</u>
<u n="5" who="S0003">what what does the?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0113">I don't have an iPhone I've got an Nokia express music <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0003">what's that? What does it do? Nothing</u>
<u n="8" who="S0113">em <pause dur="short"/> it's just a basic phone really <pause dur="short"/> just sends messages calls internet all that</u>
<u n="9" who="S0159">I don't have an iPhone either I've got a HTC Desire <pause dur="short"/> but I am getting an iPhone when my contract's up</u>
<u n="10" who="S0003">oh see is the H T whatever they are <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0130">HTC</u>
<u n="12" who="S0003">are they em meant to be are they meant to be good?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0159">they're better than iPhones</u>
<u n="14" who="S0003">are they? Why are you getting an iPhone then?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0130">no they're not cos I I used to have an HTC Wildfire and that was terrible</u>
<u n="16" who="S0003">well why are you getting an iPhone?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0159" trans="overlap">but the Wildfire's the cheap one though</u>
<u n="18" who="S0113" trans="overlap">are they Are they as bad as BlackBerrys though?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0159">blackBerrys are rubbish they always break</u>
<u n="20" who="S0130">no but I don't like BlackBerrys <pause dur="short"/> blackBerrys are horrible they always break</u>
<u n="21" who="S0003">I had a BlackBerry before and I loved BBM on it <pause dur="short"/> but now you can iMessage and you've got like WhatsApp on the iPhone</u>
<u n="22" who="S0113" trans="overlap">ping</u>
<u n="23" who="S0130">but the thing is though if you're like on pay as you go with I with em you got three you if you got the software update on it and it says something pay as you go and you haven't got like three G</u>
<u n="24" who="S0003">oh then you can't use it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0130">you can't it takes forever you can't really use it so it's pointless</u>
<u n="26" who="S0003">what is the BBM and I iMessage?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0130">yeah that's just that's just iMessage that</u>
<u n="28" who="S0003">so are you on three G I mean pay as you go?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0130">I've I've got <trunc>thr</trunc> I've got three G now but I'm on pay as you go <pause dur="short"/> I've only really got it in the past two weeks which really weird actually</u>
<u n="30" who="S0003">what is it?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0159">I'm in Orange</u>
<u n="32" who="S0003">ah Orange Orange Wednesdays I wish I was at</u>
<u n="33" who="S0113">free cinema tickets</u>
<u n="34" who="S0003">orange you get like loads more freebies don't you?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0113">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0159">I'm on O2 they just charge you so much</u>
<u n="37" who="S0003">eh Tom works for O2 don't you?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0130">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0159">you charge people too much</u>
<u n="40" who="S0130">I work for pay as you go <pause dur="short"/> actually I I I work for pay as you go inbound calls</u>
<u n="41" who="S0159">oh sorry</u>
<u n="42" who="S0130">not my problem <pause dur="short"/> if you're on contract not my problem</u>
<u n="43" who="S0159">yeah I forgive you for charging me too much</u>
<u n="44" who="S0003">I'm on Vodafone and the signal is amazing like you can get signal anywhere but they give you no freebies</u>
<u n="45" who="S0130" trans="overlap">it's all down It's all down to basically if you get <pause dur="short"/> it depends on your tariff if you work for if you have pay as you go and you're there saying oh oh you end up ringing up complaining oh I'm not getting this <pause dur="short"/> it's because you've not asked for it most of the time <pause dur="short"/> or you don't know how to do it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0113">I don't think many people on pay as you go now though <pause dur="short"/> it's a dying breed</u>
<u n="47" who="S0159">no</u>
<u n="48" who="S0003" trans="overlap">I know yeah it is</u>
<u n="49" who="S0130">no you you say that though but the <trunc>sim</trunc> the the simplicity <trunc>tari</trunc> the simplicity tariff is twenty-five pound you get like you get unlimited texts five hundred minutes I think unlimited data which is pretty much the same as a contract</u>
<u n="50" who="S0159">isn't that only to O2 though or is that the other one?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0130">that's that's for O2 but you can <pause dur="short"/> but you know what I mean like you know you people pay like I've got a mate who I work with he pays <trunc>thir</trunc> thirty quid for his contract a month <pause dur="short"/> and for a fiver less</u>
<u n="52" who="S0003">you can get the</u>
<u n="53" who="S0130">he can go on pay as you go</u>
<u n="54" who="S0003">but then you have to pay the you have to buy the phone don't you?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0130">that well yeah but that that's</u>
<u n="56" who="S0003">and then so you can't have a iPhone cos it costs a fortune</u>
<u n="57" who="S0113">he's already got a iPhone in contract <unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0130">but at the same time if you're on contract if you <pause dur="short"/> this is a fact this if you're on what like say a twenty-four month contract you end up paying about six hundred quid more</u>
<u n="59" who="S0003">oh my god really?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0130">yeah honestly <pause dur="short"/> if you're on contract for say pay as you go and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> this is This is no word of a lie <pause dur="short"/> if you're on if you're on em like em a <trunc>pi</trunc> a contract you pay so much but you pay it for so long you end up paying more back that's what than what the phone is actually worth</u>
<u n="61" who="S0003" trans="overlap">that it works out yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know I get what you mean</u>
<u n="62" who="S0130">as well as the top up <pause dur="short"/> that's no word of a lie</u>
<u n="63" who="S0159">yeah so far on my phone I've paid about seven hundred pound just for the contract</u>
<u n="64" who="S0113">how long has it been <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0003">see do you know if you actually sat down and worked it out</u>
<u n="66" who="S0130">em do you know how much the phone's worth</u>
<u n="67" who="S0159">about well when I got it it was about three hundred quid</u>
<u n="68" who="S0130">well there you go then</u>
<u n="69" who="S0003">yeah that's true actually <pause dur="short"/> if you actually did sit down <pause dur="short"/> but it's the <trunc>che</trunc> it's people can't most people can't afford to pay off right can they the the money</u>
<u n="70" who="S0113">no</u>
<u n="71" who="S0159">yeah no</u>
<u n="72" who="S0130">well that that's cos I when I was looking to get a iPhone at first I em I like I like priced it up and stuff like that and it just came out as nine hundred quid</u>
<u n="73" who="S0003">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm hm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0130">going on contract</u>
<u n="75" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0003">no it's ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> I think mine's like forty pound a month my contract I think Ryan's is even more cos he's on like bloody <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>stup</trunc> I think it's like fifty pound</u>
<u n="77" who="S0159">really?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0130">fifty <trunc>qui</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> fifty quid contract what does he get for that?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0003">he's gets like unlimited internet and his iPhone's like the biggest one that you can get oh I don't know you know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like</u>
<u n="80" who="S0113">they say em</u>
<u n="81" who="S0159">go on to Three their contracts you get like two thousand minutes five thousand texts unlimited internet for thirty-six quid</u>
<u n="82" who="S0003">God that's good <pause dur="short"/> mine's a lot <pause dur="short"/> mine's not that bad <pause dur="short"/> it's the insurance though when you pay like thirteen pound on insurance</u>
<u n="83" who="S0113">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0003">for a phone it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="85" who="S0130">yeah but then again if you'll if you end up losing it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0130">you know you're buggered aren't you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0003">yeah but a lot of insurance you get like I get insurance through my bank now <pause dur="short"/> it comes through with my <trunc>acc</trunc> em with my account <pause dur="short"/> I get free thingy</u>
<u n="89" who="S0159">ah <unclear/> shit out</u>
<u n="90" who="S0003">yeah it's ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> do we actually have to talk for fifteen minutes?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0130">fifteen it's recording?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0159">but yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0003">so all the different kinds of phones that are out there <pause dur="short"/> iPhone's got to be the biggest though isn't it?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0130">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0003">everyone's got a fucking iPhone these days</u>
<u n="97" who="S0159">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="98" who="S0003">to be fair though they don't <pause dur="short"/> I mean they were great when I first got it but it freezes a lot <pause dur="short"/> it keeps turning off all the time</u>
<u n="99" who="S0130">I think you get them for the apps though personally</u>
<u n="100" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0130">that's why <pause dur="short"/> because when I traded my my iPhone in last time and I got a BlackBerry I missed it I missed it mainly for the apps</u>
<u n="103" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0130">and the games and stuff like that</u>
<u n="105" who="S0003">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but on an <pause dur="short"/> can't you get them free like like Cut the rope and Angry Birds and stuff on an Android phone don't you get them free?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0159">yeah I get them</u>
<u n="107" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0130">not <pause dur="short"/> there's <trunc>o</trunc> no but there's certain ones that you can't get for Android that you can get for I <pause dur="short"/> it's it's <trunc>ju</trunc> it's one of those things that you kind of want it</u>
<u n="109" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0130">just cos it's an iPhone</u>
<u n="111" who="S0003">it's social status isn't it to say I've <trunc>go</trunc> yeah I've got an iPhone</u>
<u n="112" who="S0113">everyone's got iPhones now <pause dur="short"/> if you want to be original have something different</u>
<u n="113" who="S0003">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="114" who="S0159">with you Nokia</u>
<u n="115" who="S0113">this is a good phone it doesn't break</u>
<u n="116" who="S0159">Retro</u>
<u n="117" who="S0003">Nokia exactly it is retro in <unclear/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0113">can't beat a thirty-three ten they were invincible phones</u>
<u n="119" who="S0003">yes yeah they were <pause dur="short"/> good old snake</u>
<u n="120" who="S0113">you could just em</u>
<u n="121" who="S0159">my dad's still got one</u>
<u n="122" who="S0130">and there's the fifty-three hundred as well where if it drops it won't break <pause dur="short"/> apparently if you put that on charge the charge will last about two week</u>
<u n="123" who="S0003">God</u>
<u n="124" who="S0159">oh yeah I've heard about that</u>
<u n="125" who="S0003">yeah my my phone literally I charged it last night a hundred percent I'm on twenty-five percent battery life <pause dur="short"/> ridiculous</u>
<u n="126" who="S0159">I know about that <pause dur="short"/> I'm on two batteries</u>
<u n="127" who="S0130">mine doesn't last long either</u>
<u n="128" who="S0003">it is ridiculous</u>
<u n="129" who="S0113">what does everyone use their phones most for calls or texts or?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0003">texts</u>
<u n="131" who="S0130">texts <pause dur="short"/> texting</u>
<u n="132" who="S0003">texts and Facebook</u>
<u n="133" who="S0130">yeah texts and Facebook</u>
<u n="134" who="S0159">Facebook yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0003">Facebook I can't remember the <trunc>la</trunc> <trunc>ti</trunc> the last time I went on a laptop to look at Facebook <pause dur="short"/> it's always on my phone <pause dur="short"/> or my iPad or my Mac</u>
<u n="136" who="S0113">it's made social networking easier</u>
<u n="137" who="S0003">ah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0159">shit <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0003">making the world a less sociable place isn't it? Definitely</u>
<u n="140" who="S0113">you just see people now instead of talking to each other they're just say on their iPhones</u>
<u n="141" who="S0003">yeah sending texts yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0003">I do that <pause dur="short"/> if</u>
<u n="144" who="S0130">that's good though if you're bored <pause dur="short"/> like somewhere</u>
<u n="145" who="S0113">or you're sitting next to someone you don't want to talk to</u>
<u n="146" who="S0130">just get your iPhone out isn't it?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0003">mm <pause dur="short"/> I do that if I if on the street</u>
<u n="148" who="S0159">or is you're in an awkward moment</u>
<u n="149" who="S0003">you know when you're in the street and someone tries talking to you <pause dur="short"/> and where have they gone?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0130">they're up there I think they're going to the shop</u>
<u n="151" who="S0113">or that's it if you see someone you don't want to talk to you can just look down at your phone and</u>
<u n="152" who="S0003" trans="overlap">yeah you just play on your phone</u>
<u n="153" who="S0159">yeah I've done that a lot</u>
<u n="154" who="S0113">just pretend you didn't notice them</u>
<u n="155" who="S0003">yeah it's funny</u>
<u n="156" who="S0113">if it's</u>
<u n="157" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0003">is it's T Y</u>
<u n="159" who="S0113">there's not a lot more to talk about</u>
<u n="160" who="S0003">no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0113">halfway <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0003">using my phone now to communicate</u>
<u n="163" who="S0159">communicate to other people <pause dur="short"/> not being social with us here</u>
<u n="164" who="S0003">I know <pause dur="short"/> exactly exactly <pause dur="short"/> ten minutes</u>
<u n="165" who="S0159">but yeah em</u>
<u n="166" who="S0003">em <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="167" who="S0113">what was the first phone you ever had?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0003">I think it was a Nokia <pause dur="short"/> I remember actually</u>
<u n="169" who="S0003">mine was a Nokia I know that</u>
<u n="170" who="S0159">mine was a Nokia</u>
<u n="171" who="S0003">it was It was a Nokia on Orange <pause dur="short"/> like it but it was Orange phone <pause dur="short"/> do you remember that Orange Nokia?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0159">oh yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0003">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember getting it</u>
<u n="174" who="S0159">mine was a Mine was a thirty-three ten on Tesco</u>
<u n="175" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0113">I think mine was a thirty-three</u>
<u n="177" who="S0003">Tesco <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0113">I think everyone I think <trunc>ever</trunc> Nokia used to be the main thing when it started</u>
<u n="179" who="S0003">it did</u>
<u n="180" who="S0130">I had a thirty-three ten in Spain when I first moved there but when I actually got back I cos I used to borrow that phone with my sister <pause dur="short"/> but when I got back to England I actually got my own phone and I it was a Nokia but I can't remember for the life of me what what it was</u>
<u n="181" who="S0003">what it was</u>
<u n="182" who="S0130">I always used to have polyphonic ringtone I had Slipknot the millions for a as a polyphonic ringtone on it <pause dur="short"/> that was pretty cool</u>
<u n="183" who="S0113">I just I just remember playing snake all the time</u>
<u n="184" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0003">you <trunc>s</trunc> you can get snake <pause dur="short"/> I've got in on here on my iPhone</u>
<u n="186" who="S0113">it's not the same though is it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0159">yeah it's not the same though</u>
<u n="188" who="S0003">it's shit</u>
<u n="189" who="S0159">they've made it all 3D</u>
<u n="190" who="S0003">it's not great <pause dur="short"/> oh no it's not 3D</u>
<u n="191" who="S0159">isn't it?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0113">I know but it's not</u>
<u n="193" who="S0003">no it's it's proper like</u>
<u n="194" who="S0130">old school snake</u>
<u n="195" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0113">you can play snake on YouTube</u>
<u n="197" who="S0130">can you?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0003">look <pause dur="short"/> it's like that</u>
<u n="199" who="S0159">that's so cool</u>
<u n="200" who="S0113">it just still not the same as on the other phone though is it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0003" trans="overlap">but it's not it's not using buttons</u>
<u n="202" who="S0130">and when you click</u>
<u n="203" who="S0159">it's not the same when you don't hear the click of the buttons</u>
<u n="204" who="S0003">no exactly</u>
<u n="205" who="S0113">and when you couldn't use em phones for internet and stuff</u>
<u n="206" who="S0130">well you could but you get charged for it whereas now you get other tariffs and stuff like that where you get it for free</u>
<u n="207" who="S0003">I don't I don't know what I'd do if I couldn't use internet on my phone <pause dur="short"/> I use it for everything</u>
<u n="208" who="S0159">me too</u>
<u n="209" who="S0003">like if I can't spell a word <pause dur="short"/> just type it in Google</u>
<u n="210" who="S0130">I do that as well yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0003">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's all good</u>
<u n="212" who="S0113">I still just guess but yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0003">if you're on if you've got wireless as well you can watch like four O D and stuff on the iPhone</u>
<u n="214" who="S0113">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0003">it's well good</u>
<u n="216" who="S0130">it depends though like you know with your Wi-Fi cos I've had problems like you know cos I've tried watching like B iPlayer on my phone but it's the Wi-Fi just kicks out and stuff like that on my phone sometimes</u>
<u n="217" who="S0003">it's not It's not great the Wi-Fi in here though in Castle Irwell but home is</u>
<u n="218" who="S0130">that wasn't That wasn't in Irwell though</u>
<u n="219" who="S0003">was it not?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0130">that was at house that had Wi-Fi <pause dur="short"/> I was just checking it and it just wouldn't come through and it just kept cutting out all the time</u>
<u n="221" who="S0113">I remember when Bluetoothing was really popular at one point</u>
<u n="222" who="S0003">yeah Bluetooth <pause dur="short"/> that's how you'd send a song wasn't it?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0113">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> or try and just hack on to people's and look at what pictures they'd got</u>
<u n="224" who="S0130" trans="overlap">I remember <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah infrared used to be quite popular when I was at high school</u>
<u n="225" who="S0113">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0003">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0130">like you used to send videos and pics and stuff via infrared and stuff that was really weird that</u>
<u n="228" who="S0113">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0003">I used to em <pause dur="short"/> I print off a lot of pictures on my phone <pause dur="short"/> and if you've got an iPhone most you know instant print off things <pause dur="short"/> you can't print them off unless you've got a cable <pause dur="short"/> cos iPhones don't have Bluetooth</u>
<u n="230" who="S0113">Don't they?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0003">no</u>
<u n="232" who="S0130">well they do but you can only connect them via other iPhones <pause dur="short"/> you can't connect them to any other phone</u>
<u n="233" who="S0003" trans="overlap">connect it <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> to <pause dur="short"/> actually that is true they do <pause dur="short"/> cos my car's all Bluetooth and I can connect my phone to it</u>
<u n="234" who="S0130">it's really weird <pause dur="short"/> I don't get it <pause dur="short"/> I don't get the iPhone Bluetooth <pause dur="short"/> cos I think it's just mainly for iPhones <trunc>pro</trunc> other iPhones really</u>
<u n="235" who="S0003">I think the only thing with iPhones they try and be unique to them don't they to Apple <pause dur="short"/> it's just</u>
<u n="236" who="S0113">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0130">and they they don't like connecting to other</u>
<u n="238" who="S0113">no they don't they don't want to connect with the to other people</u>
<u n="239" who="S0130">phones <pause dur="short"/> it's the same with iPads though really isn't it?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0003">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0130">you know the most the <trunc>ma</trunc> ninety-five percent of their tablet market is I Apple</u>
<u n="242" who="S0003" trans="overlap">apple Apple yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0113">I think iPads are useless anyhow</u>
<u n="244" who="S0130">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I was at work actually the other day and they and they were saying like you know you'll get queries about you know em iPads and stuff like that and I actually said well do you get any other queries about other tablets? And they said very frequently you do</u>
<u n="245" who="S0003">why why do you get why do you get queries about iPads?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0130">Cos you get Cos you get you get you get three G sims don't you for the iPads don't you?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0003">oh yeah Oh yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got one on his</u>
<u n="248" who="S0159" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0130">so you get queries for the iPad and I was like saying cos BlackBerry and Samsung and</u>
<u n="250" who="S0003">yeah they've got a</u>
<u n="251" who="S0130">HTC do one as well</u>
<u n="252" who="S0003">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0130">and I was like well surely you get queries for them cos O O two must sell them <pause dur="short"/> it was like no they don't really just mainly iPads and even <trunc>the</trunc> and even iPad queries are few and far between</u>
<u n="254" who="S0003">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0113">apple are like the main players in the phone market now</u>
<u n="256" who="S0003">yeah yeah definitely</u>
<u n="257" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0003">yeah with all the new <pause dur="short"/> all their new stuff that <trunc>the</trunc> that they're releasing</u>
<u n="259" who="S0113">ten minutes</u>
<u n="260" who="S0003">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0159">I'm always on the internet on my phone just checking Facebook</u>
<u n="262" who="S0130">you get Safari and stuff like that don't you <pause dur="short"/> cos it with Apple you always have Safari</u>
<u n="263" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0113">I just basically just use Facebook and then</u>
<u n="265" who="S0130">twitter now as well</u>
<u n="266" who="S0003">twitter yeah I use Twitter on it</u>
<u n="267" who="S0159">are you on Twitter?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0003">yeah so</u>
<u n="269" who="S0130">twitter's <trunc>o</trunc> Twitter's epic I love it</u>
<u n="270" who="S0159">I can't get into Twitter</u>
<u n="271" who="S0130">it's just well funny what looking what famous people say so but yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0159">I've got it but I've just never used it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0130">you got Twitter?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0003">does it? <trunc>You</trunc> <trunc>do</trunc> I I don't use it as in to like write things on it <pause dur="short"/> you write things on it like statuses don't you?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0159" trans="overlap">yeah but I've never used it</u>
<u n="276" who="S0130">all the time yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0003">all the time <pause dur="short"/> you probably use it more than Facebook don't you?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0130">no I use Facebook more</u>
<u n="279" who="S0003">do you not? Do you think?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0130">definitely</u>
<u n="281" who="S0159">he's always on Facebook</u>
<u n="282" who="S0003" trans="overlap">em</u>
<u n="283" who="S0113" trans="overlap">Facebook I use for I use for chat now <pause dur="short"/> not really for statuses and stuff</u>
<u n="284" who="S0003">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0003">twitter's awesome <unclear/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0113" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0003">I always follow WWN on Twitter me</u>
<u n="288" who="S0113"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's very social so what's it <unclear/> like with them on the phone do you think that'll just update what you're doing <pause dur="short"/> like when you're on the go</u>
<u n="289" who="S0130">and you can see em what celebrities are fighting on it as well that's always cool</u>
<u n="290" who="S0113">it's like the a update on the go now</u>
<u n="291" who="S0130">when CM Punk was fighting <trunc>Chr</trunc> like a Twitter Twitter war with Chris Brown that was quite cool that</u>
<u n="292" who="S0113">there's always Twitter wars now <pause dur="short"/> anyone</u>
<u n="293" who="S0003">yeah that's what they say on all the news things isn't it? This was quoted on Twitter <pause dur="short"/> never on Facebook</u>
<u n="294" who="S0113">Cos it's easier to <pause dur="short"/> it's easier to see what's going on now as well with the</u>
<u n="295" who="S0003">mm <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="296" who="S0113">phones</u>
<u n="297" who="S0130">how good's your camera on your phone?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0159">my camera's not very good I've got a big crack down it</u>
<u n="299" who="S0113">mine's got a three point two megapixel slash A S</u>
<u n="300" who="S0003">yeah see iPhones aren't great for their eh <pause dur="short"/> for their cameras situation</u>
<u n="301" who="S0130" trans="overlap">I don't even know what three G S is for to be honest</u>
<u n="302" who="S0159">I though iPhones were good for cameras</u>
<u n="303" who="S0003">they are the new one's amazing but <pause dur="short"/> it's I mean it's alright <pause dur="short"/> you can edit your photos on it which is quite good like if you've got red eye you can take the you can take the red eye out of it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0159" trans="overlap">yeah that's quite cool</u>
<u n="305" who="S0113">I'd just rather use a digital camera than use my phone <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0003">yeah I would <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0113">sort your photos out</u>
<u n="308" who="S0159">if it's on the phone if you've only got to carry one thing</u>
<u n="309" who="S0130">yeah that's good though like <pause dur="short"/> the phone's like don't need anything else like before you'd have to have stuff like <pause dur="short"/> just use it for your time the</u>
<u n="310" who="S0003">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0130">date and</u>
<u n="313" who="S0159">music as well</u>
<u n="314" who="S0130">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0003">music that's the good thing with an iPhone it's got an iPod built in so it's got iTunes</u>
<u n="316" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0113">use it as a diary as well my phone as well <pause dur="short"/> and stuff</u>
<u n="318" who="S0003">diary yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0130">and you've got notes as well on it as well <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty cool</u>
<u n="320" who="S0113">have you ever Have you ever lost your phone like for a few days now it's <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="321" who="S0003">yeah you feel like you feel like your arm's been cut off don't you?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0113">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="323" who="S0003">like literally I didn't have my phone for three hours cos it froze and I couldn't get in back on and I thought I thought it's dead <pause dur="short"/> and I was like how do I communicate with the world? </u>
<u n="324" who="S0113">it's like before when you was younger you just don't realise how important it would be to you</u>
<u n="325" who="S0003">emails <pause dur="short"/> emails as well <pause dur="short"/> come straight through</u>
<u n="326" who="S0130">I don't use email on my phone</u>
<u n="327" who="S0003">do you not?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0130">I tried doing it on my <trunc>i</trunc> on my iPhone and it just didn't work</u>
<u n="329" who="S0003">you see my I get all my uni emails straight otherwise I'd never read them they go straight through</u>
<u n="330" who="S0130">I just do it straight from Safari me on mine</u>
<u n="331" who="S0159">yeah same <pause dur="short"/> I can't get like <pause dur="short"/> I got an email app on here but I can't get it to work</u>
<u n="332" who="S0003">see mine works really well <pause dur="short"/> it comes through all the time <pause dur="short"/> the only thing is they come through on here but it doesn't when I delete them it doesn't register on my Hotmail account so when I go in on a computer I've got like five thousand emails it's ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> that's so ridiculous</u>
<u n="333" who="S0159">well</u>
<u n="334" who="S0003">five minutes</u>
<u n="335" who="S0113">well em <pause dur="short"/> eh eh yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0003">eh yeah <pause dur="short"/> different shapes and sizes</u>
<u n="337" who="S0130" trans="overlap">the app store <pause dur="short"/> yeah the app the app store on iPhone's really good though cos you've got loads of different stuff as well haven't you? You can do like social <pause dur="short"/> it all comes in different categories like you've got games social lifestyle <pause dur="short"/> stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> like with social you can download different things for like Twitter Tumbler Facebook</u>
<u n="338" who="S0113">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0003">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0113">what's your favourite app on your phone that you've got now?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0003">eh Facebook <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0113">Facebook</u>
<u n="343" who="S0003">Facebook's the one that I use most</u>
<u n="344" who="S0130">it's got to be</u>
<u n="345" who="S0003">and this draw free now is really good</u>
<u n="346" who="S0130">yeah draw free's pretty</u>
<u n="347" who="S0003">draw free is really good <pause dur="short"/> I love it</u>
<u n="348" who="S0130">I've got like loads of different games going it's top</u>
<u n="349" who="S0159">I've got a good American Football game I'm always on it <pause dur="short"/> in lectures I shouldn't say but</u>
<u n="350" who="S0003">yeah I know yeah I do</u>
<u n="351" who="S0130">what game is it cos I've got one on my phone</u>
<u n="352" who="S0159">it's just called NFO</u>
<u n="353" who="S0003">to be fair though I've got my NatWest bank on there as well and I can just literally type a password and it comes up with my account <pause dur="short"/> it's really good</u>
<u n="354" who="S0130">I had that with mine but my em thingy went really weird so I couldn't do it <pause dur="short"/> like cos I changed lost my card and then I had to enter new details in so I just kinda I just deleted the app <pause dur="short"/> got bored of it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0003">I remember that when you like lost your card and when it ate it ate your card</u>
<u n="356" who="S0113" trans="overlap">I probably just didn't know that was I just use poker and gambling apps</u>
<u n="357" who="S0159">yeah it'd be like every single app on his one's a gambling or poker or blackjack</u>
<u n="358" who="S0130">I used to use eh that used to be on my em on my old HTC I used to have like loads of poker games on my on my on my HTC</u>
<u n="359" who="S0003">I've not got any poker games <pause dur="short"/> I use to love Cut the Rope <pause dur="short"/> and I don't really <pause dur="short"/> I don't play that anymore</u>
<u n="360" who="S0130">draw Something's quite cool <pause dur="short"/> oh em <pause dur="short"/> eh that Temple Runner that's a good game</u>
<u n="361" who="S0003">I don't play that because I don't like how how you have to move your phone around</u>
<u n="362" who="S0130">you get used to it though cos everyone's like addicted to it though aren't they?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0003">this is ridiculous <unclear/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0159">T Y is always on it</u>
<u n="365" who="S0003">on what Temple Run?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0130" trans="overlap">what on Temple Run?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0159">oh no I thought you <trunc>dr</trunc> that draw that one</u>
<u n="368" who="S0003">oh the Draw Something yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0113">bet his drawings are terrible</u>
<u n="370" who="S0003">that is the thing though you get addicted to apps like you really do get addicted to games completely and utterly <pause dur="short"/> I remember when I got a phone I was up till like three in the morning just playing on it</u>
<u n="371" who="S0113">well there's always like a popular app and then then a new one comes along and that's the new <unclear/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0003" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it fades out</u>
<u n="373" who="S0130">well that's what I saw with <trunc>te</trunc> that's what I saw with Temple Run as well like <pause dur="short"/> temple Run was dead popular for a bit</u>
<u n="374" who="S0003">ooh <pause dur="short"/> have you <trunc>go</trunc> ever had Scribblenauts on your phone</u>
<u n="375" who="S0130">what?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0003">scribblenauts <pause dur="short"/> it it's actually originally a Nintendo DS game then they turned it into an iPhone game and em like it's different like scenarios and you have to like to have to create objects to complete the scenarios <pause dur="short"/> it's weird</u>
<u n="377" who="S0130">I've never heard of that before</u>
<u n="378" who="S0113">me neither</u>
<u n="379" who="S0003">let's see <pause dur="short"/> what else have I got <pause dur="short"/> oh eh <trunc>d</trunc> the cinema one Flickster is good cos you just get all the cinema things up whenever <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>seja</trunc> <trunc>secja</trunc> Cezanne Sejan?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0130">time line em Train Line is quite good you get train times</u>
<u n="381" who="S0003">oh yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0113">basically yeah your phone's just like a personal organiser now <pause dur="short"/> you just <pause dur="short"/> it organises your life</u>
<u n="383" who="S0159">yeah it does</u>
<u n="384" who="S0003">yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> monopoly is the best one though <pause dur="short"/> monopoly love it</u>
<u n="385" who="S0130">monopoly</u>
<u n="386" who="S0159">monopoly is good</u>
<u n="387" who="S0003">monopoly <unclear/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0130">you're obsessed by Monopoly though aren't you Chelse?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0003">yeah I am a little bit <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I love it <pause dur="short"/> I do love Monopoly</u>
<u n="390" who="S0113">McDonald's Monopoly</u>
<u n="391" who="S0003">they brought it back out at McDonald's</u>
<u n="392" who="S0159">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've been twice already</u>
<u n="393" who="S0003">I need I need to go and buy one just so I can get it <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> did you win anything? I never won anything</u>
<u n="394" who="S0159">I won a free Big Mac</u>
<u n="395" who="S0003">I never win anything</u>
<u n="396" who="S0130">we saw T Y before and he he claimed that he got twenty percent off a holiday or something like that</u>
<u n="397" who="S0159">yeah he did <pause dur="short"/> I was with him</u>
<u n="398" who="S0003" trans="overlap">that's bullshit</u>
<u n="399" who="S0113">I won em <pause dur="short"/> eh what did I win? Some porridge</u>
<u n="400" who="S0003">porridge?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0113">the worst one</u>
<u n="402" who="S0003"><unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0130" trans="overlap">porridge at McDonald's</u>
<u n="404" who="S0113">in the morning <pause dur="short"/> porridge and a <trunc>h</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc> hot drink and an apple pie though <pause dur="short"/> that was alright</u>
<u n="405" who="S0130">to be fair though with McDonald's though you're never really <pause dur="short"/> as students you're never actually up in time to get their breakfast in reality are you?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0003">no but like <trunc>wh</trunc> what kind of breakfast finished at ten o'clock in the morning? It's ridiculous</u>
<u n="407" who="S0113">half ten isn't it?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0159">dunno</u>
<u n="409" who="S0003">half is it half ten? Stupid <pause dur="short"/> at the weekends it should finish at twelve <pause dur="short"/> it should always finish at twelve actually</u>
<u n="410" who="S0159">they should just do it all day</u>
<u n="411" who="S0130" trans="overlap">they should do both they should <pause dur="short"/> like from about eleven eh ten till twelve they should do day time meal and</u>
<u n="412" who="S0003">who wants a Big Mac at <trunc>ha</trunc> ten o'clock in the morning?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0159">I would</u>
<u n="414" who="S0003">would you?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0159">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0130">it was like that It was like that at KFC though <pause dur="short"/> cos you always used to go in <pause dur="short"/> at KFC it used to open at eleven and you always used to get people coming in at eleven o'clock getting a a family bucket at eleven</u>
<u n="417" who="S0159">really?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0130">yeah honestly I'm not even kidding <pause dur="short"/> I used and apparently I heard somewhere some KFCs they do a breakfast like you get chicken and egg in a wrap</u>
<u n="419" who="S0003">urgh no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0130">apparently <pause dur="short"/> that's what I got told</u>
<u n="421" who="S0003">Cos you you don't do breakfast at KFC do they?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0130">no they don't <pause dur="short"/> and it was just really weird like you know you just literally open up you're tired you go in and oh yeah can I get an eight eight piece family bucket please like <pause dur="short"/> it's eleven o'clock you <unclear/> why?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0003">you weirdos get a life</u>
<u n="424" who="S0113">probably just only just got up eh not got up just going to bed</u>
<u n="425" who="S0159">yeah just about to go to bed</u>
<u n="426" who="S0003">yeah I remember when I went to Magaluf we eh we ate KFC at about four in the morning <pause dur="short"/> it was great</u>
<u n="427" who="S0113">yeah we did that at about six</u>
<u n="428" who="S0130">loving life</u>
<u n="429" who="S0113">basically as soon as the club kicks out KFC got really</u>
<u n="430" who="S0003">yeah KFC</u>
<u n="431" who="S0113">it's right outside BCM though isn't it?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0003">yeah it is yeah that's why everyone went <pause dur="short"/> and then there's like Burger King just over the way and Subway</u>
<u n="433" who="S0113">and a McDonald's as well</u>
<u n="434" who="S0003">ah <trunc>Pi</trunc> there's a Pizza Hut isn't there?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0130">on Geordie Shore they were like that whenever I saw them come back from a night out they always ended up coming back with a KFC</u>
<u n="436" who="S0113">when I went When I went to Magaluf they were that's they were in was when Geordie Shore were there</u>
<u n="437" who="S0130">nice</u>
<u n="438" who="S0113">that was</u>
</body>
</text>
