<text id="S7HR">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:35:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The Tram coffee shop in Tarnow, Poland</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Checking the football results, homesickness/SAD, a student, good coffee, message from a friend, feeling responsible for students (and preparing them for exams), working on farms, dogs, media, reading, birds, umbrellas, shopping, drinking, boots. </topics>
		<activity>Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) in The Tram coffee shop in Tarnow, Poland.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0618">here we are hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0619">hello sorry I'm just gonna send this text so you're wasting your time</u>
<u n="3" who="S0618">oh well that's alright</u>
<u n="4" who="S0619"><unclear/> right I'm going to</u>
<u n="5" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so I can talk to the transcriber while you're texting then so you can probably tell we're in a coffee shop <vocal desc="laugh"/> that bean grinding noise must be quite common to a lot of our <pause dur="short"/> our recordings</u>
<u n="6" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0618">I think <pause dur="short"/> oh it's them again there they are again <pause dur="short"/> is your wi-fi actually loaded? cos I'm still trying to get erm the latest on Arsenal versus Hull <pause dur="short"/> and it says it's not loading which is annoying <pause dur="short"/> could just be that app I suppose</u>
<u n="8" who="S0619">erm</u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<u n="9" who="S0618">erm yeah so while you're doing that I'm going to have a little look at BBC football</u>
<u n="10" who="S0619">okay <pause dur="short"/> I do feel like really homesick and I think it is <pause dur="short"/> I'm turning into a Polish people who whenever anything happens you go that's the weather</u>
<u n="11" who="S0618">it's the weather</u>
<u n="12" who="S0619">you go no no I really am rather homesick</u>
<u n="13" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0619">it's not nothing to do with the weather but this is <unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0619">finally got seasonal affective disorder in February at the end of February</u>
<u n="17" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah that's not bad though I wonder if the snow makes your SAD happen a bit sort of later in the season? <pause dur="short"/> my</u>
<u n="18" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> delayed onset oh let me tell you a story I know you were gonna tell me a story but I'm going to tell you a story first</u>
<u n="19" who="S0618">you going to tell me a story?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0619">yeah me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have this student <pause dur="short"/> erm and we wrote well I sent her some comments for the report and she wrote this report and it was very good because he's not very good <pause dur="short"/> so his parents made him come to Friday discussion club</u>
<u n="21" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="22" who="S0619">a couple of weeks ago and on his way home he got hit by a car and has broken his leg <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0618">oh shit</u>
<u n="24" who="S0619">and he can't get out of bed for a month</u>
<u n="25" who="S0618">oh my god</u>
<u n="26" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and I feel really responsible if I'd</u>
<u n="27" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0619">said nicer things he'd have got a better report he wouldn't have been forced to go discussion club he wouldn't have broken his leg</u>
<u n="29" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that's funny</u>
<u n="30" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0618"><foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0619"><foreign lang="pol"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's <unclear/> because he's just like <pause dur="short"/> he's just the sort of kid who would get hit by a car like he's just one of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0618">jeepers that's nuts so in that chain of events you had a role to play there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know I feel really really responsible I need to email</u>
<u n="35" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="36" who="S0619">him this weekend and be like</u>
<u n="37" who="S0618">sorry</u>
<u n="38" who="S0619">sorry</u>
<u n="39" who="S0618">no but don't though because</u>
<u n="40" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no I know I'm only kidding like I know it's not my fault</u>
<u n="41" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> he's a like creator of his own reality man and I wonder has he created that? maybe that was sort of like the spiritual theoretical straw that broke the camel's back</u>
<u n="42" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm sorry sorry sorry sorry</u>
<u n="43" who="S0618">as he just thought right I'm not having this I'm not handling it any more</u>
<u n="44" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0618">I'm being pulled to do nothing I want to just lay here for a whole and then low and behold he's created that reality for himself</u>
<u n="46" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> you know what though?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0618">that's nuts</u>
<u n="48" who="S0619">the the worst part of this is if the if a student misses more than a few classes because they're ill</u>
<u n="49" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0619">they have to have lessons</u>
<u n="51" who="S0618">three isn't it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0619">I can't remember</u>
<u n="53" who="S0618">yeah and you have to do extra private lessons</u>
<u n="54" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah but I've got to go to his house cos he can't get out of bed</u>
<u n="55" who="S0618">ah shit</u>
<u n="56" who="S0619">so I've got to go to this <unclear/> kid's house</u>
<u n="57" who="S0618">where is he? is he far?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0619">I don't know</u>
<u n="59" who="S0618">surely you can refuse?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0619">well I don't want to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going and I hope that you will you'll go as well I was like no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0619">he'll survive without me</u>
<u n="63" who="S0618">I'm sure he will</u>
<u n="64" who="S0619">and you know like</u>
<u n="65" who="S0618" trans="overlap">cheers</u>
<u n="66" who="S0619">he is one of the weakest kids in that whole level</u>
<u n="67" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0619">so</u>
<u n="69" who="S0618">why is that?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0619">he's really lazy</u>
<u n="71" who="S0618">oh well</u>
<u n="72" who="S0619">and he's not very bright <pause dur="short"/> we</u>
<u n="73" who="S0618">I think the kids who aren't very bright you know if you can got the opportunity for some one to one time that might potentially inspire them or where they could grow and develop from that opportunity then great but if he's really lazy then</u>
<u n="74" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0618">you're not huh</u>
<u n="76" who="S0619">yeah we're doing this lesson once on different types of intelligence <pause dur="short"/> these eight or nine different intelligence blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> some of them are like well I think I I've got this sort of scientific intelligence because da da da or I've got personal intelligence because I'm empathetic</u>
<u n="77" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0619">and he was like out of these ones I think <unclear>I'm</unclear> sort of existential intelligence and the whole class and me just pissed ourselves <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> poor guy <pause dur="short"/> no wonder he's created a car accident to get away from you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just <pause dur="short"/> bully him relentlessly <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0619">oh god <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="83" who="S0618" trans="overlap">isn't this just excellent coffee by the way?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I've not tried it yet but it looks</u>
<u n="85" who="S0618" trans="overlap">you should have sat here so you can watch your man making it he just looks like he loves his job <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="87" who="S0618">born to do this job</u>
<u n="88" who="S0619">yeah there's a guy in Krakow as well who <pause dur="short"/> does make really good coffee</u>
<u n="89" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0619">and whenever erm he's not there <pause dur="short"/> I'm always like mm it's not gonna be as good</u>
<u n="91" who="S0618" trans="overlap">where's that?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0619">on the square <pause dur="short"/> it's called <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0618">oh I think you told me about that before</u>
<u n="94" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and I'm sad for you I'm sad because we couldn't sit and talk but obviously I understand and <unclear/> I hope tomorrow you will feel better to come to meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I miss you okay <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="95" who="S0618">I really thought she'd say phew I didn't wanna go either</u>
<u n="96" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0618">she might be jumping for joy <pause dur="short"/> the other thing that amuses me very much about this tram coffee shop <vocal desc="laugh"/> is the sex shop advert directly outside the window and a picture of <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's a banana and a measuring tape <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0619" trans="overlap">where? <pause dur="short"/> I know <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="99" who="S0618">I know <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="100" who="S0619" trans="overlap">nice</u>
<u n="101" who="S0618">we've twenty centimetres worth of banana <pause dur="short"/> cos we're metric here apparently <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure what the <pause dur="short"/> the <foreign lang="pol"/> means though</u>
<u n="102" who="S0619">no I don't know what that means</u>
<u n="103" who="S0618">I'm going to google that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0619">sure <pause dur="short"/> it's like erm <pause dur="short"/> an infinitive</u>
<u n="105" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0619">to something but I don't know what the word is</u>
<u n="107" who="S0618">yes never your infinitive split</u>
<u n="108" who="S0619">hm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0618">hm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0619">so</u>
<u n="111" who="S0618">so there we are</u>
<u n="112" who="S0619">that was my story anyway about my boy with broken leg</u>
<u n="113" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0619">for which I'm entirely responsible for</u>
<u n="115" who="S0618">not at all</u>
<u n="116" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I could have pushed him under that car myself <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh well it's all good</u>
<u n="118" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0619">I really <trunc>ha</trunc> I you know I get quite attached to these to <pause dur="short"/> these kids not all of them but</u>
<u n="121" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0619">I really do and <pause dur="short"/> I've been stressing all week about these shy kids and <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think about a lot <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think why am I thinking about these teenagers all the time?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0619">and I think it's well <pause dur="short"/> it's just your job</u>
<u n="125" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0619">I suppose</u>
<u n="127" who="S0618">yeah it's my perspective on that is that <pause dur="short"/> we all this free will thing and further from that we're all creators of the reality that we perceive so even these shy kids are having that experience in this moment for a reason</u>
<u n="128" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0618">part of their sort of higher and greater development <pause dur="short"/> and it's not your responsibility and it's not necessarily your place to interfere with their free will creation</u>
<u n="130" who="S0619">mm hm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0618">that is obviously serving them at this moment</u>
<u n="132" who="S0619">I know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0618">hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I just want them to <pause dur="short"/> I want them to pass the exam and in order to pass this exam they have to put on this persona</u>
<u n="135" who="S0618">mm hm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0619">because they're graded on <pause dur="short"/> having not having this personality but <pause dur="short"/> how they interact with another person in this language</u>
<u n="137" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0619">and if they don't have these social skills because they're too shy then they won't get the marks</u>
<u n="139" who="S0618">they won't do it</u>
<u n="140" who="S0619">and one of these boys he's trying to get into this International Baccalaureate class</u>
<u n="141" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh yeah cool</u>
<u n="142" who="S0619">he's in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> class at school and whereas <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in upper intermediate which is about right for fifteen</u>
<u n="143" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0619">he did FCE last year and got an A I think</u>
<u n="145" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="146" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and he's in CAE and he's fifteen so that's super high <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> mm there is no CAE for schools</u>
<u n="147" who="S0618">yeah so</u>
<u n="148" who="S0619">and no CPE for schools so the higher you get the harder it is</u>
<u n="149" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know he's got to have an adult conversation in his exam now about adult topics</u>
<u n="150" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and</u>
<u n="151" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that's difficult</u>
<u n="152" who="S0619">he's mature and he's very good at English like his words that he uses are really good and he's really considered and everything is perfect and there's no mistakes but it's forcing him to have an opinion</u>
<u n="153" who="S0618">mm hm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0619">and even forcing him to having a conversation like oh you finished early just chat to your partner</u>
<u n="155" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0619"><vocal desc="sigh"/> like they just can't chat and I think when I was fifteen could I chat?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0619">well <pause dur="short"/> yes but if it's with someone that I don't really know very well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know in another language</u>
<u n="159" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wondering can you give him like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="160" who="S0619" trans="overlap">just issue cue cards <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0618">a pebble or something and say right you know every time you hold this pebble in your left hand you take on a different persona</u>
<u n="162" who="S0619">mm hm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0618">and you then have the persona of somebody who does know how to have a conversation so just a little something you can keep in his pocket and slip into his hand</u>
<u n="164" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0618">when he needs to you know sort of switch and access so it's a bit like that oh I don't know what to say and well but if you did know what to say what would it be? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0619" trans="overlap">what would it be?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0618">so when you put the pebble in your hand you become a person who would know what to say</u>
<u n="168" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm mm hm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0618">just might be a little psychological trick that you can play with if he can be somebody else for long enough to <pause dur="short"/> pass</u>
<u n="170" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> with this upper intermediate group on Thursday like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> text me afterwards and said like that's the most they've all spoken er and all of them spoke the whole ninety minutes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0618">brilliant</u>
<u n="172" who="S0619">because I was like <unclear/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> whip cracking good</u>
<u n="174" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and some of them I was like no not enough no not enough no say it again say it again it's not good enough</u>
<u n="175" who="S0618">good for you</u>
<u n="176" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and they were like oh</u>
<u n="177" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="178" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0619">you know and like giving me like evils I was like no not having it</u>
<u n="180" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0618">good for you</u>
<u n="182" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so horrible but I said they're not my class fuck them er <pause dur="short"/> and so</u>
<u n="183" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah they used to be mine I feel a little bit protective of them</u>
<u n="184" who="S0619" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0619">it was this boy there were only seven of them there were four people missing there was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh yes are we in the adult class now?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="189" who="S0618">no</u>
<u n="190" who="S0619">he's a teenager</u>
<u n="191" who="S0618">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0619" trans="overlap">he was sat next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and he needed like <pause dur="short"/> a <trunc>ne</trunc></u>
<u n="193" who="S0618" trans="overlap">a cattle prod up the rear?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0619">well he needed a bit of an attitude transplant</u>
<u n="195" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="196" who="S0619">because <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think he was like a bit sort of oh <pause dur="short"/> affronted I suppose</u>
<u n="197" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0619">er and then there was another girl who was like dead sassy I was like woah woah woah love you'll get nowhere with that attitude</u>
<u n="199" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh was she sat next to her brother who was the muscle man with tattoos?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no no they weren't there they weren't there</u>
<u n="201" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="202" who="S0619">I really hoped they were cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has warned me about them</u>
<u n="203" who="S0618">I know</u>
<u n="204" who="S0619">and the</u>
<u n="205" who="S0618" trans="overlap">she kept flashing her cleavage at me it's like just don't do that <pause dur="short"/> don't do that</u>
<u n="206" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said something like erm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0618">I mean this is in October as well November or some cold month yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says and something like</u>
<u n="209" who="S0618" trans="overlap">put them away love</u>
<u n="210" who="S0619">asked them <pause dur="short"/> he asked them like something about having friends or something and then <pause dur="short"/> they were like oh well we just have the same friends cos we're brother and sister it it was just what you don't have any other friends apart from your mutual friends because your and they were like no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="211" who="S0618">they're going to be having babies together</u>
<u n="212" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he was getting a bit like in between us like oh sibling friends</u>
<u n="213" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0618">yes</u>
<u n="215" who="S0619">so I was really looking forward to going in and like</u>
<u n="216" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0619">having a bit of a go <unclear>at</unclear> this brother and sister</u>
<u n="218" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I really liked I really like him actually</u>
<u n="219" who="S0619" trans="overlap">but they weren't there</u>
<u n="220" who="S0618">cos he always had really cool hair he's obviously a lot older than everybody else in the class got some interesting tattoos</u>
<u n="221" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah really sad he wasn't there</u>
<u n="222" who="S0618">he's into cars you know he's you could get you can find things that he was interested in</u>
<u n="223" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu uhu</u>
<u n="224" who="S0618">like tattoos and cars to talk to him about mechanics and things like that so you know he was up for that but with her she just sort of wanted to sit and pout and put her cleavage on show which I just didn't really get</u>
<u n="225" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I didn't have either of them sadly I did have a girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's incredibly pretty with really long blonde hair</u>
<u n="226" who="S0618">is she quite short?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0618">yeah I think I remember her</u>
<u n="229" who="S0619">she needed a bit of a <pause dur="short"/> roll your eyes at me love <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0618">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0619">rolling them into next week in a minute <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="232" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0619">but I really enjoyed and there was one girl who <pause dur="short"/> I said this is gonna be a speaking and conversation lesson you won't need your textbooks and she just went all the blood drained from her face</u>
<u n="234" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0619">I was like don't have to look so worried</u>
<u n="236" who="S0618">she probably looked like that emoticon from Scream</u>
<u n="237" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she did that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0619">is it that bad?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0618">nobody's going to die it's okay</u>
<u n="242" who="S0619">really no need to look so worried <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then everyone looked at her I was like I'm sorry <unclear/> draw attention to this incredibly shy girl</u>
<u n="243" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0619">ah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> I'm not really horrible but some of them just need a kick</u>
<u n="245" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not really horrible but <pause dur="short"/> yeah there's no harm there there's no harm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no it won't do them any harm it's character building <vocal desc="laugh"/> one day I'm gonna work in a boarding school <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then shit's gonna go down</u>
<u n="247" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> oh she's says she says I'm still a little weak and I've said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that I'm not sure how long I'll be able to stay and even I have a cold today and a cough and a red nose <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's dripping</u>
<u n="249" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh bless her she shouldn't be going at all jeez</u>
<u n="250" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> stay <pause dur="short"/> in bed</u>
<u n="251" who="S0618">yeah she can catch up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for a coffee next week</u>
<u n="252" who="S0619">yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="253" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0619">she'll make herself worse</u>
<u n="255" who="S0618">yep</u>
<u n="256" who="S0619">poor thing</u>
<u n="257" who="S0618">oh nice poncho</u>
<u n="258" who="S0619">I know she looks <unclear/> doesn't she?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0619">no which</u>
<u n="261" who="S0618">I do like a poncho if ever I live in South America it'll be so I can wear a poncho every day</u>
<u n="262" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that the only reason?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0618">huh?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0619">is that the only reason?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0618">well no I'm sure it's a wonderful country with</u>
<u n="266" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0619">huge expansive rich culture to explore <pause dur="short"/> I do particularly like music I've got a friend who's exploring erm Cuba at the moment <pause dur="short"/> and she went to the Buena Vista Social club yesterday</u>
<u n="268" who="S0618" trans="overlap">nice</u>
<u n="269" who="S0619">which is like the music place of Cuba <pause dur="short"/> and yeah <pause dur="short"/> years ago I saw the film Buena Vista Social Club and I presume half of the old musicians who were in it are dead now but it's a wonderful story about all of these sort of real erm <pause dur="short"/> guys from Cuba and other parts of South America who play their instruments exceptionally well and <pause dur="short"/> erm they were taken to the States I think it might even have been Vegas or New York or LA somewhere glitzy jazzy <pause dur="short"/> erm to perform and they'd never really been out of their home towns and sort of explored wider parts of the world it was just a sort of a documentary sort of following them and their adventures it was really good <pause dur="short"/> great music <pause dur="short"/> yeah this erm Austrian farm that I could go work at <pause dur="short"/> is full of South American people I think it's mostly South American owned</u>
<u n="270" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> nice oh Spanish</u>
<u n="271" who="S0618">yeah so I could learn Spanish there and then maybe end up in Spain rather than Portugal at the end of the year <pause dur="short"/> and part of what attracted to me to that place is they've got a picture they've got a power place in their garden which presumably is some sort of lay lines type place but they've sort of drawn out this grid in the land and sort of planted it into the landscaping</u>
<u n="272" who="S0619">mm hm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0618">er just looks really cool <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think a lot of places I mean yes I do believe in earth energies and you can feel these power places but I think also humans can build up <pause dur="short"/> the energy of a place through intent so if they've been focusing on that energy of that particular place for years then</u>
<u n="274" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0618">it's gonna feel pretty powerful because of the energy they're putting into it</u>
<u n="276" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm for all the people</u>
<u n="277" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that could be pretty exciting too some great reviews for there <pause dur="short"/> and I haven't actually heard back yet from this place in Poland where I'm meant to have this Skype interview this weekend so <pause dur="short"/> because I'm keen to get something organised before I leave Poland <pause dur="short"/> I might just apply to some other places when I get home today</u>
<u n="278" who="S0619">good for you motivation station</u>
<u n="279" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well and as displacement activity to avoid packing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0619">yay</u>
<u n="281" who="S0618" trans="overlap">for a little bit longer <pause dur="short"/> I'm doing pretty well cos there's not that much <pause dur="short"/> quite frankly but it's deciding what to keep in the van and what to take back to England and store <pause dur="short"/> particularly in light of it being my uncle's loft rather than the spare room</u>
<u n="282" who="S0619">right okay</u>
<u n="283" who="S0618">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> it'll come together</u>
<u n="285" who="S0618">it will it is it's good</u>
<u n="286" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> I just don't know what to do with myself</u>
<u n="287" who="S0618"><shift new="singing"/> I just don't know what to do with myself <shift new="normal"/> is that Dusty Springfield?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0619"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="289" who="S0618">doo doo</u>
<u n="290" who="S0619">I just need to sort of just chill out a little bit</u>
<u n="291" who="S0618">when's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> back?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0619">tomorrow lunch time</u>
<u n="293" who="S0618">cool so you've got another night</u>
<u n="294" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I'm just gonna really take it easy</u>
<u n="295" who="S0618">good for you</u>
<u n="296" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> go to the gym in the morning and <pause dur="short"/> see how I feel <pause dur="short"/> just want it to be <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="297" who="S0618">have you got sun on your balcony at this time?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0619">only in the mornings</u>
<u n="299" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0619">until about two</u>
<u n="301" who="S0618">is it in the kitchen yet? <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0619">no</u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<u n="303" who="S0619">no <pause dur="short"/> oh dear nice dog</u>
<u n="304" who="S0618">mm German shepherd</u>
<u n="305" who="S0619">mm they're cute</u>
<u n="306" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I don't know why people need to hold their dog so close to the lead that's probably the <trunc>le</trunc>least pully best behaved dog that's walked past</u>
<u n="307" who="S0619">mm hm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0618">mm I really do feel for dogs here it's such a different culture erm one of my neighbours has got a new puppy and I only know that cos it's outside yipping its heart out obviously missing its mother and missing contact with its siblings</u>
<u n="309" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="310" who="S0618">erm and they just leave it there and they're outside in the snow they're outside in the wind they're outside in the rain and a lot of them have kennels and shelters but I'd have called the RSPCA by now I called the USPCA on one of my neighbours when I lived in <anon type="place"/> and had two he had two dogs taken away because of me <pause dur="short"/> fucking good job too the bastard</u>
<u n="311" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0618">erm but that job that job that dog used to live out in the garden and didn't have much by way of shelter now <pause dur="short"/> to be fair to people here the difference is that guy just let the dog live in its own shit and never cleaned it up</u>
<u n="313" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0618">and the conditions were squalid and disgusting and it was often chained up and not having an opportunity to even run around the garden where as here at least the dogs that are outdoors in minus temperatures at least they get to run around a bit so I suppose that's something in a way but even so</u>
<u n="315" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand one of my students was telling me that she's got this German shepherd at home who lives outside er and she was like it's such a nice sweet so gentle</u>
<u n="316" who="S0618">well let it in your bed then</u>
<u n="317" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I said well yeah let it in your house hang out with it more</u>
<u n="318" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0619">and she was like I was like well what do you use it for? and she was like oh well to guard the property and I was like</u>
<u n="320" who="S0618">you live in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> what are you guarding?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0619" trans="overlap">like no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> one there's no crime</u>
<u n="322" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0619">and two like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> no offence to you love but you work in the court you know you're not a judge she's not a lawyer she's in sort of administration what are you going to have in this house that's</u>
<u n="324" who="S0618">that's nickable</u>
<u n="325" who="S0619">that's nickable? apart from like TVs and laptops</u>
<u n="326" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and why this fear of crime?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0619"><unclear>which</unclear> every house in <anon type="place"/> has</u>
<u n="328" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so rather than get a dog that you ignore you're better off not buying newspapers or watching television <pause dur="short"/> problem solved</u>
<u n="329" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know and it's just like well</u>
<u n="330" who="S0618">so crime isn't a problem it's the fear of crime I wonder if that's why all my neighbours have dogs that live outside? <pause dur="short"/> a lot of them have this <foreign lang="pol">Uvargu</foreign> pies signs on the cage <vocal desc="laugh"/> when they look out there are pies <pause dur="short"/> yeah but erm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0619">yeah but I <trunc>ju</trunc> well if you're worried about that get like a better alarm system</u>
<u n="332" who="S0618">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you know <pause dur="short"/> a light that comes on</u>
<u n="334" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so there's one German shepherd near me but apart from that oh there's one boxer apart from that they're all yippy dogs yip yip yip I mean the worst that's gonna do is bite your ankle as you're kicking it so</u>
<u n="335" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm mm I suppose it wakes you up and you</u>
<u n="336" who="S0618">well <pause dur="short"/> I guess so</u>
<u n="337" who="S0619" trans="overlap">then you look out of the window</u>
<u n="338" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and there's one house that at least has two little yippy dogs which I feel is not so bad and actually near the bus stop there are two dogs</u>
<u n="339" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah just play together</u>
<u n="340" who="S0618">so they can play together and they do <pause dur="short"/> yeah and the two that are near me that play together in their front garden there's like a mesh bench and then there's another dog on its own in the other garden and I feel really sorry for it that it can't play with them as part of pack</u>
<u n="341" who="S0619" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> like the boy in striped pyjamas</u>
<u n="342" who="S0618">ah I know it's little doggy no mates but has got chicken friends</u>
<u n="343" who="S0619">nice</u>
<u n="344" who="S0618">so all my neighbours have chickens and ducks as well</u>
<u n="345" who="S0619">nice</u>
<u n="346" who="S0618">so</u>
<u n="347" who="S0619">oh I really miss dogs</u>
<u n="348" who="S0618">and there's another place I think that was in Austria too <pause dur="short"/> which is just like <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm these people take in all the unwanted dogs and cats and ducks and hens and everything</u>
<u n="349" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh I wanna work there</u>
<u n="350" who="S0618">so a big part of your job is clearing up shit from animals which I'm quite up for erm and the reviews are hilarious because the reviews range from oh it's brilliant there's one cat that comes and sits on your shoulder and you work away with it like it's a parrot and you stay there all day erm through to other reviews that have said oh there are cats everywhere it was disgusting they were even on the kitchen table and blah blah blah so it's like</u>
<u n="351" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="352" who="S0618">people's reactions to this situation are really quite different so I thought I might like to go there was well</u>
<u n="353" who="S0619">sounds fun</u>
<u n="354" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0619">the world's your oyster</u>
<u n="356" who="S0618">and I wanna learn to ride a horse <pause dur="short"/> so this time next year I want to know all about how to keep bees all about how to grow vegetables in a bio dynamic organic kind of a way and I wanna ride a horse</u>
<u n="357" who="S0619">by this time next year I want to be able to speak fluent Spanish</u>
<u n="358" who="S0618">cool</u>
<u n="359" who="S0619">cool dude</u>
<u n="360" who="S0618">and be living and working</u>
<u n="361" who="S0619">yeah in Andalusia</u>
<u n="362" who="S0618">cool</u>
<u n="363" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0618">see the mountains</u>
<u n="365" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I really want to go to South America but <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> the Zika virus is putting me off</u>
<u n="366" who="S0618">oh that's just fear it's bollocks</u>
<u n="367" who="S0619">there's loads of kids being born with small heads</u>
<u n="368" who="S0618">no it's not real</u>
<u n="369" who="S0619">what you mean it's not real?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it's a it's a media fabrication</u>
<u n="371" who="S0619">in what way?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0618">so symptoms exist and things are happening and people are happening and shit and stuff but it's like it's just like bovine thingy BSE and swine flu and bird flu and that AK47</u>
<u n="373" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0618">what are one thing whatever that virus was they bring it out every couple of years it's just to keep humanity in its place and spread fear it's not real <pause dur="short"/> what was last years in that tiny village in the west of the massive continent of Africa? what was that one? <pause dur="short"/> that everyone got all shit scared about</u>
<u n="375" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh I can't remember</u>
<u n="376" who="S0618">and some American person died or nearly died</u>
<u n="377" who="S0619">can't remember</u>
<u n="378" who="S0618">oh can't remember</u>
<u n="379" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> something nice</u>
<u n="380" who="S0618">yeah but no there's something every year it's all bollocks so no don't let fear rule your life</u>
<u n="381" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0618">in fact yeah going back to what you were saying earlier</u>
<u n="383" who="S0619">about what?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0618"><trunc>mo</trunc> be motivated by joy</u>
<u n="385" who="S0619">that's true</u>
<u n="386" who="S0618">see joy or fear <pause dur="short"/> choose the joy man</u>
<u n="387" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="388" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0619">Spain first though get my Spanish get well learn to speak Spanish</u>
<u n="390" who="S0618">cool</u>
<u n="391" who="S0619">and one of the Chinese teacher at school wants English lessons</u>
<u n="392" who="S0618">right</u>
<u n="393" who="S0619">so with me I think er and I want Spanish lessons from the Spanish teacher <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it's like money sort of going everywhere</u>
<u n="394" who="S0618">so does the Spanish teacher want to learn Chinese? that can work out really well</u>
<u n="395" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know it would really work no one pays anything <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0618">yeah there's a let scheme in Cambridge <pause dur="short"/> local something or other trading scheme where you do exactly that so you go and do an hour of something</u>
<u n="397" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0618">for someone and they give you a credit and then you spend your credit with someone else so there's no money</u>
<u n="399" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's a good idea</u>
<u n="400" who="S0618">it's just like a skills exchange this is the future</u>
<u n="401" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0618">I look forward to a moneyless economy</u>
<u n="403" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0618">in fact yeah I suppose that's the collapse of a global economy really <pause dur="short"/> which I think we're kind of on the brink of you know there are several trillions of pounds owed by whom to whom <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know it's all</u>
<u n="405" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="406" who="S0618">it's all sort of <unclear/> really isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah careful with Spanish though I had a friend who went to South America and used his Spanish and I can't remember so don't quote me exactly but I think the word for prostitute and the word for hotel are quite similar</u>
<u n="407" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0618">so he was actually wanting a hotel <pause dur="short"/> but nearly ran into a few difficulties</u>
<u n="409" who="S0619">that's hilarious</u>
<u n="410" who="S0618">yeah so I think some things can be lost in translation between Spain and South America <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0619">hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm I'm reading a book that erm <pause dur="short"/> don't really well so far I'm on twenty percent and there's no plot</u>
<u n="412" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0619">which is fine if <pause dur="short"/> it's fine if books have no plot if they're really super engaging and have really engaging characters and it just doesn't <pause dur="short"/> it's just</u>
<u n="414" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/> is it bringing you joy? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0619">I'm hoping that it will do in the next forty percent of the book and then I'll feel inclined to finish it</u>
<u n="416" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0619">at the moment I'm just like where is this book going? <pause dur="short"/> it's making me slow down on my reading cos I can't be bothered to get through it</u>
<u n="418" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="419" who="S0619">so I'm sticking to my resolutions which is Woman's Hour every day <vocal desc="laugh"/> lots of books</u>
<u n="420" who="S0618">cool</u>
<u n="421" who="S0619">Spanish <pause dur="short"/> doing very well</u>
<u n="422" who="S0618">good for you</u>
<u n="423" who="S0619">I've abandoned doing the Guardian crossword everyday <pause dur="short"/> cos that was taking up too much time and getting me down</u>
<u n="424" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0619">so that resolution failed but</u>
<u n="426" who="S0618">oh well</u>
<u n="427" who="S0619"><unclear/> there's always next year</u>
<u n="428" who="S0618">well rather than that resolution having failed maybe that resolution just wasn't necessarily appropriate for this stage and point in your life</u>
<u n="429" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0618">so <pause dur="short"/> it's been put on the back burner or the long finger and will re-emerge at a more appropriate time <pause dur="short"/> or be replaced by something different</u>
<u n="431" who="S0619">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> such pretty colours</u>
<u n="432" who="S0618">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> pigeons</u>
<u n="433" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0618" trans="overlap">gorgeous aren't they? technically that's a rock dove cos it's got two black stripes</u>
<u n="435" who="S0619">oh</u>
<u n="436" who="S0618">but well they're all much of a muchness really aren't they?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're gorgeous I love starlings for their colours <pause dur="short"/> I feel a bit cheated in a way cos I was kind of taught as a small child that starlings and all forms of crow or carrion are just</u>
<u n="439" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0618">nasty vermin like creatures</u>
<u n="441" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="442" who="S0618">and I never really appreciated them and now I've kind of done away with that out of date belief system I can really enjoy them starlings in particular are beautiful I remember at being in a hostel in New Zealand and the woman who was running the hostel being delighted almost showing off telling me we get starlings here wow <pause dur="short"/> but that was just yeah real nice they're beautiful all those rainbow colours and I love the noise that starlings make too</u>
<u n="443" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right I'm just looking at the weather because it's changed and obviously now it's nice and blue skies but it's still raining tomorrow</u>
<u n="444" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0619">oh well</u>
<u n="446" who="S0618">have you got a brolly?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0619">yeah but it's fallen to bits</u>
<u n="448" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="449" who="S0619">you know these erm <pause dur="short"/> does not spark off joy</u>
<u n="450" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="451" who="S0619">it was like a really cheap one and all of the prongs spokes <pause dur="short"/> are starting to rust</u>
<u n="452" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="453" who="S0619">you know like in a circle sort of where there joint is</u>
<u n="454" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0619">and I'm really sort of anticipating that one day that it's gonna slowly slowly collapse and close in on my head</u>
<u n="456" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0619">you know like one of those like I don't know what they're called Venus flytrap <vocal desc="laugh"/> on my head</u>
<u n="458" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> the Venus flytrap of umbrellas I like that</u>
<u n="459" who="S0619">so it's just like the saddest umbrella of all time</u>
<u n="460" who="S0618">so a decent brolly is next on the <pause dur="short"/> purchase list</u>
<u n="461" who="S0619" trans="overlap">but then again I don't want to fucking have to buy an umbrella</u>
<u n="462" who="S0618">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="463" who="S0619">cos then it's inviting rain</u>
<u n="464" who="S0618" trans="overlap">cos if you're only here till June and you're gonna have to either leave it behind or take it with you</u>
<u n="465" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0618">then yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0618">but then is there space in your life in Spain for an umbrella that sparks joy?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0619">it doesn't rain in Spain <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0618">mainly on the plane</u>
<u n="471" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0619">family in Andalusia <unclear/> will never end</u>
<u n="473" who="S0618">oh dear</u>
<u n="474" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right what time is it for a wander or a coffee or a tea or a</u>
<u n="475" who="S0618">no I'm alright on the beverage front it's three thirty-eight so</u>
<u n="476" who="S0619" trans="overlap">got half an hour</u>
<u n="477" who="S0618">yeah half and hour <pause dur="short"/> do you fancy a walk in the sun?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah where to?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0618">I don't know just a general sunny amble</u>
<u n="480" who="S0619">walk down is that market still on <pause dur="short"/> at this time? probably not</u>
<u n="481" who="S0618">no <pause dur="short"/> in fact no I didn't come that way on the bus today I got off a stop early and walked by the river instead so I don't know</u>
<u n="482" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I don't think it'll be a bit late now</u>
<u n="483" who="S0618">but I don't think it will no I think it's half day closing on a Saturday <pause dur="short"/> you think peak retail day when you get the maximum amount of the local population not at work and therefore able to shop and spend money <pause dur="short"/> that they might avail of these consumer opportunities but</u>
<u n="484" who="S0619">you know what else is <unclear/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and another thing</u>
<u n="486" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s list of very small complaints</u>
<u n="487" who="S0618">better out than in</u>
<u n="488" who="S0619">they keep closing <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0618">yes I noticed the <anon type="place"/> one has closed</u>
<u n="490" who="S0619">and the <anon type="place"/> one</u>
<u n="491" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and the Zenit one you've gotta go all the way to <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="492" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> first I was like oh I'll just go to <anon type="place"/> so I can go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0618">yeah no</u>
<u n="494" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="495" who="S0618">closed <pause dur="short"/> I could of told you that if I'd have known you were going to <anon type="place"/>'s</u>
<u n="496" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I know it's alright well I went to the one on <pause dur="short"/> here</u>
<u n="497" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0618">oh so this one's still open</u>
<u n="500" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0618">that's good</u>
<u n="502" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0618">well that's good to know</u>
<u n="506" who="S0619">I went before I met you and just nipped in because <pause dur="short"/> this one at <anon type="place"/> doesn't open on Sundays <pause dur="short"/> and I thought well I can't wait another week to go</u>
<u n="507" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it's not open on Sundays?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0619">even though it's on the big retail park</u>
<u n="509" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0619">cos I walked past that like walked past last Sunday and it was about ten am and it wasn't open</u>
<u n="511" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I thought I can't wait until next Saturday <vocal desc="laugh"/> to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0618">yeah I know</u>
<u n="514" who="S0619">so I just don't have time <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> never mind</u>
<u n="515" who="S0618">no <anon type="place"/> is the only source of one hundred percent recycled toilet roll that isn't at least three ply <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0619">good for you and it has really nice dates</u>
<u n="517" who="S0618">and it has lovely moist dates yeah that's very true <pause dur="short"/> well I don't mind the <anon type="place"/> ones in the packet they're not as good as the moist ones from <anon type="place"/> but they're not bad <pause dur="short"/> oh how was your Alma hummus?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> just the same as like</u>
<u n="519" who="S0618">just a bit too blended</u>
<u n="520" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0618">I like the look of the little pesto blob on the top though that really sparked me with ooh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it was okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was okay it tasted like hummus</u>
<u n="523" who="S0618">but a bit too</u>
<u n="524" who="S0619">but it wasn't the <foreign lang="pol"/> one this magic hummus</u>
<u n="525" who="S0618">the <foreign lang="pol"/> one yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0619">that was all hummus</u>
<u n="527" who="S0618">that was all chunky</u>
<u n="528" who="S0619">it was like actual <unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0618">yeah you could tell it's related to chickpeas rather than being smooth</u>
<u n="530" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah blended into non-existent <unclear/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0618">gonna have to make some it's the only way <pause dur="short"/> so you're coming for lentil pie tomorrow?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0619">yes please</u>
<u n="533" who="S0618">it's got booze in is that alright for non-drinking February? theoretically speaking the alcohol will have burned off in all that heat <pause dur="short"/> but it did cross my mind</u>
<u n="534" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we'll get pissed <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0618">no definitely not definitely not but it did cross my mind what do I do with the other half of bottle that's not in the lentil pie?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="537" who="S0618">ha ha ha ha ha ha <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I might have to drink that</u>
<u n="538" who="S0619">I think I just I just feel fine like I don't feel inclined and there's been loads of opportunities you know like on Tuesday night and last night when I was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like</u>
<u n="539" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0619">in normal world</u>
<u n="541" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="542" who="S0619">I would just had a pint</u>
<u n="543" who="S0618">crossed the square and gone down for a drink yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a pint with a meal and a pint somewhere else afterwards</u>
<u n="545" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0619">and no I was drinking tea</u>
<u n="547" who="S0618">it's good <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0619">it was yeah I'm it's not like I'm never gonna drink again but</u>
<u n="549" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0619">not yet</u>
<u n="551" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> going away to the UK will be my test of whether I've broken my psychological addiction</u>
<u n="552" who="S0619">mm hm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'll see cos there's you know I I will drink <pause dur="short"/> from whenever I you know I am there because it's a social thing to do I'm back with friends who drink quite a lot actually and particularly my uncle <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm but yeah it would be interesting to see when I'm there and indeed probably more telling once I leave there if I'm craving booze again</u>
<u n="554" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0618">cos I still do crave it at the moment yes but nothing like I craved it in January</u>
<u n="556" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> mm hm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0618">so <pause dur="short"/> you know I've had phases like that in the past with sugar or with biscuits or whatever and once I'm off it for a period of time the cravings disappear I'm fine</u>
<u n="558" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0618">I'll keeping checking out boots you know cos I could do with a decent pair of work boots for working on a farm but most I've seen seem quite suedey</u>
<u n="560" who="S0619">mm hm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0619">and I think I want a pair of leather boots that I can polish up and water protect</u>
<u n="562" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you need like a yeah camping shop or a sports type shop</u>
<u n="563" who="S0618">yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a look in Berlin actually</u>
<u n="564" who="S0619">walking boots leather of walking boots</u>
<u n="565" who="S0618">well I've got leather walking boots but they're proper Italian leather chunky monkey heavy proper mountaineering boots</u>
<u n="566" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0618">they're too heavyweight for</u>
<u n="568" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0618">farming <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know and I've got my half welly yard boots that I bought in Newmarket from the horse shop <pause dur="short"/> so they'll be good on colder or wetter days</u>
<u n="570" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0618">but I do need a common or garden <pause dur="short"/> grafting in the summer pair <pause dur="short"/> that aren't suede right</u>
<u n="572" who="S0619" trans="overlap">fancy a walk</u>
<u n="573" who="S0618">yeah let's see some sun <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> say bye <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0619">goodbye <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0618">bye</u>
<u n="576" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
