<text id="S7JF">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:27:49</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0039 S0043 S0126 S0158</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>University library, Salford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>Holidays</topics>
		<activity>Librarians Talking about Holidays</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0039">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Manchester, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>English</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>Northern</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Prestwich, Lancashire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Library Assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0043">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Halifax, Yorkshire, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>English</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>Yorkshire</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Salford, Greater Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12 years, 5 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services Assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0126">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Ireland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Irish</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>r_ireland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>r_ireland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>r_ireland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Library Assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0158">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>English</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>London</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Blackburn, Lancashire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12 years, 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>E-Learning support Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Fluent</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0043">we'll talking about holidays <pause dur="short"/> are we starting now? Is it recording? Right I'm going to holiday this year to Majorca in June</u>
<u n="2" who="S0039">alright <pause dur="short"/> I've just got back  I've just got back  from holiday <pause dur="short"/> I I was in Spain in Andalucía for a few days</u>
<u n="3" who="S0043">did you not go to <trunc>Nu</trunc> Nerja</u>
<u n="4" who="S0039">it was Nerja  it was Nerja</u>
<u n="5" who="S0043">Cos I've been looking at Nerja this morning cos we're looking to go somewhere in October</u>
<u n="6" who="S0039">it's very <pause dur="short"/> it's nice yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pleasant</u>
<u n="7" who="S0158">okay <pause dur="short"/> sorry I just realised <pause dur="short"/> I thought <pause dur="short"/> I was miles away but I'll be going somewhere in this country I have never been</u>
<u n="8" who="S0043">excellent</u>
<u n="9" who="S0158">except before I was born</u>
<u n="10" who="S0043">go on</u>
<u n="11" who="S0158">mum and Dad went to the Isle of Wight for their honeymoon right?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0043">and is that where it happened</u>
<u n="13" who="S0158">no</u>
<u n="14" who="S0039">it had already happened by then</u>
<u n="15" who="S0158" trans="overlap">it had already happened before then</u>
<u n="16" who="S0043"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh god</u>
<u n="17" who="S0158">so I'm going to the Isle of Wight</u>
<u n="18" who="S0039">the Isle of Wight</u>
<u n="19" who="S0158">at the end of May for the first time in fifty-two years as it were</u>
<u n="20" who="S0039">you go to the Scilly Isles</u>
<u n="21" who="S0158">we do every year</u>
<u n="22" who="S0043">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="23" who="S0158">so and it's a place we've never been to and the boss said right <pause dur="short"/> my first holiday back in eh em you know adult life as it were after being ill for all that while <pause dur="short"/> and it's somewhere she's never been <pause dur="short"/> so that's what's happened</u>
<u n="24" who="S0043">excellent</u>
<u n="25" who="S0039">and it was her her shout was it?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0158">oh yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I don't get in the way I just</u>
<u n="27" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0158">how much do you <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0043">do as you're told <pause dur="short"/> give her the money and do as you're told</u>
<u n="30" who="S0158">we're actually staying on the southern bit of the island near St Catherine's something point lighthouse <pause dur="short"/> actually underneath</u>
<u n="31" who="S0043">ah very apt</u>
<u n="32" who="S0158">light <trunc>ve</trunc> very underneath the lighthouse as I understand it <pause dur="short"/> and it's got em a window with sort of lighthouse views</u>
<u n="33" who="S0039">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0158">which should be fairly spectacular</u>
<u n="35" who="S0039">that sounds pretty good yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to eh going to Edinburgh in a couple of weeks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> just to see some friends up there <pause dur="short"/> but I'd class that as a little holiday <pause dur="short"/> a mini break yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0158" trans="overlap">yeah I would <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0039">you go up there <pause dur="short"/> you've been up there a bit</u>
<u n="38" who="S0043">I've been up there a few times <pause dur="short"/> yeah quite quite a few times</u>
<u n="39" who="S0158">do they still let you in?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0043">yes they still let me back in <pause dur="short"/> cos I do originate from Scotland</u>
<u n="41" who="S0039">do you?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0043">I'm half Scottish</u>
<u n="43" who="S0039">can't hear that in your voice</u>
<u n="44" who="S0043">no no no it's not the <pause dur="short"/> my dad's</u>
<u n="45" who="S0158" trans="overlap">is this the <unclear/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0043">well actually like my dad and my granddad on my mum's side <pause dur="short"/> so on both sides I'm Scottish <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0039">Cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always used to think you were Icelandic didn't he?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0043">well that's because of a student <pause dur="short"/> that was was because of a student <pause dur="short"/> a student asked me he says can I ask you a question and he said  he said  where do you come from? And I thought where where does he mean meaning what county? I'm local</u>
<u n="49" who="S0158">you should have said I've just come from off the shelf</u>
<u n="50" who="S0043"><trunc>Shu</trunc> shut up <pause dur="short"/> well that's what I said I said  to him I said well I said I come from Yorkshire originally <pause dur="short"/> no no no he said em he said you look like my mother and she's Icelandic</u>
<u n="51" who="S0039">it's to do with your eyes that I think</u>
<u n="52" who="S0043">you see <pause dur="short"/> so yeah so there you go so</u>
<u n="53" who="S0158">oh you know it's like the I I know  I know  what he means</u>
<u n="54" who="S0043">quite a bit Bjork like sort sort of type thing as well</u>
<u n="55" who="S0039">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see where he's coming from</u>
<u n="56" who="S0158">panda eyes this morning</u>
<u n="57" who="S0043">shut up</u>
<u n="58" who="S0039">pardon?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0043">and em panda eyes</u>
<u n="60" who="S0039">he's full of it today isn't he? It's only cos he's on tape</u>
<u n="61" who="S0043">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you don't know cos the Icelandic influence could have come down to Scotland you know</u>
<u n="62" who="S0039">definitely without doubt <pause dur="short"/> it's like the west coast of Ireland isn't it? They always go on about the Spanish influence</u>
<u n="63" who="S0043">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0039">dark skin dark hair dark eyes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0043">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0039">right that's me finished on holidays anyway</u>
<u n="67" who="S0158">I've got loads more to talk about you cut in</u>
<u n="68" who="S0039">oh yeah sorry I've loads to talk about <pause dur="short"/> you you carry on</u>
<u n="69" who="S0043"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't even joined in yet <pause dur="short"/> where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0158">then in later this year</u>
<u n="71" who="S0043">oh go ahead then</u>
<u n="72" who="S0158">oh yeah absolutely bloody hell back in the swing of things <pause dur="short"/> big time <pause dur="short"/> where are we going then? Ah we're going to France again</u>
<u n="73" who="S0043">where do you go to? Where do you go? When you <trunc>we</trunc> say again why where do you go?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0158">we've been well we've been to France several times <pause dur="short"/> this is the most recent time and we're going to the same place we've been before which is just to the east of Paris</u>
<u n="75" who="S0043">right</u>
<u n="76" who="S0158">at one of the Holiday Property One places <pause dur="short"/> so that'll be fun</u>
<u n="77" who="S0043">well that's that's what we're looking at <pause dur="short"/> we're looking at just before the the cold weather starts <pause dur="short"/> it's sort of cold now isn't it? But before winter starts again we're looking to go somewhere at the beginning of October</u>
<u n="78" who="S0158">are you <trunc>al</trunc> are you allowed to have time off then?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0043">beginning of October? Too right I am <pause dur="short"/> it's September's a bit dodgy <pause dur="short"/> september's the dodgy month <pause dur="short"/> but beginning of October and to avoid the school holidays in October as well</u>
<u n="80" who="S0158">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="81" who="S0043">so just get it cheaper but sort of like southern Spain something like that</u>
<u n="82" who="S0158">mm <pause dur="short"/> somewhere hot</u>
<u n="83" who="S0043">somewhere hot and and cheap really <pause dur="short"/> and for that time of year</u>
<u n="84" who="S0158">of course <unclear/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0043">well cos you're going to go to the Canary's and you're going to be guaranteed the weather <pause dur="short"/> but it's expensive still <pause dur="short"/> for that time of year anyway</u>
<u n="86" who="S0158">go to Majorca</u>
<u n="87" who="S0043">well we're going to Majorca in June you see so <pause dur="short"/> I know there's different parts but it's nice to go somewhere different</u>
<u n="88" who="S0158">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0043">has to be somewhere that I haven't been though cos I've been to Majorca five times <pause dur="short"/> this place we're going to</u>
<u n="90" who="S0158">have you? Alright</u>
<u n="91" who="S0043">so it would be nice to go somewhere different <pause dur="short"/> yeah it'll be nice <pause dur="short"/> so we'll see</u>
<u n="92" who="S0158">you're not going clubbing in Ibiza again like you did</u>
<u n="93" who="S0043">yeah right <pause dur="short"/> that's <unclear/> me <pause dur="short"/> clubbing in Ibiza <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0158">you could take the kids then couldn't you?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0043">they wouldn't be see dead with me <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't be seen dead with me dancing and clubbing <pause dur="short"/> can you imagine me on that program? You know that program Sun Sea and Suspicious Parents <pause dur="short"/> have you ever watched that? It's fab</u>
<u n="96" who="S0158">you haven't got to worry about the last part</u>
<u n="97" who="S0043">it's like <trunc>teenag</trunc> teenagers go on holiday by <trunc>themse</trunc> with their friends by <trunc>thems</trunc> for the first time without their parents <pause dur="short"/> unbeknown to them the parents have gone along and they're spying on them with a camera <pause dur="short"/> they're being they know they're being filmed and stuff but they don't know what for <pause dur="short"/> they've been obviously been told something different <pause dur="short"/> but em and then they come clean at the end</u>
<u n="98" who="S0158">what can we do for you? <event desc="recording skips"/> Do you want us to keep going? Okay <pause dur="short"/> how are we doing then?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0043">where did I end up? I don't know</u>
<u n="100" who="S0158">you were talking about the sprogs going on holiday</u>
<u n="101" who="S0043">aye about this eh that program</u>
<u n="102" who="S0158">going on holiday <pause dur="short"/> the Sun Sea and Suspicious Parents</u>
<u n="103" who="S0043">parent yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0158">and you haven't got parents anymore so you haven't got the problem</u>
<u n="105" who="S0043">yeah but I <trunc>j</trunc> could do on mind you I've got the problem anyway cos they've been on holiday loads of times themselves mine anyway so I wouldn't be doing that</u>
<u n="106" who="S0158">no</u>
<u n="107" who="S0043">I don't get worried <pause dur="short"/> I don't get worried anymore <pause dur="short"/> when they go on holiday by themselves</u>
<u n="108" who="S0158">they've got not to do there</u>
<u n="109" who="S0043">but there you go</u>
<u n="110" who="S0158">you've got a week week's peace then haven't you?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0043">I have got a week's peace as long as they let me know what's happening and what they're doing <pause dur="short"/> and they're safe I don't mind <pause dur="short"/> so there you go</u>
<u n="112" who="S0158">and then November we're off to the Scilly Isles again</u>
<u n="113" who="S0043">are you going back there?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0158">mm <pause dur="short"/> ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> we've got a sort of timeshare thing so we'll be going back there for the next</u>
<u n="115" who="S0043">that's Catherine's isn't it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0158">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'll be going back there for the next ten years or more</u>
<u n="117" who="S0043">oh right so it lasts that oh you've got it for that long</u>
<u n="118" who="S0158">oh yeah well <pause dur="short"/> the deal  The deal  probably is that we'll stop going after we've been going for about twelve or thirteen years</u>
<u n="119" who="S0043">is that in <trunc>to</trunc> from now?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0158">twelve or <trunc>thir</trunc></u>
<u n="121" who="S0043">or is that in that has that been in total now</u>
<u n="122" who="S0158" trans="overlap">oh no in total  in total in total  no so she can then if you  if you  sell it back to them as it were get all the money paid out for the timeshare in the first place</u>
<u n="123" who="S0043">oh right</u>
<u n="124" who="S0158">whereas if you cling on to it after that</u>
<u n="125" who="S0043">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0158">then at the end of thirty years</u>
<u n="127" who="S0043">A lifetime</u>
<u n="128" who="S0158">it just reverts to them anyway <pause dur="short"/> whereas so they want</u>
<u n="129" who="S0043">but you won't get any money back then</u>
<u n="130" who="S0158">no no exactly <pause dur="short"/> so it's plus I'll be  I'll be  in my sixties by then <pause dur="short"/> and I'll <trunc>sha</trunc> all that slogging down all the way down to Cornwall and all that kind of stuff I'll probably give that up</u>
<u n="131" who="S0043">yeah it's a bit of a trek isn't it? No <pause dur="short"/> well that's I mean you've got the <trunc>helicop</trunc> is that the one? That's the one you get the helicopter across cos that's when I've got my helicopter ride this Saturday <pause dur="short"/> weather permitting</u>
<u n="132" who="S0158">well if it's like this you'll be alright</u>
<u n="133" who="S0043">it's not supposed <pause dur="short"/> no it's supposed to be cloudy but it's not supposed to be windy <pause dur="short"/> so as long as it's not windy I suppose it <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose rain I'm not sure but eh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what they look at safety safety issues</u>
<u n="134" who="S0158">weight mostly</u>
<u n="135" who="S0043">weight oh I've got oh that's alright <pause dur="short"/> that'll be alright then I'll be fine</u>
<u n="136" who="S0158"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0043">cheeky <pause dur="short"/> you had to put your weight down as well <pause dur="short"/> don't want some big dobber in the back do you</u>
<u n="138" who="S0126">Don't think you're going to want to hear this replayed again are you? Okay so that's</u>
<u n="139" who="S0043">no it'll be good</u>
<u n="140" who="S0158">let her concentrate for a minute and we'll</u>
<u n="141" who="S0126">let me concentrate</u>
<u n="142" who="S0158">let's concentrate <pause dur="short"/> oh alright then</u>
<u n="143" who="S0043">you know she forgets really easily these days</u>
<u n="144" who="S0126">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's her age</u>
<u n="145" who="S0158">it's her age</u>
<u n="146" who="S0126">right put you card in there</u>
<u n="147" who="S0158">well she's entitled to have <unclear/> moments I suppose <pause dur="short"/> not the rate she's seems to go at the moment but</u>
<u n="148" who="S0126"><vocal desc="laugh"/> If I make a mistake now it'll be your fault</u>
<u n="149" who="S0158">oh dear</u>
<u n="150" who="S0126">so far so good <pause dur="short"/> it's when I get to this point I get a <unclear/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0043">so what's your most favourite place you've been to ever?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0158">favourite place ever? I've been to so many but I do like <trunc>A</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I do like a summer holiday in France</u>
<u n="153" who="S0043">France?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0126" trans="overlap">I like France</u>
<u n="155" who="S0043">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0158">it's quite conveniently close</u>
<u n="157" who="S0043">yeah true</u>
<u n="158" who="S0126">it's good the food is good there</u>
<u n="159" who="S0158">the food <pause dur="short"/> well it's not so bad <pause dur="short"/> I mean the for vegetarians France isn't that brilliant <pause dur="short"/> all the time <pause dur="short"/> but I just like the countryside and the vast quantities of alcohol at very reasonable prices</u>
<u n="160" who="S0043"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0158">and of course I can bring so much back <pause dur="short"/> you can fill the boot of the car up which you can't do practically anywhere else</u>
<u n="162" who="S0043">oh no oh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0158">I knew it wouldn't take long</u>
<u n="164" who="S0043"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0126">this is nothing to do with me I</u>
<u n="166" who="S0043">has somebody already <trunc>collect</trunc> is <trunc>somebo</trunc></u>
<u n="167" who="S0126">somebody hasn't logged off last time</u>
<u n="168" who="S0043">ooh that'll be Tess</u>
<u n="169" who="S0158">my next favourite place is probably Italy</u>
<u n="170" who="S0043">yeah I like Italy</u>
<u n="171" who="S0158">mostly because the food does agree with me there and the cos as a vegetarian you can eat what you like basically</u>
<u n="172" who="S0043" trans="overlap">I've been to Italy once <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I do like yeah I like Italy</u>
<u n="173" who="S0158">just generally means flying though</u>
<u n="174" who="S0043">where do you  Where do you  come from? <event desc="recording skips"/> Write it down we can talk about it <pause dur="short"/> I've been we could have been we might have been</u>
<u n="175" who="S0158">we might <pause dur="short"/> it's possible <pause dur="short"/> it's unlikely</u>
<u n="176" who="S0043">oh no we have been</u>
<u n="177" who="S0158">nearest I've been to is probably Cyprus</u>
<u n="178" who="S0043">yeah I've been to Cyprus as well <pause dur="short"/> right yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0158" trans="overlap">ah right okay</u>
<u n="180" who="S0043">yeah no it's yeah <pause dur="short"/> a long time ago <pause dur="short"/> nineteen eighty-seven <pause dur="short"/> that was a long time ago</u>
<u n="181" who="S0158">Good lord <pause dur="short"/> you must have been a bout twelve</u>
<u n="182" who="S0043">I've been what?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0158">I said you could only be about twelve</u>
<u n="184" who="S0043">give over <pause dur="short"/> I was no I was flipping heck I was <pause dur="short"/> what does this lady want? Are you alright there? Alright yeah <pause dur="short"/> ooh hang on <pause dur="short"/> right okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0126">oh you have to switch on again <pause dur="short"/> no plans yet but I have been to the Lakes just for the weekend so that was quite nice</u>
<u n="186" who="S0158">did it rain?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0126">no it was beautiful weather <pause dur="short"/> beautiful <pause dur="short"/> really really nice <pause dur="short"/> not as hot as last week but</u>
<u n="188" who="S0043">just in case you get a dry throat</u>
<u n="189" who="S0158">that's to go with your gin later on</u>
<u n="190" who="S0043"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0126">he's cheeky <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> so Yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0158">where would you like to go?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0126">where would you like to go?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0158">money no object</u>
<u n="195" who="S0126">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="196" who="S0043" trans="overlap">if you were going to have</u>
<u n="197" who="S0126">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> if I'm going going away this year I might just stay in the UK <pause dur="short"/> having had two holidays last year so I'm not doing too bad</u>
<u n="198" who="S0158">oh greed</u>
<u n="199" who="S0126">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> majorca and Barcelona <pause dur="short"/> so I think I'll just stick it stick to the UK this year</u>
<u n="200" who="S0158">bit Spanish</u>
<u n="201" who="S0043">very Spanish</u>
<u n="202" who="S0126">yeah I know  I know  it was very nice</u>
<u n="203" who="S0158">there are other places you know?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0126">oh yes yes</u>
<u n="205" who="S0043">so whereabouts though where would you go then? Or does it matter what? Is it just what you see?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0126">em <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to go back down to the Pembrokeshire coastal path <unclear/> that area <pause dur="short"/> I've been there many many years ago <pause dur="short"/> or I'd like to go up to Northumberland</u>
<u n="207" who="S0043">Northumberland? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's nice</u>
<u n="208" who="S0126">but I mean as I said we haven't decided on anything yet <pause dur="short"/> but that those those places I would like to go to</u>
<u n="209" who="S0043">and walking and that you'd get some walking done</u>
<u n="210" who="S0126">and walking a bit just a bit <pause dur="short"/> it depends on the weather doesn't it really?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0043">of course it does</u>
<u n="212" who="S0126">and I think it'll be a case of planning something at the last minute <pause dur="short"/> you know? In June or early July <pause dur="short"/> at the last minute really</u>
<u n="213" who="S0043">yeah I never when I get when I go back into the office I am going to have a look to see what if there's any like walks to do on Sunday this Sunday <pause dur="short"/> you know just to see what's round and about</u>
<u n="214" who="S0126">so where are you going to be this Sunday?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0043">no nowhere <pause dur="short"/> got nowhere planned <pause dur="short"/> just not not I don't mean go too far but I mean even if it's just to run up to something like Killingworth Lake and just having a walk round the lake</u>
<u n="216" who="S0126">I know yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0043">I don't mean anything too heavy</u>
<u n="218" who="S0126">yes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0043">but then it depends cos it just like you say it depends on the weather</u>
<u n="220" who="S0126">it depends on the weather as to where you go really <pause dur="short"/> I mean I like Derbyshire for somewhere that's not too far away <pause dur="short"/> but I mean Derbyshire now is covered in snow <pause dur="short"/> buxton way is covered in snow so they kept the <unclear/> closed and that</u>
<u n="221" who="S0043">I'm just wondering  I'm just wondering  if by Saturday if I'm up in the clouds in my helicopter I'll be able to see see far afield and see if there's any snow in different areas</u>
<u n="222" who="S0126" trans="overlap">yes of course <pause dur="short"/> yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> you'll be able to see yes</u>
<u n="223" who="S0043">I'll be <pause dur="short"/> they'll be good photographs to take as well</u>
<u n="224" who="S0158">mrs <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> this is a bindery question he wants to know about</u>
<u n="225" who="S0126">A bindery okay doke</u>
<u n="226" who="S0158"><unclear/> Does he have to send things to us by post if he doesn't turn up</u>
<u n="227" who="S0126"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hi <pause dur="short"/> can I help?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0043">yeah just talking about walking and places to walk you know</u>
<u n="229" who="S0158">do you do walking?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0043">A bit <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a good walker <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a heavy walker</u>
<u n="231" who="S0158">to the pub and back</u>
<u n="232" who="S0043"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> I've done a bit more <pause dur="short"/> that place <pause dur="short"/> you know I try I tell you how do you know that that that waterfall I <trunc>wa</trunc> we walked up in the lakes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0158">I remember you telling me about it</u>
<u n="234" who="S0043"></u>
<u n="235" who="S0158">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0043">that's what it's called <pause dur="short"/> that's where we went and then <trunc>d</trunc> when you get to the top there's a town at the top but we didn't get that far cos it was there was snow on the tops <pause dur="short"/> so er</u>
<u n="237" who="S0158">there's two excellent pubs in that part of the world too</u>
<u n="238" who="S0043">well we down at the bottom there was I don't know whether it's called the there's a tiny one em <pause dur="short"/> as you get to as you  as you get to the bottom it's on that side of you <pause dur="short"/> as you get to the bottom of the waterfall that is it's on the left hand said of you <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ti</trunc> I mean tiny <pause dur="short"/> it's actually like a an inn you know you can stay in it <pause dur="short"/> but the actual pub area's tiny</u>
<u n="239" who="S0158">yeah I think that's the one we've we've stayed at <pause dur="short"/> is that the one that's famous for all the mountaineering and all the rest of it? Lots of photographs of famous mountaineers <pause dur="short"/> we stayed there overnight when we did the coast to coast</u>
<u n="240" who="S0043" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="241" who="S0158">or whichever one it was</u>
<u n="242" who="S0043">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it was eh <pause dur="short"/> it was heavy going but it was eh it was good <pause dur="short"/> it was really nice  really nice  sunny and dry <pause dur="short"/> and sunny</u>
<u n="243" who="S0158">hello there what can we do for you? <event desc="recording skips"/> Where were we? Ah I know we were  we were  talking about  talking about  walking walking yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0043" trans="overlap">walking walking in the Lakes <pause dur="short"/> walking in the Lakes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0158">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0043">but we're going up again we're going up on the</u>
<u n="247" who="S0158">same place?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0043">twentieth <pause dur="short"/> no we're going  No we're going  to Ravenglass</u>
<u n="249" who="S0158">oh right the roller</u>
<u n="250" who="S0043">on the twentieth</u>
<u n="251" who="S0158">superb pub at the bottom</u>
<u n="252" who="S0043">A what?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0158">superb pub at the bottom</u>
<u n="254" who="S0043">right another pub</u>
<u n="255" who="S0158">yeah and and then a little railway line that winds its way up into the hills it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> and then you end up in another lovely pub called the Boot</u>
<u n="256" who="S0043">tell me what these <trunc>pla</trunc> what these are called</u>
<u n="257" who="S0158">the the one at</u>
<u n="258" who="S0043">they're called the Boot and the</u>
<u n="259" who="S0158">the the one actually at Ravenglass is the Ratty or something like that</u>
<u n="260" who="S0043">is that  Is that Is that  dead obvious where the <trunc>sta</trunc> near the station</u>
<u n="261" who="S0158">oh you can't miss is you can't <pause dur="short"/> there isn't much in that part of the world</u>
<u n="262" who="S0043" trans="overlap">it's very small isn't that <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="263" who="S0158">it's kind of its stuck on its own and you can't possibly miss is because it's right by the side of the the proper railway right? And then you have to walk a little way up to the the <unclear/> railway which is the one that takes you up to whichever village it is Boot</u>
<u n="264" who="S0043">boot?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0158">is the name of the village</u>
<u n="266" who="S0043">oh right yeah okay</u>
<u n="267" who="S0158">and there's three pubs there all of which are excellent</u>
<u n="268" who="S0043">right</u>
<u n="269" who="S0158">I've been to all three of them</u>
<u n="270" who="S0043">right</u>
<u n="271" who="S0158">tested and <pause dur="short"/> tested and tried by smelling so they're fine <pause dur="short"/> personal seal of approval and all that kind of thing</u>
<u n="272" who="S0043">excellent <pause dur="short"/> oh no that's good that'll be good <pause dur="short"/> we need to <pause dur="short"/> it's a two nighter so we're going to have one full day there so it'll be good</u>
<u n="273" who="S0158">blimey <pause dur="short"/> you branching out?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0043">no it's a cheap one give over</u>
<u n="275" who="S0158">yeah cos normally you only do one night</u>
<u n="276" who="S0043">only <pause dur="short"/> that's only to do with the price</u>
<u n="277" who="S0158">ah I see</u>
<u n="278" who="S0043">and the <trunc>of</trunc> and what  and what  the offers are <pause dur="short"/> cos if it's a <trunc>go</trunc> the offers tend to only be one night <pause dur="short"/> but this is a two nighter and it's only I say only for two of us for two nights seventy-nine pound bed and breakfast</u>
<u n="279" who="S0158">that's not bad at all</u>
<u n="280" who="S0043">not bad at all <pause dur="short"/> it's like twenty pound each isn't it? Thereabouts <pause dur="short"/> so it's not too bad</u>
<u n="281" who="S0158">I know one place cheaper than that and that's only because I get discount being a <unclear/> member <pause dur="short"/> it's not fair from there actually em <anon type="place"/> which is a place you'll have to go through to get at <anon type="place"/> Ravenglass <pause dur="short"/> you'll see it it's called the <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="282" who="S0043">yeah?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0158">but you get a discount there for your  But that brings the price down for a double room bed and breakfast thirty-six quid <pause dur="short"/> you know in this this day and age</u>
<u n="284" who="S0043">for two of you?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0158">what? That's it's room price</u>
<u n="286" who="S0043">yeah that's very good</u>
<u n="287" who="S0158">so <trunc>seven</trunc> seventy-two pounds for two nights <pause dur="short"/> and the beer is a very reasonable price <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>u</trunc> usually charges about one fifty to one pound sixty a pint <pause dur="short"/> where you think most pubs these days are a lot more expensive</u>
<u n="288" who="S0043">is it a long way to it to walk?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0158">what <anon type="place"/>? To</u>
<u n="290" who="S0043">could you walk to it <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0158">eh I I <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I've only ever been by train</u>
<u n="292" who="S0043" trans="overlap"><unclear/> further back <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if you can  I wonder if you can  still walk <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if you could walk to it and then end up there at that place</u>
<u n="293" who="S0158">investigate <pause dur="short"/> have a look at the railway line</u>
<u n="294" who="S0043" trans="overlap">you know what I mean? Yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0158">Cos I can't remember what the distance is between the two <pause dur="short"/> it's it's a fair way because em Foxguild is at the bottom of Cumbria just above Arndale and places like that Arndale Arnside</u>
<u n="296" who="S0043">Arnside</u>
<u n="297" who="S0158">right but Ravenglass if further round the side <pause dur="short"/> about about a third of the way up <pause dur="short"/> so above eh let me think about his going on towards Windscale around there</u>
<u n="298" who="S0043">yeah cos it would be nice just to have a really good just a good day out you know be it part walking drive maybe I bet we have to drive I don't know but</u>
<u n="299" who="S0158">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there's lots of things you can do round there</u>
<u n="300" who="S0043">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos it's near the it's on the coast isn't it?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0158" trans="overlap">and it's it's worth having a look at places like <trunc>Barr</trunc> not Barrow-in-Furness <pause dur="short"/> other one something in Furness <pause dur="short"/> warton-in-Furness is a lovely little town</u>
<u n="302" who="S0043">ah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0158">again <pause dur="short"/> full of loads of nice pubs <pause dur="short"/> nice walks you can do from there</u>
<u n="304" who="S0043">yeah it's a case of looking at maps <pause dur="short"/> it's just looking at maps and stuff isn't it? And just seeing what's around</u>
<u n="305" who="S0158">well your nearest public library has got all those <unclear/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0043">oh <pause dur="short"/> my little library</u>
<u n="307" who="S0158">where do you live?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0043"><unclear/> Heights <pause dur="short"/> there's a little there's a we have a little pub at <unclear/> At <trunc>bre</trunc> well</u>
<u n="309" who="S0158">hi there what can we do for you? <event desc="recording skips"/> Ah you <pause dur="short"/> no no no no sorry sorry <pause dur="short"/> you're all together that's <unclear/> but Jo has just gone to get a cup of tea so she'll be back in a moment and we can carry on from there</u>
<u n="310" who="S0126" trans="overlap">ah yes yes <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="311" who="S0158">we were talking about walking in the Dales</u>
<u n="312" who="S0126">we were talking yeah walking walking somewhere</u>
<u n="313" who="S0158">oh no sorry <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>wa</trunc> walking in the Lakes</u>
<u n="314" who="S0126">walking in the Lakes</u>
<u n="315" who="S0158">she she doesn't do much but what she does has a choice apparently <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0126">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is</u>
<u n="317" who="S0158">from the car to the pub <unclear/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0126">no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was going well she's on her helicopter ride on Saturday</u>
<u n="319" who="S0158">she is</u>
<u n="320" who="S0126">so she can see what's nice and where what isn't covered in snow</u>
<u n="321" who="S0158">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you're going on your helicopter ride so you're not</u>
<u n="322" who="S0043">I am indeed</u>
<u n="323" who="S0158">where's that gonna be?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0043">where when when? Saturday</u>
<u n="325" who="S0158">oh</u>
<u n="326" who="S0043">at Barton</u>
<u n="327" who="S0158">oh that's not far</u>
<u n="328" who="S0043">no it's just from Eccles</u>
<u n="329" who="S0126">but you're up for fifteen minutes so you can travel quite far</u>
<u n="330" who="S0043">yeah it's great that's that's not going to <unclear/> much</u>
<u n="331" who="S0126">she's not going to outer space</u>
<u n="332" who="S0043">I'm not going to yeah no I'm not I'm not going to go above the clouds</u>
<u n="333" who="S0158">go on then</u>
<u n="334" who="S0043">yeah <pause dur="short"/> who wants me now?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0126">David</u>
<u n="336" who="S0158">so so we're hoping to go skiing next year again</u>
<u n="337" who="S0126">oh very good yes</u>
<u n="338" who="S0158">Cos we haven't been for a couple of years now cos of the boss not being well so I</u>
<u n="339" who="S0126">yeah I know yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0158">that'll be good <pause dur="short"/> probably to Italy</u>
<u n="341" who="S0126">yes <pause dur="short"/> you like Italy don't you?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0158">well I <pause dur="short"/> for a vegetarian it's the ideal place to go cos you can eat all over the place and they don't think you're strange</u>
<u n="343" who="S0126">yeah no I agree <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0158">so if you go to France and Germany and Austria and places like that like and you say sorry I don't eat meat and they look at you like you've got a third arm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0126">yes <pause dur="short"/> austria particularly I find that yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0158">you don't what? You don't eat meat? Is there something wrong with you</u>
<u n="347" who="S0126" trans="overlap">you don't eat meat <pause dur="short"/> very strange yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> but Italy is great saves you</u>
<u n="348" who="S0158">it is well there's no  there's no  em there's no big deal about not eating meat there <pause dur="short"/> which is great <pause dur="short"/> plus the booze is wonderful <pause dur="short"/> and even better it's reasonably cheap compared to French Austria Spain</u>
<u n="349" who="S0126">yeah I suppose it is really yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0158">especially Switzerland where they charge you an arm and a leg</u>
<u n="351" who="S0126">oh Switzerland is mega expensive yes yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0158">it's a real rip off and they take the money off you left right and centre and you don't get very much in return from what I've found in eh in Switzerland so <pause dur="short"/> we won't ever be going back there <pause dur="short"/> we went once for a week just to see what it was like and the boss said right that's it <pause dur="short"/> that's permanently crossed off the list <pause dur="short"/> so I mean</u>
<u n="353" who="S0126">well it's always they're always a bit grumpy as well there as well I find</u>
<u n="354" who="S0158">Grumpy</u>
<u n="355" who="S0126">that's what I've noticed <pause dur="short"/> I've only ever been through it once and that was in</u>
<u n="356" who="S0158">probably cos you weren't spending money at the time</u>
<u n="357" who="S0126">yeah that's it <pause dur="short"/> I didn't have any money I was a poor student</u>
<u n="358" who="S0158">it's not the point <pause dur="short"/> if you go through Switzerland they expect you to cough up in one way or the other</u>
<u n="359" who="S0126">that'll explain why they were grumpy with me</u>
<u n="360" who="S0158"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So yeah I bet you didn't even have a credit card in those days did you?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0126">no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we had credit cards in those days <pause dur="short"/> it's that far back</u>
<u n="362" who="S0158">no please please they've had them at least since the late nineteen sixties</u>
<u n="363" who="S0126">well when we first got married we didn't have a credit card <pause dur="short"/> cos I the first holiday we went abroad <pause dur="short"/> well first time we flew to Spain <pause dur="short"/> we'd been to France <unclear/> I know we didn't have a credit card because we had spent up all our money and we were delayed about fourteen hours at Alicante airport you know</u>
<u n="364" who="S0158">nothing to do and no money to spend</u>
<u n="365" who="S0126">nowhere nothing to do no money to spend it yes yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0158">ooh that's a drag</u>
<u n="367" who="S0126">and hungry as well</u>
<u n="368" who="S0158">so how old  how old  were you then?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0126">I don't know</u>
<u n="370" who="S0158" trans="overlap">roughly roughly</u>
<u n="371" who="S0126">I <pause dur="short"/> twenties anyway <pause dur="short"/> but that was seventy something</u>
<u n="372" who="S0158">right <pause dur="short"/> so when was the first time you flew?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0126">oh the first time I flew was when I was a student</u>
<u n="374" who="S0158">right</u>
<u n="375" who="S0126">and that was nineteen sixty-nine or seventy <pause dur="short"/> sixty-nine probably <pause dur="short"/> it was  It was  a</u>
<u n="376" who="S0158">how many wings did it have?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0126">it had the propellers for all I can remember <pause dur="short"/> no it was em <pause dur="short"/> we went to New York actually</u>
<u n="378" who="S0158">did you? First time</u>
<u n="379" who="S0126">yeah that's it <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah we <pause dur="short"/> it was either New York or Chicago we flew to <pause dur="short"/> no we flew to Chicago <pause dur="short"/> so that was a long journey</u>
<u n="380" who="S0158">was that a family trip?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0126">no no that was a student you know working <trunc>ow</trunc> we we everybody at that time went away from the three or four months during the summer and they worked abroad</u>
<u n="382" who="S0158">oh right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="383" who="S0126">and America was the place that everybody went to <pause dur="short"/> earned enough money to keep them going for the rest of the year</u>
<u n="384" who="S0158">okay</u>
<u n="385" who="S0126">and a lot of the men folk eh who were repeating engineering for a few years <pause dur="short"/> they'd go in May and they'd come back in October <pause dur="short"/> and they'd have enough money made for the rest of the year</u>
<u n="386" who="S0158">oh right <pause dur="short"/> you didn't have grants and stuff?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0126">because <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> well they they didn't have grants <pause dur="short"/> I think I had a grant but they were probably a bit older and they were the older ones <pause dur="short"/> so that that's what they did <pause dur="short"/> so eh you worked for the summer and then that was that would have been the first time I flew</u>
<u n="388" who="S0158">so the first time I flew the first time I was eleven</u>
<u n="389" who="S0126">gosh</u>
<u n="390" who="S0158">eleven at the time <pause dur="short"/> I was I I went all on my own as it were</u>
<u n="391" who="S0126">oh exciting</u>
<u n="392" who="S0158">indeedy <pause dur="short"/> I was an unaccompanied minor which meant I got a hostess to look after me the whole way <pause dur="short"/> this is I thought ooh this is good</u>
<u n="393" who="S0126" trans="overlap">life's never been so good since</u>
<u n="394" who="S0158">I never get that kind of attention normally <pause dur="short"/> I flew flew to the south of France to stay with my aunt and her husband and their kids <pause dur="short"/> she lives at Antibes which is a very nice part of the world to live let me tell you but at eleven you don't really notice this kind of stuff you know <pause dur="short"/> and yeah the car was a Roller <pause dur="short"/> and the the one in between was a Porsche</u>
<u n="395" who="S0043">oh yes</u>
<u n="396" who="S0158">and we went I went the day before I was twelve right? Because if I was twelve the price doubled <pause dur="short"/> under twelve you're a child over twelve you're an adult or you're taking up an adult seat</u>
<u n="397" who="S0126">gosh</u>
<u n="398" who="S0043">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0158">and <unclear/> the price went from twenty-four pounds to forty-eight if I went the following day <pause dur="short"/> so I went the day before my birthday <pause dur="short"/> twenty-four quid return</u>
<u n="400" who="S0043">what about coming back?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0126">ah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0158">no see already bought the ticket by then <pause dur="short"/> done deal</u>
<u n="403" who="S0043">ah right right</u>
<u n="404" who="S0126">yes of course</u>
<u n="405" who="S0043">they don't look at that now though <pause dur="short"/> they always look at your date you you your age on the date you come back</u>
<u n="406" who="S0158">oh right well yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0126">do they?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0043" trans="overlap">that's what they count now yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you're two flying is free <pause dur="short"/> so but if you're two over your holiday</u>
<u n="409" who="S0158">oh right</u>
<u n="410" who="S0043">and before you flight they do  they do they do  charge you</u>
<u n="411" who="S0126">do they? Yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I mean I can't remember</u>
<u n="412" who="S0043">I've just had some very very bad news <pause dur="short"/> my my helicopter flight has been cancelled</u>
<u n="413" who="S0158">oh dear</u>
<u n="414" who="S0043">due to problems with the helicopter</u>
<u n="415" who="S0158">ah</u>
<u n="416" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0126">it's alright no I'm fine honestly no I'm fine it's okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0158">just <unclear/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0043">devastated</u>
<u n="420" who="S0126">yeah I I <pause dur="short"/> I won't be able to see anyone <pause dur="short"/> sit down</u>
<u n="421" who="S0043">so I'm not going</u>
<u n="422" who="S0158">this we'll we'll we'll hear this disembodied voice but we won't be able to see where it's coming from</u>
<u n="423" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0043">that low down</u>
<u n="425" who="S0126">that low down</u>
<u n="426" who="S0158">we've got a customer <unclear/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0126">oh yeah okay</u>
<u n="428" who="S0043">yes there's problems with the helicopter</u>
<u n="429" who="S0158">can you not go and threaten to go and fix it for them</u>
<u n="430" who="S0043">no <pause dur="short"/> I am a mechanic <pause dur="short"/> I could fix it</u>
<u n="431" who="S0158">exactly <unclear/> With lots of sucking your teeth and going</u>
<u n="432" who="S0043" trans="overlap">so I've now got  I've now got  to wait till the thirtieth of June</u>
<u n="433" who="S0158">right is that the next time it takes off in</u>
<u n="434" who="S0043" trans="overlap">millions of miles <pause dur="short"/> no there there's there was  there was  a date in June date in <trunc>Ju</trunc> in August and one in September</u>
<u n="435" who="S0158">right</u>
<u n="436" who="S0043">so eh <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh shut up <pause dur="short"/> I'm devastated I was all geared up <pause dur="short"/> I was all geared up for my flight</u>
<u n="437" who="S0158">she's got her flying helmet and boots and everything like that and</u>
<u n="438" who="S0043">no</u>
<u n="439" who="S0158">been practicing spinning around in the kitchen she was to the idea</u>
<u n="440" who="S0043">oh one minute alright sorry</u>
<u n="441" who="S0158">I knew what she was talking about</u>
<u n="442" who="S0043">no I thought she said just hang on a  hang on a  minute one minute</u>
<u n="443" who="S0158" trans="overlap">in a minute <pause dur="short"/> in a minute she's going to go mm <pause dur="short"/> we can stop at that point</u>
<u n="444" who="S0043">and do you and you and do you realise this is the longest talk talked to me without giving me grief</u>
<u n="445" who="S0158">I'm saving it up for a <unclear/> time <unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0043">what's that one minute up? That's it back to normal</u>
<u n="447" who="S0158">you safe just for a little</u>
<u n="448" who="S0043">oh no but are you devastated for me?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0158">no not really</u>
<u n="450" who="S0043">oh</u>
<u n="451" who="S0158">the same thing happened to me <pause dur="short"/> it took months before it actually happened when it should have done</u>
<u n="452" who="S0043">I know because you're you're stuck with them aren't you? You know <pause dur="short"/> and obviously come the thirtieth of June something else might happen <pause dur="short"/> but then cos my token it ran out it runs out at the end of em August</u>
<u n="453" who="S0158">yeah but if they  if they  mess up it's the the the</u>
<u n="454" who="S0043">the class <pause dur="short"/> it's yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> so like I I've got a chance to do one in September you know if if eh if all fails</u>
<u n="455" who="S0158">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the the same thing happened to us they kept putting if off and putting it off and putting it off <pause dur="short"/> and there was one day <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> woke up <pause dur="short"/> we had went to a party alright and e we were hoping and praying that they were going to ring up and say it's cancelled because she had a banging hangover and the last thing she wanted was to go up in a bloody helicopter and going a funny colour of green anyway</u>
<u n="456" who="S0158">oh no</u>
<u n="457" who="S0043">so that was quite good <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm devastated</u>
<u n="458" who="S0158">indeed <pause dur="short"/> what about the other half</u>
<u n="459" who="S0043">I told I haven't told him yet <pause dur="short"/> that was just that was the phone call there</u>
<u n="460" who="S0158">has he been in a helicopter before?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0043">I don't think so</u>
<u n="462" who="S0158">oh right <pause dur="short"/> a first for both of you</u>
<u n="463" who="S0126">I've not been in a helicopter either</u>
<u n="464" who="S0043">oh he isn't going <pause dur="short"/> he's only paid for me</u>
<u n="465" who="S0158" trans="overlap">are you?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0043">he's not coming with me</u>
<u n="467" who="S0158">is he? Oh I see <pause dur="short"/> ah sorry I thought that was</u>
<u n="468" who="S0126">no she's <trunc>o</trunc> she's flying solo</u>
<u n="469" who="S0043">I'm flying solo</u>
<u n="470" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0158">so I was right <pause dur="short"/> it is a one way ticket</u>
<u n="472" who="S0043">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Hey that minute's not up yet shut up <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="473" who="S0126">one way ticket</u>
<u n="474" who="S0158">yeah he's eh <pause dur="short"/> soon as you're up there  Shut your bank account</u>
<u n="475" who="S0043">hey he's only it's not that bad <pause dur="short"/> it's only fifteen minutes <pause dur="short"/> shut up</u>
<u n="476" who="S0158">yeah but you can get a long way in quarter of an hour</u>
<u n="477" who="S0126">that's what I said <pause dur="short"/> you can get a long way in fifteen minutes in a helicopter</u>
<u n="478" who="S0158">he's a head start at least wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0043">he's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the car he is <pause dur="short"/> doing a runner</u>
<u n="480" who="S0158">I said  I said  the minute she's up in the air he's off</u>
<u n="481" who="S0043">at least I  At least I  haven't got too far to get home have I?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0158">that's true yes</u>
<u n="483" who="S0043">it's only round the corner</u>
<u n="484" who="S0158">it's what you'll find when you get there and all the furniture's gone and</u>
<u n="485" who="S0043">shut up you</u>
<u n="486" who="S0158">lots has changed</u>
<u n="487" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0126">can't do that in fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="489" who="S0158">exactly <pause dur="short"/> but that's what he could get up to <pause dur="short"/> you're up there hovering</u>
<u n="490" who="S0043">I could hover over my house and juts check</u>
<u n="491" who="S0158">you could <pause dur="short"/> just yeah just tell the pilot</u>
<u n="492" who="S0126" trans="overlap">yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> go and check it out</u>
<u n="493" who="S0158">just just that way a bit towards Eccles <pause dur="short"/> down a bit  Down a bit  I'd get your camera out photograph</u>
<u n="494" who="S0043">hover over</u>
<u n="495" who="S0126">on the roof <pause dur="short"/> yes yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0158">on a rope <pause dur="short"/> down on the ladder</u>
<u n="497" who="S0126">go down yeah keep a check on him</u>
<u n="498" who="S0158">your own version of Goggle Earth isn't it? Just with the <trunc>Eccl</trunc> Eccles no Eccles earth</u>
<u n="499" who="S0043" trans="overlap">my version of Mission Impossible</u>
<u n="500" who="S0158">it's like Middle Earth but not quite so much happens there</u>
<u n="501" who="S0043">oh shut up <pause dur="short"/> oh god</u>
<u n="502" who="S0158">are we done?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0043">whey</u>
</body>
</text>
