<text id="S7JG">
<header>
		<rec_length>3:18:53</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-15</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0046 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Food, films, the military </topics>
		<activity>Friends cooking and eating dinner, chatting, watching a movie</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0046">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Labourer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0041">so I really lively said why don't just say hello just say morning? </u>
<u n="2" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my mum would've been exactly the same <pause dur="short"/> when I've got visitors round she's always popping in like d'you have a nice time? You alright? </u>
<u n="3" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like I don't I don't' think it's strange at all</u>
<u n="4" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> no I've always seen it as really sweet</u>
<u n="5" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like why would you be argumentative in that way and I I can remember if you were maybe sixteen seventeen</u>
<u n="6" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0041">you would've been like mum come on leave us alone but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like she keeps saying to me all the time there's only two years difference between us <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking two years</u>
<u n="8" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0041">like she's twenty-three this year</u>
<u n="10" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0041">and I thought I didn't I thought she was twenty-two this year <pause dur="short"/> I was like what? </u>
<u n="12" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh yeah when you told me that even <trunc>m</trunc> even when you said that she was twenty-two you see I'd be surprised</u>
<u n="13" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0084">Cos she acts like an eighteen year-old</u>
<u n="15" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah she does</u>
<u n="16" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's cos it's probably cos she's never moved out <pause dur="short"/> and so she's never grown up more than eighteen</u>
<u n="17" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>c</trunc> just couldn't believe it</u>
<u n="18" who="S0084">that is really badly behaved</u>
<u n="19" who="S0041">yes really</u>
<u n="20" who="S0084">I'm surprised you know obviously it was always gonna be quite hard for her mum to ask her to leave and she obviously hasn't done that</u>
<u n="21" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think she has any intention of it to be honest <pause dur="short"/> cos I suppose while <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s there <trunc>sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> pays her rent cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying oh you know I um I'm gonna get this new job basically it's just like an after school club cos she works at the school so she'd get more hours</u>
<u n="22" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0041">um and she was like oh so I can earn a bit more money cos I'm absolutely skint all the time <pause dur="short"/> And inside I was bubbling cos I was like are you taking the piss? </u>
<u n="24" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0041">she earns about a <trunc>hu</trunc> a hundred pound less than me a month and she lives at home and she's talking to me about being skint</u>
<u n="26" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh right and she lives at home yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> and your rent is a joke</u>
<u n="27" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I was like seriously? And she was like yeah I know I said tell me about it she said no really <pause dur="short"/> I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how much money do you think I earn? </u>
<u n="28" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0041">she was like well you know a bit a little bit more than me and I was like yeah a hundred pound she was like well there you go then <pause dur="short"/> I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I doubt very much that your rent's like mine she says I do pay rent <pause dur="short"/> I said yes and I doubt very much it's five hundred pound a month <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="30" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="31" who="S0041">she was like well no but it's two hundred <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="32" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/> so she's got an extra two hundred pounds on top of you then?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0041">so she yeah she's she's comparing two hundred pounds to my five hundred <pause dur="short"/> I mean in some months it's four five five so still works out weekly so actually it's not five hundred pounds it's four five five</u>
<u n="34" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah but still <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but still so much</u>
<u n="35" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I was just like what? And I was like</u>
<u n="36" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I can't believe she charges you twenty quid a week more than she charges me</u>
<u n="37" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0084">for a room</u>
<u n="39" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0084">only just bigger than mine <pause dur="short"/> think it's just absolutely outrageous <pause dur="short"/> I think she definitely put the rates up when we moved in</u>
<u n="41" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0084">she just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't really live in the real world so she's no idea how much rent costs</u>
<u n="43" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no and she was like</u>
<u n="44" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos she doesn't need to</u>
<u n="45" who="S0041"> Yeah so that so that means there's not that much difference between us and I was like yeah um and pay for food </u>
<u n="46" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0041"> and I pay for transport and I pay the car insurance <pause dur="short"/> And I said well this month with the car fiasco that was fun <pause dur="short"/> and the whole time I mean I didn't I wasn't I wasn't saying it to have a dig I was saying it so that she kind of understood that really her situation isn't that bad</u>
<u n="48" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0041">D'you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="51" who="S0041">and she just wasn't getting it <pause dur="short"/> not at all</u>
<u n="52" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she lives on a different planet though doesn't she? I mean it is</u>
<u n="53" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0084">she's a nice girl but it must be difficult to be friends with someone like that because you are so different</u>
<u n="55" who="S0041">it's just craziness <pause dur="short"/> like I don't I didn't expect her to go oh yeah poor you </u>
<u n="56" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0041">I expected her to maybe appreciate that having her mum like that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0084">yeah she's lucky to have that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and stop being so rude to her</u>
<u n="60" who="S0084" trans="overlap">to be able to to say yeah to not take her for granted and to appreciate what she's got</u>
<u n="61" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0084">well that's the thing cos you would think that having spoken to you know once or twice about your family situation the thought would've occurred actually d'you know I haven't had half as much drama with my family as I've as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s had with hers maybe I should be a bit more grateful about what I've got going on at home whereas people like her you tend to find that they're just as selfish because</u>
<u n="63" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0084">they um they just see it see their problems they don't see other people's problems <pause dur="short"/> they don't see that what they've got actually is quite a good situation</u>
<u n="65" who="S0041">very very strange <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna fill this with the</u>
<u n="66" who="S0084">okay and I will get the thing for the gravy</u>
<u n="67" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that type of mentality I saw in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> earlier today <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="68" who="S0084" trans="overlap">so family?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Shit</u>
<u n="70" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0041">played there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> um he said oh well <unclear/> my Dad's <unclear/> I can't believe he didn't come over at four <unclear/> and I was like yeah I said you know it's pretty bad </u>
<u n="72" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0041">um he said but some time it might be a generation thing cos my dad doesn't you know show emotion at all really</u>
<u n="74" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and I said and it's different cos you know you were really seriously hurt</u>
<u n="76" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0041">um and your dad's <unclear/> in the corner but <pause dur="short"/> yeah well he did he did text you and he did try and call cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was cancelling his calls</u>
<u n="78" who="S0084">was he?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> that seems a bit mean then to say oh he's not making an effort to come round </u>
<u n="81" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0084">yeah that's the thing you know he's he's an independent business man like it must be difficult to sort of juggle the two</u>
<u n="83" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0084">I'm not making excuses you know he might well be a twat but</u>
<u n="85" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0084"><unclear/> like</u>
<u n="87" who="S0041" trans="overlap">ah I had broccoli for lunch like the other day just broccoli just broccoli on its own <unclear/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0084" trans="overlap">ah yum <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean I just love broccoli <pause dur="short"/> I think it's just the best thing <pause dur="short"/> broccoli and gravy for me it's just</u>
<u n="89" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0084">like the best thing ever <pause dur="short"/> apart from roast potatoes and broccoli <pause dur="short"/> um roast potatoes and gravy</u>
<u n="91" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and gravy <pause dur="short"/> he's so mental though</u>
<u n="92" who="S0084">you're telling me</u>
<u n="93" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah and he said um he said oh yeah I can kind of you know I can kind of understand that apologies for a bit of bra showing but I'm a bit hot now <pause dur="short"/> um he said oh you know I can kind of understand that a little bit but he came</u>
<u n="94" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0041">round here and the first thing he did was start bartering for a an argument and I was like really? you know your your well your son's pretty sick <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="96" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0041"> What d'you know what did he say? And he said oh well he came and said you know your you know right <trunc>w</trunc> when did this happen? so I told him</u>
<u n="98" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0041">and then he was like um and you been drinking? And <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said well yeah a double or two <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="100" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0041">and then he just started off going off on one <pause dur="short"/> and I thought are you surprised look at the state of your face</u>
<u n="102" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0041">from drinking</u>
<u n="104" who="S0084">D'you think any parent is gonna say well done mate ?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and if he had what kind of a parent would he be?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you what type of parent would he be if he didn't say shit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like come on that's ridiculous </u>
<u n="108" who="S0084">yeah what you doing? </u>
<u n="109" who="S0041">to which he would reply Shut your face I'm an adult I get it it's embarrassing enough as it is <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="110" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="111" who="S0041"> Thanks like but <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="112" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but it they wouldn't be a parent if they didn't worry</u>
<u n="113" who="S0041">no they wouldn't be a parent if they didn't say that</u>
<u n="114" who="S0084">my mum would go you know any parent would you know any normal parent would go pretty mental at the sight of you if they thought that because of drinking you could</u>
<u n="115" who="S0041">that's what you'd done</u>
<u n="116" who="S0084">but you'd also you could it could've been far worse if if it was a car which we don't know</u>
<u n="117" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0084">you could've gone under the wheels of a car just for larking around</u>
<u n="119" who="S0041" trans="overlap">could be dead</u>
<u n="120" who="S0084">D'you what I mean I it's parents usually get annoyed because they're scared</u>
<u n="121" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0084">and they get annoyed with you when you do stupid things because they're scared that something serious is gonna happen to you <pause dur="short"/> and it's just it's just immaturity isn't it?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0084" trans="overlap">you'd think moving out you'd get more of an appreciation for what your parents do for you</u>
<u n="125" who="S0041" trans="overlap">ahh should I start carving d'you think?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0084">ooh yum <pause dur="short"/> yeah you're really good at that <pause dur="short"/> I think it helps that the chicken is so delicious and so easy to just fall apart</u>
<u n="127" who="S0041" trans="overlap">huh <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="128" who="S0084">is this enough broccoli for you? D'you want me to <trunc>s</trunc> do it all? Shall we do it all?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0041">uh I don't mind that's fine for me</u>
<u n="130" who="S0084">yeah perfect okay</u>
<u n="131" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> let's save some broccoli for next broccoli indulgence</u>
<u n="132" who="S0084">Will we? <unclear/> forget</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="133" who="S0084">mm yum</u>
<u n="134" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">is it on fire? <vocal desc="gasp"/> amah-zing</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">it is on perfect fire</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">A <trunc>p</trunc> the perfect amount of fire</u>
<u n="138" who="S0041">perfect amount on fire <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">delish</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">what I might do is I had a bit of a an issue last time let's just get another plate to put the chicken on</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0041">and put the chicken on one plate</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0041">Don't know if you're supposed to cut chicken with this but we can just it anyway</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">how many plates do we need?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And we're gonna put the chicken on here to cut and then put the</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084">ahh yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0041">chicken that I cut off on this one</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">um no I would like</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">more plates</u>
<u n="156" who="S0041" trans="overlap">individual plate one for each leg</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Yummy <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="160" who="S0041">ah it looks pretty this is like a picture of a perfect chicken</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084">isn't it though <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sss</trunc> ahh</u>
<u n="162" who="S0041">where's the where's the thing that's wrapped round it?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084" trans="overlap">this ring here on the side</u>
<u n="164" who="S0041">oh no <pause dur="short"/> oh god</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0041">oh god <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what's going on</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0041">just want it to break</u>
<u n="169" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">oh I'm really scared</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0041"><event desc="sound of snapping"/> Ohh <pause dur="short"/> we don't own scissors do we?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0041">try this <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's it</u>
<u n="175" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's the one</u>
<u n="176" who="S0041">that's it <pause dur="short"/> where did you go?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Just get a rogue piece of string in your dinner</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's fine <pause dur="short"/> that's fine <pause dur="short"/> bit of fibre <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="181" who="S0084">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> hot water bottle <pause dur="short"/> ahh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="182" who="S0041">you don't eat the skin do you?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0084">no thank you</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<event desc="sound of heavy rain"/>
<u n="184" who="S0041">holy crap</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="185" who="S0084">how you doing?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0041">it's reaining</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">seriously raining isn't it?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's raining bad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0084">bloody Nora</u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">dunno if that might be done yet <pause dur="short"/> oh we definitely need to take the cabbage out now</u>
<u n="191" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0041">yeah I thought the broccoli had already gone in the cabbage will be dead by now</u>
<u n="193" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> okay that's fine <pause dur="short"/> um let's drain that</u>
<u n="194" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> drain over there</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">if you chuck out a big pan <pause dur="short"/> cos I'll quickly fish out <trunc>broccol</trunc> the brockles</u>
<u n="197" who="S0084">fish out a big pan right</u>
<u n="198" who="S0041">yeah cos I'm gonna save the water from the cabbage</u>
<u n="199" who="S0084">ah okay</u>
<u n="200" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="202" who="S0041">Cos all the vitamins go in it <pause dur="short"/> and then we'll we can make the gravy with it</u>
<u n="203" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yess</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">and then we can pretend like we're all full of goodness</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">yeah <trunc>m</trunc> we're not just pretending it's we're having all the good things <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">gromit</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">gromit <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing to me <pause dur="short"/> jesus <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> with big palm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0041">ah <trunc>ss</trunc> ah <pause dur="short"/> in hindsight I think we might've fallen for this broccoli catastrophe last time</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah we get a bit I get a bit um lost <pause dur="short"/> d'you need this?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084">to scoop?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041">there it is look</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">it's lovely yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0041">rogue brockles <pause dur="short"/> you get on there</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084">we did get we did? Ah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0041">no stabbing that</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0041">yeah there is there we go</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> so now we need to drain that into that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> we can do that</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084"><unclear/> for fuck's sake <pause dur="short"/> bloody house</u>
<u n="222" who="S0041">maybe you should put both of them down in case they burn you</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0041">like I just</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0084">fire fire in my face <pause dur="short"/> ohh</u>
<u n="228" who="S0041">where's the scoop? The scooper <pause dur="short"/> there we go <pause dur="short"/> there we go <pause dur="short"/> this is a great thing I mean it's served with spaghetti innit?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> no yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0041">it's totally better for cabbage <pause dur="short"/> there we go</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">well that can just sit there can't it?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0041">yeah we don't care about that</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">you</u>
<u n="234" who="S0041"><trunc>Hhh</trunc> <trunc>ahh</trunc></u>
<u n="235" who="S0084">ooh dear <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> that <pause dur="short"/> cabbage</u>
<u n="236" who="S0041">ooh ahh <pause dur="short"/> bernard</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084"><unclear/> about removing your <vocal desc="laugh"/> Just being a dickhead just ignore me <pause dur="short"/> being a <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> twat <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="238" who="S0041">I think considering the amount of immense pain you must be in right now it's going pretty well</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Just being a <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> knob </u>
<u n="240" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Being a knob <pause dur="short"/> Ahh see I'd quite like some white wine now</u>
<u n="242" who="S0041">vino</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">all I have is Southern Belle it's not quite the same</u>
<u n="244" who="S0041">southern Belle <pause dur="short"/> ahh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="245" who="S0046">I'm so jealous</u>
<u n="246" who="S0084">are you jealous? What of the chicken?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0046">the smell</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0046">the smell is loveliness</u>
<u n="250" who="S0084">it's our new favourite thing <pause dur="short"/> not cooking dinner</u>
<u n="251" who="S0046">hardly been able to eat <unclear/> with the pain</u>
<u n="252" who="S0084">aww <pause dur="short"/> you alright?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0041"><trunc>D'y</trunc> <trunc>men</trunc></u>
<u n="255" who="S0046" trans="overlap">my eye won't stop bleeding <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go for another coffee though</u>
<u n="256" who="S0084">oh well this has just boiled</u>
<u n="257" who="S0046">ah thanks</u>
<u n="258" who="S0041">have you had any more sleep?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0046">I keep dosing <pause dur="short"/> I keep dosing <pause dur="short"/> it's it's annoying actually <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> annoying</u>
<u n="260" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="261" who="S0046">chicken actually</u>
<u n="262" who="S0041">mm mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0046"><unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="264" who="S0046">might have a chicken treat <pause dur="short"/> might take the edge off <unclear/> of your roast</u>
<u n="265" who="S0041">try</u>
<u n="266" who="S0084">are you alright for drink? Are you gonna have your Coke?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0041">yeah thank you</u>
<u n="268" who="S0084">I've got a plan <pause dur="short"/> is that <unclear/> down your trousers?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0041">ooh that's a good idea</u>
<u n="270" who="S0084">there you go <pause dur="short"/> not a lot of room in your trousers</u>
<u n="271" who="S0041" trans="overlap">in there</u>
<u n="272" who="S0084">it's fine <pause dur="short"/> ahh it's like a baby</u>
<u n="273" who="S0041">it's the best type of baby</u>
<u n="274" who="S0084">it's the kind of baby that you don't need to feed</u>
<u n="275" who="S0041">or worry about clothing or whining</u>
<u n="276" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> or <trunc>whi</trunc> or whining <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0041">I'm not a fan of the whiners</u>
<u n="278" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> bloody babies <pause dur="short"/> ohh <pause dur="short"/> delicious and nutritious tastes just like chicken</u>
<u n="279" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0084">we need to use all your gravy <pause dur="short"/> we always use your gravy actually Charles</u>
<u n="281" who="S0041">that's okay</u>
<u n="282" who="S0084">are you sure you don't mind?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0041">no not at all</u>
<u n="284" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/> look at all that is there more chicken than before?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0041">there might be</u>
<u n="286" who="S0084">woww</u>
<u n="287" who="S0046">did you buy another one did you?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0046"><unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0084">yeah we had to wait a little bit but it was fine <pause dur="short"/> it was worth it</u>
<u n="291" who="S0041">yeah it was worth the wait <vocal desc="laugh"/> worth the wait</u>
<u n="292" who="S0084">didn't actually seem to take that long though the wait</u>
<u n="293" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="294" who="S0084" trans="overlap">because we were looking at ice cream for an hour</u>
<u n="295" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0084">and talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0041">who um cute as he is just really isn't fanciable</u>
<u n="298" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> not at all <pause dur="short"/> bit of a shame</u>
<u n="299" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but even I said this <pause dur="short"/> he's got like a gorgeous accent</u>
<u n="300" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0041">and he's really really sweet <pause dur="short"/> but there's just something about him nobody could put their fingers on it that he's just makes him not fanciable</u>
<u n="302" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah well maybe because he does seem so young</u>
<u n="303" who="S0041">yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> didn't even eat the skin <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't even eat the skin and I really like the skin</u>
<u n="304" who="S0084" trans="overlap">you're doing very well I was gonna say</u>
<u n="305" who="S0041">I'm then <trunc>g</trunc> I'm going to eat this bit here</u>
<u n="306" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Good for you <pause dur="short"/> you're going to do what now?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0041">I'm going to eat this bit that's on here</u>
<u n="308" who="S0084">that's fine cos that's wings that doesn't really count <pause dur="short"/> mm just falling off <pause dur="short"/> yum I need all of that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0041">all of it</u>
<u n="310" who="S0084">that leg meat's so nice actually <pause dur="short"/> so tender</u>
<u n="311" who="S0041">put it in put it in the mouth</u>
<u n="312" who="S0084">put it in the mouth <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like my broccoli pretty crunchy I dunno about you</u>
<u n="313" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> can't be doing with overcooked veg <pause dur="short"/> bit concerned that we might've overcooked cabbage but I'll eat cabbage no matter how it's cooked</u>
<u n="314" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0041">even if it's about to away</u>
<u n="316" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you might be getting a lot of cabbage cos we have <unclear/> it</u>
<u n="317" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that's fine by me</u>
<u n="318" who="S0084">Ohh <pause dur="short"/> alright <pause dur="short"/> you off</u>
<u n="319" who="S0041">D'you want me to help with the draining again?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0084">ah I think you're alright <pause dur="short"/> thanks love</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="321" who="S0084"><event desc="sound of rattling"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> ooh <pause dur="short"/> delicious</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041">gravy gravy goodness</u>
<u n="323" who="S0084">hahh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="324" who="S0084">what we need is a tray for the crème de menthe</u>
<u n="325" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="326" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0041">oh we didn't see if there was a film on</u>
<u n="328" who="S0084">ah you ninny <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0041">ninny <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure there will be something on</u>
<u n="330" who="S0084">I'm feeling pretty confident <pause dur="short"/> we'll find something <pause dur="short"/> you ow <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> and now and then trays for us <pause dur="short"/> are you gonna have a tray with a <unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0084">on your own tray? Just get you your tray <pause dur="short"/> that's yours</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="333" who="S0041">it's going well</u>
<u n="334" who="S0084"><unclear/> You're doing well not to eat it all</u>
<u n="335" who="S0041">yeah I mean it does want to go from the chicken into my mouth <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It wants to go</u>
<u n="337" who="S0041">not me</u>
<u n="338" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0041">not me wanting it to go</u>
<u n="340" who="S0084" trans="overlap">nothing to do with you <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0041">it wants to go</u>
<u n="342" who="S0084">I mean I've not doubted you for a moment</u>
<u n="343" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0084">never in my life <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0084">honestly I believe everything you tell me Charles</u>
<u n="347" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0084">there'd be no reason for me to doubt you</u>
<u n="349" who="S0041">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="351" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="352" who="S0084">that's not what we do here</u>
<u n="353" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> certainly would never lie about these type of things and how</u>
<u n="354" who="S0084"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0041">necessary it is to put things like chocolate and chicken in in to the mouths</u>
<u n="356" who="S0084">yep I mean you're not prone to exaggeration either</u>
<u n="357" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>n</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0084">with the <unclear/> that you do</u>
<u n="359" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> um <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's uh drama queen <pause dur="short"/> not here</u>
<u n="362" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> oh that's hot isn't it? God <pause dur="short"/> this is why we shouldn't cook <pause dur="short"/> it all just ends in disaster <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm lumping you in with me <pause dur="short"/> you're actually not a disaster zone</u>
<u n="363" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="364" who="S0084">it's just me</u>
<u n="365" who="S0041">I'm not too sure</u>
<u n="366" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> keep you under wraps <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> mm mm mm </u>
<u n="367" who="S0041">um I'm I'm doing what's called chicken shredding now</u>
<u n="368" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0041">only I think if you know how to cook a <trunc>chick</trunc> cut a chicken properly all this just comes off in the slices but um</u>
<u n="370" who="S0084">think that's what they teach you at chef school</u>
<u n="371" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0084">chicken shredding</u>
<u n="373" who="S0041">chicken <vocal desc="laugh"/> chicken shredding if it was a duck I'd be a winner</u>
<u n="374" who="S0084">that's</u>
<u n="375" who="S0041">Cos you shred duck</u>
<u n="376" who="S0084">that's what you do</u>
<u n="377" who="S0041">there we go I think we're good</u>
<u n="378" who="S0084">ah amah-zing</u>
<u n="379" who="S0041" trans="overlap">there's underneath here <pause dur="short"/> where we <trunc>d</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I'm a bit funny about the things like that cos they might have bits in</u>
<u n="380" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> a bit of gristle I don't need any gristle</u>
<u n="381" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah I don't want that <pause dur="short"/> I think that's pretty good these bits are just white <pause dur="short"/> there we go I think we're good to go</u>
<u n="382" who="S0084">ahhh <pause dur="short"/> yum <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="383" who="S0084">think we better put that in the bin outside</u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084">uhh you stay there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="386" who="S0041">just leave it and throw this straight in what d'you think the likelihood of that ground being wet is? Pretty high?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">High yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">you've got some shoes by the door</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041">yeah I've got the little platforms</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> mm mm mm-mm <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">ah ah I've got pyjamas on I didn't consider going out in me jamas did I?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0041">I'm just gonna do it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="395" who="S0041">just ran out to the bin yeah yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> D'you need some more cabbage?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0041" trans="overlap">you know um I think I'm just about good for cabbage d'you think you might need some more broccoli to compensate</u>
<u n="400" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0041">for your lack of cabbage?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0084">no it's alright cos I've got more broccoli than you have so um that's fine by me</u>
<u n="403" who="S0041">give it <trunc>pro</trunc> I think that that's</u>
<u n="404" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0041">just required here</u>
<u n="406" who="S0084">that's just that's just fine <pause dur="short"/> thanks thanks thanks</u>
<u n="407" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh god <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0084">the condiment tray <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0041">the condiment tray shall I take the condiment tray shall I take the condiment tray and the knives and forks in?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0084">oh lovely <pause dur="short"/> can I add one thing to the condiment tray?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0041">oh certainly not</u>
<u n="412" who="S0084">I'm sorry but it has to I have to have my squeezy on there</u>
<u n="413" who="S0041">okayy</u>
<u n="414" who="S0084">thanks thanks um</u>
<u n="415" who="S0041">D'you think I d'you think we might need a bit thicker gravy?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0084">oh do we need more?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0041">think we might</u>
<u n="418" who="S0084">oh yeah <trunc>truf</trunc> shove shove</u>
<u n="419" who="S0041">I mean I probably shouldn't use this fork that I've got in my hand but</u>
<u n="420" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0084">yummy</u>
<u n="423" who="S0041">just thinking that how clumsy I am for it to run off my plate</u>
<u n="424" who="S0084">this is true this is why I thought bowls would be a good idea</u>
<u n="425" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what's required here</u>

<u n="426" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Just thinking purely of my own um clumsiness <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna dig in <pause dur="short"/> is that alright?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0084">I'm gonna put some of these on your plate these are yours</u>
<u n="429" who="S0041">chuck it chuck anything on</u>
<u n="430" who="S0084">chuck it all you like that <pause dur="short"/> and that <pause dur="short"/> and now make way make way</u>
<u n="431" who="S0041">might put the wings on on the side actually <pause dur="short"/> might put them on a plate <pause dur="short"/> cos I'll put I'll end up putting the bones back on my</u>
<u n="432" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0041">plate</u>
<u n="434" who="S0084">you need a side plate</u>
<u n="435" who="S0041">I need a baby baby plate <pause dur="short"/> where's the baby that one <pause dur="short"/> I like this one</u>
<u n="436" who="S0084">aww <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0041">this little plate</u>
<u n="438" who="S0084">it's like an old nana plate</u>
<u n="439" who="S0041">I'll put this on the nana plate</u>
<u n="440" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="441" who="S0041">and put them on a condiment tray</u>
<u n="442" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0041">um I'm a little bit concerned that the gravy pieces</u>
<u n="444" who="S0084">are sitting on the top?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> does that usually happen?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0084">I think when you add it when it's not as hot <pause dur="short"/> so maybe if you just add a bit of boiling water on the top maybe that would help</u>
<u n="447" who="S0041">ah bugger <pause dur="short"/> ohh</u>
<u n="448" who="S0084">buggeration <unclear/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0041">ahhh</u>
<u n="450" who="S0084">did you just scald yourself?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0041" trans="overlap">well it's definitely still hot</u>
<u n="452" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0041">definitely still hot</u>
<u n="454" who="S0084">I can attest to that</u>
<u n="455" who="S0041">maybe I just need to keep stirring a little while</u>
<u n="456" who="S0084">just keep swimming</u>
<u n="457" who="S0041" trans="overlap">see what happens</u>
<u n="458" who="S0084" trans="overlap">just keep swimming</u>
<u n="459" who="S0041">maybe I need to put the whisk in</u>
<u n="460" who="S0084">yeah the whisk is pretty good <pause dur="short"/> maybe you just need to um I mean it'll all taste the same won't it?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0041">yeah it'll just look slightly um</u>
<u n="462" who="S0084"></u>
<u n="463" who="S0041">bizarre <pause dur="short"/> where is my whisk?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0084">it's up here</u>
<u n="465" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0084">waiting to be washed up <pause dur="short"/> it is <trunc>po</trunc></u>
<u n="467" who="S0041" trans="overlap">bloody whisk</u>
<u n="468" who="S0084">this is possibly the biggest dinner in the world <pause dur="short"/> we whisked the gravy you ninny</u>
<u n="469" who="S0041">ahh <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of whisking"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0084"><unclear/> for the whisk</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="471" who="S0041">yess</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="472" who="S0041"><trunc>Sss</trunc> mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0084" trans="overlap">you might have a bit of</u>
<u n="474" who="S0041">Ohh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="475" who="S0084">is it working?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0041">I've seen it's seen better days but I think it will be fine</u>
<u n="477" who="S0084">it'll all go down the same way</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="478" who="S0084">success?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0041">I think it will be fine <pause dur="short"/> I hope it will be fine <pause dur="short"/> I'm <event desc="sound of dropping something"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0084">could you imagine <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0041">Marmite catastrophe</u>
<u n="482" who="S0084">Chuffing Nora</u>
<u n="483" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'll go and take <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> uh?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="485" who="S0041">not you</u>
<u n="486" who="S0084">you silly rabbit</u>
<u n="487" who="S0041"><event desc="sound of bang"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0084">are you not content with breaking my all my things?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0084">what am I gonna do with you? I think you need to sit down <pause dur="short"/> are you delirious?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> think I'm having</u>
<u n="492" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> delirious from lack of food</u>
<u n="493" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think I'm <trunc>del</trunc> I think I'm delirious from all the chicken goodness</u>
<u n="494" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You haven't seen anything yet you haven't even seen your plate yet <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah well as <unclear/> go by this is gonna be awesome</u>
<u n="496" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Right I've got the water bottle <pause dur="short"/> check <pause dur="short"/> plate of goodness <pause dur="short"/> check <pause dur="short"/> ooh</u>
<u n="497" who="S0041">here <pause dur="short"/> let's move all these clothes <pause dur="short"/> this I don't know how I managed to line everything else up <pause dur="short"/> and not these</u>
<u n="498" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well not on my behalf <pause dur="short"/> but not the black things</u>
<u n="499" who="S0041">no I didn't automatically not choose the <trunc>bla</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's bloody amazing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I knew it</u>
<u n="503" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0084">I knew</u>
<u n="505" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0084">fucking knew it</u>
<u n="507" who="S0041">that was it <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What is this one <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0041" trans="overlap">ah look at all the things</u>
<u n="510" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="511" who="S0041">let's put you on</u>
<u n="512" who="S0084">yes please</u>
<u n="513" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> look at my bed all nicely made <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0041">with <vocal desc="laugh"/> with an ice pop rocker on it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0084">well naturally <pause dur="short"/> where else would it be?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0041">that's where all the</u>
<u n="518" who="S0084">Good</u>
<u n="519" who="S0041">all the ice pop rockers live</u>
<u n="520" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> All the things <pause dur="short"/> mm mm mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0041">well</u>
<u n="522" who="S0084">that's gone well</u>
<u n="523" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0041">I'm having serious issues today</u>
<u n="526" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0041">there we go <pause dur="short"/> that'll do</u>
<u n="528" who="S0084">yess</u>
<u n="529" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="530" who="S0084">May I</u>
<u n="531" who="S0041">chicken</u>
<u n="532" who="S0084">deliver to you your dinner <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0041">I don't think we should call it a dinner I think it needs to be like something a bit more epic</u>
<u n="534" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm mm <trunc>diii</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> feast</u>
<u n="535" who="S0041">feast</u>
<u n="536" who="S0084">banquet</u>
<u n="537" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0084" trans="overlap">banquet's a good word <pause dur="short"/> is banquet a French word? Q U E <pause dur="short"/> latin word?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I want to know now though <pause dur="short"/> shall I tell you what's on the good stuff?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0084">ooh black black pepper <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> let's find some eighties movie would be quite nice</u>
<u n="541" who="S0041">umm we've already missed half of that <pause dur="short"/> we've got Britain's Got Talent</u>
<u n="542" who="S0084">ah I saw I saw a bit the other day</u>
<u n="543" who="S0041" trans="overlap">but unfortunately it's just finished so that</u>
<u n="544" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So we haven't</u>
<u n="545" who="S0041">we have not <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've just lied</u>
<u n="546" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that was a lie</u>
<u n="547" who="S0041">um Ugly Betty <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> love Happens</u>
<u n="548" who="S0084">it's a bit cheesy but okay</u>
<u n="549" who="S0041">Aaron something stars in this <vocal desc="laugh"/> romantic drama as a self-help guru who falls for Jennifer Aniston while on a lecture tour</u>
<u n="550" who="S0084"><trunc>Ab</trunc> abort <pause dur="short"/> abooort <pause dur="short"/> umm but whatsit Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie are engaged <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> They're getting married <pause dur="short"/> I saw it in the news this morning</u>
<u n="551" who="S0041" trans="overlap">awww</u>
<u n="552" who="S0084">yeah they've got about twelve children now haven't they?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0041">thirty-nine</u>
<u n="554" who="S0084">the <trunc>t</trunc> all of the children in fact <pause dur="short"/> they've adopted all the children of the world <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0041" trans="overlap">all the <trunc>ch</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah they have yeah <pause dur="short"/> the Magnificent Showman <pause dur="short"/> circus drama with John <trunc>W</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> John Wayne</u>
<u n="556" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="557" who="S0041" trans="overlap">there's nothing on</u>
<u n="558" who="S0084">what is going on?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">what's on the BBC? On the Beeb? Oh god</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041" trans="overlap">formula One</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">ooh no abort</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041" trans="overlap">human Planet <pause dur="short"/> formula One</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> don't want John Wayne</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">what's A Night To Remember? Titanic</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">oh god</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041"><vocal desc="sigh"/> Pooh's Heffalump movie</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">Pooh's <trunc>Heff</trunc> yes good good</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041">that's it I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately <pause dur="short"/> saint Trinian's what year is it</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that's pretty funny that's the old one</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">I haven't seen the new one I've only seen the old ones</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041">I think it's that's it it's Saint Trinian's or Love Happens I'm afraid</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084">ah mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">I'm intrigued by neither so it's your choice <pause dur="short"/> what else have we got going on? That's it I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> pooh's Heffalump Movie again</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084"><vocal desc="sigh"/> It has not gone well</u>
<u n="576" who="S0041">it's <vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's not it's not gone well</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084">on the plus chicken's delicious <pause dur="short"/> thanks Ron</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh yess</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084">umm <pause dur="short"/> what are the options Pooh's Heffalump Movie?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0041">this this is Love Happens that's on in the background <pause dur="short"/> oh no this is Ugly Betty <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0041" trans="overlap">ugly Betty or Saint Trinian's or the other thing</u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">um Saint Trinian's shall we try? Remember it being really funny but I dunno if that's cos I was a child</u>
<u n="584" who="S0041">why is it saying I can't watch it now? Yes I can</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="585" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/> Don't you even think about it <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="586" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="587" who="S0041">oh piss <pause dur="short"/> ohhhh</u>
<u n="588" who="S0084">um BFG it is <pause dur="short"/> not <trunc>h</trunc> not going well</u>
<u n="589" who="S0041">oh oh my life <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> bit what's on there? Or Pride And Prejudice is on the side there</u>
<u n="590" who="S0084">pride And <trunc>Prejud</trunc> but you only just watched that would you watch it again?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="592" who="S0084">hm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0041">on a loop</u>
<u n="594" who="S0084">we can watch that</u>
<u n="595" who="S0041">I've watched it about three times</u>
<u n="596" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0041">shall I put that on?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why not <pause dur="short"/> I do like it I mean she's not too annoying in it</u>
<u n="599" who="S0041">or we could put G I Jane on</u>
<u n="600" who="S0084">G I <trunc>Ja</trunc> what do you have it?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0041">yeah it's just here <pause dur="short"/> it's here</u>
<u n="602" who="S0084">oh ohh we can go for G I Jane <pause dur="short"/> I mean you did only watch it last night</u>
<u n="603" who="S0041">I don't mind</u>
<u n="604" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking d'you fancy a trip to Duxford at some point?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0041"><trunc>D</trunc> uh Duxford?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I mean I know you're joining the navy not the RAF it's supposed to be really interesting</u>
<u n="607" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0084">and you see the planes</u>
<u n="609" who="S0041">do you?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and you need to learn about the war don't you so you probably should go</u>
<u n="611" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I need to learn about all the wars I probably need to go to more more places like this</u>
<u n="612" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I always think when it's the airshow I want to go but it's like a hundred million pounds</u>
<u n="613" who="S0041">is it?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0084">it's really expensive um I might be exaggerating</u>
<u n="615" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I don't even know what this is the <anon type="place"/> Airshow I hear about it all the time at work and I never really know what they're talking about I just</u>
<u n="616" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="place"/> is part of the Imperial War Museum</u>
<u n="617" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="618" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and they <trunc>d</trunc> they have lots of planes from the earlier wars like World War One and World War Two <pause dur="short"/> and they just have lots of it's a museum basically <pause dur="short"/> and they <trunc>d</trunc> a couple of times a year they do airshows so like the Red Arrows and the RAF planes like the old ones they take them up in the air and they fly them around and</u>
<u n="619" who="S0041">Ohh</u>
<u n="620" who="S0084">yeah it's quite exciting but it's really expensive <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="place"/> the road in is really there's only one road and it gets really <trunc>jo</trunc> uh jammed</u>
<u n="621" who="S0041" trans="overlap">jam packed <pause dur="short"/> how much is a million pounds?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0084">mm about twenty-five pounds</u>
<u n="623" who="S0041">is it to go to an airshow?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0084">it's really really popular</u>
<u n="625" who="S0041">oh that is a bit extreme isn't it I thought you were gonna say like</u>
<u n="626" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> what you need is someone living under the <trunc>air</trunc> the flight path</u>
<u n="627" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0084">and then you can go for free</u>
<u n="629" who="S0041">maybe we should go there <pause dur="short"/> walk up and down lots</u>
<u n="630" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0041">and make friends with someone</u>
<u n="632" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0041">some old granny <pause dur="short"/> some old nana</u>
<u n="634" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> sounds like a plan</u>
<u n="635" who="S0041">pS if you start watching this and you find it really boring maybe I just liked it because she's in the navy</u>
<u n="636" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="637" who="S0041">you're gonna need to say</u>
<u n="638" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="sound of talking in film"/>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="639" who="S0084">sensitivity <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="640" who="S0041">this dinner is epic</u>
<u n="641" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="642" who="S0041">definitely mushed cabbage</u>
<u n="643" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0041">I still love it though</u>
<u n="645" who="S0084">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="646" who="S0041">D'you want me to turn this up?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0084">it's alright for me <pause dur="short"/> is it alright for you?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0041">mhm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="649" who="S0041">you know when um Dan said his son had been ravaged?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0084">ravaged savaged yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0041">savaged ravaged <pause dur="short"/> savaged <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="652" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0041">um did he said therefore I'm gonna burn the bed?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's what I'm insisting</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="655" who="S0041">this is the job that they're gonna create in the navy for us that she's doing now</u>
<u n="656" who="S0084">intelligence officer</u>
<u n="657" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="659" who="S0041">well I hope they</u>
<u n="660" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's weird that they don't have it already</u>
<u n="661" who="S0041">I don't really understand how you can't</u>
<u n="662" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="663" who="S0041">maybe they borrowed somebody else's <pause dur="short"/> ah I think that might be gravy in my hair</u>
<u n="664" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Saving that for later</u>
<u n="665" who="S0041">mhm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's really nice</u>
<u n="668" who="S0084">you can suck on it tonight when you're in bed</u>
<u n="669" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying when she was a kid she used to suck on her hair</u>
<u n="670" who="S0084">lot of kids do</u>
<u n="671" who="S0041">do they?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0084"><trunc>M</trunc> I I know girls when I was at school who used to do that <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0041">suck on your hair</u>
<u n="674" who="S0084">my ex <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to work in a hospital worked in theatre he was like an anaesthetist and um once had a young girl come in eleven or twelve complaining of stomach pains <pause dur="short"/> they opened her up and there was a massive ball of hair in her tummy <pause dur="short"/> like a cat</u>
<u n="675" who="S0041">shiit</u>
<u n="676" who="S0084">she'd been sucking on her hair and swallowing the hairs and it formed a ball in her stomach <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="677" who="S0041">that's rank</u>
<u n="678" who="S0084" trans="overlap">isn't it yeah there's loads of stuff like that though there was a guy who used to swallow forks <pause dur="short"/> like in a mental <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of something dropping"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/> mm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Your face then <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Your face then is the best thing I've seen</u>
<u n="684" who="S0084">slowmo <pause dur="short"/> right sort that out in a minute when I'm not eating my dinner <pause dur="short"/> yeah there was a guy who was just gone in the head I think</u>
<u n="685" who="S0041">he used to swallow forks? How did he even get them down?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0084">no idea it's amazing well I was I guess sword swallowers they manage to um it's just fighting your gag reflex isn't it?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0041"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well sword swallowers get you <trunc>s</trunc> get a sword all the way down don't they?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0041" trans="overlap">would a sword be not big? Really I thought it was a joke I thought it was like a false sword</u>
<u n="690" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no no no no <pause dur="short"/> you just fight your gag reflex which obviously takes training <pause dur="short"/> and you can swallow the sword it goes all the way down your oesophagus <pause dur="short"/> like all the way down <pause dur="short"/> obviously incredibly dangerous cos if your gag reflexes kick in I guess you'd cut your throat to ribbons I dunno <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's really dangerous</u>
<u n="691" who="S0041">shabs</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="692" who="S0041">no ooh god no all my life I just thought it was like some big hoax</u>
<u n="693" who="S0084">no no it's real they really really really do it <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0041">cripers</u>
<u n="695" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="696" who="S0041">this really is top draw <pause dur="short"/> yes they went through all the paperwork of all the <trunc>g</trunc> women have <trunc>h</trunc> ever achieved highly in the navy <pause dur="short"/> and she chose the prettiest looking one basically what didn't look too much like a man</u>
<u n="697" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0041">Cos she said you know I don't if I'm gonna get a poster gonna get a poster girl out this I don't want them ugly</u>
<u n="699" who="S0084">nice</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="700" who="S0041">sword fucking sword swallowers</u>
<u n="701" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0041">fucking sword swallowers</u>
<u n="703" who="S0084">I know</u>
<event desc="sound of tv stops noise of background talking starts"/>
<u n="704" who="S0046">I loaded up me uh <unclear/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0041"><unclear/> something you might enjoy</u>
<u n="706" who="S0084"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="707" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/><unclear/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0046">you know I don't do milk <pause dur="short"/> and I don't want these bottles</u>
<u n="709" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/> Who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0084">hm?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/> Who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0046">but at least something</u>
<u n="713" who="S0084"><vocal desc="misc"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/> Crazy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="sound of tv restarts"/>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="716" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0084">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="718" who="S0041">think of all the vitamins we've been eating now</u>
<u n="719" who="S0084">Mhmm <pause dur="short"/> and then we're gonna undo all the good work</u>
<u n="720" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Don't think it's undoing <pause dur="short"/> I think it's probably</u>
<u n="721" who="S0084">complementing?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0041">complementing</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="723" who="S0041">I really want to Google to see if the Navy Seals are actually our version of the Marines or whether they're better than our Marines</u>
<u n="724" who="S0084">hm I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I mean our Marines are pretty insane</u>
<u n="725" who="S0041">hm <pause dur="short"/> but in further on in the film when all the people are lined up to join the Navy Seals they go through and they say you know Sir Lieutenant Commander Royal Marine I'm sure I heard him say Royal Marine</u>
<u n="726" who="S0084">it might not mean the same as here though</u>
<u n="727" who="S0041">oh yeah maybe</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="728" who="S0084">mhm <pause dur="short"/> delish <pause dur="short"/> meat sweats</u>
<u n="729" who="S0041">I was gonna say I wonder when the meat sweats are gonna come</u>
<u n="730" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mhm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="731" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0041">I love it how there has to be someone for her not to be a lesbian</u>
<u n="733" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="734" who="S0084">what um what rating is this?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0041">I'm gonna go for a fifteen from here</u>
<u n="736" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> go go Gadget eyes</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="737" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="738" who="S0041">that's so nice</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="739" who="S0041">I'm a bit full</u>
<u n="740" who="S0084">you're a bit full? No <pause dur="short"/> that's just a pain barrier <pause dur="short"/> beat it</u>
<u n="741" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="742" who="S0084">oh he's a knob</u>
<u n="743" who="S0041">yep</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="744" who="S0041">that was a burp that came out</u>
<u n="745" who="S0084">rah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="746" who="S0041">oh god is it only three <trunc>d</trunc> three weeks to D Day now</u>
<u n="747" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="748" who="S0041">shit</u>
<u n="749" who="S0084">three weeks on Wednesday</u>
<u n="750" who="S0041">oh god <pause dur="short"/> three weeks</u>
<u n="751" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0041">two weeks</u>
<u n="753" who="S0084">but you only started training two weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> and you've already you're already four minutes within the <unclear/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> nick's making me do something something tomorrow I don't know <pause dur="short"/> something to do with sprinting</u>
<u n="755" who="S0084">oh my god</u>
<u n="756" who="S0041">that sounds intense</u>
<u n="757" who="S0041">yeah I'm a little bit concerned</u>
<u n="758" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I need to join the <unclear/> this week <pause dur="short"/> that's nice</u>
<u n="759" who="S0041">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="760" who="S0041">the barber <pause dur="short"/> thought she said Barbara was my next stop and I kept thinking who the fuck's Barbara?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0084">and why would you well why would you say barber when you're a gir?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> she's supposed to have her head shaved <pause dur="short"/> like he said no it's alright as long as it's off your neck and out of your face then that's fine by me <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="763" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="764" who="S0084">are you gonna have to say that? Permission to speak? </u>
<u n="765" who="S0041">maybe in front of the captain</u>
<u n="766" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0041">dunno <pause dur="short"/> what look at how many ranks he's got on his lapels</u>
<u n="768" who="S0084">oh god <pause dur="short"/> he's a bit serious</u>
<u n="769" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> how many has she got? She's lieutenant did they say?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="771" who="S0041">that's what I'll be</u>
<u n="772" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="773" who="S0041">or <trunc>s</trunc> or am I sub-lieutenant? I think <unclear/>'s a sub-lieutenant and I'm providing her if I basically do my job properly</u>
<u n="774" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="775" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="777" who="S0041">and do we say left-tenant in English?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0084">um lieutenant</u>
<u n="779" who="S0041">Cos I've heard so many people say left-tenant </u>
<u n="780" who="S0084">mhm <pause dur="short"/> usually Americans I think</u>
<u n="781" who="S0041">Ohh cos I had a look cos I was reading I was like but it says lieutenant so why were people saying left-tenant and I thought is it two different words</u>
<u n="782" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no it's the same <pause dur="short"/> but you can spell it with an F</u>
<u n="783" who="S0041">can you?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> bloody English</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="785" who="S0084">can't believe I've eaten all my dinner <pause dur="short"/> what an animal?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0041">dessert I'm gonna finish it</u>
<u n="787" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I just needed a little breather that's all</u>
<u n="789" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I might regret it in five minutes when it all hit hits my stomach</u>
<u n="790" who="S0041">uh yes <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="791" who="S0084">I might start crying</u>
<u n="792" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>Hor</trunc> made her look all sweaty <pause dur="short"/> it's the meat sweats</u>
<u n="793" who="S0084">holding my tummy <pause dur="short"/> I'm having a baby</u>
<u n="794" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> A chicken baby</u>
<u n="795" who="S0084">A chicken baby</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="796" who="S0084">so they don't like her cos she's got boobs</u>
<u n="797" who="S0041">yes basically <pause dur="short"/> you know what they like they're all like squaddies and hmm this is all men</u>
<u n="798" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0041">Grr</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="800" who="S0084">God</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="801" who="S0084">is this a true story then? They never used to let women in the Navy Seals?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0041">well <trunc>u</trunc> I don't know if they <trunc>s</trunc> do now</u>
<u n="803" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0041">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> we certainly don't let them in the Marines</u>
<u n="805" who="S0084">Don't we?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> the only thing the only way a woman can be in the Marines is if they play in the band</u>
<u n="807" who="S0084">awww</u>
<u n="808" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0084">that's shit</u>
<u n="810" who="S0041" trans="overlap">which I think is fine <pause dur="short"/> I don't really see a problem with it <pause dur="short"/> probably cos I won't don't wanna go to war <pause dur="short"/> mind you I suppose if you really wanted to do that and you're a girl I can't imagine any girl that would want to but if you did I could see that being a bit unjust</u>
<u n="811" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that's because they think that women aren't as tough as men</u>
<u n="812" who="S0041">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="813" who="S0084"><trunc>Opera</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="814" who="S0041">marine Force Recon <pause dur="short"/> uh-oh</u>
<u n="815" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0041">I don't think a woman could be in the Marines <pause dur="short"/> they'd have to be built like a wrestler or something</u>
<u n="817" who="S0084">yeah the Marines you meat you meet are fucking hench</u>
<u n="818" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they have to train with thirteen stone on their back</u>
<u n="819" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="820" who="S0041">that's more than me</u>
<u n="821" who="S0084">yeah it's more than me <pause dur="short"/> I'm eleven stone</u>
<u n="822" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that's a lot</u>
<u n="823" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="824" who="S0041">like I I couldn't even if I really wanted to there's no way I could walk with you on my back <trunc>ne</trunc> <trunc>mi</trunc> never mind run <pause dur="short"/> couldn't do it</u>
<u n="825" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no and they've gotta go on a hike</u>
<u n="826" who="S0041">yeah like nine miles they have to do</u>
<u n="827" who="S0084">yeah like in Welsh mountains in the rain</u>
<u n="828" who="S0041">I just I couldn't do that <pause dur="short"/> and I can't imagine any amount of training where I would be able to do that</u>
<u n="829" who="S0084">I was gonna say cos you go from the Navy don't you?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="831" who="S0084">you don't go in as a Marine</u>
<u n="832" who="S0041">no I think you can <pause dur="short"/> think you might be able to</u>
<u n="833" who="S0084" trans="overlap">can you?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0084" trans="overlap">God <pause dur="short"/> think you have to have been training</u>
<u n="836" who="S0041" trans="overlap">the only true <pause dur="short"/> you <trunc>f</trunc> your training's much more difficult <pause dur="short"/> and even the entry requirements <pause dur="short"/> like their fitness test they'll run they run two <pause dur="short"/> so the first one they have to do in the same amount of minutes as me <pause dur="short"/> and the second one they have to do in ten minutes and they have to do the second one straight after the first one</u>
<u n="837" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0084">they have to beat their time on the second run?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so they run it <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah so they run it and have to get my time <pause dur="short"/> and then even if you're forty there's no restriction like age bracket like in the Navy</u>
<u n="841" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="842" who="S0041">and then after that I don't know how long they get but it's basically straight away <pause dur="short"/> they probably get a breather get a drink or something and then do it again but they have to do it in ten minutes</u>
<u n="843" who="S0084">I don't know now</u>
<u n="844" who="S0041">we're gonna learn to hate him</u>
<u n="845" who="S0084">I already do hate him</u>
<u n="846" who="S0041">with his moustache</u>
<u n="847" who="S0084">did you ever have that French VHS tape at school? Moustache The Cat? And he used to speak French <pause dur="short"/> I used to watch it <pause dur="short"/> moustache</u>
<u n="848" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="849" who="S0084">he was a little French cat</u>
<u n="850" who="S0041">aww</u>
<u n="851" who="S0084">yes I think I think you um have missed out there we had Moustache <pause dur="short"/> he was very cute</u>
<u n="852" who="S0041">I think I might need <trunc>sh</trunc> Moushtache</u>
<u n="853" who="S0084">moushtaaaache</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="854" who="S0041">I remember watching <trunc>s</trunc> couple of episodes of some type of Spanish sitcom type thing</u>
<u n="855" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="856" who="S0041">which was basically like our our version of Fawlty Towers like</u>
<u n="857" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0041">he was a cleaner in a in a block of flats <pause dur="short"/> and it's like slapstick comedy</u>
<u n="859" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="860" who="S0041">definitely wasn't Moustache <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0084">moooustache</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="862" who="S0041">oof <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realize he was on top of the boat</u>
<u n="863" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's funny <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="864" who="S0084">is he really sunburnt? Master Chief?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="866" who="S0084">that's his title? I wanna be Master Chief</u>
<u n="867" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Master Chief King</u>
<u n="868" who="S0084">master Chief King Of All The Universe</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="869" who="S0084">what are they doing?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="870" who="S0084">aww <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="871" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/> That was on his legs</u>
<u n="872" who="S0041">he goes under</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="873" who="S0084">meh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="874" who="S0041">not me <pause dur="short"/> I'm full of joy</u>
<u n="875" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> think that's a lie</u>
<u n="877" who="S0084">I suppose that's it you don't wanna say you're in pain otherwise he'll beat you to within an inch of your life</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="878" who="S0084">what are they doing? press-ups under water?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0041">um those funny ones <pause dur="short"/> you know you drop your bum</u>
<u n="880" who="S0084" trans="overlap">how weird</u>
<u n="881" who="S0041">have you ever tried doing it?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0084">no is it really hard?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't do one <pause dur="short"/> you might be able to cos you beat me at press-ups the other day</u>
<u n="884" who="S0084">umm <pause dur="short"/> I would've thought it was easier <pause dur="short"/> cos that's how I do press-ups normally <pause dur="short"/> I drop my bum more than I drop my whole body</u>
<u n="885" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> I think the idea is that it's harder to drop drop the front the front of your the front of your chest so low</u>
<u n="886" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="887" who="S0041">I think that's it</u>
<u n="888" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> why are there a helicopter just hanging out there? In case any of them drown?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0041">maybe <pause dur="short"/> ambulance airlift</u>
<u n="890" who="S0084">Ohh</u>
<u n="891" who="S0041">yeah she tried to tie her hair up out of her face and he pushed her in the water</u>
<u n="892" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="893" who="S0041">stop fannying on with your hair</u>
<u n="894" who="S0084">well fair enough why isn't her hair tied up?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0041">yeah I think it might've been when she started</u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="897" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Master Chief? He's a meanie</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="898" who="S0041">oh yeah I forgot he makes them eat rubbish out of the bin not even have dinner</u>
<u n="899" who="S0084">what what?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="901" who="S0084">to break their spirits?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="903" who="S0084">does this not make you worry? I mean I know you're not going in the Marines but still</u>
<u n="904" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> while I was watching it yesterday and I thought I hope to god that this is really really extreme and that nothing like this would ever happen anywhere near at all ever <pause dur="short"/> look they're just fighting to get dinners and stuff <pause dur="short"/> bloody ridiculous</u>
<u n="905" who="S0084"><vocal desc="sigh"/> shit <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> that's intense</u>
<u n="906" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and later on obviously must've not been able to have time to everything so they shove them back out again in a minute <pause dur="short"/> they they get they there's a really really bad bit after this really difficult training and you think holy shit how are they all <trunc>al</trunc> still alive? </u>
<u n="907" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="908" who="S0041">and then he says right you've got three minutes to get something to eat and they run up and he has those trash cans out like what they're putting the rubbish in now and that's what he gives them to eat</u>
<u n="909" who="S0084">Jesus</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="910" who="S0084">just why? Just why would you do it to yourself</u>
<u n="911" who="S0041">I've no idea <pause dur="short"/> I really don't <pause dur="short"/> don't get it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="912" who="S0084">was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> upset about not going for the walk?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0041">no she was like <pause dur="short"/> well I said to her well why don't you know you go and get trainers and stuff in preparation for next weekend and she was like um</u>
<u n="914" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0041">she said she couldn't get into town until half two which I find very strange seen as you know it's only half three now</u>
<u n="916" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0041">and we've done loads of stuff</u>
<u n="918" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0041">um and she said oh yeah um probably should do and I said oh and I thought maybe she's gonna want me to go with her <pause dur="short"/> and I said okay well I'll come and meet you after work on Wednesday cos it's late night shopping </u>
<u n="920" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0041"> and I finish at four <pause dur="short"/> And she was like oh alright then um I finish work at half three so should be with you about half four <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="922" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0041" trans="overlap">whatever</u>
<u n="924" who="S0084">uh in the bin</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="925" who="S0084">to be fair you would just eat food out the bin wouldn't you cos you'd be starving?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you just see him do did they do <trunc>s</trunc> the medical thing yet?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0084">I don't think so</u>
<u n="928" who="S0041" trans="overlap">they came out the water and they were so cold that they had a medical officer had to check every single one individually</u>
<u n="929" who="S0084">to make sure they weren't dead?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0041">make sure they weren't dying yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0084">Jesus</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="932" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="933" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="934" who="S0041"><unclear/> my?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0084"><unclear/> in the kitchen</u>
<u n="936" who="S0041">sweet <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="937" who="S0084">ah thank you mate</u>
<u n="938" who="S0041">just take this as well <pause dur="short"/> d'you not like this bit?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0084">no I don't like that bit</u>
<u n="940" who="S0041">oh I like that better than the other bit</u>
<u n="941" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I don't like the stalky bit <pause dur="short"/> do you?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0084">that's funny</u>
<u n="944" who="S0041">oh thanks mate</u>
<u n="945" who="S0084">one chicken down <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> one <pause dur="short"/> chicken nil <pause dur="short"/> you alright for enough hands?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0041">got it</u>
<u n="947" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="948" who="S0084">apparently it means someone</u>
<u n="949" who="S0041" trans="overlap">she even gives him his food</u>
<u n="950" who="S0084">oh does she?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0084">that's very cute <pause dur="short"/> it means my sweet Papa <pause dur="short"/> it's in Italian <pause dur="short"/> it's Puccini <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>co</trunc> oh <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="953" who="S0041">can't understand the words</u>
<u n="954" who="S0084">oh <trunc>niero</trunc> Babbino Caro or something <pause dur="short"/> dunno you'll know</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="955" who="S0041">Don't know what Papa is</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="956" who="S0084">I think it's Babbino <pause dur="short"/> o Mio</u>
<u n="957" who="S0041" trans="overlap">did you say sweet?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0084">yeah My Sweet Papa <pause dur="short"/> o Mio Babbino Caro I think that's what it's called</u>
<u n="959" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Caro C A R O</u>
<u n="960" who="S0084" trans="overlap">R O mm</u>
<u n="961" who="S0041">thought it was carino <pause dur="short"/> no that's Spanish <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="962" who="S0041">this is this is what terrifies me here</u>
<u n="963" who="S0084">running in the rain?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> they have to do this course thing and this live fire</u>
<u n="965" who="S0084">live fire?</u>
<u n="966" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="967" who="S0084">they wouldn't do that to you would they?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0041">I fucking hope not <pause dur="short"/> the army do it</u>
<u n="969" who="S0084">the army do it I've seen films where the <trunc>e</trunc> where they do it in the army and someone got shot and killed</u>
<u n="970" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0084">in the <trunc>y</trunc> no in the film <pause dur="short"/> but you cos you've gotta crawl and the fire's above your head and you've gotta crawl</u>
<u n="972" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0084">through the course <pause dur="short"/> and someone gets caught in something and starts to freak out and lifts their head and they get killed they get shot</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="974" who="S0084">she's gotta use some special steps?</u>
<u n="975" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="976" who="S0084">hilarious</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="977" who="S0041">it's like a box thing</u>
<u n="978" who="S0084">oh god</u>
<u n="979" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Can you imagine that? I can't think of anything worse</u>
<u n="980" who="S0084">how are they? Where's the live fire?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0041">now <pause dur="short"/> it's anything above the</u>
<u n="982" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> I don't know if they actually do this though</u>
<u n="983" who="S0041">I hope not</u>
<u n="984" who="S0084">I mean it seems incredibly dangerous</u>
<u n="985" who="S0041">doesn't it?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="986" who="S0041">they've been firing a shot right next to her head</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="987" who="S0041">God I just <trunc>g</trunc> just looking at it makes me wanna die</u>
<u n="988" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think they'd make you do it <pause dur="short"/> mm I hope</u>
<u n="989" who="S0041">I fucking hope not look at all those flame throwers and mines and <pause dur="short"/> I hope this is so far from the truth</u>
<u n="990" who="S0084">I mean would they not tell you? I mean that's what you need to ask really <pause dur="short"/> that's quite crucial information</u>
<u n="991" who="S0041">yeah I think I need to ask this <pause dur="short"/> that makes me feel like I can't breathe very much</u>
<u n="992" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="993" who="S0084">oh and strobe lighting oh my god you just wanna be sick</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="994" who="S0041">ahh yeah I remember what happens now</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="995" who="S0041">I bet that's the thing she's supposed to use</u>
<u n="996" who="S0084">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> hilarious</u>
<u n="997" who="S0041">like a box with steps on it</u>
<u n="998" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="999" who="S0041">cos all the men like to just climb <trunc>an</trunc> over wall</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1000" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0084">and how did the rest of them get up?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I know what happens</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0084">Cos they like trod on her head</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0041">so she was like helping up all the massive heavy men <pause dur="short"/> look he just ran and</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0084">jumped on her back yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0084">and then how how does she get over? They just leave her?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0041">no well the <trunc>thi</trunc> the thing is that she helps up the last person properly the last person over is supposed to pull the last man over</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1011" who="S0041">so technically if she wasn't a woman and had that box that'd be her gone now she'd'a failed the course because of that</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0084">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> but then do they not are they not viewing all this are they not watching it all</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0041">yeah but nobody knows that they're viewing it</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0041">like like that guy who was the Gun Master Chief person that just saw it through his gun rifle</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0084">Ohh</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0041">but he only knows cos he was trying to shoot her</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0084">nice</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1019" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1020" who="S0041"><unclear/> fucking cold her is</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0084" trans="overlap">aww <pause dur="short"/> aww <pause dur="short"/> yeah but you're not joining the Marines just keep telling yourself that <pause dur="short"/> where are they now?</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0041">still on the base</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0084">what are they squirting them with? Is it whipped cream? Open wide</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1024" who="S0084">he's gotta do the course again</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0041">he's gonna quit <pause dur="short"/> if you <trunc>ri</trunc> if you get up and you can ring the bell any time you want</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1027" who="S0041">three rings and you quit</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0084">and he's got blood coming out of his head <pause dur="short"/> so does she pass the course then?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0041">yeah but she doesn't understand cos she was the last one</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the guy that left her</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0041">has failed it <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't have to leave but he failed that particular part</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? That one with the blood?</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0041">uh no <pause dur="short"/> it's this one</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1037" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1038" who="S0041">so no one else knows what he's talking about but they guy's giving it him because he left her behind and he knows it</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> even though he was trying to shoot her himself</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes that's it must be right</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I think that sounds a little bit like double standards but it's fine <pause dur="short"/> I'm allowed to kill her but you're not <pause dur="short"/> I suppose the thing is they don't want them to leave anybody behind</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I don't think they would've actually killed her <pause dur="short"/> I think he was shooting near her just to put her off</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/> they're all leaving</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0084">not getting emotional here</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0041">they just are all the way through they're like they're purposely trying to make them fail all the time</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose that's it cos you put yourself those these people put themselves in difficult situations <pause dur="short"/> you've got to be prepared</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1050" who="S0084">kick it</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0041">spit at it</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1053" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1054" who="S0041">like the women have to do less press-ups and stuff don't they than men? He's saying she's a woman she gets thirty seconds free</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0084">ahhh</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0041">she's like fuck off I don't want thirty seconds free </u>
<u n="1057" who="S0084">it'd be so hard not um take it though wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0041"> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd be like yes please </u>
<u n="1059" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> so hard <pause dur="short"/> I dunno how I feel about all this <pause dur="short"/> cos basically women are can't be as strong as men like can they?</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0041">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I don't know if <trunc>y</trunc> they can</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0041">like think of like Miss World Wrestler people</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0084">mm yeah but I think genetically apart from various freaks don't think women are supposed to be</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0041" trans="overlap">if they can do it d'you think women can do it?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0041">Cos she now to be one of these people would not need to as physically fit</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0041">as the Miss World <trunc>Sh</trunc> strong you know those people?</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0041">I dunno</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1071" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> where are you doing?</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0041">well you can't see from where you're sat but I took my nail polish off the other day</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0041">and left nail polish remover round the pad on there and it's burnt it all burnt <unclear/></u>
<u n="1075" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Ohh <vocal desc="laugh"/> Shit</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's still not even set properly</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0084">oh my god</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0041">like it's all gone</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0084">that's pretty corrosive</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0041">bubbly</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0084">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> so it's melted the plastic</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's gone down to <trunc>p</trunc> yeah the plastic's like Play-Doh on this bit</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0084">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> you're a brainfart</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0041">you're a <trunc>brain</trunc> you're a brainfart</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0084">mm hmm hmm <pause dur="short"/> what I resent Lieutenant</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0084">mm hmm <pause dur="short"/> I think he's in The Walking Dead actually that I was watching this morning that's a bit weird</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0041">that's not the man that you were trying to tell me about is it?</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0084">Andrew Lincoln no he's just one of the characters <pause dur="short"/> oh let's just find a picture of Andrew Lincoln</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0084">sorry <pause dur="short"/> try again <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> try again <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Delete <pause dur="short"/> delete him now</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1092" who="S0084">oh he was in Love Actually <pause dur="short"/> d'you remember Love Actually? He's the one who's in love with Keira Knightly</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0041">oh yes that's not who I was thinking of <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1094" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0041">at all</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0084">I think that is from Love Actually actually that picture</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0041">that's not who I was thinking of at all</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0084">ah I see now <pause dur="short"/> well actually this Walking Dead thing is pretty good <pause dur="short"/> quite like it <pause dur="short"/> oh that's a picture from it <pause dur="short"/> stop <pause dur="short"/> abort <pause dur="short"/> andrew James Clutterbuck is his real name <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1099" who="S0041" trans="overlap">Clutterbuck</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0084">that's a much better name than Lincoln</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0041">I'd rather be called Clutterbuck <pause dur="short"/> andrew James Clutterbuck</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0084">I like it <pause dur="short"/> this is him in The Walking Dead looking a bit sweaty <pause dur="short"/> and a bit hairy</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0041">huhh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1104" who="S0041">certainly not who I was thinking of</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0084">no but he's pretty cute</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0041">he is pretty hot</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0084">mm is this where she shaves her head? Pretty fortunate for you Demi you've got a nice shaped head <pause dur="short"/> what about the rest of us?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she does look quite manly though I think when she shaves her head off like her features and her face aren't very feminine</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0084">no it's like Hilary Swank she's a a really ugly woman isn't she?</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0041">which one's she?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0084">oh gawd I dunno why I <trunc>r</trunc> I tell you these things</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0041" trans="overlap">is she in? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0084" trans="overlap">boys Don't Cry</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> got it <pause dur="short"/> I got a new one</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1116" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I've got a new one <pause dur="short"/> I thought you were talking about her that's in um <trunc>C</trunc> <trunc>C</trunc> Casanova <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>o</trunc> the angel at the end</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0084">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0041">blond</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1119" who="S0041">eucch <pause dur="short"/> eoow</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0041">eucch <pause dur="short"/> oh god head off the hair really freaks me out <pause dur="short"/> having hair off the head</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You're such a weirdo</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0041">I've got Chelsea to bring the razor with her when she comes <pause dur="short"/> let me see if she can thin out the front of my hair you know where my fringe is growing out and try and blend it into the rest of it</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0041">so it's gone <pause dur="short"/> have like a little party</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1126" who="S0041">I'd like to go on a quick like walk somewhere cos I really want to put the apple pies in my mouth <pause dur="short"/> but there's just not room yet</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0084">I know <pause dur="short"/> I really want to eat them <pause dur="short"/> I really want to eat them <pause dur="short"/> really really badly now</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0041">badly <pause dur="short"/> give me the pie</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0084">really really badly</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1131" who="S0084">what's occurring?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0041" trans="overlap">D'you it's really hard to see when these when it's light out here <pause dur="short"/> last night was really easy to see</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I can't see anything really <pause dur="short"/> I can see some white underpants</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0041">it's really Mister Fickle isn't it? They're taking the piss basically cos she's walked in</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0041">and they've taken tampons out of her bag</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0084">Cos they're totally nice</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0041">yep</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1139" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Dee dee dee di dee <pause dur="short"/> dee dee dee dee <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1140" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1141" who="S0084">uh model has natural twenty inch waist <pause dur="short"/> twenty inch</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0084">rank as hell</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0084">oh my god you have to see this photo</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0041">have you got the photograph of the twenty inch waist?</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0084">she says it is natural she <trunc>do</trunc> that is rank as all hell <pause dur="short"/> they shouldn't put her on a catwalk they should hospitalize her</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/> Ohh shiit</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0084">she says that's natural <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that's natural <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously you know that</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0084">modelling agencies are in big trouble now aren't they if they um hire size zero models <pause dur="short"/> so they can be all like yeah I'm naturally size zero <pause dur="short"/> that's not okay <pause dur="short"/> I think she looks like a size zero would hang off her <pause dur="short"/> like her boob and waist area looks <trunc>n</trunc> okay</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0041">okay</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0084">I mean looks skinny but looks okay <pause dur="short"/> she her waist is really really pinched</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0041">I can't believe that's a real person</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0084">mm something's gone wrong there</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I mean the dress accentuates it doesn't it the dress she's wearing makes you see it worse cos it makes her top and her bottom look bigger because of the frills</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but still <pause dur="short"/> yeah but still <pause dur="short"/> because you must wonder about her organs like they must either be tiny or squished</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0041">I think she's had one of those trainers on you know? Like Dita Von Teese?</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0084">oh maybe yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0041">those things that you wear all tend to overuse it makes you shaped like that doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0084">but look at her legs</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0041">massive gap you could fit your fist in between them</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0084">ah it's not normal <pause dur="short"/> she's Romanian</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0041">is there any other pictures of her apart from that red dress?</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0084">see her hips are thirty-two inches <pause dur="short"/> um I dunno <pause dur="short"/> the Human Hourglass <pause dur="short"/> eighty-four pounds</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/> what?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0084">she weighs eighty-four pounds</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1169" who="S0084" trans="overlap">half of me</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0041">oh it's <trunc>awf</trunc></u>
<u n="1171" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/> Thirty-four eighty-four <trunc>pou</trunc> eighty-four pounds?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0084">which is what's that divided by fourteen?</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0084">divide by ten is is eight so it's it's less than eight stone seven stone</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so unfair <pause dur="short"/> holy shit that's nearly half of me</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1177" who="S0041">holy Yackerbuckackers</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0084">what is her name I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> ioana Spangenberg <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0041">that's normal</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><trunc>Ior</trunc> Iona Ioana <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0041">that's not normal <pause dur="short"/> that's not no</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0084">it's not normal at all is it?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0084">Ioana Spangenberg</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1185" who="S0046">hiya</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0084">ridiculous voice</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0041">fuck <pause dur="short"/> fuck</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0084">nobody talks like that</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0041">no we should've put a Spanish film on</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Spanish Spanish Spanish <pause dur="short"/> where are the images? <trunc>Hedi</trunc> oh here we go</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0041">is there more?</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0084">yeah I've Googled them now <pause dur="short"/> there's all all the same dress weirdly</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0041">ahh I want to see <trunc>nes</trunc> anything other than that</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0084">oh she went into a cat suit here <pause dur="short"/> if you scroll to the <trunc>l</trunc> right</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1197" who="S0041">eugh look at <trunc>tho</trunc> those awful platforms</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1199" who="S0041">she doesn't look as well she she's wearing something disgusting but she doesn't look as crazy there</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0084">no <trunc>d</trunc> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I mean she looks insanely skinny</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't imagine a real person that skinny</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0084">but the but the waist definitely is so much skinnier than the hips <pause dur="short"/> but the hips <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know they doctor these images so that you're people's legs you know makes them look skinnier by making a hole between the legs but I think her legs probably do look like that cos she's so skinny</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0084"><pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1205" who="S0041">oh shit</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what the? What is the doing? Pull-ups? Oh my god</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0041">holy shit <pause dur="short"/> I knew it <pause dur="short"/> it's not natural at all</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0084">huh?</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0041">she's had a waist trainer on</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0084">oh fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> that's disgusting like the her hips there <pause dur="short"/> oh makes me feel sick <pause dur="short"/> is that photo supposed to? Does she think she looks good?</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0041">I think so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw a programme on it once <pause dur="short"/> um it's I think it was like Jerry <trunc>Spri</trunc> I might even have been Jerry Springer <pause dur="short"/> and there's a massive group of people in America that do it <pause dur="short"/> from being young teens um in some like little village in the outback or you know somewhere in the middle of nowhere</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0041">um cos they wear all fifties clothing</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0041">and I mean that's by the far the most extreme version <pause dur="short"/> not the most extreme version I've seen in my life but if it <trunc>w</trunc> had o' been naturally it'd've been by far the most extreme one</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> Disgusting</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0041" trans="overlap">are they putting her in the catwalk then?</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0041">are they?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0041">shit</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0084">ooh <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> look at you <pause dur="short"/> what is this? What is this?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0041">thought that was a spider but there isn't it's hanging off my sock <pause dur="short"/> it's just a little bit of cotton</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yummy</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1225" who="S0084">hm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1226" who="S0084">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1227" who="S0041">and she looks like a man now</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of clapping"/>
<u n="1229" who="S0084">ooh I'm getting close to pie time</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0041">yeah I'm getting close to pie time</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1231" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <unclear/> </u>
<u n="1232" who="S0041">I'm quite inclined to put a <trunc>Span</trunc> Spanish film on</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> think I might <unclear/></u>
<u n="1235" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0041">thought I forgot how much <unclear/></u>
<u n="1237" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> dee dee di dee dee dee <pause dur="short"/> aww <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s applying for her Berlin course today <pause dur="short"/> it's the day she can start her application process <pause dur="short"/> she's been waiting since I dunno November since she found out about this MA <pause dur="short"/> I really hope she gets it cos she really is so excited about it</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0041">aww</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0084">it's the best one <pause dur="short"/> best place yet <pause dur="short"/> and Berlin is a pretty awesome place <pause dur="short"/> be a really fun place to live for a year <pause dur="short"/> I think if she does go I'll probably move back in with my mum</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and you'll be in the Navy <pause dur="short"/> um just to say money <pause dur="short"/> she's already asked me to move back in and while I don't really want to it would be a good opportunity to not spend any money</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1243" who="S0084">ooh that'd be nice</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1244" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1245" who="S0084">oh I've got my mum's version of Talk To Her <pause dur="short"/> cos I said that when we tried to watch it on yours we couldn't get the subtitles to work and I didn't know if it was my disc but she's taken a copy and said she's watched it and the subtitles work so</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0041">ah we could do that then</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0084">we could watch that or we could try <pause dur="short"/> I dunno why it didn't work before</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> try that</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0084">what are they doing? She's gotta pull herself in the boat?</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and she doesn't make it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1251" who="S0084">umm</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0041">and that stupid knob every time makes some type of bad comment about her <pause dur="short"/> and so because he makes the comment they all get put back in</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1254" who="S0041">but then they all blame it on her cos they're like oh you were the dead weight <pause dur="short"/> And then it's only just at this point where someone pulls pulls up the rest of the squad <pause dur="short"/> they said it's not her fault it's his fault for commenting on it</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0084">aww</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0041">Cos the whole point is that we should be a team</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> men are so stupid</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1258" who="S0084">have they got um inflatable neck braces on or something?</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1260" who="S0041">world War Two</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0084">disgusting isn't it? I mean they had segregation in the in America until nineteen sixty-eight</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0041">yeah that doesn't make sense to me at all</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0041">that's so late</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's not very it's very it's very recent</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0041">it's so late</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0041">like in my head when I saw the pictures of this happening <pause dur="short"/> you know you're seeing books and on films and stuff I think of it as being about nineteen forty <pause dur="short"/> nineteen thirty-nineteen forty which to me</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what the Civil Rights Movement?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0041" trans="overlap">which to me <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> which to me is still late</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0041">but that's that's what I think of segregation people on different buses that's when it happened</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> well yeah it was happening then but it was happening right during the forties fifties sixties</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0084">I mean Rosa Parks who was the what they say is the start of the Civil Rights Movement when she refused to give up her seat to a white person like she was um a sixty year-old black woman travelling home on the bus from work <pause dur="short"/> and obviously at that point there was segregation there was a black area of the buses and the black people had to sit out that was at the back</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0084">and she refused to give up her seat to a white person <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think she was abused but I think you know she was certainly shouted at and that was the start when people would then sort of get involved and start having you know um <trunc>sta</trunc> started rioting and started protest movements and that was nineteen fifty-nine <pause dur="short"/> so that was really late and it wasn't until um JFK um abolished segregation and brought in the Civil Rights Act that um that that sort of thing was sort of made illegal <pause dur="short"/> but that wasn't until nineteen sixty-five</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that's crazy <pause dur="short"/> no that's <trunc>n</trunc> that's not long ago</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0084">well no <pause dur="short"/> it's only fifty years isn't it?</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0041">like <trunc>peo</trunc> people that</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0084">mm <trunc>d</trunc> and certainly the mindset didn't change overnight d'you know what I mean like? <trunc>B</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> if you go to America most of the shitty jobs there are being done by black people just as if you come to this country most of the shitty jobs are being done by Eastern Europeans</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes it is still not equal by any means <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's like men and women it's not equal here</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0084">it's not equal anywhere really</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0041">that's her husband</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0041">and he's giving them information about her</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0084">he's such a massive knob</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0041">yeah you think he's being a knob but but he's actually doing it because then any information about her that's being made available to the Navy he knows about</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0041">so you hate him now</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1293" who="S0041">I'm sure he said um <pause dur="short"/> well maybe he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> think he said I thought he said that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was coming over last night but I think he I don't I think I got it wrong I think he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1294" who="S0084">aww</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1295" who="S0041">can't believe this and look it's got this cotton wool stuck to it now</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> D'you need to is there a button underneath it you need to press?</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0041">no it's there <pause dur="short"/> come and touch it</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0084">no I don't want that</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0041">you do</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0084">why's it pink? Was that the colour of the nail varnish</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1303" who="S0041">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1304" who="S0084">that's not gone well</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0041">oh I've got it off <pause dur="short"/> they're just chunks of plastic are coming off</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0084">God you forget how corrosive that stuff is</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0041">well it's just it was just a nail polish remover that smelt like bubblegum <pause dur="short"/> and I took my nail polish off really late at night and left it on there</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1309" who="S0041">and just like leant over and put it on there in the morning this had happened <pause dur="short"/> your glass</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0041">empty <pause dur="short"/> kitchen</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0084">lovely <pause dur="short"/> that's where it lives thank you <pause dur="short"/> awwmm I suppose it needs to be quite <trunc>st</trunc> uh strong to take the nail varnish off <pause dur="short"/> my mum always used to go spare when I was taking the nail varnish off and I'd like leave <trunc>thing</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> like on the sink or on the floor for people to tread on and she was like it's corrosive it's corrosive <pause dur="short"/> and I was like what do you think it's gonna do? It's not that acid</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0041">yeah till now</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but obviously obviously it's pretty bad</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0041">well it's kind of seeped into the plastic now <pause dur="short"/> and so even though I took it off here three days ago the plastic's it's changed the chemical composition of the plastic it's squidgy</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> rucch <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> hell</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> mm mm mm </u>
<u n="1319" who="S0041" trans="overlap">sick <pause dur="short"/> d'you think it might be near pie time?</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0084">I think it's definitely pie time now <pause dur="short"/> this was the windmill that we went to yesterday</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0041">aww <pause dur="short"/> how what the oh it's so pretty</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0084"> it's so pretty <pause dur="short"/> it's something</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's a really nice</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0084">at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> um oh that way windmill <pause dur="short"/> you can't go in the windmill though that's the thing</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0041">aww</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0084" trans="overlap">hawthorn <pause dur="short"/> that's just spring blossom around</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> springy</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0084">and that one</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0041">well it sounds like you had a really nice day</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0084">it's what I wanted for Easter <pause dur="short"/> didn't ever get it for Easter</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0041" trans="overlap">where it is <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1332" who="S0084">it is ten pounds though which is a bit excessive</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0041">well they didn't have it for very long cos I secretly went to try and get you one and they didn't have anywhere</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0084">awww that's very sweet <pause dur="short"/> oh I never wiped the gravy off this</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0041" trans="overlap">Ohh <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0084">mm I'll just save it for later <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it's probably machine washable isn't it? I'll <trunc>b</trunc> I'll bang it in the wash before I give it back to you</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> be fine <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0084">D'you think it is pie time?</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0041">maybe</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0084" trans="overlap">High time we had pie time</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0041" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> I'll wash the pots first</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0084">no I'll come and give you and hand <pause dur="short"/> let's pause this shabazz <pause dur="short"/> how do we make it stop? Ah I don't like it you know when they used to have the adverts for the marines and they used to have them coming out the water and you couldn't see them and then you could see them and it was really scary like something out of a horror movie <pause dur="short"/> I didn't like it his hair <pause dur="short"/> you remind me off it definitely smells of chicken</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0041">does it like?</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's how I like it</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Gonna walk in there all the time and wish that you had more chicken</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0084">gonna make you quite upset</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0041"><unclear/> light choices but I had a look on the packets and they were really quite well they are light choices</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0084">well stuff like that's really bad for you anyway <pause dur="short"/> you know even if it's low fat it's gonna be high in salt <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1351" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0084">you're better off doing what you're doing <pause dur="short"/> and making stuff from scratch then you know exactly what's in it <pause dur="short"/> in fact I might get a tuna steak out for dinner tomorrow with a guy</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1353" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Ow Monday tomorrow how did this happen?</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0084">oh god</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0041">forgot all about Monday</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1358" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1359" who="S0084">I've forgotten about Mondays</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0041">it's so unfair</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0084">I didn't recognize recognize my alarm when it went off on Tuesday morning though</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1363" who="S0084">didn't know what was going on <pause dur="short"/> I just feel I'm just very rested from my six days off <pause dur="short"/> it's very nice <pause dur="short"/> ah that reminds me I've got to put washing in <pause dur="short"/> and we have to make a soup at some point</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0041">ahh</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0084">should I try and find Talk To Her?</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> that's stewing</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0041">think we can enjoy the weekend a little bit more with some pie and <trunc>s</trunc> before we have to think about soup and</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0041">washing and all that type of stuff</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0084"><unclear/> first</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1372" who="S0084">and we have Talk To Her which is the one that didn't work from my boxset</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0084">the next film after those ones was Volver which came out a few years ago</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0041">ah I love that film</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0084">and the more <trunc>re</trunc> the more recent one the <unclear/> that weird one was Broken Embraces <pause dur="short"/> which was also Penelope Cruz</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0084">who apparently is</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0041">as what?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0084">it's um Almodvar's muse like his inspiration</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0041">Ohh</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0084">kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> which is nice</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0041">well I'll watch any <pause dur="short"/> any and all</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0084">all of those <pause dur="short"/> we could try Talk To Her cos I think that's <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit weird that one</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0041">okay <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't know why I think that in any way it would be weird considering</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1387" who="S0041">the others</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> yummo <pause dur="short"/> these were pretty bargainous weren't they a pound?</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0041">yeah they were bargainous</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0084">hope we don't get addicted <pause dur="short"/> and then it's not bargainous cos then it's a million million pounds</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0084">like they throw you to other good stuff</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0041">in our defence had we realized how good that was we would've more bought</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0084" trans="overlap">we would've bought twelve <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1395" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0084">we bought shares in the company</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Pretty yeah</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> thanks for doing the washing up mate <pause dur="short"/> appreciate it <pause dur="short"/> got cabbage everywhere</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> extra cabbage everywhere</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's what I like</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0041">cabbage in everything from now on</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0084">it was pretty tasty even though you know we cooked it to within an inch of its life</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's certainly not supposed to</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1405" who="S0041">supposed to be that mushy</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0084" trans="overlap">we just got just got a bit carried away with the chicken</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1408" who="S0084">you know?</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0041">got a bit distracted by the goodness of the chicken</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't paying attention</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0041">we never do when there's chicken involved</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0084">when it's smelling that good</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0041">oh maybe I don't want any of this water</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> chick chick chick chick chicken </u>
<u n="1415" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> how long do pies take? Are the pies done yet?</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0084">um soon <pause dur="short"/> I cleverly didn't look at the time when I put them in cos I like you know to risk these things</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> living on the edge</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> we can see</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0084">is it alive?</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0041">yeah you need to all get out of there</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1423" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0041">I uh my theory with the putting the <trunc>th</trunc> putting things down the <trunc>pl</trunc> hole the plughole is that if it fits it's going down</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1427" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1428" who="S0084">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> it's not</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0041" trans="overlap">then if it doesn't I've gotta fish it out</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0084">well I think if it were your house you might be more worried about these things but as it's Trude's</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0084">couldn't give too hoots <pause dur="short"/> going down there <pause dur="short"/> oil</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1434" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Petrol</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0084">petrol <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> all the booze <pause dur="short"/> lit matches you know?</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1437" who="S0084">just to see what would happen <pause dur="short"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1439" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't see what the problem is</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Like matches yeah <trunc>booh</trunc></u>
<u n="1441" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> on the petrol <pause dur="short"/> I mean to be honest the house has gotta be torn down</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1443" who="S0084">there's no saving this house</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0041">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1445" who="S0084">that little drip tray under there <pause dur="short"/> honestly everything is a bodge</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1447" who="S0084">I think you know we're taking our life in our hands every time we come through the front door</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Welcome <pause dur="short"/> we should make a sign for the front door saying Welcome to the crack den <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1449" who="S0084">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Enter at your own risk <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1450" who="S0041">anything health and safety please leave at the door</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0084">I'm wondering if she's the kind of landlord to be <trunc>rea</trunc> a real stickler about your deposit</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0041">yeah probably right</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos she can fuck right off if she thinks she's keeping any of our deposit</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah she can fuck right off <pause dur="short"/> cos that's why every time she comes I remind that even though she cleaned the carpet when I moved in it's marked to fuck</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0041">and that I have not done that</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0084">she well that's the thing when I moved in she'd only cleaned around the bed so there's loads of dirt where the bed <trunc>s</trunc> was that they hadn't cleaned</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/> Nice</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0084">Cos they didn't because that stupid filthy girl didn't move out on time <pause dur="short"/> that's not my problem <pause dur="short"/> she didn't paint the walls like she said she was going to</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I got a <trunc>cor</trunc> a little <trunc>cor</trunc> corner of my ceiling painted as opposed to</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1462" who="S0041">anything serious</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> no she can fuck off <pause dur="short"/> and that all the holes in the wall are holes that she has drilled <pause dur="short"/> so it's a no from me</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's a no from me</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0084">so that'd be nice three hundred pounds back in the kitty</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> so when when does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> find out if she gets it then?</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0084">I dunno it's <trunc>b</trunc> all these things just take time I don't think they even bother to give you a date <pause dur="short"/> obviously this course starts in September</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0041" trans="overlap">well that's</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0084">with my MA I applied I think in the December or the January when I first found out found about out about it but this course you could only apply from today</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0041">gonna love pie</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0084">pie's gonna be awesome <pause dur="short"/> pie and ice cream </u>
<u n="1472" who="S0041">actually ahh look it's got little stars on the top</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0084">yeah man <pause dur="short"/> just gonna let it melt a little bit before we do the scooping</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0084">I do have a scoop <pause dur="short"/> an actual scoop</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0041">I think if I just tip it upside down it'll pop right out <pause dur="short"/> just like that</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> on the pie</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0041">on the pie yep <pause dur="short"/> which which was I putting on?</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0084">umm Talk To Her</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0041" trans="overlap">the other one the other one Talk To Her <pause dur="short"/> this one</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> alright <pause dur="short"/> good stuff</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0041">oh we ate chicken in here</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1484" who="S0041">can't say that I minded though if I'm honest</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0084">aww it's delicious <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> hmm I might eat your ice cream while you're out the room</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0084">just <trunc>p</trunc> just warning you <pause dur="short"/> you think it's been twelve minutes?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0041">which one's yours?</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0084">uh left <pause dur="short"/> the other left</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0041" trans="overlap">this one? <vocal desc="laugh"/> You see the hesitation <pause dur="short"/> which one's left again?</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm just gonna serve these cos I can smell I can smell pie</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0041" trans="overlap">D'you remember <unclear/>? Yeah just do it</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0084">ah yeah thing about serving hot things in metal tins is it's hot</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0041">D'you want me to have a go? How you gonna get it out of the tin?</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0084">I'm gonna prise and try and prise</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0041" trans="overlap">with your fingers?</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there we go <pause dur="short"/> it's not too bad</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0041" trans="overlap">aww <pause dur="short"/> aww</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0084">it's not too bad <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0041">I'm quite I'm really quite excited now</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0084">at the imminent pie ice cream</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><event desc="sound of banging"/> Ahh</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0084">there you go my love</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0041">thanks mum</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0084">you are very welcome <pause dur="short"/> ohh the smell of pie</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0084">this needs to happen every day <pause dur="short"/> of my life</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0041" trans="overlap">with the pie would you like spoon or fork or both or?</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0084">oh I've got them here</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0041">ah yeah winner <pause dur="short"/> thanks <pause dur="short"/> thanks <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1511" who="S0084" trans="overlap">thank you <pause dur="short"/> and that's for you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1512" who="S0041">is the thingy working?</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0041">yep yep <pause dur="short"/> yep it's working</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1516" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> scrumptious</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1517" who="S0041">it's all working <pause dur="short"/> it's all working goodness</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeahh <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0084">Ohh yummy <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1521" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0084">wowsers</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you can't even wait</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0084">no time <pause dur="short"/> no time to wait</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0041">tastes really strange compared to the other one <pause dur="short"/> it's like Passo</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0084">yeah it is a bit weird isn't it? It's got sour cream in it</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I like it <pause dur="short"/> must have <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> all in my mouth</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0041">all the mouth <pause dur="short"/> all the mouthness</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0084">amazing <pause dur="short"/> amazeballs <pause dur="short"/> take this</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0041">thank you for the tea dear</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0084">you're welcome you're welcome</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0041">I've had everything I need</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0084">um all the things yeah</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0041">D'you need help with things?</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's become a bit serious <pause dur="short"/> hang on let me stop being silly <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0041">uh I think they're both doing it <pause dur="short"/> the other one's doing it now</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1541" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0084">I mean I don't think you can really ask those sorts of questions of his films</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I think you've just got to accept</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0084">the first one we watched Skin I Live In <pause dur="short"/> every scene we were like why? </u>
<u n="1545" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1546" who="S0084"> But why? But why? But why? But oh my god <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1547" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah I think we'll just have to learn to accept the wonder</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> or is this the one this isn't the one we already watched it is?</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0041">hang on <pause dur="short"/> I think I might've watched a little bit of it while I was trying to work my <trunc>rem</trunc></u>
<u n="1550" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1551" who="S0041">remote</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0084">what's the one we actually watched? All About My Mother?</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0084">no Bad Education <pause dur="short"/> that was the one we watched</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0041">yeah it was that one <pause dur="short"/> I liked that one</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1559" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1560" who="S0041">she seems like she's in pain</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0041">she's certainly not happy</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0084">hm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> modern theatre <pause dur="short"/> bit weird</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1564" who="S0041">although I do quite like it I mean in real life</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0041">think it's quite entertaining</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0084">some of it <pause dur="short"/> some of it's a bit too abstract <pause dur="short"/> mm if you can't understand why they're doing it</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I feel upset that I'm not gonna understand</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1570" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1571" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1572" who="S0084">spanish men just seem so effeminate don't they?</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0041">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1574" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0041">wow they didn't look like real boobs did they? See how much they weren't moving?</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0041">maybe they weren't real boobs</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1579" who="S0084">could you imagine anything worse?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1580" who="S0084"></u>
<u n="1581" who="S0041" trans="overlap">she must've been like that for some months</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but in that I thought they <trunc>w</trunc> that was when they were like we've got to turn the um life support machines off <pause dur="short"/> mm well how long do they keep someone alive in a coma?</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0041">I have no idea <pause dur="short"/> I really have no idea <pause dur="short"/> she's got clothes specially made</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1585" who="S0041">what a? Certainly not long enough for them to have clothes specially made</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well maybe it's different there <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's private <pause dur="short"/> like here the NHS would be like no that's very interesting <pause dur="short"/> been in a coma for two days <pause dur="short"/> can I <trunc>t</trunc> turn it off? </u>
<u n="1587" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Twenty minutes <pause dur="short"/> off</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0084">need the bed I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> she's in Volver isn't she it's one of the <trunc>sis</trunc> she's a sister?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1589" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1590" who="S0041">she didn't breathe though <pause dur="short"/> there was a pause then another pause <pause dur="short"/> Good evening Lydia <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1591" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1592" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1593" who="S0041">I just got chalk in my ice cream</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> you have some sort of like fudgy thing in there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1595" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1596" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1597" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1598" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Hilarious</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0041">um I don't think you're allowed to do that</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0084">just hang on to your um <vocal desc="laugh"/> your guests</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0041" trans="overlap">guests</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1602" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1603" who="S0041">this I find madness</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0041">have you seen how many people get squashed in the streets when they do the ball <trunc>th</trunc> running thing</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0041">every year someone gets killed and they still do it</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0084">yeah think they <trunc>th</trunc> they think it's tradition but it's barbaric</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1609" who="S0041">hasn't he been in one as well?</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0084">one that we've seen?</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> he uses the same people</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1613" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0084" trans="overlap">hmm</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0041">is that bull bleeding?</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0084">yeah they kill the bull</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0041"> What? Why?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1618" who="S0041">why? Why do they do that?</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0084">if you're the bull</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0041">I did not know that</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0084">I thought they'd made it illegal <pause dur="short"/> maybe not <pause dur="short"/> cos they were there was a massive outcry cos they said it's out tradition it's our tradition But it's horrible</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0041">I never realized they killed the bull</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1624" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> well that really hit the spot</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0041">mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> sweet goodness</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0084">ohhh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1627" who="S0084">oh I wish I could just speak another language without you know like having to study</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0041">that'd be great</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0084">that'd be awesome <pause dur="short"/> aww</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1630" who="S0084">who's in the bottom of my <unclear/> slippers <pause dur="short"/> this is what you get when you buy things for a pound from Primark</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><event desc="sound of makes animal"/> wah poor bah lamb</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0041">poor thing</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0084">oh excuse me</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1635" who="S0041">why do they call him that?</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0084">does it mean the boy </u>
<u n="1637" who="S0041">yeah the the no the son of</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0041">well it means the boy of but the way she's saying it's like</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it means it means  the son of okay</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0084">and what about if it's il like I L Niño cos you know like that some things are called Il Niño <pause dur="short"/> does that mean the as opposed to</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0084"> of </u>
<u n="1645" who="S0041">El El Niño or is the masculine Il Niño <pause dur="short"/> don't know <pause dur="short"/> Il 's um Italian</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0084">italian <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1647" who="S0041">it's not niño <pause dur="short"/> so I can't understand where il and niño together would be <pause dur="short"/> where did you read it?</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0084">um it's something to do with like a weather front <pause dur="short"/> or something I don't really understand <pause dur="short"/> it's like a a thing to do with global warming or something <pause dur="short"/> I don't really understand it</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0084">but there's also a a band and I can understand why you know if you're a <trunc>ba</trunc> if you had a name for a band it might not be correct <pause dur="short"/> but the this weather front's called Il Niño</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0041">oh well I know now</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0084">what's he doing?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1653" who="S0084">squidging something</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1654" who="S0084">can't see</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0041">I can't see Flo</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1657" who="S0041">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1658" who="S0084"><vocal desc="sigh"/> papapapapapa </u>
<u n="1659" who="S0041">getting a bit impatient I want to know what he's doing</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0084">yeah what is he doing?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1661" who="S0084">think he killed something <pause dur="short"/> think something small is in our <trunc>b</trunc> in the bin <pause dur="short"/> and why would she scream? I mean if that'd been you and you'd seen a spider you'd've screamed like that</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0084">so it could be something she's scared of</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0041">skunk</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0084">skunk</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1667" who="S0084">weasel <pause dur="short"/> badger</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> badger was my next</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0084">badger you'd be in big trouble if there was a badger in your house <pause dur="short"/> they're pretty vicious</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0041">are they?</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0084">really vicious</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0084" trans="overlap">they're pretty big as well they're bigger than you think</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0041">how big's a badger?</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0084"><trunc>W</trunc> this big</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0041">off the floor?</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're big</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0041">you mean like as big as a dog?</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0084">like yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> some of them <pause dur="short"/> not all of them some of them are pretty big</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I thought a badger was like this</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> if you if the badger feels threatened you are fucked <pause dur="short"/> cos it will come at you and it will start biting you <pause dur="short"/> it will attack you <pause dur="short"/> it will attack a human</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0041" trans="overlap">holy shite</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0084">but you never really see them cos they're very um private animals <pause dur="short"/> have you never read The Wind In The Willows? Badger lives in the deep dark woods</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1684" who="S0041">oh snake it was a snake <pause dur="short"/> it was a snake they killed before</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0084">okay fair enough</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0041">I'm feeling pretty sick now</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my head hurts <vocal desc="laugh"/> from all the goodness <pause dur="short"/> so is she now in a hotel cos she'd scared that there's a snake?</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0041">I really don't <trunc>kn</trunc> I don't really know why she's in the hotel <pause dur="short"/> maybe she already always intended to go there but she had to go to collect her bag or something</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1689" who="S0084">that's a horrible alarm</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would break it</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0084"><trunc>K</trunc> throw it out of the window <pause dur="short"/> do you hear my alarm in the morning?</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0084">keep meaning to ask you this <pause dur="short"/> cos when I when it goes off it's really loud and I keep turning it down but then it's still quite loud <pause dur="short"/> but I need it to be loud to get me up</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0084">but it doesn't wake you up? Okay good</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0041">D'you ever hear mine?</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0084">no but I'm always up before you</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> just wondered cos I I snooze it but it goes up every five minutes</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0084">Ohh</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0041">I like it that way cos if I've only got half an hour to get ready then I'd <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1701" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah mine snoozes for ten minutes <pause dur="short"/> but I so I set it for six <pause dur="short"/> and then if if I know I've got things to do I could get up at ten past six <pause dur="short"/> but if I push it I get up at twenty past six</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0041">yeah no I never hear it</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0084" trans="overlap">leave at seven</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1704" who="S0084">they're allowing him to cut her hair?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1705" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1706" who="S0041">they speak really fast</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1708" who="S0041">like she even made a mistake then cos she was speaking so fast</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0041">like I don't know if all Spanish films are spoken so quickly <pause dur="short"/> but Spanish people don't speak that fast</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0084">really <pause dur="short"/> I to me I I not speaking Spanish it sounds <trunc>de</trunc> it all sounds fast</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0041">she speaks normally <pause dur="short"/> anna speaks normally <pause dur="short"/> doesn't</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0084">D'you think it's the difference between city folk and rural folk</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0041" trans="overlap">might be <pause dur="short"/> or maybe it's because of whereabouts they're from cos I can't really tell the accents apart</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0041">well I can but I don't couldn't tell you where they're from</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1717" who="S0084">oh what?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1718" who="S0041">oh god <pause dur="short"/> oh god the smell of this is making me feel sick</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0084">you haven't <trunc>d</trunc> have you not finished it?</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0041">yeah I've finished it</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0084">oh good <pause dur="short"/> good good good</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0041">oh just the smell of it the smell of all the goodness</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1724" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1725" who="S0084">I wish somebody would come and make my soup for me</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0041">that would be nice <pause dur="short"/> I really don't feel the inclination to make soup</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1727" who="S0041">do you really understand what's going on the whole film right now?</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0084"><trunc>N</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No I don't know if this is the past or this is the <trunc>f</trunc> present <pause dur="short"/> basically we've just found out that they were a couple</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0041">oh them two together were a couple?</u>
<event desc="sound of film stops"/>
<u n="1730" who="S0041">I didn't do it</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What did you do?</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0041">I didn't <unclear/> The remote's over here</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0084">aww</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0041">umm</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0084">make it work <pause dur="short"/> d'you think we've had a power cut? No cos your thing flashed up with DVD</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1737" who="S0084">and delete</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1739" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Try and turn that light on</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1741" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1742" who="S0041">um <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't really know what just happened</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0084">and rest</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1745" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1746" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1747" who="S0084">your TV is like arson <pause dur="short"/> mode</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0041"><trunc>D'y</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> d'you know? I think it's I think it's got a mind of its own <pause dur="short"/> like did I tell you the other day just I was just watching something <pause dur="short"/> and I was like stood over doing something and it just turned itself on to DVD <vocal desc="laugh"/> and started playing funny Pride And Prejudice</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1750" who="S0041">and I was like this is</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1752" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1753" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1754" who="S0041">just did it</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0084">it's so weird</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0041">I think I uh need to take it back to the shop</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1758" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Say fucking got a mind of its own</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's alive</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0041">I think it's alive</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0084">that's pretty hilarious</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0041">I have got the warranty and everything for it <pause dur="short"/> so I really should do this now while it's still in the warranty</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0041">although <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's never done this to me before so that's a new one</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's just turned itself <vocal desc="laugh"/> off <pause dur="short"/> did you have to turn it back on?</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0041">uhh</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0084">how did you fix it?</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0041">what when it went off when it?</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0084">just now</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0041">oh no I pressed it on <pause dur="short"/> it didn't do it itself</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0084">excuse me <pause dur="short"/> no on</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0041">english <pause dur="short"/> next</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1773" who="S0041">is this where we were? <trunc>A</trunc> we've not seen this bit</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0084">oh yeah we have</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this'll do won't it? So</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0041">they were a couple together</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0084">yeah they were a couple <pause dur="short"/> and he was saying he was single in the <trunc>ca</trunc> when they get in the car <pause dur="short"/> then he was used to sleeping on the sofa when they broke up</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0041">ahh <pause dur="short"/> I thought when he broke up with someone else <pause dur="short"/> fucking move <pause dur="short"/> yeah when we broke up fine</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1780" who="S0084">it's really annoying it stays there for ages</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0041"> Come on <pause dur="short"/> mooove <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>S</trunc> </u>
<u n="1782" who="S0084">several months later <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0041">there we go</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0084">so this is the present okay</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0041">or maybe just the closer past</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0084">uh <trunc>u</trunc> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1787" who="S0041">so they're together now are they? Again?</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0084">they're uhh presumably <pause dur="short"/> is he El Niño?</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0041">I didn't think he was <pause dur="short"/> I thought the other guy was <pause dur="short"/> so he must be</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0084">oh the guy was in a stand and they said the will ravage her <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> dunno <pause dur="short"/> he's a different ex</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1791" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1792" who="S0041">she did not say holy shit </u>
<u n="1793" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1794" who="S0041">she said the C word</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0084">huh <pause dur="short"/> foxy</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1796" who="S0041">did she use to be a ballet dancer? Did I read that in the back of the DVD?</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0084">what this one? Oh I dunno</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0041">maybe I got confused <pause dur="short"/> I think she's well protected if she gets stabbed by the bull</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1800" who="S0084">could they sew you in</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0041">no that's just to pull the buttons through the hooks <pause dur="short"/> it's a button puller</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0084">Ohh <pause dur="short"/> smarts</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0041">kinda want one of them outfits</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1805" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Just to parade around in</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0084">fine <pause dur="short"/> I kinda want the pink tights</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0041">yeah I liked them</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0084">they're pretty awesome</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0041">shit <pause dur="short"/> why are all? Why are there loads of them?</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0084">uh is it a competition maybe? Dunno</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0041">where's my tea where's my tea?</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0084">careful under your foot <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1813" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1814" who="S0041">hm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1815" who="S0084">God <trunc>w</trunc> would you though?</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0041">no</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1817" who="S0041">not fond of <unclear/></u>
<u n="1818" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1819" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Shit why would you do that?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1820" who="S0041">it's just gonna spear her in two</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1821" who="S0041">what happened?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1822" who="S0084">I thought it was red rag to a bull so why are these in pink?</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0041" trans="overlap">pink <pause dur="short"/> dunno <pause dur="short"/> and how did she manage to get speared?</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0084">well she was she had to kneel down I dunno why she was the one who had to be kneeling <pause dur="short"/> she I guess it's like a <trunc>t</trunc> like a sign of respect you have to kneel to the book <pause dur="short"/> and why she had to do it when there's a load of them in the ring maybe they take it in turns <pause dur="short"/> I dunno who this one is</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0041">no</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1826" who="S0041">maybe she's the one that's in the coma</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1828" who="S0084">oh she's the sister</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1829" who="S0084">yeah I think you're right I think she's the one in the coma</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0041">yeah that'll help <pause dur="short"/> keep lighting candles</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1831" who="S0041"></u>
<u n="1832" who="S0084">hm?</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0041">lot <unclear/> Talk To Her</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0084">meaning?</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0041">well they might be he not</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0041">it's a bit too much mess I reckon <pause dur="short"/> dunno what the other reason is</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0084">mm because nurses are bastards</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0041">yes that's probably</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0084">they only take that job to torture people</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1842" who="S0041"><unclear/> still in there?</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0084">yeah I think so</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1844" who="S0041">why would you call someone Boy Valencia though?</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0084">maybe that's just his stage name</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0041">oh really <pause dur="short"/> he's got a hot back whoever he is</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> he looks like a frog</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0041">his face looks a bit like a frog</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0084">unfortunate</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1850" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1851" who="S0041">D'you find it strange how other cultures think their music sounds good and we don't?</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0084">D'you not like any world music?</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0041">yeah I like it but I I it shocks me how the taste's so different like if somebody</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0041">even in English started singing like this</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0041">english people are like what's he wailing at? </u>
<u n="1858" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0041">D'you see? D'you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I can that yeah yeah absolutely but I suppose you can appreciate whether you like that something's good and you can like it but yeah obviously everyone's cultures are gonna be different</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0041">mm like the way he sings the manner in which he sings</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0084">Cos there's like the way that they play guitar is known as Spanish guitar isn't it?</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0084">the way that they pluck at the strings rather than strum like it's a very Spanish way of playing <pause dur="short"/> but they think it sounds good and you can think it sounds good but yeah it is different</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0041">I suppose it's like the fashion is what I mean more like</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0041">it's not fashionable in England to sing that way</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0084">yeah you wouldn't have someone in the charts singing like that</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0084">but I think people</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0041" trans="overlap">in their charts they do</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0084">they do yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think there's <trunc>pro</trunc> there's quite a bit market for world music here so I think people do like it</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0041">for what?</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0084">there's a big um there's a lot of uh interest in world music here</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0084">people really like it <pause dur="short"/> I suppose the more you travel the more you hear music from other countries</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> apparently there's Italian music on my iPod actually cos I would just put it on the random songs and just press skip I was like ooh ooh forgot about you </u>
<u n="1878" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1879" who="S0084">and of course you've got like Eurotrash stuff as well haven't you which is pretty bad</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1881" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1882" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1883" who="S0084">bet you do</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0041">yeah I do yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got loads of it</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0084">that's why you're not in charge us of the music <pause dur="short"/> ever</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0041">ever <pause dur="short"/> I'm not in charge of the music ever cos I have a horrendous taste in music</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1888" who="S0041">I openly admit it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1889" who="S0041">I think when Hilary Duff came up on my uh</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0084">ah man alive</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0041">iPod was a tell-tale sign</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0084" trans="overlap">who was that? Hannah Montana?</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0041">kind of but before her</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0041">she was Lizzy McGuire</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0084">Lizzy McGuire yeah</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1898" who="S0084">see where are they now cos she's supposed to be in a coma?</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1900" who="S0084">huhh <pause dur="short"/> just staring at naked women?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1901" who="S0084">hm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1902" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1903" who="S0041">can you run in a coma?</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0084">I've no idea</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1905" who="S0084">so you can have no eyes when you're in a coma?</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can be in a waking coma can't you? My dad was in one for like three three four weeks</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0084">Jesus Christ</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0041">you wouldn't know <pause dur="short"/> we didn't know <pause dur="short"/> well we did <pause dur="short"/> cos they told us but otherwise you wouldn't know <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't remember anything</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0084">so he was waking up? But he wasn't really?</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0041" trans="overlap">he was awake <pause dur="short"/> he was awake for <pause dur="short"/> he didn't sleep for three weeks</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0041">he didn't sleep for three weeks</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0084">he didn't sleep?</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0041">he wouldn't sleep <pause dur="short"/> they kept giving him shitloads of medication and he wouldn't go to sleep</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0084">so they call that a coma?</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0041">it's a waking coma so</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0084">Ohh</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0041">he was talking to people wandering round and interacting <pause dur="short"/> but he won't remember any of it because apparently it's all subconscious your body you you as you know you now is kinda shut off</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0084" trans="overlap">is asleep <pause dur="short"/> how do they know that?</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos your body goes to <trunc>sl</trunc> if your body goes through <trunc>trau</trunc> trauma your body shuts down to protect itself</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> but how do they know that you're in a coma if you appear to be normal? They ask you like test questions something?</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you don't know what what day it is stuff</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0041">who's the Prime Minister and all that shite and because he wasn't sleeping I think that's one of the things if you don't if you're not sleeping then they know that your body is basically although you're moving</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0041">your body on the inside is trying to sleep</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0084">oh my gawd <pause dur="short"/> god the brain is mad isn't it?</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hence why he was singing the American <vocal desc="laugh"/> that he made up in an American accent</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0084">ohhhh bless</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0041" trans="overlap">of <trunc>wh</trunc> he asked me I got it went to hospital one day and it was my fault cos he wouldn't eat anything either <pause dur="short"/> so I was sneaking him Kentucky Fried Chicken you know the <trunc>p</trunc> the popcorn balls?</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0084">ahh right</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0041">so on the way home</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1934" who="S0041">I'd get Mars bars and Kentucky Fried Chicken popcorn balls and sneak them in before my mum got there</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0041">cos I knew he'd eat it <pause dur="short"/> and I kept saying to him don't tell her will you <pause dur="short"/> don't tell her <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1937" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0041">he was like no no no </u>
<u n="1939" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1940" who="S0041" trans="overlap"> Want some chicken? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1941" who="S0084">awww</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0041">and he used to reply like that no no no we won't tell her <pause dur="short"/> No no no <pause dur="short"/>  You just keep eating <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1943" who="S0084" trans="overlap">aww <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> aww</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0041">and then she'd come in <pause dur="short"/> Are you hungry?  No no no no <pause dur="short"/> And I'm thinking shit he's gonna say it</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No no <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1946" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> a nurse said to me so whereabouts in America is your dad from? </u>
<u n="1947" who="S0084"><trunc>N</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1948" who="S0041">I said what? He was singing down the down the thing Kentucky Fried Chicken </u>
<u n="1949" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1950" who="S0041"> Alabama Chicken Chicken Pie <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1951" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1952" who="S0041">just stupid shit</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0084">oh bless</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1955" who="S0041">it's called <unclear/> Forgot that word</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1956" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Thought it was her dad</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1957" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1958" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> ah no <pause dur="short"/> belly's angry</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0084">bellyyy <pause dur="short"/> what's going on with your rumbly tummy?</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0041">oh it's making noise <pause dur="short"/> it's angry <pause dur="short"/> it's angry that I fed it</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1962" who="S0041">agua</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1963" who="S0041">he didn't say</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1964" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1965" who="S0041">oww</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Aww you getting pains?</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0041">yeah it's alright I think it's just meat pains <pause dur="short"/> I think it'll go</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0084" trans="overlap">definitely meat pains <pause dur="short"/> umm d'you mind chucking me a pillow love?</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0084">as we <unclear/> so nicely earlier <pause dur="short"/> cos I do wanna just rest my head while I have a little lie down <pause dur="short"/> perfect thank you</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0041">and this one</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0084">oh no I'm alright actually <pause dur="short"/> or if you're sure <pause dur="short"/> if you're sure <pause dur="short"/> thanks thanks <pause dur="short"/> oo <pause dur="short"/> oo <pause dur="short"/> umm <pause dur="short"/> ah magnifique</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1973" who="S0084">hmm hmm hm</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0041">I like to feed this one</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0084">do you?</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0084">huh <pause dur="short"/> hola <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d'y</trunc> is he in love with the girl who's in the coma?</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0041">Don't know</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1978" who="S0041">that doesn't really look like the woman that's</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0084">no this is a different woman <pause dur="short"/> this is the woman you know when he saw her just now and he was looking at the woman who had bare boobs?</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0084">that was her</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0041">oh so it wasn't the same woman</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0084" trans="overlap">there's two <trunc>wom</trunc> it's <pause dur="short"/> there's two women</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0041">ohhh</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0084">so when he was on the balcony just now he was on the balcony of the girl he loves the bullfighter's room</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0084">and then this I imagine she had an accident when she was dancing <pause dur="short"/> don't know if that's her</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the other guy that's not El Niño is basically just making friends with her because he's stuck at hospital all the time</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0084">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> maybe he thinks she had nice boobs</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0041">probs</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0084">I know he's some sort of <trunc>wr</trunc> writer-journalist isn't he so maybe he thinks there's a story there <pause dur="short"/> cos he that's how he met the bullfighter cos he wanted to write a story about her</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1992" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1993" who="S0041">well</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0084">yeah he was in the in the because that was when he saw the bullfighter that was when they met in the <trunc>th</trunc> they were all there watching the ballet <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>th</trunc> and Benigno was there as well cos then Benigno went away and told Alicia oh I went to see this amazing ballet like the women throw themselves around <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="1995" who="S0041" trans="overlap">ohhh <pause dur="short"/> and he was already there</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0084">he was there <pause dur="short"/> and Mistress Whatsherface she was there</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0041">mistress Whatsherface <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1998" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0041">yeah that's her name</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0084">that's definitely her name <pause dur="short"/> um but who was the one was it that when that black and white scene was happening that's when I woke up <trunc>i</trunc> was that Benigno raping her?</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0041">I think it must've been</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0084">going into her va-jay-jay</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0041">yeah but even I thought that's what in hindsight that's what it must've meant <pause dur="short"/> however</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2005" who="S0041">when the black and white thing finished</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0084">mm?</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0041">he was fully clothed massaging her</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0084">and that was when her dad came in? Well that was earlier</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0041">her dad didn't come in <pause dur="short"/> no he just they just chatted and then that was it</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0084" trans="overlap">hmm</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0041">like it's not like when the black and white thing finished he was naked</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0084" trans="overlap">huhh <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> but he must've done cos she was pregnant</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0084">presumably</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> must've done</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0084">no he never actually said I raped her </u>
<u n="2017" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0084">but presumably he did <pause dur="short"/> I suppose in his head it wasn't rape because it was some great love affair and she was in love with him because he was crackers</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> of course <pause dur="short"/> that's yeah that's exactly what happened <pause dur="short"/> it's made my head mash a bit <pause dur="short"/> I think that crossed with that</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0084" trans="overlap">all the food <pause dur="short"/> the food coma</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0041">the food coma</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0084">I uh I had to rest my eyes for a little bit there I couldn't keep them open</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Need to put that washing in</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0084">oh I know</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0041" trans="overlap">but I don't seem to be moving</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0084">D'you know what that means?</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0084">I have to make bloody soup</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0041">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="2030" who="S0084">I don't even know what I've got to make soup with <pause dur="short"/> that's interesting</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0041">that's fun</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0084">that's that's my favourite</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0041">I don't wanna make soup <pause dur="short"/> but I know tomorrow I'm gonna want soup for lunch</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0084">living on a budget</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0041">gonna cook it <pause dur="short"/> all the soupy goodness</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2036" who="S0041">I do need all the soupy soupy goodness <pause dur="short"/> and that means that I'm only having the calories from one meal a day <pause dur="short"/> doesn't it cos I don't count the soup as having anything in it that would be two chopped tomatoes and onions that counts as zero</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Does it?</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0041">anything that I eat that's got just vegetables or just fruit counts as zero</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0041">so the soup's only got chopped tomatoes and onion in</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0041">so that counts as zero</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0084">more like five it's</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0041">and</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0084">it's nought but okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2046" who="S0041" trans="overlap">the apple <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And the apple that I eat counts as zero</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0084">but if you were doing Weight Watchers that would count</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0041">uh yes <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0084">doesn't it count?</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0041">I can't remember if it's Weight Watchers or the other one where all you can eat as much fruit and veg as you like <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <trunc>r</trunc></u>
<u n="2051" who="S0084"><foreign lang="fre">Null points</foreign></u>
<u n="2052" who="S0041" trans="overlap">in real life it has got <foreign lang="fre">points</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> but the yoghurt I eat in the morning</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0084"><foreign lang="fre">Null points</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> ohhh <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> this hurted my pretty face</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2055" who="S0084">my pretty face</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0041">I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="2059" who="S0084">thing is with these Spanish films they make my brain ache <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="2060" who="S0041" trans="overlap">how many calories is in a tin of chopped tomatoes? Cos my tin of chopped tomatoes lasts me a week</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0084">three</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0041">but three whole calories</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> They're really good for you</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2065" who="S0084">yours has got chilli in them though hasn't it?</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0041">no I've last one did but that that wasn't the way forward</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2068" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2069" who="S0084">that was when you blew your head off</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I <trunc>d</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> uh yeah</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2072" who="S0041">that was when I was <trunc>bl</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was when I was blowing my head off chilli soup for lunch</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2074" who="S0041">and then had chilli chilli con carne for tea <pause dur="short"/> so <vocal desc="laugh"/> by the time <vocal desc="laugh"/> by the time I'd eaten tea</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2076" who="S0041">I'd actually <trunc>bl</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd actually burnt my face off</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2078" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2079" who="S0084">um sounds very therapeutic actually</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes it was</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0084" trans="overlap">people would pay good money for that you know?</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and not not just fucked up <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2083" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The chilli technique <pause dur="short"/> the chilli regime</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think it's called the chilli diet</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2086" who="S0041" trans="overlap">people like when you come in it'll be like everybody in the room here's a chilli diet <pause dur="short"/> ohh</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0084">Ohh if not you're onto a ground breaking new plan</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah yeah yep</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0084">where you just sweat out all the calories</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><trunc>U</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2091" who="S0084">and remove a layer of skin from your face</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0041" trans="overlap">just burn it off <pause dur="short"/> yep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2093" who="S0084">Ohh</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0041">burning calories in a whole new dimension <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> right I'll go and fill the kettle up full of soup</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0041">awww</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0084">we'll do it really quickly</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0041">awww <pause dur="short"/> I didn't cook anything at all <pause dur="short"/> I just threw it all in there</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0084">you just threw everything in?</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0041">all together</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0084">it's just you're like the best cooker in the world</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2103" who="S0084">you're so good</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0084">you don't even need to cook it</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's just magic</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0041">it's just magic</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0084">wowww</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0041">it's yeah it just</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0084"><unclear/> your skills?</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0041">I <trunc>kn</trunc> I know I don't I'm just I'm just that good</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0084">you're just unreal <pause dur="short"/> don't think I've got more garlic <pause dur="short"/> have you got garlic?</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0041">yeah loads of garlic</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0084">loads of garlic <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> thanks chicken</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0041">I did however forget tomato puree but I think uh I don't think I'm really gonna notice</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I keep meaning to buy some <pause dur="short"/> gonna use the whole chilli <unclear/> I made that disgusting soup a few weeks ago <vocal desc="laugh"/> Have to try and make it a bit more bearable <pause dur="short"/> ahh <pause dur="short"/> baked beans</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0084">something died? Yeah don't show me <pause dur="short"/> is there gremlins in there? <vocal desc="laugh"/> This happened</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2121" who="S0084">by magic <pause dur="short"/> what is that doing in there?</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0041">it was in the bad and I didn't know it was in the bag and I just <unclear/></u>
<u n="2123" who="S0084">you're such a numpty Gromit</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0041">aww</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0084">how do these things happen to you hey?</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0041">I don't know I mean people do say to keep nail polish in the fridge to stop it from going off <pause dur="short"/> like going gloopy</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0084" trans="overlap">going off</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0041">I don't think you're supposed to leave it right at the back where it freezes</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0084">probs not</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0084">Cos that's when it gets a bit unhappy</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0041">oh crap</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2135" who="S0084">D'you know what you haven't made in a while? Now that I've got the lentils out? Daal</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0041">correctomundo</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0084">maybe you uh overdid it a bit with the daal</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0041">D'you have to close that again? No I do I do quite like the daal but um I didn't want to put lentils in because then it'll add more calories to it <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0041">and work seems to be the only place where I can control what I eat</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2142" who="S0041">otherwise I just eat everything in the fridge</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that smells pretty strong <pause dur="short"/> that nail varnish</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0041">I thought you meant my soup <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say yeah so?</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2146" who="S0041">it's perfectly cooked why wouldn't it smell lovely?</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2148" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2149" who="S0084">have you even put the heat under it?</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> it's on heat some heat now <pause dur="short"/> looks lovely</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0084">it's it's winning <pause dur="short"/> winning</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2153" who="S0084">this is how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does cooking</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0041"><trunc>D</trunc> no this is how the world should be cooking <pause dur="short"/> the proper way</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0084">think you're on your own there my friend</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0041">think we're meant to put some thickener in hey? How many calories are in you? Ah well I'm just gonna put a tablespoon of this in</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0084">did you put oil in?</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0041">none of that</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0084">none of that hanging around for frying</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0041">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> we didn't fry anything so I figured it became quite redundant</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2164" who="S0041">rather redundant <pause dur="short"/> so yeah just threw it all in put the lid on and then</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0084">took a step back</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0084">surveyed the masterpiece</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2169" who="S0041">I mean nobody knows how it's gonna go of course</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0084">think we might do <pause dur="short"/> think we might know</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0041">well I don't know cos if I can eat this one this'll be a hat trick</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="2173" who="S0041">three edible soups in a row</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0041">if that's not tempting fate I don't know what is</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0084"> ahhhh <pause dur="short"/> they're gone</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2177" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2178" who="S0084">heaven's <unclear/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="2179" who="S0041">fire in the hull</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0041">there you go <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="2182" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/> That's my favourite colour of soup</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You mean lumps of white floating in red?</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0041">fine <pause dur="short"/> when it gets blended it'll all go together</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0084">that's like that coconut juice that we saw in Stowbridge bits of death floating in it</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yess <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah it looks like that <pause dur="short"/> yum</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2189" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2190" who="S0084">well at least you're the only one eating it</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0041">that's true <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2192" who="S0084">so</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0041">at least I'm not trying to force it upon anybody else</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0084">to be fair it is only vegetables <pause dur="short"/> know what I mean? Vegetables and herbs so how badly wrong can it go? Sss</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0041">uhh</u>
<u n="2196" who="S0084">famous last words and all that <pause dur="short"/> it's usually when you try and put vegetables in it that don't belong?</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0084" trans="overlap">like I tried to put baby sweetcorn in the soup and it went mental</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> I remember that <pause dur="short"/> I did that too</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0041">I had baby sweetcorns and mange tout <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2202" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And it tasted like the Earth</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0041">it tasted like the Earth yes I do yeah nice</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0084">so note to self don't do that <pause dur="short"/> I've got some mushrooms that are rotting in the fridge so that'll be tomorrow's dinner <pause dur="short"/> rotten mushrooms</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2206" who="S0084">Cos I like those</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0041">that's my favourite type of mushrooms</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0084">only if they're rotten</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0041">only if they're rotten <pause dur="short"/> otherwise it's just not cricket</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0084">exactomundo</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0041">think that's all the things I can chuck in</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0084">it's all you need</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be great</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0084">feeling pretty confident for your soup?</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think it's think it's good <pause dur="short"/> it's all good</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0084">alll clever</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0041">it's all goodness</u>
<u n="2218" who="S0084">mm you</u>
<u n="2219" who="S0041">I see no problem at all <pause dur="short"/> on the last one I made I must've reeked of garlic cos I think I must've put about three teaspoons of that in it</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh well it's very good for you <pause dur="short"/> anti-ageing</u>
<u n="2221" who="S0041">anti-ageing</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I think <pause dur="short"/> that's what they say</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0041" trans="overlap">apart from that I didn't put oil in it now maybe I should have to break some of my bad fats down</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> olive oil is very good for you</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0041">in fact I can put this one can't I that's for dressings cos I'm not cooking with it it's just going in the soup</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0084">I think you're right mate I mean I didn't understand that because it does taste weird if you cook with it</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0041">does it?</u>
<u n="2228" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well comparatively <pause dur="short"/> you know you can really taste it <trunc>i</trunc> in the cooking</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0084">A lot of people usually put it on dressing as a dressing</u>
<u n="2231" who="S0041" trans="overlap">D'you think I can taste it in my soup?</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0084">you'll be able to taste it yeah</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0041">think I quite like it though</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0084">that's alright then</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0041">Don't know</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0084">I mean it's good for you it is it is olive oil so it's a good fat <pause dur="short"/> my dad has it on salads <pause dur="short"/> I don't even like it <pause dur="short"/> but it's très Mediterranean silly</u>
<u n="2237" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2238" who="S0084">weevils</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0041">weevils? Any weevils?</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0084">mm sadly no <pause dur="short"/> I need some</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0041">must try harder</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0084">need some protein</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0041">must try harder to grow the weevils because of the <unclear/> that one requires <unclear/> weevils</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0084">onions <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> on the way</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2245" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2246" who="S0084">the wrinkles?</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0084">I don't believe you've got wrinkles</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2250" who="S0084">noo</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0041">permanent as well</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0084">I can't see any</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0041">on my head</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0084">it is all in your head</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0041">no I've seen them no there's loads of them I just need botox to stop them</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0084">naa</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2257" who="S0041">when you relax your face any wrinkles you can see are permanent</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0084">when you relax your face okay</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0041">I can see loads</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0084">it's usually best not to look at them <pause dur="short"/> you'll only get depressed</u>
<u n="2261" who="S0041">it's the head ones that are worse I don't mind the eye ones so much it's the head ones <pause dur="short"/> only the head ones</u>
<u n="2262" who="S0084">show <pause dur="short"/> where? Aww I can barely see them</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0041">I know but they'll get worse</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0084">mm just means that you've had a lifetime of laughter or something like that</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0041">what I need to do is inject them so that</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0084">inject them</u>
<u n="2267" who="S0041">they don't get worse</u>
<u n="2268" who="S0084">with acid</u>
<u n="2269" who="S0041">with acid</u>
<u n="2270" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2271" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="2272" who="S0084" trans="overlap">sensible <pause dur="short"/> funny girl</u>
<u n="2273" who="S0041">yeah I think I need to inject them with acid</u>
<u n="2274" who="S0084">we're all mad <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what we do need?</u>
<u n="2275" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="2276" who="S0084">wine</u>
<u n="2277" who="S0041">end of wine</u>
<u n="2278" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2279" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Wine in the soup</u>
<u n="2280" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2281" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wine in everything</u>
<u n="2282" who="S0084" trans="overlap">wine <pause dur="short"/> just <trunc>wi</trunc> just wine but yeah wine in the soup <pause dur="short"/> where is the wine?</u>
<u n="2283" who="S0041">all the wine in the world ever</u>
<u n="2284" who="S0084">all of it <pause dur="short"/> dunno why we don't have the wine <pause dur="short"/> that was bad planning</u>
<u n="2285" who="S0041">I don't know why there's empty bottles of wine in here</u>
<u n="2286" who="S0084">what? That's just that's just taking the piss</u>
<u n="2287" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> there's an empty bottle of Chardonnay that's been in here for ages</u>
<u n="2288" who="S0084">ahhh <pause dur="short"/> they're having a giraffe</u>
<u n="2289" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="2290" who="S0084">there's something wrong in the head with them</u>
<u n="2291" who="S0041">I have an empty bottle in the back of my room that's good cos I can't remember the name of some of the wines</u>
<u n="2292" who="S0084">of what of wines?</u>
<u n="2293" who="S0041">yes and I wanted that one again</u>
<u n="2294" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> it's amazing</u>
<u n="2295" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I've really upset the balance of the world with my stomach round about now <pause dur="short"/> it's causing me pain</u>
<u n="2296" who="S0084">that's bad <pause dur="short"/> ummm water <pause dur="short"/> bet you haven't had much water today</u>
<u n="2297" who="S0041">no quite</u>
<u n="2298" who="S0084">haven't seen you drink any water <pause dur="short"/> cos it flushes the <trunc>oes</trunc> your kidneys out</u>
<u n="2299" who="S0041" trans="overlap">more <pause dur="short"/> more water <pause dur="short"/> more water please</u>
<u n="2300" who="S0084">do it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2301" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2302" who="S0084">funny girl</u>
<u n="2303" who="S0041">D'you know what I think you need?</u>
<u n="2304" who="S0084">uhh <pause dur="short"/> ponies?</u>
<u n="2305" who="S0041">no one of those chillies in your mouth <pause dur="short"/> home grown</u>
<u n="2306" who="S0084">the green chillies?</u>
<u n="2307" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yep</u>
<u n="2308" who="S0084">I mean that would be pretty funny</u>
<u n="2309" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2310" who="S0084">for you</u>
<u n="2311" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="2312" who="S0084">not so much for me <pause dur="short"/> poor little chilli plant I was gonna re-pot it this weekend <pause dur="short"/> that hasn't that hasn't happened</u>
<u n="2313" who="S0041">look at that bad boy there look at this</u>
<u n="2314" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this one</u>
<u n="2315" who="S0041">three years</u>
<u n="2316" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="2317" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/> Come on fatty</u>
<u n="2318" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="2319" who="S0041">perfect <pause dur="short"/> can't believe it's living</u>
<u n="2320" who="S0084">I dunno what it what it needs cos the leaves look really unhappy <pause dur="short"/> I think it might need re-potting cos the stem is really chunky now <pause dur="short"/> like when I got it that was as thick as like was like that</u>
<u n="2321" who="S0041">oh was it? Oh</u>
<u n="2322" who="S0084" trans="overlap">quite small yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's quite quite epic now <pause dur="short"/> so I might do that tomorrow when I get home from whatever I'm doing tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> whatever that is</u>
<u n="2323" who="S0041">the soup's cooked now forever</u>
<u n="2324" who="S0084">ah it's ready okay I'm ready go</u>
<u n="2325" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> That's ready now</u>
<u n="2326" who="S0084">ah go on then enjoy</u>
<u n="2327" who="S0041">umm no I've I'm full</u>
<u n="2328" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2329" who="S0041">I'm full from all the dinners so</u>
<u n="2330" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Okay <pause dur="short"/> we have had many dinners</u>
<u n="2331" who="S0041">so I would love to whilst I would love to um unfortunately it's gonna have to be a no from me</u>
<u n="2332" who="S0084">well that's a bit bloody convenient isn't it?</u>
<u n="2333" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2334" who="S0084">isn't that just a bit bloody convenient? Lentil on the floor</u>
<u n="2335" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2336" who="S0084">fine</u>
<u n="2337" who="S0041">favourite</u>
<u n="2338" who="S0084">ice cream</u>
<u n="2339" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2340" who="S0084">from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2341" who="S0041">favourite</u>
<u n="2342" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2343" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah my stomach</u>
<u n="2344" who="S0084">ah is it really that bad?</u>
<u n="2345" who="S0041">yeah it's gurgling <pause dur="short"/> it's gurgling</u>
<u n="2346" who="S0084">ah shit man <pause dur="short"/> sounds a bit serious</u>
<u n="2347" who="S0041">like holy fuckers what have you been eating that's what he's saying to me</u>
<u n="2348" who="S0084">all the food</u>
<u n="2349" who="S0041">well <pause dur="short"/> I think he should just shut up and give be grateful to be perfectly honest</u>
<u n="2350" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean you starve it all week</u>
<u n="2351" who="S0041">you'd think</u>
<u n="2352" who="S0084">and now you'd think it'd be very happy with you <pause dur="short"/> and tomorrow it'd be sad again cos tomorrow there's no food on the agenda</u>
<u n="2353" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> none of that</u>
<u n="2354" who="S0084">none of the actual food <pause dur="short"/> not during the week</u>
<u n="2355" who="S0041">I'm afraid not</u>
<u n="2356" who="S0084">alright here we go <pause dur="short"/> just cook <pause dur="short"/> ooh <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't me that was this</u>
<u n="2357" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That sounds healthy</u>
<u n="2358" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="2359" who="S0041">not like it's about to explode at all</u>
<u n="2360" who="S0084">nooo <pause dur="short"/> no driver <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="2361" who="S0041">so what's the difference between what's in a passata and what's in <trunc>chop</trunc> chopped tomatoes</u>
<u n="2362" who="S0084">there's a <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> it's um just the tomatoes so they've I think what they do is they cook the tomatoes they take them out of the skin and then they bottle them</u>
<u n="2363" who="S0041">ahh</u>
<u n="2364" who="S0084">so there's no skins on the <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> sieved tomatoes <pause dur="short"/> sieved</u>
<u n="2365" who="S0041">ahh</u>
<u n="2366" who="S0084" trans="overlap">so you don't have all the shite in it <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't like all the bits</u>
<u n="2367" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh I like the bits</u>
<u n="2368" who="S0084">noooo <pause dur="short"/> I know everybody else does but I don't really like it</u>
<u n="2369" who="S0041">you you don't love the bits?</u>
<u n="2370" who="S0084">Don't really like the bits</u>
<u n="2371" who="S0041">Ohh</u>
<u n="2372" who="S0084">is it that bad?</u>
<u n="2373" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2374" who="S0084">have a little lie down which obviously is what we've been doing all afternoon but more of a lie down</u>
<u n="2375" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2376" who="S0084">another lie down</u>
<u n="2377" who="S0041">it'll it will go <pause dur="short"/> it will go</u>
<u n="2378" who="S0084">it will go <pause dur="short"/> we need more pie</u>
<u n="2379" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> we ate all the pies</u>
<u n="2380" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="2381" who="S0041">which I feel is the only way that anyone can live</u>
<u n="2382" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2383" who="S0041">eating all the pies</u>
<u n="2384" who="S0084">you do have to eat <pause dur="short"/> and if you're gonna eat you might as well eat pie</u>
<u n="2385" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why not?</u>
<u n="2386" who="S0084">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm I don't wanna go to work tomorrow</u>
<u n="2387" who="S0041">mm mm</u>
<u n="2388" who="S0084">big scary meeting is fast approaching <pause dur="short"/> the</u>
<u n="2389" who="S0041">scary meeting?</u>
<u n="2390" who="S0084">yeah the one that I have to chair <pause dur="short"/> it's like a supplier feedback thing <pause dur="short"/> one of our suppliers is coming in and I have to as the name would suggest feed back <pause dur="short"/> oh it's gonna be horrible</u>
<u n="2391" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="2392" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> wanna <pause dur="short"/> and my boss</u>
<u n="2393" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that does not sound like fun</u>
<u n="2394" who="S0084">it's not a fun time <pause dur="short"/> my boss is gonna call in from New York and then her boss our Operations Manager wanted to get in on the act <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> Just not just not looking forward to it <pause dur="short"/> but I've put together like some talking points as opposed to like an agenda cos it's a review of the project <pause dur="short"/> sort of gone through and looked at where we went over budget and whether schedules are on time and any major issues and just noted them all down and sent them out to everybody just put Sarah to discuss  Jo to discuss  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to discuss <pause dur="short"/> and then at least everyone's kind of got an idea of what's gonna be talked about</u>
<u n="2395" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2396" who="S0084">I think in actual fact it'll be harder reining them in than it would be to get them to talk <pause dur="short"/> so think it's more it's just the idea of it <pause dur="short"/> don't really want to sit</u>
<event desc="sound of barking"/>
<u n="2397" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2398" who="S0084">just sit there <pause dur="short"/> that's just the puddle <pause dur="short"/> that's just</u>
<u n="2399" who="S0041">okay</u>
<u n="2400" who="S0084">where the puddles go</u>
<u n="2401" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2402" who="S0084">that's just fine</u>
<u n="2403" who="S0041">that's just where the puddle lives</u>
<u n="2404" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2405" who="S0041">that's where all the puddles live</u>
<u n="2406" who="S0084">that's what I do with this house</u>
<u n="2407" who="S0041">just where all the puddles live we don't mind <pause dur="short"/> we like puddles</u>
<u n="2408" who="S0084">I'd prefer them to live there <pause dur="short"/> if anywhere <pause dur="short"/> really <pause dur="short"/> d'you think there's a movie on now?</u>
<u n="2409" who="S0041">maybe I'll have a look <pause dur="short"/> I'm starting to like be concerned about what this is made with?</u>
<u n="2410" who="S0084">what d'you think you might be allergic? To something in there?</u>
<u n="2411" who="S0041">no it's just skimmed milk <pause dur="short"/> this is how I usually feel if I have milk</u>
<u n="2412" who="S0084">Ohh but it <trunc>w</trunc> skimmed milk obviously I mean <trunc>u</trunc> it's still two percent milk</u>
<u n="2413" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I have have skimmed milk don't I?</u>
<u n="2414" who="S0084">oh is that what you I thought you had UHT?</u>
<u n="2415" who="S0041">oh is that different?</u>
<u n="2416" who="S0084">UHT isn't real milk</u>
<u n="2417" who="S0041">Ohh</u>
<u n="2418" who="S0084">UHT is fake milk <pause dur="short"/> well I mean it's milk but they they they pasteurize it or something <pause dur="short"/> heat treated yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they do something to it</u>
<u n="2419" who="S0041">oh I see</u>
<u n="2420" who="S0084">whereas actual milk is <trunc>m</trunc> is milk from a cow untreated</u>
<u n="2421" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2422" who="S0084">so that might be where we're going wrong</u>
<u n="2423" who="S0041">maybe</u>
<u n="2424" who="S0084">so your body's not used to processing the the dairy?</u>
<u n="2425" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="2426" who="S0084">ahh</u>
<u n="2427" who="S0041">maybe that's it <pause dur="short"/> just don't know</u>
<u n="2428" who="S0084">but then would it've been? That would've been the case in the froyo last week?</u>
<u n="2429" who="S0041" trans="overlap">in the froyo yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2430" who="S0084">I would've thought but I don't know</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2431" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> Hello <pause dur="short"/> I'm Devilmoo <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="2432" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2433" who="S0041"> I'm addicted to chocolate and love base jumping <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="2434" who="S0084">obviously</u>
<u n="2435" who="S0041">base <pause dur="short"/> jumping</u>
<u n="2436" who="S0084">that's where they jump from building to building isn't it?</u>
<u n="2437" who="S0041">I thought that was parkour</u>
<u n="2438" who="S0084">no that's what <unclear/></u>
<u n="2439" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="2440" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2441" who="S0041">holy shit <pause dur="short"/> that's normal</u>
<u n="2442" who="S0084">what for cows?</u>
<u n="2443" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="2444" who="S0084">no it's not really normal for humans <pause dur="short"/> let alone Ermintrude</u>
<u n="2445" who="S0041">he was high as a kite all the time <pause dur="short"/> yeah you're certainly edible</u>
<u n="2446" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2447" who="S0041">I think</u>
<u n="2448" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="2449" who="S0041">yours alright?</u>
<u n="2450" who="S0084">quite herby isn't it?</u>
<u n="2451" who="S0041">herby?</u>
<u n="2452" who="S0084">herb</u>
<u n="2453" who="S0041">it needs a blending</u>
<u n="2454" who="S0084">D'you want the blender?</u>
<u n="2455" who="S0041">oh yeah I'll do it now while I'm stood actually</u>
<u n="2456" who="S0084" trans="overlap">the really nice quiet blender we have</u>
<u n="2457" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that would be better</u>
<u n="2458" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2459" who="S0041">come here</u>
<u n="2460" who="S0084">what is occurring?</u>
<u n="2461" who="S0041">is that does that the fridge talking again?</u>
<u n="2462" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know when it sounded like it was gonna explode a few weeks ago d'you remember?</u>
<u n="2463" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2464" who="S0084">that was a bit of a scary time</u>
<u n="2465" who="S0041">let's leave the kitchen</u>
<u n="2466" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> everybody back</u>
<u n="2467" who="S0041">I'm quite</u>
<u n="2468" who="S0084">ahh <pause dur="short"/> you still doing your milkshakes?</u>
<u n="2469" who="S0041">um they're good for before I go running</u>
<u n="2470" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="2471" who="S0041">the best thing is to live at work <pause dur="short"/> like they have just left it here for ages but it needs to live there cos I steel their skimmed milk and I have a under my desk</u>
<u n="2472" who="S0084">oh nice <pause dur="short"/> I see that now</u>
<u n="2473" who="S0041" trans="overlap">sometimes I still have this <pause dur="short"/> I'll have this</u>
<u n="2474" who="S0084">aha <pause dur="short"/> but never both?</u>
<u n="2475" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<event desc="sound of blender"/>
<u n="2476" who="S0041">the problem with this I've realized is that it's so liquidy that the <trunc>bul</trunc> the stuff escapes</u>
<u n="2477" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2478" who="S0041">from the blender <pause dur="short"/> and I see it whooshing round and I'm thinking get through the blender </u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2479" who="S0041">Cos it's got so noisy I just stopped <trunc>si</trunc> doing this</u>
<u n="2480" who="S0084">stopped blending</u>
<u n="2481" who="S0041">but then I found chunks of tomato</u>
<u n="2482" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that'll happen <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think the blender is just shite <pause dur="short"/> it is only from Wilkos <pause dur="short"/> and I kept finding large bits of carrot in my carrot and coriander soup this week</u>
<u n="2483" who="S0041">D'you know what I think? I think it's because we're not patient enough to wait for it to blend</u>
<u n="2484" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> and I wasn't cutting up the carrots particularly small either <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> to be fair</u>
<u n="2485" who="S0041">something yeah</u>
<u n="2486" who="S0084">it was making a quite difficult job for it <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Yummy yummy yummy <pause dur="short"/> very funny <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> with him?</u>
<u n="2487" who="S0041">um he text me to ask how uh last weekend was <pause dur="short"/> when I saw my dad</u>
<u n="2488" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2489" who="S0041">very nice blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> how's your mum? Yeah lovely <pause dur="short"/> granny was really impressed with her little egg cosy</u>
<u n="2490" who="S0084"><event desc="sound of making high pitched"/> ooh </u>
<u n="2491" who="S0041">and I was like yeah wonderful blah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="2492" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> blah</u>
<u n="2493" who="S0041">you up to anything nice this weekend? Oh no he asked me if we'd had a bet on the Grand National</u>
<u n="2494" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="2495" who="S0041">at work and I said actually no we didn't <pause dur="short"/> was that your stomach</u>
<u n="2496" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's having issues <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2497" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="2498" who="S0084">I wonder if we poisoned ourselves</u>
<u n="2499" who="S0041" trans="overlap">probably isn't <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was just thinking that <pause dur="short"/> anyway uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> back at the farm</u>
<u n="2500" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2501" who="S0041">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> so he says um my horse um fell over </u>
<u n="2502" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2503" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Balls <pause dur="short"/> actually did you ever see Steve in the Grand National <pause dur="short"/> what he did <pause dur="short"/> Dot my horse fell over dot balls </u>
<u n="2504" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2505" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2506" who="S0084">my horse fell over</u>
<u n="2507" who="S0041">I <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="2508" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I jumped apparently so cos when I was going on the <trunc>be</trunc> the website to bet it said how many of them will finish and I thought surely they all finish but no loads of them don't finish apparently <pause dur="short"/> cos it's really hard <pause dur="short"/> really hard course</u>
<u n="2509" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> turns out</u>
<u n="2510" who="S0084">so <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sss</trunc></u>
<u n="2511" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Gutted</u>
<u n="2512" who="S0084">sucks to be him</u>
<u n="2513" who="S0041">sucks to be you <pause dur="short"/> um yeah and I was like no I didn't hahahahaha <vocal desc="laugh"/> as if your horse decked it</u>
<u n="2514" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2515" who="S0041">um it what you doing is what you I said what you I hope you're doing you doing anything fun this weekend?  Oh I'm in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing?  Oh well thinking about going to <anon type="place"/> um in the sunshine obviously before it rained <pause dur="short"/> um have a nice hope you both have a nice weekend </u>
<u n="2516" who="S0084">very grown-up</u>
<u n="2517" who="S0041">and he said oh that that sounds lovely that should be nice <pause dur="short"/> Thanks <pause dur="short"/>  You too <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="2518" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well at least he didn't go on and say yeah we're gonna do this we're gonna do that </u>
<u n="2519" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="2520" who="S0084">so he's learned</u>
<u n="2521" who="S0041">yes that that was good <pause dur="short"/> I did prepare myself that that could be the reply</u>
<u n="2522" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> We're gonna be holding hands in the sunshine <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="2523" who="S0041">euuch</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2524" who="S0041">am I allowed to put this in here even if it's hot?</u>
<u n="2525" who="S0084">it's um uh yeah</u>
<u n="2526" who="S0041">what is that?</u>
<u n="2527" who="S0084">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I mean some might say I put it in there</u>
<u n="2528" who="S0041" trans="overlap">uh-oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> tomato</u>
<u n="2529" who="S0084">oh that's fine you can just eat that when you it'll just be a bit of bit of flavour</u>
<u n="2530" who="S0041" trans="overlap">must be a surprise</u>
<u n="2531" who="S0084">surprise <pause dur="short"/> bit of texture</u>
<u n="2532" who="S0041">think it's just one rogue</u>
<u n="2533" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2534" who="S0041">one rogue piece of tomato <pause dur="short"/> so whichever <trunc>w</trunc> whenever I get that that's the lucky bowl</u>
<u n="2535" who="S0084">that's the winner <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="2536" who="S0041" trans="overlap">this soup is um looking rather watery</u>
<u n="2537" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> you'll have to just <trunc>pu</trunc> poor it in a cup or something rather than drink it with a spoon</u>
<u n="2538" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a Cup-A-Soup</u>
<u n="2539" who="S0084">might need to make some moor during the week</u>
<u n="2540" who="S0041">oh no as long as it fills this it'll it'll eat</u>
<u n="2541" who="S0084">it'll be alright</u>
<u n="2542" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah there's loads here</u>
<u n="2543" who="S0084">oh okay then <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="2544" who="S0041">I don't haven't really considered about how I'm gonna get this container to work</u>
<u n="2545" who="S0084">um in your bag</u>
<u n="2546" who="S0041">oh yeah I mean</u>
<u n="2547" who="S0084">if you put it flat at the bottom of your sports bag</u>
<u n="2548" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2549" who="S0084">and then load it into the top</u>
<u n="2550" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and in a few carrier bags</u>
<u n="2551" who="S0084">and a few carrier bags just in case what does it leek that one?</u>
<u n="2552" who="S0041"><trunc>N</trunc> well I haven't tried this one before with the runny soup</u>
<u n="2553" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="2554" who="S0041">the last one was the other one that I lent from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and believe me that'll eat</u>
<u n="2555" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah but he gets his all of his from Chinese shops</u>
<u n="2556" who="S0041">right that's the <unclear/></u>
<u n="2557" who="S0084" trans="overlap">done in the microwave</u>
<u n="2558" who="S0041">no this is the one with the blue thing came out</u>
<u n="2559" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2560" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2561" who="S0084">that's pretty hilarious</u>
<u n="2562" who="S0041">so maybe I want to try just a little bit of you</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2563" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2564" who="S0084">go go <pause dur="short"/> go go</u>
<u n="2565" who="S0041">go go <pause dur="short"/> thinking about using the one of these <unclear/> I think the start of any problem</u>
<u n="2566" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> did you not put any stock in?</u>
<u n="2567" who="S0041">yeah I put one chicken and one vegetable but I think I need more</u>
<u n="2568" who="S0084">yeah I definitely find that the the bouillon or whatever it's called lasts the like it really you really notice the flavour more than</u>
<u n="2569" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2570" who="S0084">when you use Oxo cos I think last week I only used one cube and it was um did add much more flavour to it</u>
<u n="2571" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2572" who="S0084">although loads of calories in there</u>
<u n="2573" who="S0041">is there?</u>
<u n="2574" who="S0084">two hundred and forty-three per hundred grams</u>
<u n="2575" who="S0041">think like you'd have to eat the whole thing wouldn't you? To eat a hundred grams</u>
<u n="2576" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Uh</u>
<u n="2577" who="S0041">I think one's enough</u>
<u n="2578" who="S0084">A hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="2579" who="S0041">there you go</u>
<u n="2580" who="S0084">okay so the whole thing <pause dur="short"/> where what's that? Half again of two hundred and fifty <pause dur="short"/> hundred and twenty-five</u>
<u n="2581" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2582" who="S0084">so three hundred and seventy odd</u>
<u n="2583" who="S0041">so per spoonful</u>
<u n="2584" who="S0084">twelve</u>
<u n="2585" who="S0041">there's probably about yeah I was gonna say about about ten</u>
<u n="2586" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2587" who="S0041">did it actually say twelve</u>
<u n="2588" who="S0084">it said twelve <pause dur="short"/> per serving of five grams which is what a teaspoon?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2589" who="S0084">A natural enhancer of all soups stews casseroles sauces savories rice and grain dishes <pause dur="short"/> and a delicious hot drink <pause dur="short"/> instantly soluble in hot water</u>
<u n="2590" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's quite full of itself isn't it?</u>
<u n="2591" who="S0084">as stock four teaspoons per litre <pause dur="short"/> yeah probably need to put some more in actually</u>
<u n="2592" who="S0041" trans="overlap">wondering how it says like for all stews I'm sure if I was making like crab stew that would</u>
<u n="2593" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2594" who="S0041">go with it</u>
<u n="2595" who="S0084">oh I put it everything <pause dur="short"/> I put it in pasta when I'm cooking pasta</u>
<u n="2596" who="S0041">do you?</u>
<u n="2597" who="S0084">tastes nice</u>
<u n="2598" who="S0041">do you?</u>
<u n="2599" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I put it in rice and make the rice quite sticky</u>
<u n="2600" who="S0041">think I need some white pepper in</u>
<u n="2601" who="S0084">yeah help yourself <pause dur="short"/> on the bar there <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="2602" who="S0041">I have some in here</u>
<u n="2603" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="2604" who="S0041">there it is look <pause dur="short"/> um then you know just like that <pause dur="short"/> that helps <pause dur="short"/> and then I think that's finished <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2605" who="S0084">that's the fastest soup making in the west</u>
<u n="2606" who="S0041">well when you're as good a cook as I am</u>
<u n="2607" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's kinda just comes so naturally to you</u>
<u n="2608" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="2609" who="S0084">just don't know how you do it</u>
<u n="2610" who="S0041">years of practice</u>
<u n="2611" who="S0084">that'll be it <pause dur="short"/> shitting hell I think I've got some sort of spasm</u>
<u n="2612" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2613" who="S0084">I mean I really do <pause dur="short"/> think there's something wrong with me <pause dur="short"/> given me some sort of some sort of twitch</u>
<u n="2614" who="S0041" trans="overlap">alright <pause dur="short"/> oh that's okay</u>
<u n="2615" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> happy with that?</u>
<u n="2616" who="S0041">third edible soup in a row</u>
<u n="2617" who="S0084">oh my god she's only done it again</u>
<u n="2618" who="S0041" trans="overlap">now put a bit of <pause dur="short"/> well I haven't got any Lee And Perrins left</u>
<u n="2619" who="S0084">oh I've <pause dur="short"/> no I've only got soy sauce</u>
<u n="2620" who="S0041">oh can I put soy sauce in? It's the salt I like of the soy sauce</u>
<u n="2621" who="S0084">the <trunc>sal</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> the salt?</u>
<u n="2622" who="S0041">yeah the salty taste</u>
<u n="2623" who="S0084">ah fucking hell every time</u>
<u n="2624" who="S0041" trans="overlap">did you? What was it called? Grot?</u>
<u n="2625" who="S0084" trans="overlap">garotte <pause dur="short"/> to garotte yourself</u>
<u n="2626" who="S0041" trans="overlap">just tried to garotte yourself? Are you okay?</u>
<u n="2627" who="S0084" trans="overlap">aww yeah <pause dur="short"/> just being a knob</u>
<u n="2628" who="S0041">Garotted</u>
<u n="2629" who="S0084">how is it seven o'clock already?</u>
<u n="2630" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="2631" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="2632" who="S0041">take it back</u>
<u n="2633" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="2634" who="S0041">take it back</u>
<u n="2635" who="S0084">um I'm not Superman I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> I can <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="2636" who="S0041"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="2637" who="S0084">should have a shower actually</u>
<u n="2638" who="S0041">right that means you're cooked <pause dur="short"/> now</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2639" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2640" who="S0041">you're cooked <pause dur="short"/> with made with love</u>
<u n="2641" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2642" who="S0041">all the love</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2643" who="S0041">I'm always terrified when I clean this that I'm gonna cut my own fingers off</u>
<u n="2644" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Please be careful with your fingers <pause dur="short"/> just leave that there in readiness <pause dur="short"/> mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> alright <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <unclear/> shoot myself</u>
<u n="2645" who="S0041">I need to do nothing <pause dur="short"/> that's what I need to do</u>
<u n="2646" who="S0084"><vocal desc="sigh"/> That sounds like a brilliant idea</u>
<u n="2647" who="S0041">nothing</u>
<u n="2648" who="S0084">well at this point you have to make a decision whether to <unclear/> pyjamas or have a shower and just can't be arsed <pause dur="short"/> need to take a shower <pause dur="short"/> I have the will to cook a shower</u>
<u n="2649" who="S0041">did you try the pomegranate stuff yet?</u>
<u n="2650" who="S0084">the who?</u>
<u n="2651" who="S0041">the pomegranate stuff</u>
<u n="2652" who="S0084">pomegranate stuff</u>
<u n="2653" who="S0041">the <trunc>s</trunc> shower stuff that I have</u>
<u n="2654" who="S0084">oh yeah I did try it the other day <pause dur="short"/> it was really nice</u>
<u n="2655" who="S0041" trans="overlap">smells good doesn't it?</u>
<u n="2656" who="S0084">yeah really really nice <pause dur="short"/> cos it's quite um a gentle smell</u>
<u n="2657" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2658" who="S0084">like it's not overpowering <pause dur="short"/> no it's really nice</u>
<u n="2659" who="S0041">Hahaha <pause dur="short"/> cold <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> warm</u>
<u n="2660" who="S0084">did you just fill that whole thing up with boiling water?</u>
<u n="2661" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2662" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="2663" who="S0041">when you say it like that it sounds crazy <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2664" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well heaven forbid you do something that's crazy <pause dur="short"/> crazy <pause dur="short"/> put you there <pause dur="short"/> cook my pretties cook <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="2665" who="S0041" trans="overlap">what's going in the soup today?</u>
<u n="2666" who="S0084">um today um <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> um</u>
<u n="2667" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="2668" who="S0084">we have um some tomatoes <pause dur="short"/> well we started off by frying an onion</u>
<u n="2669" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="2670" who="S0084">we added garlic</u>
<u n="2671" who="S0041">what you mean you actually fried it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="2672" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I fried yeah I mean I know it's not it's a pretty <trunc>sh</trunc> traditional way of cooking <pause dur="short"/> it's quite old fashioned <pause dur="short"/> it's not very new vogue <pause dur="short"/> which is not really in keeping with the cooking regime in the Union</u>
<u n="2673" who="S0041">in the Union</u>
<u n="2674" who="S0084">um but I did <pause dur="short"/> fried in olive oil <pause dur="short"/> added garlic <pause dur="short"/> already prepared <pause dur="short"/> umm</u>
<u n="2675" who="S0041">by your fair hand from scratch with a garlic <unclear/></u>
<u n="2676" who="S0084" trans="overlap">by my fair hand <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="2677" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2678" who="S0084">wouldn't have it any other way <pause dur="short"/> that I've been storing in my lader</u>
<u n="2679" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2680" who="S0084">um I did red lentils stock hot water passata salt black pepper and</u>
<u n="2681" who="S0041">goodness</u>
<u n="2682" who="S0084">and your aunt</u>
<u n="2683" who="S0041">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="2684" who="S0084">and your <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2685" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> perfect</u>
<u n="2686" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ready</u>
<u n="2687" who="S0041">done</u>
<u n="2688" who="S0084">not done <pause dur="short"/> bloody lentils take about a million years</u>
<u n="2689" who="S0041">because you're supposed to boil it with the lentils</u>
<u n="2690" who="S0084">yeah I did at the beginning but then I <trunc>w</trunc> was getting really carried away</u>
<u n="2691" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2692" who="S0084">I was really really getting ferocious <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>boi</trunc> boiled it when I first put them in but I didn't wanna carry on boiling them cos it was getting a bit full-on</u>
<u n="2693" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well just leave it <pause dur="short"/> just leave it on low it'll do</u>
<u n="2694" who="S0084"><unclear/> at the bottom</u>
<u n="2695" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2696" who="S0084">if I leave it on that</u>
<u n="2697" who="S0041">oh yeah you don't wanna do what I did to my soup that time and burnt it <trunc>s</trunc> it was foul</u>
<u n="2698" who="S0084"><trunc>Exa</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> this is my problem</u>
<u n="2699" who="S0041">that was extreme</u>
<u n="2700" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what I'll do <pause dur="short"/> that was cancer <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2701" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was cancer <pause dur="short"/> if I'd ever seen it in my life</u>
<u n="2702" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I did the I did the same though <pause dur="short"/> I then wondered why my soup tasted of burning</u>
<u n="2703" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Why does my soup taste of burning?</u>
<u n="2704" who="S0084">and then when I got to the bottom of the pan I realized it was because it was black</u>
<u n="2705" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2706" who="S0084">so that went really well I really enjoyed that soup that cancer that I was cooking <unclear/></u>
<u n="2707" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think everybody needs a good bout</u>
<u n="2708" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2709" who="S0041" trans="overlap">try one <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> try and build up your immunity and all that</u>
<u n="2710" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah it's like inoculations you know?</u>
<u n="2711" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's fine</u>
<u n="2712" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I think <trunc>do</trunc> doctors have started prescribing it to be honest</u>
<u n="2713" who="S0041">yes I think so <pause dur="short"/> and <vocal desc="laugh"/> and side portion of ham</u>
<u n="2714" who="S0084" trans="overlap">cancer sausages <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ham and cancer sausages</u>
<u n="2715" who="S0041">ham and cancer sausages yeah</u>
<u n="2716" who="S0084">you haven't got any cancer sausages left have you? <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2717" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No no none of those left now</u>
<u n="2718" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Good <pause dur="short"/> god now I've <trunc>f</trunc> I've eaten all my cancer sausages <vocal desc="laugh"/> Obviously <pause dur="short"/> keep up</u>
<u n="2719" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2720" who="S0084">I've eaten all the cancer <pause dur="short"/> that's that's some <unclear/> I wouldn't that around <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2721" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2722" who="S0084">obviously <pause dur="short"/> it's the first thing to go</u>
<u n="2723" who="S0041" trans="overlap">with all the good stuff <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2724" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2725" who="S0041">can't leave those beauties lying around for someone</u>
<u n="2726" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> not for anyone any old bloody tea leaf to handle for their own</u>
<u n="2727" who="S0041" trans="overlap">Tom Dick or Harry</u>
<u n="2728" who="S0084">no Absolutely <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>wi</trunc> wise words <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wise words</u>
<u n="2729" who="S0041"><unclear/> buggers</u>
<u n="2730" who="S0084">I'm going to</u>
<u n="2731" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2732" who="S0084">have a very quick shower and then come and check on this</u>
<u n="2733" who="S0041">that sounds wise</u>
<u n="2734" who="S0084">you may see if there's a good family movie</u>
<u n="2735" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll see what I can find on there</u>
<u n="2736" who="S0084">if not you're gonna have to enact something for me for my own entertainment</u>
<u n="2737" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2738" who="S0084">A play</u>
<u n="2739" who="S0041" trans="overlap">well I think it's going going to include gurgly tummy and cancer sausages</u>
<u n="2740" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Write the theme tune <pause dur="short"/> sing the theme tune</u>
<u n="2741" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2742" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2743" who="S0041">I'll get on that</u>
<u n="2744" who="S0084">if you could <pause dur="short"/> that would greatly amuse me <pause dur="short"/> right where is everything I own <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> Shit it's freezing in here <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
</body>
</text>
