<text id="S7KK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:27:49</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0266 S0270 S0271</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Planning trip to Nepal; travelling: previous trips and experiences, including trips when much younger; sausages, coffee; the Village Shop; Farm Shop; offering (or not) advice for a new born baby; job as school display co-ordinator; new free school meals system + lunch box content; food, menu, allergies and gluten free diets; husband's work in the home including cooking; war time food/diet; mother-in-law's war time journey from Siberia to Africa; relationships and jobs; sport: Tour of Britain bike race passing through local area, Iron Man and speaker's daughter's training/ achievements in this.</topics>
		<activity>Friends discussing Travelling, local rural shops, food and gluten free diets, war time diets and travels, sport (Tour of Britain and Iron Man)</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0266">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Almondsbury, Gloucestershire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0270">
				<exactage>66</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Berkeley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Gloucestershire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>35</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0271">
				<exactage>68</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>High Wycombe</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Buckinghamshire/Devon</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Northnibley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>school administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0266">so when are you <pause dur="short"/> going to Nepal?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0270">in November <pause dur="short"/> my last two weeks in November</u>
<u n="3" who="S0271" trans="overlap">is it booked?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0270">no but that's the plan and we have got places <pause dur="short"/> on a</u>
<u n="5" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0270" trans="overlap">erm organised</u>
<u n="7" who="S0266" trans="overlap">who's who's we?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0270">oh well it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I don't know who else might want to come <pause dur="short"/> she wants to leave it loose and be brave and organise it when we get there and erm I don't <pause dur="short"/> and erm looking out the erm looking on websites for flights <pause dur="short"/> you can't get a we haven't been able to find a flight for less than nine hundred pounds so</u>
<u n="9" who="S0266" trans="overlap">are you gonna fly straight there?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0270">well that was the hope I mean this was</u>
<u n="11" who="S0271" trans="overlap">can't you</u>
<u n="12" who="S0266" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0270" trans="overlap">no this was</u>
<u n="14" who="S0271" trans="overlap">can't you just</u>
<u n="15" who="S0270" trans="overlap">Mumbai via Mumbai</u>
<u n="16" who="S0271" trans="overlap">can't you fly to well Delhi and then get a</u>
<u n="17" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0271" trans="overlap">internal flight?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0270">yes well that's what</u>
<u n="21" who="S0266" trans="overlap">no go overland it's so nice it's so</u>
<u n="22" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah? what</u>
<u n="23" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0270" trans="overlap">train?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0266">no er on erm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0270">bus?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0266">yeah buses it's very exciting</u>
<u n="28" who="S0270">mm I could do that <pause dur="short"/> I'm happy with that <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0266">but if you fly in and you fly out it's such a culture shock when you arrive and <pause dur="short"/> surely?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0270">well yes that's true</u>
<u n="31" who="S0266">well er you're not going trekking are you?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0270">we are going to be walking but we're going to be doing</u>
<u n="33" who="S0266" trans="overlap">are you gonna climb Mount Everest?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0270" trans="overlap">on a no absolutely not I've looked at it</u>
<u n="35" who="S0266">have you got Sherpas?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0270" trans="overlap">and it's extremely challenging <vocal desc="laugh"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't really want to do anything <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I said well we won't see anything if you don't walk so erm I want to go on this organised trek which is easy to moderate and is you know whereas you look at some of the others and they might say <vocal desc="gasp"/> eighteen miles or eighteen kilometres I should say erm and things like that so I think <pause dur="short"/> the one I'm looking at is definitely geared at for people who are erm less fit</u>
<u n="37" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0270">which is good but looking on erm looking on the website initially at this holiday it looked as if it was rather expensive but now that we can only find a flight for only find a flight for nine hundred <pause dur="short"/> pounds and it doesn't mean seven hundred pounds</u>
<u n="39" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I'm sure you can flights to Delhi and Mumbai for four or five hundred pounds can't you?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0270">well if we looked just at those</u>
<u n="42" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0270">it would probably be cheaper than looking at Kathmandu</u>
<u n="44" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0270">I mean you have you been? because you've been to India</u>
<u n="46" who="S0271">no I've just been to Delhi and Rajasthan <pause dur="short"/> but we got internal flights when we were there</u>
<u n="47" who="S0270">yeah?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0270">and when did you go <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0266">mm oh I went as a youngster</u>
<u n="51" who="S0270">oh was this when you were doing your greyhound and before you got to Greece or after?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0266">mm <pause dur="short"/> the middle of sort of travelling yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0270">cos I haven't done any of it you see and I'm very conscious of that that I may not <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but I think</u>
<u n="55" who="S0270">very soon</u>
<u n="56" who="S0266">things have changed since then cos I went overland and you could go through places like <pause dur="short"/> erm Iraq</u>
<u n="57" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0271">mm cos you went to Afghanistan</u>
<u n="59" who="S0266" trans="overlap">Turkey went through</u>
<u n="60" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0266">I spent a lot of time in Afghanistan yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0266">and then Pakistan and there was fighting then</u>
<u n="64" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0266">civil war but it wasn't like perhaps as dangerous as</u>
<u n="66" who="S0271" trans="overlap">how did you travel there?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0266">erm I went on a <pause dur="short"/> a bus actually all all the way from London to Kathmandu</u>
<u n="68" who="S0271">mm blimey</u>
<u n="69" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but came back on public transport</u>
<u n="70" who="S0271">blimey</u>
<u n="71" who="S0266">with chickens and camels and</u>
<u n="72" who="S0271">who did you go with or were you on your own?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0266">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's a leading question</u>
<u n="74" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0266">the reason I went was because I'd been in a relationship for a very long time with a boy when I was young <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> when we'd split up I felt that I wasn't very independent so I decided that er I should be a bit more independent</u>
<u n="76" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0266">so I went to London and bought a ticket a one way ticket to Kathmandu</u>
<u n="78" who="S0270">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> didn't realise that was the start of the big one</u>
<u n="79" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I didn't know anyone</u>
<u n="80" who="S0271" trans="overlap">what did your mother think of that?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0266">well you know parents in those days didn't seem to worry <pause dur="short"/> and there were no mobile phones</u>
<u n="82" who="S0270">no</u>
<u n="83" who="S0266">and you'd er I gave poste restante addresses in a few places I thought I might be going to</u>
<u n="84" who="S0271">sent me a postcard letter</u>
<u n="85" who="S0266">yep so I'd send a letter once a fortnight and I'd pick up the odd letter from them once I fortnight</u>
<u n="86" who="S0270">what about international phone calls? when I was in Austria you could do</u>
<u n="87" who="S0266">well in Europe you could but you you couldn't</u>
<u n="88" who="S0271" trans="overlap">you had you had to</u>
<u n="89" who="S0266" trans="overlap">in those countries</u>
<u n="90" who="S0271" trans="overlap">book them really didn't you?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0266">oh I dunno I never even tried</u>
<u n="92" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0266">we were</u>
<u n="94" who="S0270">for how long did you spend doing it then? it must have taken up a very long time</u>
<u n="95" who="S0266" trans="overlap">going there I think took about er do you know I can't remember? I've got it somewhere in a diary that I'm close to finding</u>
<u n="96" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0266">turning out all my junk erm probably about three months going there</u>
<u n="98" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0271">so how did you finance it?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0266">I worked <pause dur="short"/> erm and saved money and it was very cheap</u>
<u n="101" who="S0271">mm mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0266">I think the whole trip was only <pause dur="short"/> I dunno a hundred and twenty pounds or something like that</u>
<u n="103" who="S0271">and I thought I did quite well coming back from Greece on my own</u>
<u n="104" who="S0266">did you?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0266">how did you come back on your own?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0271">well erm cos I was there for a year and I decided to go round the islands so I did that and I suppose that gave me some confidence so I thought well I'll be able to travel overland back to England so I got on a bus and went to Corfu and then got the ferry round to Dubrovnik</u>
<u n="108" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0271">and I met these four Australians in a camper van on the boat and</u>
<u n="110" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but in those <trunc>d</trunc> what what year was this?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0271">I think it was nineteen</u>
<u n="112" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0266" trans="overlap">that was when</u>
<u n="114" who="S0271">nineteen seventyish</u>
<u n="115" who="S0266">mm so Tito was still there in Yugoslavia</u>
<u n="116" who="S0271" trans="overlap">probably</u>
<u n="117" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0271">and these Australians I think they probably weren't getting on very well two doctors and two nurses and they <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="119" who="S0266" trans="overlap">why did you meet them?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0271">on the boat going to Dubrovnik and they said would you like to?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0266" trans="overlap">why did you go to Dubrovnik and not Italy?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well cos I wanted to go through Yugoslavia</u>
<u n="123" who="S0266">oh right okay</u>
<u n="124" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I was actually heading up to Hamburg where my cousin lived so I joined them and we travelled up through Yugoslavia erm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0270">in their bus?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0271">in their camper van they had a tent as well <pause dur="short"/> and then erm where did we get to? I <trunc>thi</trunc> we went to southern went to Salzburg we went in the mines there I remember that erm southern Germany I suppose and then I got the train up to Hamburg to stay with my cousin who was</u>
<u n="127" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so when did you say goodbye to these people?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0271">I said goodbye to them at er erm Strasbourg <pause dur="short"/> but I kept in <trunc>tou</trunc> I moved back to London after that and I kept in touch with them I remember going to some parties and one of the guys <pause dur="short"/> this really short little chap he used to come round and sit on my lap <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0271">in my flat he was really small he was a doctor an Aussie guy</u>
<u n="130" who="S0270">sounds very weird</u>
<u n="131" who="S0266" trans="overlap">why did he sit on your lap? Weren't there enough chairs?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0271">he was just a funny sort of he just used cos he was I was quite tall and he was <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="133" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0271">and I I <pause dur="short"/> in recent years since</u>
<u n="135" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0271">since my two have been in Australia</u>
<u n="137" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0271">I'd quite like to look him up again cos I stayed fairly friendly with him and then I think he must have gone back to Australia or something <pause dur="short"/> he was a gynaecologist</u>
<u n="139" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah it has all these connotations this <trunc>st</trunc> and I wonder how</u>
<u n="140" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0270">did he just do it to tease you and come and sit on your lap or did he have</u>
<u n="142" who="S0271" trans="overlap">no well when we were sitting</u>
<u n="143" who="S0270" trans="overlap">conversations?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0271" trans="overlap">when we were sitting in the living room with the flatmates and friends and there weren't enough chairs he used to sit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0266">did he fancy you then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0271">no no he was too short for that I don't think he fancied me</u>
<u n="147" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0271">he was like five foot one or two quite small for a guy</u>
<u n="149" who="S0270">obviously bright which was a compensation</u>
<u n="150" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0271">so they were both gynaecologists both erm both the blokes <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="152" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so this was that was before you met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0271">in <trunc>ni</trunc>nineteen seventy <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I went on holidays <pause dur="short"/> in seventy-six I went on an overland trip to Russia</u>
<u n="154" who="S0266">did you? in seventy-six cos that was in the</u>
<u n="155" who="S0270" trans="overlap">that was quite brave</u>
<u n="156" who="S0266" trans="overlap">by yourself?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well it was no it was on a you know bus with lots of Australians and people so we went</u>
<u n="158" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm as they do on their way home</u>
<u n="159" who="S0271">and we we went through Holland and Scandinavia Finland St Petersburg <pause dur="short"/>  Moscow <pause dur="short"/> poland and then <pause dur="short"/> back to England and I think I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> soon after that our conversation started by saying oh I've just been to Poland <pause dur="short"/> talking about him being Polish</u>
<u n="160" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0271">and I</u>
<u n="162" who="S0270" trans="overlap">so where did you actually go when you went to Poland that time?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0271">we went stopped in Warsaw</u>
<u n="164" who="S0270">mm I hear that's a really good place to go</u>
<u n="165" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="166" who="S0270">if you're starting</u>
<u n="167" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and Russia was quite scary</u>
<u n="168" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0271" trans="overlap">really because <pause dur="short"/> you could I think they were booked in to go to certain places at certain times and on the roads there'd be check er checkpoints with guards and that checking that you were at a certain place at a certain time and we got to Moscow and you had to have a in tourist guide taking you to the places that you have booked out and the food was not very good either it was <pause dur="short"/> summer and it was just cabbages no nice fruit to eat <pause dur="short"/> and tea that's about the all there was to drink and then travelling into Poland you could just see the difference that the fields the crops were bigger <pause dur="short"/> it just looked so much more prosperous than <pause dur="short"/> than Russia</u>
<u n="170" who="S0270">you were quite both quite intrepid weren't you? I don't think I did anything like that</u>
<u n="171" who="S0271">and I I went on another overland trip down to Morocco</u>
<u n="172" who="S0266">have some peanuts</u>
<u n="173" who="S0270" trans="overlap">thanks</u>
<u n="174" who="S0271">thank you that was just in a minivan I mean just</u>
<u n="175" who="S0266" trans="overlap">with?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0271">it was just one of these little overland companies so erm <pause dur="short"/> went down through Madrid and over to Tangier and down to Fes and back up again that was quite interesting</u>
<u n="177" who="S0266">but it was quite adventurous in those days to go off and</u>
<u n="178" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well it felt adventurous</u>
<u n="180" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><trunc>e</trunc>even if you went on those trips</u>
<u n="181" who="S0271" trans="overlap">to go and live in Greece <pause dur="short"/> that I did</u>
<u n="182" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0271">particularly from my background my parents had never been abroad</u>
<u n="184" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0270">did you learn some of the <trunc>la</trunc> the?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I learnt how to swear at people in Greece <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I'm not good</u>
<u n="187" who="S0270" trans="overlap">anything else?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0271" trans="overlap">at languages</u>
<u n="189" who="S0266">but it was a very different</u>
<u n="190" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0266">Greece in those days cos you couldn't get things like things like <trunc>s</trunc> erm butter or Nescafé or</u>
<u n="192" who="S0271" trans="overlap">we had we <trunc>did</trunc></u>
<u n="193" who="S0266" trans="overlap">there was no instant coffee you just had to</u>
<u n="194" who="S0271" trans="overlap">though we had Nescafé</u>
<u n="195" who="S0266">did you? well what year</u>
<u n="196" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0266" trans="overlap">was that then?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0271">that was erm sixty-nine</u>
<u n="199" who="S0266">where did you find Nescafé?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0271">I didn't buy it but the family seemed to have it it's who you know isn't it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0266">I used to take it back in my suitcase with sausages</u>
<u n="202" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0266">and you never had butter <pause dur="short"/> except that special Corfu <unclear>Kerkyra's voutyro</unclear></u>
<u n="204" who="S0271">I don't remember butter very much</u>
<u n="205" who="S0266">I used to miss butter when I used to go there</u>
<u n="206" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but the woman I the woman I worked for was PA to Latsis that big</u>
<u n="207" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0271" trans="overlap">ship owner and I think through connections with him she possibly got certain things</u>
<u n="209" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah cos you couldn't get it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0266">I mean there weren't even supermarkets in those days</u>
<u n="212" who="S0271" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="213" who="S0266" trans="overlap">they were all corner shops it was very</u>
<u n="214" who="S0271">but erm I did have an American boyfriend there <pause dur="short"/> so I think I might have</u>
<u n="215" who="S0266" trans="overlap">American?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0271">American yeah I met this erm American bloke <pause dur="short"/> he was in the army on a base there cos there were quite a few Americans there then weren't there?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0271">so did a bit he was quite interested in sight seeing so we went up to Delphi and places on my days off</u>
<u n="219" who="S0266">how long did that last?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0271">not my friendship with him?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0271">mm six months?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0271">and then through my sister I was complaining that I didn't ever meet any Greek men and she was at university in Kent and her good friend was a Greek guy and <trunc>sh</trunc> they put me in touch with their friend in erm <pause dur="short"/> in Athens er he was a very tall Greek</u>
<u n="225" who="S0266">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0271">probably as tall as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0266" trans="overlap">in contrast to the gynaecologist</u>
<u n="228" who="S0271">mm <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> erm we'd all go</u>
<u n="229" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you used to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0266">oh right and did he take you out?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0271">yeah we went out with his friends for meals and <pause dur="short"/> and then it was time for me to leave I came back the main reason I came back was my younger sister was having a heart operation <pause dur="short"/> which unfortunately she died through having that but <pause dur="short"/>  that's why I came back</u>
<u n="232" who="S0270">good job you did then because actually</u>
<u n="233" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0270">you got to see her didn't you?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0270">mm I think you were very intrepid both of you my most intrepid thing was going over when I was nineteen on the train going back again to meet the boy that I'd fallen in love with on the erm sixth form trip <pause dur="short"/> and I did stay and work there but erm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0271">that was quite intrepid for those times</u>
<u n="238" who="S0270">mm I don't know <pause dur="short"/> for me it was I was just a baby really still growing up thinking of sausages back to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s conversation erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bought back erm five</u>
<u n="239" who="S0266" trans="overlap">sausages from <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0271">five kilos of</u>
<u n="241" who="S0266">from Poland <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0271" trans="overlap">Polish sausages from Poland</u>
<u n="243" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they didn't take much in their case but they bought it full back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0271">yeah they're so much nicer than British sausages</u>
<u n="246" who="S0270">you were saying you'd taken sausages to Greece what I was</u>
<u n="247" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="248" who="S0270" trans="overlap">it made me remember</u>
<u n="249" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they'd brought them back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well you could get sausages but they weren't like English sausages I suppose they were probably very good sausages but well unlike this the rubbishy English ones</u>
<u n="251" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well Polish sausages are pure meat there's not much fat in them <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> they're good</u>
<u n="252" who="S0270" trans="overlap">they will do <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>can't you</unclear> come</u>
<u n="253" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so what are you gonna do with them are you gonna?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0271" trans="overlap">we've eaten them</u>
<u n="255" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I I've come to invite you to <trunc>Ne</trunc></u>
<u n="256" who="S0271" trans="overlap">we've just had some tonight</u>
<u n="257" who="S0270">to Nepal <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and put them in the freezer</u>
<u n="259" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">alright</u>
<u n="260" who="S0271">we had quite a few Kabanos those little</u>
<u n="261" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0271">thinny ones we ate those for lunch those</u>
<u n="263" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well you can get those in Lidl now or aren't those good?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0271">they're not quite as good</u>
<u n="265" who="S0266">like</u>
<u n="266" who="S0271">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> told you about Ulan Bator did he?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0266">mm <pause dur="short"/> he was really enthused</u>
<u n="268" who="S0271">did he tell you how</u>
<u n="269" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0271" trans="overlap">he's got the connections there?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0266">do you know that?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0270" trans="overlap">when I went and saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for a chat on the <pause dur="short"/> for a cup of tea somewhere</u>
<u n="275" who="S0271" trans="overlap">cos er yeah cos erm <pause dur="short"/> it was quite funny really going back to where he was at college in Poznań had a picture of him standing on the steps of the <trunc>co</trunc> the art college</u>
<u n="276" who="S0266">and when he got speaking to <pause dur="short"/> was it an old art teacher of his?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0271">no when he went to Poland for a year he he went to the art college and the secretary there he said to her I <trunc>ha</trunc> I've got nowhere to live and she said I think my parents have got a room so he actually lived with her parents and stayed friendly with her and we've just he's always exchanged Christmas cards with her and so we did go and see her when we went to Poland about fifteen years ago and erm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but not since?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0271">no and so</u>
<u n="280" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0271">she through a friend is in touch with this Mongolian guy who erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knew quite well who he taught <pause dur="short"/> to speak English</u>
<u n="282" who="S0270">I think it's lovely that you might get to see him</u>
<u n="283" who="S0271">well it's not happened yet</u>
<u n="284" who="S0270">mm <pause dur="short"/> have you not managed to get an email sorted?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0271" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> no I think it's to do she is retired and she's still got connections with the art college in Poznań with people who are in touch with him</u>
<u n="286" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0271">so it's a matter of linking all that up</u>
<u n="288" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm exciting <pause dur="short"/> where are you two headed off shortly then for your holiday?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0271">yeah which bit?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0266">oh just <pause dur="short"/> a relaxing beach holiday really</u>
<u n="291" who="S0270">which beach?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0266">erm in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0271"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0266"><anon type="place"/> you know</u>
<u n="295" who="S0271">yeah up the top right</u>
<u n="296" who="S0266">east of yeah top right</u>
<u n="297" who="S0270">east of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0271">I think that was erm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0266">I'm just gonna get you another drink <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0270" trans="overlap">okay alright</u>
<u n="301" who="S0266">do you want the same? who's driving?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0270" trans="overlap">er yes er me so I probably should have lemonade <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="303" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well I'll give you a spot of wine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are you ready for a top up?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0271">a small top up please</u>
<u n="305" who="S0266">do you want anything else to eat?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0271">no I'm good thank you</u>
<u n="307" who="S0266"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're not eating anything</u>
<u n="308" who="S0271">well I'm talking</u>
<u n="309" who="S0270">well she well had erm she had erm a meal before you came didn't you?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0271">I did have my Polish <trunc>saus</trunc></u>
<u n="311" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh your sausages?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0271">had Polish sausage <unclear/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so what's the difference with them?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0271">well it's mm smoky <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0266">spicy?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0271">not not</u>
<u n="317" who="S0270" trans="overlap">oh no?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0271" trans="overlap">spicy no <pause dur="short"/> you can eat them hot or cold these ones you've probably seen them <pause dur="short"/> in supermarkets oh I think it's Polish week at Lidl tomorrow</u>
<u n="319" who="S0266">oh is it?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0266">I think Lidl is just great</u>
<u n="323" who="S0271">so I usually have to go and get to the gherkins <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> likes them in brine which is</u>
<u n="324" who="S0270" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="325" who="S0271" trans="overlap">how the Poles have them not in vinegar</u>
<u n="326" who="S0270">blimey <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="327" who="S0266">do you still erm eat their yoghurt?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0271">yeah I like their yoghurt</u>
<u n="329" who="S0266">cos I used to catch you in there sometimes buying a Greek yoghurt or</u>
<u n="330" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm oh so he brings you back a coffee does he?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0266">who?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0271"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0266">no I went and got it myself</u>
<u n="334" who="S0271">oh I see</u>
<u n="335" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I went to get some celery to make <unclear/> things</u>
<u n="336" who="S0271" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="337" who="S0266">and I have to have a Costa Coffee every</u>
<u n="338" who="S0270">do you just heat it up in the?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0266">no I drink it warm cold</u>
<u n="340" who="S0270" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="341" who="S0266">no I make it last all day they're so expensive</u>
<u n="342" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0270">and where do you go to get that?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0266">ah <pause dur="short"/> down at erm <pause dur="short"/> the garage</u>
<u n="345" who="S0270">not <anon type="place"/> services?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0266">at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0270">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="348" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you know the opposite your</u>
<u n="349" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I think er yes I do</u>
<u n="350" who="S0266" trans="overlap">brother in law's</u>
<u n="351" who="S0270">I yeah <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0270">yeah I go there to erm get my car washed etcetera</u>
<u n="354" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0270">quite often</u>
<u n="356" who="S0266">well I go</u>
<u n="357" who="S0271"><unclear/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and yeah and tomorrow there's a secret code if you go into Starbucks anywhere between eleven and twelve and say the word cocoa</u>
<u n="359" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0266">you get a free <pause dur="short"/> latte</u>
<u n="361" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0266">so I'm going tomorrow</u>
<u n="363" who="S0270">er <trunc>w</trunc><trunc>w</trunc>where where is one?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0266">between eleven and twelve</u>
<u n="365" who="S0270" trans="overlap">where is one?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0266" trans="overlap">if anyone's free and wants to come with me</u>
<u n="367" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah where is one?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0266">well <pause dur="short"/> the services</u>
<u n="369" who="S0270" trans="overlap">where is the <trunc>Star</trunc></u>
<u n="370" who="S0266">er <anon type="place"/> services</u>
<u n="371" who="S0270">oh right</u>
<u n="372" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I think she knows where all the coffee places are</u>
<u n="373" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0266">I don't really like I prefer Costa er to Starbucks</u>
<u n="375" who="S0271">they're gonna sell coffee down the village shop aren't they?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0266">what? Costa?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0270">I think they already do</u>
<u n="378" who="S0266" trans="overlap">if they get a Costa machine I shall be there every day</u>
<u n="379" who="S0270" trans="overlap">they already do they already do sell coffee</u>
<u n="380" who="S0266">what kind of coffee?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0270">mm I'm not sure</u>
<u n="382" who="S0271">you know about the village shop do you?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0266"><trunc>n</trunc>no tell me about the village shop the latest</u>
<u n="384" who="S0271">do you know the woman in the post office there?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0266">they employed someone new didn't they?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0271">cos she's taking on the lease of the shop and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been given the sack</u>
<u n="387" who="S0266">oh really? <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh gosh she's</u>
<u n="388" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and she's just very upset</u>
<u n="389" who="S0270">I mean that must be awful cos she's</u>
<u n="390" who="S0266" trans="overlap">that must be quite quite serious</u>
<u n="391" who="S0270" trans="overlap">she's been really involved</u>
<u n="392" who="S0271">I mean people don't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I think she's very</u>
<u n="393" who="S0270" trans="overlap">very loyal</u>
<u n="394" who="S0271" trans="overlap">organised efficient loyal conscientious but these middle class women <pause dur="short"/> think she's not a salesperson</u>
<u n="395" who="S0270">she isn't she doesn't</u>
<u n="396" who="S0271" trans="overlap">she isn't</u>
<u n="397" who="S0270" trans="overlap">present a good persona when you go in <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="398" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but will it make any difference? I mean people either go in a shop or they don't</u>
<u n="399" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I would've thought if she'd been employed surely she'll have some rights</u>
<u n="400" who="S0271">yeah she's gonna go for she told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she's going to go for redundancy and what she can get out of it</u>
<u n="401" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0266">so who actually employed her? was it the village? the Co-operative?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I think the the yes the Co-op <pause dur="short"/> whatever that is</u>
<u n="404" who="S0266">well it's the group of people who've got shares in the village shop isn't it?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think they're</u>
<u n="406" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so who made that decision?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0271">there was a meeting</u>
<u n="408" who="S0270" trans="overlap">there was a big meeting mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0271" trans="overlap">in August which <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I missed cos</u>
<u n="410" who="S0270">which er yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0271">we weren't around</u>
<u n="412" who="S0270">we were both away</u>
<u n="413" who="S0266">oh really?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0270">didn't realise the significance of the importance of it</u>
<u n="415" who="S0266">because the whole wasn't the whole the the big sort of issue before was the fact that they were gonna lose the post office part?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0271">well that seemed to er</u>
<u n="417" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and then</u>
<u n="418" who="S0271" trans="overlap">work out that</u>
<u n="419" who="S0266">and then a new lady</u>
<u n="420" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0266">came in</u>
<u n="422" who="S0271">yes</u>
<u n="423" who="S0266">and this is this lady that's where does she come from? is she local?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0271">yes</u>
<u n="425" who="S0270">she is cos er</u>
<u n="426" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> or</u>
<u n="427" who="S0270">she is local</u>
<u n="428" who="S0271">somewhere up that way</u>
<u n="429" who="S0270">she's local</u>
<u n="430" who="S0266">so she's taking on the whole?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0270">I think she is the right kind of person <pause dur="short"/> she'll be able to talk to the locals run the post office and be quite</u>
<u n="432" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0271">the question is</u>
<u n="434" who="S0270" trans="overlap">er she's very approachable</u>
<u n="435" who="S0271">the question is <pause dur="short"/> will there still be volunteers? I mean I I wouldn't want to volunteer if it's going in her pocket <pause dur="short"/> I would've I would've volunteered</u>
<u n="436" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so <trunc>ha</trunc>has the status changed then? it's not a charity anymore it's a</u>
<u n="437" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0266">business concern is it?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm it was a lease or something</u>
<u n="440" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I was gonna say how on earth will that work?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0271">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I thought they'd got a they owned the building the trustees</u>
<u n="442" who="S0266">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought that everyone put in money to buy the building</u>
<u n="443" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0270">er someone lives in the flat which is part of the er</u>
<u n="445" who="S0266">but that's rent is it?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0266" trans="overlap">rented so the rent helps to pay</u>
<u n="449" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm it's not cost effective it was never going to work as a business and so this may <pause dur="short"/> may help</u>
<u n="451" who="S0271">you've still got to get</u>
<u n="452" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so what's she doing?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0271" trans="overlap">people to go in the shop though</u>
<u n="454" who="S0266" trans="overlap">she's renting it</u>
<u n="455" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0266" trans="overlap">she's renting it off the</u>
<u n="457" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0271" trans="overlap">she's bought the lease or something like that hasn't she?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0266">oh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0266">so does that <trunc>s</trunc> mean there's no more nightmare er situation where <pause dur="short"/> you've got people worrying the whole time about it closing and</u>
<u n="463" who="S0271">the problem is the</u>
<u n="464" who="S0270" trans="overlap">there'll be deliveries Sunday <trunc>newspap</trunc></u>
<u n="465" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s couldn't make a go of it and they were fairly friendly I mean how is she gonna make it any different?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0266">what did the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s do then? did they lease it as well?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they owned it didn't they?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0270">er I don't know I remember</u>
<u n="469" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh before <anon type="place"/> village bought it?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0271">mm and also there was that miserable guy erm <pause dur="short"/> you know the brother in law of the lady dentist</u>
<u n="471" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0271">he was he was a bit</u>
<u n="473" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah but that was before the whole <trunc>vill</trunc> or the villagers</u>
<u n="474" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0266" trans="overlap">took it over <unclear/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm before it became a community shop</u>
<u n="478" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0270">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a massive massive issue for any small businesses let alone a community shop but some people still seem to have made a success of it the one in <anon type="place"/> seems to run</u>
<u n="480" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> is very successful</u>
<u n="481" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0271">my sister in law helps there</u>
<u n="483" who="S0266">but why is it successful?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0270">it still has definitely <pause dur="short"/> definitely <trunc>s</trunc>shorter shop hours and things</u>
<u n="485" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they do they do sandwiches and foodie things there</u>
<u n="486" who="S0270">do they?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0270">I think it's all about footfall isn't it? if you don't get the footfall how can you possibly?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0271">yeah it's the footfall</u>
<u n="490" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0271" trans="overlap">doesn't matter who's serving</u>
<u n="492" who="S0270">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I do think it's very hard</u>
<u n="493" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0270" trans="overlap">to get the market right people er go to drop in they're going to want a post office they do want a <trunc>Lott</trunc> a Lottery ticket <pause dur="short"/> and they do want staple things</u>
<u n="495" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah but they don't do Lottery tickets any longer</u>
<u n="496" who="S0270">okay</u>
<u n="497" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they weren't high enough turnover er tut</u>
<u n="498" who="S0270" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="499" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they took it away from them</u>
<u n="500" who="S0270">okay</u>
<u n="501" who="S0266" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0271">you see the there's</u>
<u n="503" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it it's the fact that it's not on the main road and it hasn't got parking</u>
<u n="504" who="S0271" trans="overlap">it's cos it's not on the main road</u>
<u n="505" who="S0266">or it hasn't got parking</u>
<u n="506" who="S0271">no parking you go there and you can't park</u>
<u n="507" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm see I I never think of going there and I should really I should support it</u>
<u n="508" who="S0270">well that's because your local one is <pause dur="short"/> is much closer surely?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0266">yeah but it's not <trunc>har</trunc> it's hardly a village shop it's a the one I go to's a Spar</u>
<u n="510" who="S0270" trans="overlap">no no no but I mean your local shop</u>
<u n="511" who="S0271">but these middle class</u>
<u n="512" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well my local shop is what?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0270">is the Spar</u>
<u n="514" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0270">er why would you be going to <anon type="place"/>? it's not nearly so near</u>
<u n="516" who="S0266" trans="overlap">to to <trunc>suppor</trunc> to support it because it's a erm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0271">well I usually go there and buy eggs</u>
<u n="518" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you know it's a community</u>
<u n="519" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0271" trans="overlap">we get our paper from there <pause dur="short"/> and if I've forgotten anything now and again I buy a card</u>
<u n="521" who="S0270">well I go there</u>
<u n="522" who="S0271">and but</u>
<u n="523" who="S0270">for those kind of things</u>
<u n="524" who="S0271">I've found</u>
<u n="525" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but I mean they do things like Hobbs bread don't they there?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0271">yes I don't like Hobbs bread very much</u>
<u n="527" who="S0266">don't you? I find it's</u>
<u n="528" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and it's quite expensive and <trunc>actua</trunc></u>
<u n="529" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I thought it was supposed to be so good</u>
<u n="530" who="S0271">we don't eat much bread I suppose</u>
<u n="531" who="S0270">they've tried to offer</u>
<u n="532" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and <trunc>th</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took me in there once and sat me down on the floor even which was very embarrassing <pause dur="short"/> cos they do a good exchange of books</u>
<u n="533" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0270" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah that's really nice that's a very local village shop thing</u>
<u n="535" who="S0266">but I mean there's no money in that I think I</u>
<u n="536" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0266">I think what was what were they a pound or something?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0270" trans="overlap">no no no fifty P</u>
<u n="539" who="S0266">fifty P</u>
<u n="540" who="S0270">mm well there is a little bit of trickle of money I guess but it's always gonna be difficult for things keep thing like vegetables isn't it because they go</u>
<u n="541" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well they just go off</u>
<u n="542" who="S0270" trans="overlap">they go off mm so I think it's a very difficult task</u>
<u n="543" who="S0271">it is</u>
<u n="544" who="S0266">are there a lot of people in erm <anon type="place"/> though that haven't got cars and can't get out?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0271">I think there's a few old people in the erm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0271">old people's places</u>
<u n="548" who="S0270">it's a <trunc>su</trunc> it's supposed to be a basic essential isn't it?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0271" trans="overlap">it is useful if you're</u>
<u n="550" who="S0270">supposed to be essential</u>
<u n="551" who="S0271" trans="overlap">cooking something like I was and I've not got the right ingredients</u>
<u n="552" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0270">it was very good for a for a</u>
<u n="554" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but it's just too expensive they can't sell things as cheap as Lidl or Tesco so</u>
<u n="555" who="S0270" trans="overlap">er no but if you were going to go there <pause dur="short"/> gonna supplement your weekly shop there aren't you?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0271">yeah but it's still cheaper than getting spend on petrol in your car and</u>
<u n="558" who="S0266">I'd have thought there would there would have been quite a few elderly <trunc>p</trunc> people there and <pause dur="short"/> young mums who'd use it but it would never work in this village <pause dur="short"/> because</u>
<u n="559" who="S0270">but people do go to the farm shop you know in <anon type="place"/> you see cos you can get</u>
<u n="560" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but that's terribly expensive</u>
<u n="562" who="S0270">I know but I'm surprised who I've seen in there I've only been in a few times but it's been quite a cross</u>
<u n="563" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> spends a lot of money in</u>
<u n="564" who="S0270" trans="overlap">a section of the</u>
<u n="565" who="S0266" trans="overlap">she doesn't does she? it's I mean it's shockingly expensive in there</u>
<u n="566" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but there's there's young mums with with erm babies who I've seen in there</u>
<u n="567" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0271" trans="overlap">how how can they have got the money?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I don't know how they can afford to</u>
<u n="571" who="S0271">how can they how have they got the money?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0270">husband with a good job I suppose <pause dur="short"/> but I think it's terribly easy to park there you can have a coffee</u>
<u n="573" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you can have a cup of this you can have a cup of <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I had a disgusting coffee there about six weeks ago</u>
<u n="576" who="S0270" trans="overlap">did you?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0270">and you pay a lot for your vegetables there but you can get some quite nice</u>
<u n="579" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it's not only that you see a quiche or something and you think</u>
<u n="580" who="S0270" trans="overlap">it's artisan</u>
<u n="581" who="S0266">oh I'll really</u>
<u n="582" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0266" trans="overlap">treat</u>
<u n="584" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0270">and you can yeah so</u>
<u n="586" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you know myself</u>
<u n="587" who="S0270">you can buy quite a lot of nice artisan food that's readymade that</u>
<u n="588" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah but it's so expensive</u>
<u n="589" who="S0270">I know that's why I don't go there but that is why people go there you can it's terribly convenient and you can pop in you can definitely park</u>
<u n="590" who="S0266">mm yeah that's true</u>
<u n="591" who="S0270" trans="overlap">and you can pick up all the things you need and yes it will cost you quite a lot more <pause dur="short"/> but I think maybe if you were <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="592" who="S0266">well if you're feeding only one person you can buy something that'll last you</u>
<u n="593" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0266">you know three nights</u>
<u n="595" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I think that's how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> manages</u>
<u n="596" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0270" trans="overlap">to do it really</u>
<u n="598" who="S0266">that's how I'd <pause dur="short"/> work it out</u>
<u n="599" who="S0270">sorry</u>
<u n="600" who="S0266">but if you were trying to feed</u>
<u n="601" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0266">other people as well <pause dur="short"/> there used to be the most amazing woman you know the one erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> farm shop what was it called? actually on the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0271">oh yes the one who cooked the cakes and</u>
<u n="604" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0271">she was such a hard worker</u>
<u n="606" who="S0266">oh and she she</u>
<u n="607" who="S0271" trans="overlap">she was baking cakes on the</u>
<u n="608" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0271" trans="overlap">premises</u>
<u n="610" who="S0266">oh and things like quiches and</u>
<u n="611" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0266">it and it was so reasonably priced and you could order it as well</u>
<u n="613" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0266">in advance if you you know</u>
<u n="615" who="S0270">I don't know why she stopped why did she stop?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0266">I think it all got too much for her</u>
<u n="617" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0266">and then this other woman took over and she was useless <pause dur="short"/> she didn't have and she had really nice erm product stuff in the shop as well</u>
<u n="619" who="S0271">she had</u>
<u n="620" who="S0266" trans="overlap">lovely cheeses</u>
<u n="621" who="S0271">she had cheese yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0266">and and</u>
<u n="623" who="S0271" trans="overlap">used to get some</u>
<u n="624" who="S0266">lots of local sort of you know</u>
<u n="625" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0266" trans="overlap">that Stinking Bishop</u>
<u n="627" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but what what happens then of course is that people are finding markets like Tesco's Finest or erm Waitrose or whatever they're selling their wares to supermarkets</u>
<u n="628" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they don't sell that sort of cheese though do they Tesco? it's quite boring</u>
<u n="629" who="S0266">Waitrose does in <anon type="place"/> and things like Stinking Bishop but it's much more expensive</u>
<u n="630" who="S0270" trans="overlap">no I disagree I disagree you can get very nice cheeses</u>
<u n="631" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but there's stuff that she had in jars like the pickles and things</u>
<u n="632" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0271">were quite good <pause dur="short"/> maybe she had to help on the farm or</u>
<u n="634" who="S0270">maybe</u>
<u n="635" who="S0266">I don't know and she had children didn't she?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="637" who="S0266">and she used to employ people to work there</u>
<u n="638" who="S0271">she did and she was busy</u>
<u n="639" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but they were very nice ladies</u>
<u n="640" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0266">and they had everything like for example really nice cards that</u>
<u n="642" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="643" who="S0266" trans="overlap">local artists had painted</u>
<u n="644" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0266">and they'd printed the <pause dur="short"/> cards and</u>
<u n="647" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but they were there as the</u>
<u n="648" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I I used to spend a fortune when I went in there</u>
<u n="649" who="S0271">mm they also had the trellis work and stuff outside didn't they?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0266">mm and you could get potatoes and</u>
<u n="651" who="S0270">mm what happened to that wonderful place off the <anon type="place"/> was it <anon type="place"/>? <anon type="place"/>? we used we went to a very eclectic place that sold</u>
<u n="652" who="S0266">did we go?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0270">yeah didn't we go that one time off the <anon type="place"/>? we got off a back road and there was erm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0266" trans="overlap">whereabouts <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? because erm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0270" trans="overlap">it was erm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> is miles away</u>
<u n="657" who="S0270">oh right that's not the right road then and we were off the <anon type="place"/> and we were cutting down probably the road to <anon type="place"/> from the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0266">right oh</u>
<u n="659" who="S0270">and erm</u>
<u n="660" who="S0266">what after <anon type="place"/> or something?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0270">and erm they were it was a very eclectic place called selling erm vintage this and vintage that and also you could have cups of tea and things</u>
<u n="662" who="S0266">food or</u>
<u n="663" who="S0270" trans="overlap">er yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0266">junk?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0270">no no no</u>
<u n="666" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you're not talking about the junk shop?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0270">yeah it was a junk shop but it was also it was erm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0266" trans="overlap">not the one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes to?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0270">no no not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0266">not yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0271"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't be buying stuff still is she?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0270">they've got a wedding coming up so I think they're buying things for the garden cos the wedding's going to be in the garden</u>
<u n="673" who="S0266">I don't know what place you're talking about</u>
<u n="674" who="S0271">the wedding's not going to</u>
<u n="675" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0271">oh you mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wedding not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0270">so yes she is buying things statues and things for the garden</u>
<u n="680" who="S0266">I can't think what place you're</u>
<u n="681" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0266">thinking about</u>
<u n="683" who="S0271">you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have been told not to listen to anyone over forty giving advice about babies? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0270">cos it's all out of date</u>
<u n="685" who="S0271">it's out of date how did we manage to bring our children up? <pause dur="short"/> don't you think that's that's rather cruel cos they can't even listen to their own mothers can they?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0266">who told them that?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0271">health visitors and people</u>
<u n="688" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="689" who="S0271">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to <trunc>th</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> he said to them I'll give you some advice my mother always used to erm boil up milk with poppy seeds in it to give to us to make us sleep and the shocked horror on their faces</u>
<u n="690" who="S0266">who's faces?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0271"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0271">not don't listen to anyone over forty and there's him saying this to them</u>
<u n="694" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so who told you that they did?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0271">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told me <pause dur="long"/> and I <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="696" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but that's almost as bad as you know <pause dur="short"/> telling people what when they're pregnant or they've had babies to giving them advice the whole time it's almost as bad just to say that you know to say that you can't get advice from anyone over forty</u>
<u n="697" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0271">so she was telling me this with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> standing beside her <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wife and so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a young person said well if you offer advice it's like you're criticising the the person and the baby if you say you should do it that way it means that what they're doing is totally wrong that's the way a young person looked at it I would look at it oh that's not going right I could suggest that and maybe it'll help them</u>
<u n="699" who="S0266">or just talk about when you did it</u>
<u n="700" who="S0271">when I</u>
<u n="701" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you did it</u>
<u n="702" who="S0271" trans="overlap">did it</u>
<u n="703" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0271">it really helped or</u>
<u n="705" who="S0270">I found it usually helped me to talk to other mums</u>
<u n="706" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but people do interfere</u>
<u n="707" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0266">do people do interfere horribly don't they?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0271">I didn't</u>
<u n="710" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and they're always you know</u>
<u n="711" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I didn't have anyone to interfere with me</u>
<u n="712" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="713" who="S0271">did your mother interfere?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0266">no but when I was in Greece with babies I mean god</u>
<u n="715" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="716" who="S0266">it the you know</u>
<u n="717" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0266">being told all the time what to do</u>
<u n="719" who="S0270"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s erm son and partner just had twins and erm she's desperate cos she doesn't think they're doing anything you know it's really really difficult they were both born early they're both quite small and I can't believe that they've been sent home without any other help</u>
<u n="720" who="S0271">where is this? is this in England?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0270">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0271">mm it's not the one in</u>
<u n="723" who="S0270">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0271"><unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="725" who="S0270">so erm I can't believe that and she feels well you know because it's daughter in law not</u>
<u n="726" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0270">son in law that</u>
<u n="728" who="S0271">is the girls</u>
<u n="729" who="S0270" trans="overlap">it's very very very difficult for her to deal with and she can see that a lot of the struggles could be you know</u>
<u n="730" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0270" trans="overlap">helped along</u>
<u n="732" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="733" who="S0270">and erm I'm saying well get in the professionals because then at least they might take their advice but they actually aren't getting you know extra visits or anything and these babies were some ridiculously small weight</u>
<u n="734" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but don't they have to go to clinics to be weighed or</u>
<u n="735" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I expect so</u>
<u n="736" who="S0271" trans="overlap">don't people come round?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I expect so but no</u>
<u n="738" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they must still do that</u>
<u n="739" who="S0270">but I don't think it's you know they could do with much more serious help than they're getting I think <pause dur="short"/> I'm certainly quite grateful I didn't start with twins <pause dur="short"/> be quite difficult wouldn't it? two what an onslaught</u>
<u n="740" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well it's it's difficult enough having them fairly close together</u>
<u n="741" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="742" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but yours were closer together than mine</u>
<u n="743" who="S0270">mm the girls were yeah <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="744" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0270">er having two exactly the same that's not going to be at all easy is it?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0270">so er mm in the old days <pause dur="short"/> I guess</u>
<u n="748" who="S0266">it's terrible we talk about the old days it's only our youth it sounds like we're talking about Victorian times</u>
<u n="749" who="S0270">mm that's true</u>
<u n="750" who="S0266">what do you mean when you say the old days?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0266">you mean our youth or do you mean</u>
<u n="753" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="754" who="S0266">way back?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0271">I know ideas</u>
<u n="756" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I can't remember what you were saying</u>
<u n="757" who="S0270">no I was conscious</u>
<u n="758" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><trunc>idea</trunc></u>
<u n="759" who="S0270" trans="overlap">of this recording</u>
<u n="760" who="S0271" trans="overlap">ideas change a little bit</u>
<u n="761" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0271">don't they? cos when when we were young the thing was to put your baby out in the pram outside in the garden wasn't it?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0266">mm I mean I mean</u>
<u n="764" who="S0271">fresh air</u>
<u n="765" who="S0266">yeah and er er a net over it</u>
<u n="766" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0266">so the cats didn't go and sleep on its face</u>
<u n="768" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah but it's <trunc>import</trunc> you wrap them up warmly and they were out in the fresh air and it made them sleep</u>
<u n="769" who="S0266">yeah you'd <trunc>l</trunc> under the trees and</u>
<u n="770" who="S0271" trans="overlap">or you couldn't you couldn't hear them crying so they went to sleep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0270">and we had to not lie the baby on its back but lie it on its side and now it's lie it on its back and yes you can sleep in the same bed if you're a <unclear>taught her</unclear> not to roll over and do something I mean I <trunc>thi</trunc> it's all it is different I think I'm sure there are things the same the thing is if you love and care for it that's all you can do</u>
<u n="772" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I think the other thing is they're meant to be in the same bedroom as you for six months in a cot</u>
<u n="773" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="774" who="S0266">they are meant to be or not?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0271">I think that's the latest idea</u>
<u n="776" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="777" who="S0270">I think there are quite strong differences to <pause dur="short"/> over the decades</u>
<u n="778" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but they'll probably change their mind again</u>
<u n="779" who="S0270">what's this notepad for?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0266">nothing I was just gonna make some notes</u>
<u n="781" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0266">does anyone need a another drink or something different to eat?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0270">no</u>
<u n="784" who="S0266">or something different to drink?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0271">no I'm fine</u>
<u n="786" who="S0270" trans="overlap">it's because I can't have those biscuits that I've eaten some of course</u>
<u n="787" who="S0266">oh you've eaten some?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0270">yeah what's the attraction?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0270">the attraction of carbohydrate is very strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0271">if your body</u>
<u n="792" who="S0270" trans="overlap">cos that's what it is</u>
<u n="793" who="S0271" trans="overlap">thinks you should eat it you should eat it like</u>
<u n="794" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="795" who="S0271">like me and cake today <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was nice cake</u>
<u n="797" who="S0266">what cake?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0271">er well</u>
<u n="799" who="S0270">I shouldn't have cake</u>
<u n="800" who="S0271" trans="overlap">at work it was someone's birthday <pause dur="short"/> some carrot cake homemade carrot cake with nice orange butter icing</u>
<u n="801" who="S0266">but you're not gluten free or anything are you?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0271">no I'm not gonna get into that sort of rubbish</u>
<u n="803" who="S0270">it's not rubbish and you'll see was that</u>
<u n="804" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so why were you feeling guilty about the?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> weight</u>
<u n="806" who="S0266">oh weight well you don't look er</u>
<u n="807" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0270">I'm just conscious of sitting down at work aren't you</u>
<u n="809" who="S0271">I'm conscious of not moving around enough</u>
<u n="810" who="S0266">mm so mm</u>
<u n="811" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you must do some sitting with your</u>
<u n="812" who="S0266">mm yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0270"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="814" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0271">it's not good really</u>
<u n="816" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I've been about three days I've been I dunno eighteen hours on the trot</u>
<u n="817" who="S0270">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="818" who="S0266" trans="overlap">anyway what did you do at <pause dur="short"/> what did you do at erm <pause dur="short"/> work today did you have to renegotiate your position?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0271"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0270">er no I thought I was going to but I had all my I had what I could print off available er displays you've done in the recent past <pause dur="short"/> annoyingly couldn't find some serious ones which I must have somewhere but couldn't locate them</u>
<u n="821" who="S0271">so as</u>
<u n="822" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well what?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0271" trans="overlap">you've gone along you've taken photos have you?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0270">oh yes I don't</u>
<u n="825" who="S0271">that's good</u>
<u n="826" who="S0270" trans="overlap">if I take anything down I know</u>
<u n="827" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="828" who="S0270">otherwise you can't prove you've done it</u>
<u n="829" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="830" who="S0270">some people have taken some things down without my taking a photograph</u>
<u n="831" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="832" who="S0270">which upsets me greatly <pause dur="short"/> because I have massive ownership of them when I've done them</u>
<u n="833" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="834" who="S0270">erm no I don't have to present it at all</u>
<u n="835" who="S0266">so did you have a meeting?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0270">I tried to but he just came out of his office and we walked around and discussed stuff and <pause dur="short"/> and that's it when do I go in? oh usually Tuesdays and Wednesday I said but it's you know negotiable I can do more or less or whatever and then the next thing I knew it's all coming up at a staff meeting and everybody's coming and approaching me so it was great</u>
<u n="837" who="S0271">so he</u>
<u n="838" who="S0266" trans="overlap">what approaching you to congratulate you?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0271" trans="overlap">he's <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="840" who="S0270" trans="overlap">as oh er no as to what</u>
<u n="841" who="S0271" trans="overlap">he's mentioned it at a staff meeting to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to organise the</u>
<u n="842" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0270">so erm we've been talking erm you know which is what I always did before without all this other stuff erm we were talking <pause dur="short"/> you know talking to the teachers themselves about what boards would <pause dur="short"/> would we would locate things at but erm even though we've cut out a lot of boards you know a lot has a lot there's been a lot of changes there's still masses to do you couldn't possibly do it without someone else you know each classroom has between four and six boards of their own and then there's the communal boards which I'm responsible for <pause dur="short"/> so even though we've taken them down and painted over and done all sorts it's still about forty</u>
<u n="845" who="S0271">forty?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0270">so forty boards mm</u>
<u n="847" who="S0271">phew</u>
<u n="848" who="S0270">about <trunc>fort</trunc> and that's without the new classrooms <pause dur="short"/> so I dunno what's gonna happen when we've got the new classrooms</u>
<u n="849" who="S0271">so how often do they want them changed?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0270">erm <pause dur="short"/> well some of them mm <unclear>and often</unclear> and a great deal you know the major ones that you can see in the main lobby <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and at least erm holding more than half termly but the others probably half termly <pause dur="short"/> and some things stay up a long time because they're an ongoing</u>
<u n="851" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="852" who="S0270">changing you know face so <pause dur="short"/> I would love to do lots more erm and it's these <unclear>Invictum</unclear> Games isn't it I think I've definitely got to put something up so when I go in on Tuesday</u>
<u n="853" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but did you?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I shall just suggest that I have to do that</u>
<u n="855" who="S0266">do you just put up what you want or is it?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0270" trans="overlap">no no no no</u>
<u n="857" who="S0266">who who?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0270" trans="overlap">it's topic work er topic work and</u>
<u n="859" who="S0266" trans="overlap">for the whole school or for?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0270">er yeah yeah nursery through to I do foundation stage key stage one and key stage two</u>
<u n="861" who="S0266" trans="overlap">no but just the topic</u>
<u n="862" who="S0270">oh no the topics are they run <trunc>f</trunc>for er different phases so they'll be erm</u>
<u n="863" who="S0271">there's a new curriculum though isn't there? so will there be different new things to put up and?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0270" trans="overlap">er well we have a new systems of phonics yeah it's now called Sound Write</u>
<u n="865" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but the sort of things</u>
<u n="866" who="S0270">not Read Write Inc so we're now doing Sound Write which I don't know much about I did listen in when I was outside in the corridor doing the boards <pause dur="short"/> I want to get something about that</u>
<u n="867" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but history</u>
<u n="868" who="S0270">we've got</u>
<u n="869" who="S0271" trans="overlap">history's changed hasn't it? different things that</u>
<u n="870" who="S0270">erm</u>
<u n="871" who="S0271">cos one of our teachers is going to Stonehenge for her topic</u>
<u n="872" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="873" who="S0271">so I don't know what</u>
<u n="874" who="S0270" trans="overlap">oh lovely</u>
<u n="875" who="S0271">that is</u>
<u n="876" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="877" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="878" who="S0270">great fun erm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I know three four are doing Tudors which we have done in the past</u>
<u n="879" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="880" who="S0270">erm <pause dur="short"/> and we're doing dinosaurs in year one at the moment which will be a fun one to do <pause dur="short"/> and we always have you know erm <unclear>wonder walls</unclear> so improving writing and improving improving maths targets and things like that and erm yeah be exciting I'm erm looking forward to it now we've got them started I am absolutely pooped though I can't believe how it's not <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0271">cos you can't sit down and that does it must keep her fit</u>
<u n="882" who="S0270">oh I do</u>
<u n="883" who="S0271" trans="overlap">more than me sitting in a chair all day</u>
<u n="884" who="S0270">I do a lot of stretching <vocal desc="laugh"/> I have repetitive strain in this muscle terrible repetitive strain <vocal desc="laugh"/> <event desc="unintelligible"/> it's ridiculous I can't tell you I can't sleep through it sometimes it's quite ridiculous I've got to get it looked at <pause dur="short"/> er but yes I am pleased that I haven't had to fight my corner there was no question of it but obviously</u>
<u n="885" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so is that the academic year then you'll be there?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0270">I think it's open because I haven't sent a contract</u>
<u n="887" who="S0271">so what do you do</u>
<u n="888" who="S0270" trans="overlap">cos I don't really</u>
<u n="889" who="S0271">just claim a monthly claim?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0270" trans="overlap">the hours I work</u>
<u n="891" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="892" who="S0270">yeah just I just claim the hours I work <pause dur="short"/> but we're missing a lot of these strategic management team that were involved when I was originally employed you see so they're all they fall fallen by the wayside if not officially left <pause dur="short"/> they're off on <pause dur="short"/>  erm sick leave</u>
<u n="893" who="S0266">and probably won't return</u>
<u n="894" who="S0270">I think so</u>
<u n="895" who="S0266">so what's morale like amongst the teachers that are there?</u>
<u n="896" who="S0270">erm well the new ones have lifted <pause dur="short"/> er the general atmosphere because they've come in with a completely new attitude</u>
<u n="897" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="898" who="S0270">because obviously they were it's now</u>
<u n="899" who="S0266">now an academy</u>
<u n="900" who="S0270">now yeah <pause dur="short"/> now an academy so they haven't had preconceived ideas there was we have someone who's been there for nearly twenty years who's still massively enthusiastic although she is forty</u>
<u n="901" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="902" who="S0270">so we've got all sorts but we've got some really good new young teachers and of course those who have been there a while had lots and lots of changes and I think they are the ones who are not particularly coping well but the ones the one who haven't coped at all well of course aren't actually there so no and I think we've got the new good head I think he's good at the moment he's really listening so that's important isn't it? I think he's got a massive task I so couldn't be him <pause dur="short"/> and we've got a lot of new faces I'm trying to introduce myself to them there's a lot of kind of very senior <trunc>peo</trunc></u>
<u n="903" who="S0271" trans="overlap">have to very big label <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="904" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="905" who="S0270">oh no they just don't bother to talk to me</u>
<u n="906" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I I'm the one who doesn't oh</u>
<u n="907" who="S0270" trans="overlap">so very senior people</u>
<u n="908" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0270">so I've been shaking hands today I thought no I'm actually going to do this I think it's really weird <pause dur="short"/> and I I do miss the status of being a teacher I do not have any status <pause dur="short"/> it's very weird and one of the sweet like Somali ladies was saying to me you know cos she's known me as a teacher I used to teach her son</u>
<u n="910" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="911" who="S0270">and er he's now moved on to his secondary school and she was saying you know erm and what are you doing? I said oh just the display <pause dur="short"/> at least it's a job</u>
<u n="912" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="913" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="914" who="S0270" trans="overlap">so sweet so sweet I thought I'm not going to go into this but I have actually retired and this is you know an option but they're so sweet <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it's interesting to see all these er ladies they've got a very dinner system at the moment where but we have employed so many people to help the dinner time along <pause dur="short"/> you know apart from all our dinner</u>
<u n="915" who="S0271" trans="overlap">with this new free school meals for infants</u>
<u n="916" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="917" who="S0266">yes tell <trunc>t</trunc>tell tell us</u>
<u n="918" who="S0270" trans="overlap">only for infants is it it's not going to be for juniors?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0271">it's reception reception year one and year two</u>
<u n="920" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="921" who="S0266">so everybody gets free school meals?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0270">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0266">and who cooks it?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0271">well it's where it's normally cooked</u>
<u n="925" who="S0266">just keep talking but I'll be back</u>
<u n="926" who="S0271">mm well</u>
<u n="927" who="S0266">in just one second</u>
<u n="928" who="S0271">our our meals are cooked at <anon type="place"/> primary school <pause dur="short"/> and the <trunc>peo</trunc></u>
<u n="929" who="S0266">and is it like airline meals?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0271">no it comes they serve them out onto plates <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="931" who="S0270">oh I see they they come but in large</u>
<u n="932" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they come in</u>
<u n="933" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0271">a big er a heat proof box</u>
<u n="935" who="S0270">mm mm</u>
<u n="936" who="S0271">and we've got a heated servery so they put the food in there <pause dur="short"/> and serve it out</u>
<u n="937" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="938" who="S0271">they've got those plastic plates have you got those? with compartments in them</u>
<u n="939" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="940" who="S0271">so they put puddings on with the</u>
<u n="941" who="S0270" trans="overlap">ours is cooked ours is cooked onsite <trunc>wi</trunc> yeah but we do have compartmentalised things yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0270">but ours are cooked onsite</u>
<u n="944" who="S0271">but</u>
<u n="945" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I didn't realise it wasn't going to involve the juniors</u>
<u n="946" who="S0271">no <pause dur="short"/> but erm we haven't got a huge take up you know</u>
<u n="947" who="S0270">mm?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0271">just over half because lots of young children are quite fussy <pause dur="short"/> the teacher was telling me today oh that one doesn't like sausages well if you don't even like sausages</u>
<u n="949" who="S0270">mm so they've come with their own</u>
<u n="950" who="S0271">they bring a lunchbox</u>
<u n="951" who="S0270" trans="overlap">erm yeah okay</u>
<u n="952" who="S0271" trans="overlap">they don't have to have it</u>
<u n="953" who="S0270">so they're having sandwiches yeah</u>
<u n="954" who="S0271" trans="overlap">so they can bring sandwiches and the other thing is if erm they've got an older sibling in the juniors it would mean if the young one had a cooked meal the older one would probably say I want a cooked meal and if you can't afford it <pause dur="short"/> you just give them both a lunchbox</u>
<u n="955" who="S0270">mm mm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0271">and the biggest take up did I tell you that? it's <anon type="place"/> where</u>
<u n="957" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="958" who="S0271" trans="overlap">where there are more wealthy parents so they're all</u>
<u n="959" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="960" who="S0271">having the lunches and</u>
<u n="961" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="962" who="S0271">the poor fussy children are not having them</u>
<u n="963" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="964" who="S0266">but why aren't they having them cos they don't like the food?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0271" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="966" who="S0270">may er they can</u>
<u n="967" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and they're fussy</u>
<u n="968" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but they could have those options they have the option of no</u>
<u n="969" who="S0271" trans="overlap">there is no option</u>
<u n="970" who="S0270">no come on er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it</u>
<u n="971" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but the thing is at home they probably eat quite a limited range of food <pause dur="short"/> so when it's something like I dunno lasagne or something they won't have it cos they've never had it at home</u>
<u n="972" who="S0266">so what do they eat?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0271">they bring a lunchbox in</u>
<u n="974" who="S0266">and what</u>
<u n="975" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah they're gonna have</u>
<u n="976" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and what's in the lunchbox?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0270" trans="overlap">they're gonna have sandwiches from home</u>
<u n="978" who="S0271">sandwiches and</u>
<u n="979" who="S0270">cos we've</u>
<u n="980" who="S0271" trans="overlap">rubbish food crisps and things</u>
<u n="981" who="S0270" trans="overlap">we've talked an awful lot at school about having healthy healthy lunchboxes</u>
<u n="982" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="983" who="S0270">masses and masses I'd like to do that again and start with the Start Write you know</u>
<u n="984" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I think I think the <trunc>m</trunc>money</u>
<u n="985" who="S0270">start for</u>
<u n="986" who="S0271" trans="overlap">all these billions that are being spent should have been spent on educating mothers on doing lunchboxes and helping them <pause dur="short"/> cook decent food at home rather than</u>
<u n="987" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="988" who="S0271">I don't know how you do it but rather</u>
<u n="989" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I remember being shamed er by you when you used to cook <pause dur="short"/> your er cereal bars for your children</u>
<u n="990" who="S0271">did I?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0266" trans="overlap">to put in their lunchbox yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0270">flapjacks</u>
<u n="993" who="S0266">cos I remember I</u>
<u n="994" who="S0270">was it? oh okay</u>
<u n="995" who="S0266" trans="overlap">cos I remember I no no healthy ones</u>
<u n="996" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="997" who="S0266">not even flapjacks cos I used to sometimes buy those</u>
<u n="998" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I don't remember doing healthy stuff</u>
<u n="999" who="S0266">you know the whatever it is you put in lunchboxes you buy what they want <pause dur="short"/> and I always noted that you when you were cooking</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0271">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was really <trunc>fuss</trunc></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0266" trans="overlap">very healthy</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0271">if they <trunc>wan</trunc> I was not a health freak with food I <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0266" trans="overlap">no but you were sensible</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0271">chocolate cake I used to make it every day cos that's all he liked</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0266">chocolate cake?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0271">yeah and he liked erm garlic sausage so he had garlic sausage sandwiches and chocolate cake every day</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0266">always the same?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0271">virtually <pause dur="short"/> no he didn't eat a green vegetable till he was about fifteen</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0266">gosh <pause dur="short"/> and how how tall is he now?</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0271">six six</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1013" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1014" who="S0266">ridiculous <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were you into</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0270">mm?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0266"><trunc>lunchbo</trunc>? I used to make my own children make their sandwiches <pause dur="short"/> from a very young age for a whole week on a Sunday and put them in the freezer</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0270">gosh terribly organised</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and then and then they had to get them out</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0270">yeah</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0266">in the <trunc>morn</trunc> er I don't know in the morning <pause dur="short"/> cos I thought I'm not gonna do this for sixteen years or something whatever it is</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah but also you were working</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0266">yeah I <trunc>th</trunc> erm I I it was quite hard <pause dur="short"/> on them</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0266">but</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0271">I wish I'd been firmer getting them to do jobs but they never <pause dur="short"/> I always gave in and did things</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0270">you're quite firm with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about doing jobs <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1028" who="S0271">he's quite happy to do it <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm going to work and he's at home <pause dur="short"/> you know he does all the cleaning and all the cooking</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0266">does he?</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0270">well not when he's actually doing a job which is a painting or whatever</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0271" trans="overlap">he well he was he was well he was painting</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0270" trans="overlap">that's a bit rough isn't it?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0271">four days a week and doing cleaning the house on the fifth day</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0270">but he would still be doing <pause dur="short"/> the cooking in the evening?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0271">he's been doing the cooking for <trunc>s</trunc> quite a few years now <pause dur="short"/> cos he likes cooking and he likes listening to The Archers so at seven o'clock he cooks a meal and listens to The Archers so it works quite well <pause dur="short"/> I clear up and do the shopping</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0270">mm oh so it's a good</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0271">and I do the laundry he is hanging stuff</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0271" trans="overlap">on the line now and getting it in folding it neatly</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0270">did he discover that himself or did you ask him to do it?</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0271">no he offers <pause dur="short"/> cos he feels sort of guilty I think <pause dur="short"/> it's alright</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0266">so what kind of menus do you have what sort of meals do you have?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0271">well I quite often have roast on Sunday and then have some heated up <pause dur="short"/> we had a curry on Saturday which he made</u>
<u n="1045" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hi</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0270">hiya</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0271">heated that up when I</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0270" trans="overlap">are you gonna come and join in?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0266">you must be hungry</u>
<u n="1050" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er no I'll eat something later dear when you're finished</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0266">oh no okay</u>
<u n="1052" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<event desc="begin overlap"/>
<u n="1053" who="S0270">hello come on then come in and cook</u>
<u n="1054" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well I'm no I'll be in in a minute</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0270">okay</u>
<u n="1056" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what's she say on there?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0270"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1058" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<event desc="end overlap"/>
<u n="1059" who="S0271">we had Polish sausages we have casseroles he makes <pause dur="short"/> erm or get <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1060" who="S0266">always advertising</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0271">chops and things we always have meat virtually every day cos his Polish meat</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0270" trans="overlap">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> likes his meat</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I do</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0271">always</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0270" trans="overlap">a lot of cooking for two days on my own</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0271">well that's two days that's quite often it's it's good that</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0270">mm I find when you have people round for supper as I did on Saturday you cook far too much and then you can eat the rest of it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0270">for a long time afterwards <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1071" who="S0271">mm some days</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I'm very into garlic <pause dur="short"/> garlic mushrooms and then these you know cos I can't have pasta now only this pretend stuff which is quite ghastly it's really really solid it's quite horrible erm I've started erm using the courgettes as pretend linguini which is it linguini? whichever that pasta is so you shave them and erm you just cook it all in the pan it's absolutely awesome <pause dur="short"/> and if you want meat you can add bits of bacon which is very nice <pause dur="short"/> it's actually very quick and very easy so it's garlic mushrooms and then <pause dur="short"/> a courgette</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0271">mushrooms can be tricky</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0271">eating I don't know if I can actually eat them really</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0270">mm?</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0271">I think I get aching bones when I eat mushrooms</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0270">mm? I'm alright with those it sounds like it's the yeast in it</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0271">yeah I think so I <pause dur="short"/> cos we we usually have mushrooms for breakfast on Saturday and Sundays</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1081" who="S0271">I found that</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you're very particular with your meals aren't you? do you organise them when you go shopping once a week sort of thing?</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0270">mm I'm much more</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0271" trans="overlap">we always have a fried breakfast on Saturday and Sundays</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm I'm much more about what is the yellow label or what's the deal at the time</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0271">well I do buy deals and put them in the freezer</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0270">and then you can plan them in for your next time</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0270">terribly organised <pause dur="short"/> I'm not actually that organised really but I don't have to be anymore I am when my family is about <pause dur="short"/> but I don't have to be</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0271">so what sort of things do you eat then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how long's this got to be on for?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0266">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> as long as we want to talk you're ready for another glass of wine I can see</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0270" trans="overlap">no I'm not I've had enough</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0266">well I'll give you some lemonade <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0271">do you plan or do you just go to the shop and get something?</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0266">both really</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0271">mm <pause dur="long"/> we we</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I'm quite into cooking when I've got time at the moment</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0271">I'm not because I've <pause dur="short"/> not been practised</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and not so much meat I don't really like <pause dur="short"/> a lot of meat</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0270">I'm having fish</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0266">I like good meat</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I've been told to have more oily fish</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0266">where do you buy your meat?</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0271">I quite I think the meat in Sainsbury's isn't too bad their steak and erm joints and things in the butcher's counter</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0270">well I do eat a bit of <unclear/></u>
<u n="1108" who="S0271">they're quite expensive</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0266">yeah I I do sometimes but</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0266">we don't eat meat more than twice a week</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0271" trans="overlap">no don't you?</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0270">don't you? what do you have instead fish?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well we eat fish fish</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah I like fish</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0266">and then sometimes if I do</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0270" trans="overlap">well you've still got to find something</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0266">sort of erm I dunno stuffed aubergines or <pause dur="short"/> stuffed vegetables <pause dur="short"/> those <trunc>ki</trunc> I like those kind of</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0266">in the summer</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0270">mm <pause dur="short"/> I I love it's not that I don't love vegetables she told me to increase my vegetables by a hundred percent <pause dur="short"/> it's just I find</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0266" trans="overlap">who did you go to? did you go to</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0270" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0266" trans="overlap">that same lady that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes to?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0270">mm I did because I couldn't get I had been going to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for years actually even though I</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0266" trans="overlap">to who?</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0270"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0270">for years</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0266">is that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s woman?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0270">no but I couldn't get in an appointment with her she got to be so difficult and I rang <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she could see me <pause dur="short"/> so I'm I'm now with her</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0266" trans="overlap">cos she's supposed to be very good isn't she?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0270">she's great I know erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't believe in it but I feel much better</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I don't believe in it at all</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0270">you don't have to</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0271">and</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0266">I do cos I see how well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is from</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0266">keeping off</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0271">well I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s better because she's not working</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0266">no I well I don't know about that</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0270">she has masses of other serious <trunc>med</trunc> er medical issues <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well what sort of</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well she's just too busy in life</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0270">mm oh yeah</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0266" trans="overlap">she she should slow down</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0270">yeah but she takes she takes joy in it though <pause dur="short"/> doesn't she?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0266">erm</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0270" trans="overlap">she takes pleasure out of</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0266">yeah I just think sometimes she gets</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0270" trans="overlap">pleasure out of a lot of things grandchildren and stuff</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0266">yeah but she gets onto all these committees and she</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm but then</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0271">it's too much</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but she chooses to do that</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0266" trans="overlap">chapel and church</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0270">she chooses to do that</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0266">yeah but I don't think she should</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0270">oh I see I see what you mean</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0266">you know go along and enjoy it but not erm organise it which is <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm you need some people who just likes organising don't they</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0266">I never see her cos she's always erm</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0270">well we could never see you you were always busy</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0266">ah but that's because I'm working</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0266">but she kind of retired through <pause dur="short"/> ill health</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0271" trans="overlap">health and</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0270">and then</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0266">and should really be slowing down and</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0271">but she's been better since she retired though hasn't she?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and enjoy her life</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0270" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0271">with her aching muscles and things</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0270">thank you well that's also because she's changed her diet which you don't believe in but it has made a difference to her</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0271" trans="overlap">not at all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1178" who="S0270">it has made a difference</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0266" trans="overlap">no I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>yo</trunc> you must agree that perhaps you never eat unhealthy</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0271">well I do I</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0266" trans="overlap">food</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0271">I eat meat all the time don't I?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0266">well that's not necessarily unhealthy but if you were to eat lots of cream cakes and biscuits for a whole day</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I'd get fat</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0266">well it's not only that you'd feel</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0270">you would feel differently</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0266">differently and it's just that you don't do it so that when you have someone who has a pretty bad or probably a very healthy diet but supplements it with</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to eat loads of chocolate I don't know if she still does</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> then if you haven't experienced that you probably don't realise how bad how ill you can sometimes feel if you're not</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0271">but what I don't understand is</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0266" trans="overlap">eating healthy food</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0271" trans="overlap">what sort of test if the medical profession</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0270">thank you</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0271">can't test for it how can these quacks test for it?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0270">well you've straight away judged them by calling them a quack haven't you? So</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0271">yeah but how do they test it?</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you've already decided</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0271">I mean</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0270">they are as medically and</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0271" trans="overlap">a proper</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0270">they are as medically qualified in a different way</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0271">but if <trunc>th</trunc> if real doctors can't test for it how can people like that test for it?</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0270">yeah but if your doctor is</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0271" trans="overlap">that's what I don't understand</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0266">but doctors probably can</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0270" trans="overlap">there are just different kind of doctors</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but they just can't be you know they haven't got the the resources to do it</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0271" trans="overlap">you get allergy doctors and people <pause dur="short"/> cos I've been to them</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0266">mm but this isn't allergies <pause dur="long"/> is it?</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0270">cos it's more serious than that</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0266">if you go to an allergy doctor it's to see if you're</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0270" trans="overlap">if you if you were to eat a food that rushed straight through your body and made it impossible for you to leave home you would stop eating it wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0271">er probably but I might think I've got Crohn's disease or something like that</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0270">I think she's been tested for those things <pause dur="short"/> and she's proved okay so then she's gone off to find out what it is that's caused all these things and it's extremely erm <pause dur="short"/> difficult to function isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> that's what caused <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to go this and it's exactly the same with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it just rushes straight through her body you can't go to work you can't leave home <pause dur="short"/> so you stop eating those foods so there is definitely a reason for you to do it <pause dur="short"/> this definitely affects your body</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0271">and that's gluten in wheat?</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0270">yes it's wheat</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0270">and</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but everybody can't be allergic to gluten which is what it sounds like in <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1221" who="S0266" trans="overlap">no but it's a new phenomenon it's now isn't it? it's all it's er</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but every it wouldn't be possible for everybody to be allergic to gluten</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0266">but we didn't have <pause dur="short"/> erm gluten did we in wheat?</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0270">erm</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0266">I thought I thought it was because it's imported from <pause dur="short"/> canada?</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0270" trans="overlap">it's because yes because America has been erm</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0266" trans="overlap">America</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0270">and they've been supplementing all these you know like when you buy a erm an oatcake if you look on it you'll see that actually it contains wheat now and that's because it's much cheaper to produce</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0271">but this gluten</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but isn't it tampered with? erm if you go to sort of countries that are growing their own wheat</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0270">mm I suspect if you were yeah doing</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and if you eat bread there you're absolutely fine</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0270" trans="overlap">organically or yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0271">but people have trouble with bread here because they don't let it rise properly do they <pause dur="short"/> and it's not properly the yeast is not</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0270">it has preservatives in it all sorts of things</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0271">and it's got all sorts of things in it</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0270">mm that's what <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="1238" who="S0271" trans="overlap">that's not the flour it's the</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0270" trans="overlap">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s saying</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0271" trans="overlap">it's the way it's made rather than what it actually is</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0270">if you aren't having trouble with any foods then it's fine but if you if you're</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well I probably am</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but if you're</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0266">well you're not</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0270">but if you</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0266">because you're not rushing to the loo all the time</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0271">I do sometimes if I've got</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but that isn't the that isn't the only consequence <pause dur="short"/> that isn't the only consequence that isn't the consequence for me <pause dur="short"/> I thought I had a very serious disease actually I don't think it I don't find it at all funny that I thought that <pause dur="short"/> I actually felt really very ill so I went to see her and I took those things out of my diet and I felt a great deal better</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0271" trans="overlap">so what did she test you with to prove it?</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0270">erm well</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well why do they they don't need to test you do I mean I I</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0270" trans="overlap">ask you all sorts of questions for a start</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0266" trans="overlap">surely you can just start eating</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I mean they'd just tell everybody they're allergic this is just taking the <trunc>oppos</trunc> they tell everyone they're allergic to gluten they they virtually take everything out of their diet and that's really bad cos you should be eating a balanced diet of a bit of everything not take great chunks out of your diet</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah that's if you're if you that's if you're inverted commas normal but if you has a have a <trunc>suscept</trunc> I mean some people it's like dairy <pause dur="short"/> if</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0266" trans="overlap">they drink cow's milk</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><trunc>m</trunc>medical</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0266" trans="overlap">they</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0271">doctors</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0266">feel ill</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0271">will say <trunc>th</trunc> lots of people are lactose intolerant that</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0271" trans="overlap">can be tested can't it though <pause dur="short"/> I understand that cos people like Japanese people can't <pause dur="short"/> eat dairy can they?</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0266">no</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0271">cos they can't digest it genetically</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you know your</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0271">can't digest it</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you know your daughter in law is very <pause dur="short"/> erm what what is it that they eat in Korea?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0271">Kimchi</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0270">yeah so she doesn't like to do without it and that's what's <pause dur="short"/> I think happened in a</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0271" trans="overlap">that's <trunc>pro</trunc> <trunc>b</trunc> probiotic</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0270">that's what's er I think</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0271" trans="overlap">gets rid of the bacteria</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0270" trans="overlap">what's happened in western diets is that there's an awful lot of wheat in it <pause dur="short"/> an awful lot of milk</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0266">and dairy</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0270">erm I bought I was bought up entirely on erm masses and masses of all that sort of stuff we had loads of <unclear>eggs</unclear> and loads of milk <pause dur="short"/> and I do notice if I drink cow's milk now very seriously only eat cow's cheese</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0271">well you might be lactose intolerant which could be tested properly that would prove it to you</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0270" trans="overlap">well fine I don't mind if I am tested properly</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0270">I'm quite happy with the present testing but yes</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0266">but also the milk that you were drinking as a child would have come straight from the farm</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0270">mm okay</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0266">but you know you you look at the milk you're buying nowadays</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0266">goodness knows what</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0270">it still was I think it was</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0266" trans="overlap">happens to it</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0270" trans="overlap">only tuberculosis tested I don't think it was anything else and then it would just go through the cooler and be</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0266">yeah and you'd drink it</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0270" trans="overlap">yeah pasteurised it wasn't I guess was it none of those things</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0271">there was something on television a couple of nights ago and they testing <trunc>past</trunc>pasteurised milk and unpasteurised and the bacteria on the slide with the unpasteurised it was just covered in bacteria <pause dur="short"/> but I think maybe we all got used to eating that sort of</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0271" trans="overlap">bacteria</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0271">when we were younger and now</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you do need certain</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0271">if we tried to eat it</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0270">you do need certain</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0271">probably couldn't now</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0266">well it's like all these allergies people who have got asthma and erm <pause dur="short"/> all these things</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0271">but maybe people always had it but there was</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but young kids that no I think cos when we were just</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0271" trans="overlap">outside</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you know we we were outside we played on the floor in filth we ate</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0266" trans="overlap">filth ate worms even</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0266">I was a child and now they're so overprotected</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and why</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0266">and <trunc>every</trunc> you know everything's hoovered and cleaned and</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0271">why are people</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0266" trans="overlap">all this</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0271" trans="overlap">allergic to peanuts when people in places like Malaysia where they eat peanuts in everything <pause dur="short"/> they're not allergic to them?</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0271">why are British babies and children can't eat peanuts?</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0270">well there are children in my school that are allergic to peanuts who are not British</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0271">I know so <pause dur="short"/> how come <pause dur="short"/> some are and some aren't?</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0270">but that has a very serious consequence it's not just a question of</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well it can kill you</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0270">exactly so if you have that kind of shock <pause dur="short"/> then it's good that you have cut it out</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0271">but we didn't hear about that when we were children did we?</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0266">no</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0270">well maybe we didn't know the cause of that shock did we? If someone had died in that way like having a bee sting that you're <pause dur="short"/> allergic to we didn't know the cause of it I guess we would know that but maybe not with peanuts I mean if you go back would they have even been a?</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and how many peanuts did did we have in our childhood?</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0270" trans="overlap">wouldn't have been in our diet</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0271">we probably didn't have peanuts but then we</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0270" trans="overlap">and so they wouldn't have been in our diet</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0271" trans="overlap">we didn't have peanuts butter but lots of people did have peanut butter didn't they?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0266">I remember having peanut butter</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0270">what as a child?</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0266">well teens I think it came in</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0270">I don't remember it all you see my</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0271">I don't remember peanuts or</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0270">my <unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0266">or perhaps a student <pause dur="short"/> peanut butter on toast</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0271">but we used to eat far</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0270" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0271">we used to eat a lot of carbohydrates because we used to have cooked puddings at school</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0271">and at home</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but we used to do a lot of sport</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0271" trans="overlap">erm cakes</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and exercising</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0271">and</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0266">and walking</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0271">biscuits</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0270">that's right we were busy weren't we?</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0271">we didn't eat as many things as things like crisps</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0266">well there weren't crisps really were there?</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0271">there were with the little blue bags in it</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0266">oh and the salt packet <pause dur="short"/> yeah but they were a special treat</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0271">they were a special treat</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0270">that's right</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0266">they weren't every day</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0270">I think that's the difference</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and I think pizzas are really</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0270" trans="overlap">is that we didn't have so many treats</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0271" trans="overlap">bad for people the they're fattening</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0266">what?</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0271">pizza</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0271">I think that's why kids are fat</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0270" trans="overlap">do you not make them anymore? <pause dur="short"/> you used to make your own</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0271">mm I used to make them for children but <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's nothing in them that's particularly good <pause dur="short"/> the stuff you buy it the shops <pause dur="short"/> it's not even real cheese on them</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0270">mm if you make your own it would be better but it's still</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well I used to make my own</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0270">still lots of erm carbs isn't it rather than too much anything else <pause dur="short"/> they are lovely though if they're homemade</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0271" trans="overlap">we used to eat we used to eat <pause dur="short"/> toast and dripping</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0271">in fact you still get that in Poland they give it to you as erm a free kind of starter bread with a dripping pot with erm bits of meat erm</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1377" who="S0271">at the bottom it's really nice</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0270">mm my dad used to save all the meat <pause dur="short"/> for dripping</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0271" trans="overlap">but it's a cold country in the winter</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0271">so people need to eat fat</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0270"><trunc>peo</trunc> I remember mum saying that people used to come to the door for fat</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0270" trans="overlap">from erm <anon type="place"/> erm the prisoners of war used to come and try and exchange things they'd made for fat <pause dur="short"/> and of course farmers still had a bit of fat you were allowed every so often to kill a pig and things like that must have been quite ghastly though mustn't it? we are very lucky probably</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but probably very healthy</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0271">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mother came to Britain because of a bucket of fat</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0270">really?</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0271">cos you know her wartime travels don't you?</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0271">I've told you that you know prisoner in Siberia and in recent years we found out that she had to travel down through Kazakhstan lost at least one child if not two and ended up in Africa in a hospital working and they had the choice of going to America Britain or back to Poland and she had to come to Britain because she'd got a bucket of fat that she could take on the boat</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0266">that she'd saved up</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0271" trans="overlap">been saving</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0266">what and only the boat would allow it?</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0271">mm couldn't take it on a plane could she to America</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0270">I really admire her endurance</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0266">would they have gone on planes in those days?</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0271">oh they probably wouldn't would they? they'd gone on a <trunc>ferr</trunc> they'd have gone on a Queen Mary type thing wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0271">whatever it was that's when</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but she was only allowed to take it to Britain</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0271">whatever it was I can't remember the details now but</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0271">she had a very tough life</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0270">has any of it been written down?</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0271">erm their <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did do some internet <pause dur="short"/> research and found I mean there have been people putting stuff on the internet about similar people that did similar things and did I tell you that erm in her papers there were some bits of Russian on on some bits of paper so the friend in <unclear/> daughter speaks Russian and so she translated it and one of them was a death certificate of one of her children died in Kazakhstan <pause dur="short"/> but she always said she had a baby on the train that died on the train <pause dur="short"/> so whether she'd had the baby that died on the train <pause dur="short"/> and then er she she was living in Kazakhstan for a bit I think this child it said on it she died of pneumonia</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0270">bless her</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0270">so in the end she had had more children but in the end there was</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0270"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his sister</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I did say to her once what was the name of your baby? and she couldn't remember she went <trunc>M</trunc>Maria whether she was making it up or not</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0271">I don't know</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0266">who was this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0271"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mother</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0266">mother?</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0266">so by the time she came to Britain and settled how was she when she had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0271">erm</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0266">so these are actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sisters?</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0271">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister's older than him so she's born in forty-nine <pause dur="short"/> and she <trunc>wa</trunc> she was born in nineteen fourteen <pause dur="short"/> so she was thirty-five mm</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0270">mm and what happened</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1430" who="S0270">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s father at this point he was still <trunc>ar</trunc> around? were they?</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well the story of the war was they were living in eastern Poland and the Russians were on the other side and they took them prisoners and they were going to shoot <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s father cos he worked as a land agent in a uniform and they thought he was a soldier and he dug his own grave and she just begged the Russians to save him so they took them prisoners and they went off to Siberia <pause dur="short"/> for a while don't know how long and did speaks of having no shoes and erm this baby that died on a train and then there was the course of the war the Russians became allies and there were Polish soldiers were fighting they formed an army erm fighting with the allies and the men went down to north Africa <pause dur="short"/> and fought and <pause dur="short"/> they travelled up through Italy and they fought at the battle of Monte Cassino one of the worst battles of the war and he actually lost touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mother <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>sh</trunc> the women went all through Kazakhstan she never mentioned it must have been overland somewhere or other to erm north Africa <pause dur="short"/> and worked in a hospital there and then they got back together the Red Cross put them back together I suppose there were lots of displaced people the Red Cross were</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0271">doing things like that</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0266">so where were they reunited in</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and I think it must have been in this country don't know where or how cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never asked her any questions when she was alive</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0270">what a shame</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0271">too late</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0270">mm <pause dur="short"/> but even things that that I thought I would never forget about my father</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0270">I have</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0270">they've got muddled it's really frustrating you should write it down</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah we should write it down</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0270" trans="overlap">cos mm what an amazing</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0271">and there are</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0270">family though</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0271">on the internet you can find ships with the lists of the passengers on them that came back they can't find a name on <pause dur="short"/> any of those <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0271">she was a happy person didn't have to go to a counsellor</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0270">mm she was probably grateful for each day</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0271" trans="overlap">bad arthritis possibly from being in the cold in Siberia I don't know</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0270">but if you've lived through all that</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I think she just didn't look backwards</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0270">yeah but in if you live through all that you are going to <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1455" who="S0271" trans="overlap">lived for for the children <pause dur="short"/> she always seemed quite a happy person</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0270"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought a lot of her didn't he?</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0266">well I think also here they were very welcoming to Poles</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0266">so there wasn't this sort of erm</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0271">well they'd fought for this country</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0266" trans="overlap">problem of being foreigners or whatever</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and my family's connection with them was that erm have I told you about my mother and a Pole?</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0266">no</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in the war in <anon type="place"/> my grandfather worked as a civilian mechanic at the local airbase and lots of Polish pilots were based there so he used to invite them back to tea at weekends and she met this Pole that and there's this big question mark she was married then <pause dur="short"/> did she have an affair</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0270">thank you</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0271">with him or not? and the we've got her diaries with and <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0266">this is your mother then?</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0271">this is my mother <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1471" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she always spoke about them being so polite which they are erm gentlemen because the the fighter pilots were er the upper class people cos they were the ones that could fight could fly <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> so when I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they met him down at the hospital in Taunton when my sister was there in hospital and my dad said on the phone he's a nice guy <pause dur="short"/> what's his other name? so I went er <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> what sort of name is that then? erm it's Polish <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1472" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1473" who="S0271">cos he was always making nasty remarks about Poles all through our young life</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0270">cos of your mother?</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0271">and he was they had a fight he'd say and what were you doing in nineteen forty-two?</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1477" who="S0271">it cropped up all the time when we were young</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0271">they were always fighting <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't good</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0271">but they stayed together</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0266">and accepted <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1484" who="S0271">yeah they liked him</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0271">my dad said to me he's too good for you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1487" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0271">it's usually the other way round isn't it?</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm so where did you meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in Taunton in the hospital?</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0271">no no no that I was going out with him then and he was down for the weekend or something and we went to see my sister no we lived in I lived in London in a house and there was a party over the road <pause dur="short"/> and he <pause dur="short"/> his friend knew the guy who was giving the party so we met at this party <pause dur="short"/> he'd met another woman the week before and it was a toss of the coin who he phoned up</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1493" who="S0271">he came in and I seemed to rather like tall blonde blokes I'd had a tall blonde German boyfriend and my friend said to me he looks your type you could probably make him lose weight</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1495" who="S0271">never managed that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1496" who="S0271">so that's where we met <pause dur="short"/> and then when his father died he got <pause dur="short"/> a job down here he wanted to come down here <trunc>work</trunc>worked for a place where he'd worked as as a student <pause dur="short"/> and so we came down here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1497" who="S0270">locations usually are decided by work aren't they?</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0270">which is why I'm always amused that you know people get qualified as teachers or whatever and expect to work</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm locally</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0270">yeah and it you know I I who would have thought I would have ended up in London it so wasn't anywhere I had ever planned to go and not live and work <pause dur="short"/> but we both got jobs there you see so that was that</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0271">it's difficult for young professionals now isn't it that if you're both got a job the chances are you're not gonna find one in the same place are you?</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0271">unless you're very lucky</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0266">mm that's right</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0271">what does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do?</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0266">erm <pause dur="short"/> he's a sort of like a head hunter in oil and gas</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0271">mm so he's in oil and gas</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0266" trans="overlap">he works for a <trunc>Nor</trunc> is it Norwegian is it Norway that's hot on that? a Norwegian company</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0270" trans="overlap">so recruitment like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1511" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0270">only in a different area</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0266">suppose so</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0271">mm well both of mine work in oil and gas <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was working for a Norwegian company</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0266">oh right it must be Norway then yeah</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0271" trans="overlap">and the</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0266">he spends a lot of time going up to <anon type="place"/> is it <anon type="place"/> or is it?</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0271"><anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0266"><anon type="place"/> yeah and he flies up and down there <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0271" trans="overlap">so he's recruiting what people for the oil rigs and things?</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0266">no well no no no the really top top top people</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0266">I think</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0271">how did he get into that was he business studies or something you need or?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0266">no cos he did sport I think</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0271">oh</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0266">he's a he's a sportsman</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0271">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0266">really</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0271">I think Norwegians cos they've had oil and gas for a long time haven't they? They <pause dur="short"/> I mean they've probably got companies all over the world <pause dur="short"/> now</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0266">mm this was a a small <trunc>comp</trunc> a big company in Norway that set up a <pause dur="short"/> branch in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1532" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0266">and I think he was recruited then because then they flew they were very nice they flew all well all of them I think about six of them</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0266">over to Norway for a weekend treated them <pause dur="short"/> really well</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0266">yeah they went for meals and dinners where you had fifteen courses and you have to eat all sorts of</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> interesting things</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0266">interesting things</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0266">and erm and they're into sport so they'd have to go on sort of <pause dur="short"/> thirty mile bike rides and skiing and</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0271" trans="overlap">cos they do all this overland skiing don't they?</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0271">and not down hills over</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0271">land</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0266">then they come over here and do really boring things <pause dur="short"/> like erm quadbike racing and things cos <pause dur="short"/> I suppose we haven't got the facilities here for more exciting things mm talking about sport today</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0270">it came through the Tour of Britain</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0266">absolutely</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0271"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0270">I can't</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0266" trans="overlap">went in to see it</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0270">I know I can't believe</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0270">I didn't realise it was today</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0270">I'd have changed my work day</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0270">if I'd known</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0271">where did you go?</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0266">I didn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went and I'm</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0271">did he go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0266" trans="overlap">really glad I didn't go well we were either gonna go to <anon type="place"/> cos it was uphill</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0271">mm mm</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0266">we thought it would be slower to watch or <anon type="place"/> going up <anon type="place"/> out of <anon type="place"/> up the hill there and I in the end I didn't I didn't go he went to <anon type="place"/> well by <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1566" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0266">but I watched it on the telly</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0266">and it was absolutely fascinating I watched them all the way</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I've watched it on the news but not from</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0266" trans="overlap">from erm I I recognised it when they went through <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1572" who="S0270">excuse me</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0266">and then watched</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0271" trans="overlap">was it <anon type="place"/>? <anon type="place"/> wasn't it yeah?</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0266"><trunc>ye</trunc> er <anon type="place"/> yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1576" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0266">and then er they dropped down to <anon type="place"/> and then it was <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1579" who="S0270">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1580" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0270">I recognised that one</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0271">yeah they had that on the telly didn't they?</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and all the beautiful woods along the escarpment</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0266">and then down to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1587" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0266">and <anon type="place"/> was absolutely packed every school you passed</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I cannot believe I didn't do</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0266" trans="overlap">the village school there were loads of kids outside</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0271" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to the <trunc>memoria</trunc> you know the war memorial</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0266">oh did it gets packed with people there</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0271">it wasn't he didn't think it was too busy</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0266">well it made the they actually the people made the route because</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0271">no they had they didn't go round the memorial</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0266">no no</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0271">the route was just</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0266">straight up yeah</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0271"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0266">but the the people made the curve of the</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0266">track <pause dur="short"/> and the only place where they had</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0271" trans="overlap">he took he took quite a few photos</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0266" trans="overlap">parked cars <pause dur="short"/> was up that road from the war memorial</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0266">they obviously couldn't move them</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0271">cos people park overnight there I suppose to</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0266">I don't know what they do</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0270">can't even park outside there <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1611" who="S0266" trans="overlap">always</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0271">is there always cars there?</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0266" trans="overlap">always cars</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0270">it's always <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1615" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it was the only place the whole <trunc>ti</trunc> I was watching for about an hour and it was the only place</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0266">where you can actually</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0266">see cars on the road</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0270">I'm so cross that I didn't</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0270">realise that it was today</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but it was very <pause dur="short"/> it was such a beautiful</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0266">er day in a way</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I think he saw Bradley because he's got a beard now hasn't he?</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0270">yes</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0271">and one of his photos you can see somebody with a beard</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0271">he took quite a few photos</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0266">and then I did you watch the end when they went up erm</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0266"><anon type="place"/> road and onto there</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0271" trans="overlap">oh yes I saw that yeah</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0266">and followed the</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I didn't</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0266" trans="overlap">suspension bridge up to the park?</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I didn't I didn't see who</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0270" trans="overlap">who won it?</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0271" trans="overlap">it was a Pole</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0266">yeah erm</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah I can't think of his name now</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0266">yeah it was but this is only the leg isn't it?</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0270">yeah</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0266">erm they're off to Devon tomorrow</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0271">did you see in the paper they think it was er probably a Pole who was er Jack the Ripper?</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0270">no</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0271">well someone's written a book they've done DNA testing on a shawl of one of the victims and <pause dur="short"/> relatives and things</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0270">mm golly</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0266">no you missed</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0266">an epic erm</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0270">I am very very erm disappointed</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0266" trans="overlap">thing</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0270">that I didn't do it</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0266">it it it was just really nice to see</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0270">I don't know what what land I was in</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0271" trans="overlap">it was such a nice day as well</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm and every school there were kids outside with flags and things</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0271" trans="overlap">did you see they've done all that knitting those that erm</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0266"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do finish these if you want</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0271" trans="overlap">knitted little erm</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0270">mm thank you</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0271">tops in <anon type="place"/> or somewhere to make <pause dur="short"/> bunting out of tops</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0271">is it?</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0266">he didn't know where it was but there the erm commentators were absolutely useless <pause dur="short"/> had no idea and he was saying that</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0266">when they were in <anon type="place"/> they were up in some other place <anon type="place"/> er it was he was miles out</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0271">last night on HTV they they said about it and they <trunc>sai</trunc> they did little maps Stroud Dursley Bristol</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1678" who="S0266">it didn't go anywhere near <trunc>Br</trunc></u>
<u n="1679" who="S0271">Dursley yeah</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0266" trans="overlap">Dursley</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0271">no</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0266">went right through Stroud that was</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0271" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0266">interesting to watch</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0270">I'm really really cross that I wasn't</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and they went you know it was so nice they were all whizzing</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0270" trans="overlap">stood on the side of the road somewhere</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0266">they were all driving right on the</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0271" trans="overlap">it goes so quick</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0266" trans="overlap">right hand side of the road</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0266">and then they were going round the roundabouts the wrong way <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0266">some roundabouts they were going both sides of the roundabout</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0266">the right and the left</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1698" who="S0271">they go so fast</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0266">yeah and then there was a bloke who had a double puncture <pause dur="short"/> and do you know how they <trunc>ch</trunc> er they changed two tyres in er just over a minute</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0271">and is that the team?</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0266">yeah the car that follows behind</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0266">they literally he</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0270" trans="overlap">extraordinary isn't it?</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0266" trans="overlap">unclipped it</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0266">and then the bloke got out the back</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0266">with a new wheel and put it on and then</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0270" trans="overlap">amazing</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0266" trans="overlap">he drove off</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0266">and the back one had gone as well so and he was in the lead I think</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0266">and he would have won if he hadn't had that <pause dur="short"/> it I think it's terribly dangerous it looks very dangerous because <pause dur="short"/> erm they're going very fast</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0266">and if people</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0270" trans="overlap">their speeds</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0266">aren't kept back you know it's up to you</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0266" trans="overlap">to to get out the way</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0271" trans="overlap">well old erm Froom had an accident didn't he in the Tour de France is it Froom? Froom?</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0266">what happened?</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0270">not not</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0271" trans="overlap">he he</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0270" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0271" trans="overlap">fell off he broke his shoulder or something didn't he?</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0266">well why did he fall off?</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0270">he crashed into things</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0271" trans="overlap">he crashed into somebody</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0266">what on a cyclist?</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0270" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0266" trans="overlap">or a pedestrian?</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0271">a cyclist I think you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had an accident on her bike in the summer?</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0266">no</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0271">yeah she had <pause dur="short"/> cos she's in training for the world championships in Hawaii next month</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0266">are you going out to watch her?</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0271" trans="overlap">she's qualified for that no <pause dur="short"/> she's qualified for that but erm she was on a cycle path quite a long way out of Perth so you know it's just beside the freeway so nobody around and a tree had come down so to avoid it she just sort of skidded and fell on the ground and she cut her knee sort of like like that she could see the bone</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0271">great big cut as big as that and so she phoned up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was out kite surfing didn't answer his phone phoned her friend didn't answer and then luckily a couple of people came along on bikes and they phoned the ambulance <pause dur="short"/> which got there just at the same time as her friend actually got there to pick up a bike so she was in hospital overnight and had to have an operation to sew it up</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0271"><trunc>te</trunc> twelve stiches</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0266">was that before or after the wedding?</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0271">it that was in only about a month ago</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0266">oh right mm gosh</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0271">so</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0270">but she's fit and well enough to be</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0271">she's so</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0270">resume training?</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0271">so the hospital said she erm it's three weeks before the stitches come she phoned us up she only ever phones if there's something bad I'm in hospital <pause dur="short"/> and she'd already phoned her coach before she phoned us and the coach said I'll get you to see a sports doctor the hospitals always give you a black picture of things so she saw a sports doctor within ten days he'd took the stiches out and had her swimming again and erm <pause dur="short"/> and she was when she was the first week she was on a bike and you could see the bike behind her in the living room cycling with one leg <pause dur="short"/>  cos she's on this strict training programme for the championships <pause dur="short"/> so she got a bit behind</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0266">so what what's she doing what erm sports what?</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0271">Ironman</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0266">right which is?</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0271">twenty-<trunc>si</trunc> no it's a two mile swim <pause dur="short"/> I think it's erm a hundred and twenty miles on the bike something like that and then a marathon</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0270">they don't mean a hundred and twenty miles do they?</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0271">yeah they do</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0270">what a hundred and twenty kilometres? both of them are ridiculous amounts</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0271" trans="overlap">no I think it's miles</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0270">yeah? wow</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0271">takes about ten hours</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0266">and where's she doing that? where are the championships?</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0271">Hawaii</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0266">is that world championship?</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0271">world championships you have to <trunc>qualif</trunc></u>
<u n="1768" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so who is she representing is she representing</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0271" trans="overlap">Australia</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0266">has she got an Australian passport?</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0266">and a British</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0266">she kept her British</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0270">so</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0271">she said <pause dur="short"/> she says Britain put her off sport <pause dur="short"/> australia has given the opportunity to do sport <pause dur="short"/> so that's why she does it for Australia</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0270">well that's circumstances really not nothing that</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0271" trans="overlap">mm but you know school sport if you're not that good at it puts you off doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0270">mm but it's the opportunity to do something I think the weather in Australia</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0271" trans="overlap">I mean she could have</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0270">for a start</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0271">she yeah the weather I mean maybe if she <pause dur="short"/> bikes had been</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0271">a thing when they were young she might have done that she always she did go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1787" who="S0270">she certainly did I remember</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0270">very awesome swimmer <pause dur="short"/> so there's how long is the run then?</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0271">a marathon? twenty-six miles</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0270">oh right it's very serious isn't it?</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0266">and swimming is that in the sea or?</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0271">in the sea <pause dur="short"/> that's what does it</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but it can be in a lake can't it?</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0271">it can be in a lake when she was in Las Vegas last year it was in a lake <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0270" trans="overlap">she did very well there didn't she?</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0266" trans="overlap">have you been to see her yet in any of the races?</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0271">erm we did see her do something in Australia <pause dur="short"/> but she went to Taiwan in March in a race she's tenth in the world in her age group</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0266">is she?</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0266">gosh</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0270">pretty awesome</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0266">that's amazing</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0271">that was last year's figures yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0270" trans="overlap">but you've seen her unexpectedly a lot this year haven't you?</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0270">she was saying it's put out the the schedule for going over cos you've had the wedding</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0271" trans="overlap">because she's uses her holiday up to go to these races and things</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0266">well does she get sponsored?</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0271">her coach would like her to go professional but you know that's difficult isn't it living on that when you've got a mortgage and everything? <pause dur="short"/> so you know</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but does the government pay for her</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0271">no</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0266">air fares or?</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0271">no</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0266">nothing?</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0271">no</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0266">cos surely even in this country we pay</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0271">no if you're not a professional</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0266" trans="overlap">the athletes pay</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0271">she does beat professionals quite often <pause dur="short"/> mm I don't know how she'll do cos she's had these two weeks where she wasn't training properly <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0266" trans="overlap">brilliant</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0271">she's got a swimming coach she's got a coach so all the money goes on this <pause dur="short"/> she had to be retaught swimming cos the British way of teaching swimming <pause dur="short"/> was not very good <pause dur="short"/> don't know <trunc>qui</trunc> how quite <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1825" who="S0270">very very exciting</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but I mean that's amazing cos you don't</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0271" trans="overlap">her best sport is cycling she's as fast as men at cycling</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0271">mm <pause dur="short"/> with the running she's average and I think the swimming it's probably her least <pause dur="short"/> good sport <pause dur="short"/> she does her training with a guy for the cycling they're sort of equal but he's faster than her at running <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1830" who="S0266">but I mean you don't you you were never sporty were you?</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0271">I might have been mightn't I?</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1833" who="S0266">what do you mean you might have been? like</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0270" trans="overlap">you might have been</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0266">if you'd been a boy in Australia?</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I love that you might have been</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0271">well I might have <trunc>be</trunc> quite good at cycling</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1839" who="S0271">I might have been mightn't I?</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1841" who="S0266">well anyone can say you might have been if you didn't try it you don't know</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's so funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1843" who="S0271">she's a very</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I think I actually could have been a fantastic entertainer you know</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0271"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1846" who="S0270">I I think I could have been a dancer</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0271">well I was</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0270" trans="overlap">and a singer</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0271">I was totally put off sport at school</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1851" who="S0271">I was quite good at skating and balancing</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0270"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear I think that's so funny</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0266">but you never rode a bicycle?</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0271">I did have a bike I used to ride my my bike but I mean young girls didn't</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you couldn't do it competitively could you in those days?</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0271" trans="overlap">there was no such thing as I mean my bike was like this with three gears on it</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0270">I'm still struggling with having this new bike er erm because I can't <trunc>w</trunc> there's three options three grades on the left hand three grades on the right it's so confusing I I'm still working with the middle grade on the left and er you know whatever I can find on the right</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1860" who="S0270">I can still get round my I did about an hour and twenty on the weekend on one of my rides and I still haven't <vocal desc="laugh"/> found out what all the other ones on the left are for it's so confusing cos if you get the wrong gear in the wrong place you just mess up you can't get up any hills unless you're in the right one so I have I don't know if I'll never find out what all those are it's a bit like my car I keep finding these new buttons and think I should <pause dur="short"/> read the instruction book because <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know what some of them are for</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0271" trans="overlap">when I went to see my cousin in Surrey in the holiday she'd got a newish car she'd got things stuck on the dashboard telling her <vocal desc="laugh"/> how to do things which</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1863" who="S0271">she said I don't know what to do with all these knobs and things and so she's got instructions stuck on there</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0270">well at least she's trying to find out</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0271">yes</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0270">I keep I keep discovering these new buttons and think oh I wonder what that's for <vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't needed it and this is how long have I had it? <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm five years plus isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> or is it longer? I was surprised to find it was India it was two thousand and five and now I've got to have all these booster jabs</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0271" trans="overlap">jabs</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0266">oh what to go to Nepal?</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0266">so who else are you going to recruit into your party?</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0270">oh anyone who wants to come who's fit enough to walk <pause dur="short"/> that kind of walking</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0271">she'll be testing people</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0270">no I won't I can't</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0266">and when is it sorry?</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0270">erm in the last two weeks ish of November <pause dur="short"/> cos that's when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can go</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0266" trans="overlap">quite soon</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0270">mm</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0270">I'm already in training I started in <anon type="place"/> I didn't know I was</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0271" trans="overlap">so did you tell them it's</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0270" trans="overlap">going to Nepal but</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0271">did you tell them at school that you'll be there then or is it?</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0270">yes that would be good erm no</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1886" who="S0270">I haven't told them anything like that</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0266">do you want some more wine or do you want a coffee?</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0271">no thank you cos I'm working tomorrow</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0270">just a spot</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0271">exactly</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you've gotta go to work tomorrow?</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0271">I'm going to work tomorrow</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0266">oh <pause dur="short"/> you are?</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0271">yeah</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0266">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0271">well every day aren't I?</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0271">what's the time now?</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0266">sure</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0270">ten o'clock</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it's only ten o'clock <pause dur="short"/> erm well what can I</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0271">mm</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0266">can get you? tea or <trunc>coff</trunc></u>
<u n="1904" who="S0270" trans="overlap">I would love a tea</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0266">you'd love a cup of tea</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0270" trans="overlap">please</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0266">what would you like?</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0271">I'll have a maybe a glass of water</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0266">right shall I switch this off?</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0271">a stress</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
