<text id="S7MF">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:37:47</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-08-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0441</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home - kitchen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Work, the weekend, house party, living arrangements, communications, complaining, friends.</topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with housemate. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, inviting, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0441">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Mental Health Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">how did the erm party go then so what happened? what did you get up to?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0441">we just stayed here really</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0441">went to the pub at like I don't know what time like eleven or something</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0441">just went to the pub and came back</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">the local pub in <anon type="place"/> how was it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0441">fine</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0441">it was really good really really good time</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">that's good ah oh what time did they all leave on the Sunday?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0441">mm like two half two</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">oh so just before I got back maybe? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0441">maybe ah maybe not maybe one then cos they we were in bed about one so</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0441">maybe it was earlier than that</u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> what broke?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0441">what do you mean? is that mine or yours?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">yours er there was glass on the floor</u>
<u n="20" who="S0441">oh a glass</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439">oh I see so I didn't think anything significant broke I was just wondering</u>
<u n="22" who="S0441">when was that on <trunc>Sa</trunc>Saturday morning?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">Sunday</u>
<u n="24" who="S0441">I was going to say cos we've swept and mopped since then so</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">oh yeah no I thought it it was just in the corner I dropped something so I swept up and there was some glass in there and I was just like ah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0441">just a glass</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0441">fucking fridge</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">huh?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0441">I'm complaining about the fridge</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439">the fridge is crap we really really need to get it sorted but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is just so rubbish I don't understand she's like the worst estate agent ever</u>
<u n="34" who="S0441">well I understand that she's waiting for this woman to get back to her but what I'd do is</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it doesn't take that long</u>
<u n="36" who="S0441" trans="overlap">even if she's taking ages I would <pause dur="short"/> at least ring and say explain what was going on just be like</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0441" trans="overlap">just so you know I am still trying to get hold of her but I can't get hold of her</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">she didn't even leave like emails or anything she just doesn't respond</u>
<u n="40" who="S0441">yeah it's not hard to leave an email is it?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="42" who="S0441">not at all</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">yeah it's really annoying</u>
<u n="44" who="S0441">I'll I'll ring them tomorrow see what they like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says</u>
<u n="45" who="S0439">and it's just and like the fifteen pound thing it's fifteen pounds like it's not breaking the bank balance it's not</u>
<u n="46" who="S0441">and how long does it take to go and ask the finance company wherever they are?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah exactly why don't you say well why doesn't the landlady just say she just take fifteen pounds off your rent it's so simple</u>
<u n="48" who="S0441" trans="overlap">really easy</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439">it's fifteen pounds they're just the worst estate agents</u>
<u n="50" who="S0441">can we er get rid of the red cabbage please?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0439">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh fuck <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0441">it won't come out will it?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0439">it will it will come out <pause dur="long"/> I'll empty it but</u>
<u n="54" who="S0439">oh god you ah you've exploded everywhere ah oh oh there's no wipes oh there is there's no more wipes in there</u>
<u n="55" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I bought some a minute ago</u>
<u n="56" who="S0439">oh red cabbage leaks everywhere</u>
<u n="57" who="S0441">apparently it does yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0439">so any gossip any gossip happen at the weekend although to be fair you don't really live round each other anymore so no more gossip but hey</u>
<u n="59" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no not really everyone was doing actually really quite well</u>
<u n="60" who="S0439">oh that's good</u>
<u n="61" who="S0441">yeah it is good they've all got jobs they're all happy</u>
<u n="62" who="S0439">where is everybody based now? all over the place?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm yeah mostly London really</u>
<u n="64" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0441">erm they're all south like south Essex it's pretty easy</u>
<u n="66" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0441"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so close to here I didn't even realise but it took her about half an hour to get here</u>
<u n="68" who="S0439">she lives in <anon type="place"/> doesn't she?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0441">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0439">yeah so oh just chuck the whole thing out forget it forget emptying it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">no no I don't want to <unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0441">no no I mean chuck the whole jar in the bin</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439">oh I see no I'll try I'll try try and be recycling and environmentally friendly although erm this bin will probably need emptying at some point <pause dur="long"/> that's such an amazing colour though</u>
<u n="74" who="S0441">it's a good colour</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">maybe that's what they used in the olden days maybe they like</u>
<u n="76" who="S0441">even in the hot water it's a cool colour</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439">yeah it's kind of like it's not purple but it's not blue it's like</u>
<u n="78" who="S0441">it's like UV</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0441">it's cool</u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">you wouldn't know that pickled cabbage would be so exciting</u>
<u n="82" who="S0441">we're very excited by it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0441">anything else to go in the fridge? I don't think it will take it any more</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">mm what time did erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> leave on <trunc>Sa</trunc> on Sunday?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0441">we I took him to work er</u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">oh did you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0441">to the station this morning yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439">how was that how did that work out? was it alright?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0441" trans="overlap">fine actually it'll be really easy we just need to plan it a bit better next time cos he sort of was he didn't know what train he was going to get so</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439">oh I see</u>
<u n="92" who="S0441">we sort of did a trial run it would be fine we just need to sort of maybe leave fifteen minutes earlier cos then he can get he can get to work earlier</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">did you go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0441"><anon type="place"/> cos I was in <anon type="place"/> that morning anyway</u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">oh I see okay that's good</u>
<u n="96" who="S0441">yeah it worked pretty well</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439">yeah that's very cool</u>
<u n="98" who="S0441">yeah it was cool</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439">at least it means that he doesn't have to rush back or anything</u>
<u n="100" who="S0441">exactly and it's it was quite nice actually sort of to have Sunday <trunc>of</trunc> evening together it was quite good</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0441">quite relaxed er oh yeah lights</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">ah yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0441">got nice Dettol wipes cos they're good</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">are they <unclear/> at Home Bargains</u>
<u n="106" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439">I love Home Bargains every time yeah every time I go in I'm just surprised how cheap it is</u>
<u n="108" who="S0441">yeah wow really?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">it's just like how did I buy ten things it only came to three pounds</u>
<u n="110" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">er have you got any plans for this week?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0441">er no just going to the gym Wednesday Thursday I was going to go on Friday but the class isn't on so I'm not going to go</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">oh is it Insanity or whatever it's called?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0441">I don't know why it's not on</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming over on Friday night?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0441">no I'm going home going cos my mum needs someone to look after the cat</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439">oh fun times</u>
<u n="118" who="S0441">so I'm cat sitting at the weekend</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">and then seeing you on Sunday? yeah where is it in town?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0441">I don't actually know oh no it's our side of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="122" who="S0441">so yeah it's in <anon type="place"/> but it's good</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">yeah okay</u>
<u n="124" who="S0441">I can't remember what the place is called but I need to add them to our <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0441">it's like seventeen pound for <unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">thank you yeah I mean that's cool thank you it'll be so cool to have like an afternoon tea I haven't had a proper one in ages it'll be so nice</u>
<u n="128" who="S0441">me neither you got er</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439">oh yeah damn it</u>
<u n="130" who="S0441">you can probably put that in the wash right now</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">yeah I'll go and soak it stupid</u>
<u n="132" who="S0441">stupid bloody cabbage</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439" trans="overlap">bloody old cabbage</u>
<u n="134" who="S0441">I think mine's oh no it's still a bit pinky erm yeah I think I think the last time I had afternoon tea was the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one like last year it is so good</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">it's so nice it's <trunc>to</trunc> this weekend's going to be a good weekend I'm going I'm going out Friday night</u>
<u n="136" who="S0441">oh yeah I did see that sorry I can't come</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">no it's alright don't worry er and then we're going to go to <anon type="place"/> on Saturday I was going to invite you but I wasn't sure whether <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was down or not</u>
<u n="138" who="S0441">that'll be really cool</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">yeah I haven't been to it for like ages</u>
<u n="140" who="S0441">where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439">erm south London</u>
<u n="142" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">so I think we're going to go to <anon type="place"/> cos I want to go to <anon type="place"/> and then go to</u>
<u n="144" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that would be a good reason</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> go to <anon type="place"/> in the afternoon</u>
<u n="146" who="S0441">cool</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">or <unclear/> yeah so just like a more cultural day</u>
<u n="148" who="S0441">I'm quite poor this month I'm really</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">yeah I'm so ridiculously poor it's <trunc>rid</trunc> awful but I get paid next week so I'm happy about that oh it's so funny I went out for dinner with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no I didn't I went out for lunch with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last week at work</u>
<u n="150" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">and do you know she goes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I really want to start doing more couturel stuff in England</u>
<u n="152" who="S0441">what?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">and I was like what? and she went no couture stuff you know I was like no I've got no idea what the hell you're talking about she goes couturel I was like saying it louder doesn't help me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she goes you know like castles and stuff couture you mean cultural</u>
<u n="154" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">you utter idiot she also came up with path walk</u>
<u n="156" who="S0441">path walk what's that?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">well path and then sidewalk but a path walk</u>
<u n="158" who="S0441">okay path walk</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">I was like oh bless you</u>
<u n="160" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I get the logic</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">yeah I was like oh I understand it but erm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0441">but no</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439">no <pause dur="short"/> one's American and one's English and yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0441" trans="overlap">they don't go together really</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">she was like oh <pause dur="short"/> I was like nice try though love nice try</u>
<u n="166" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah good effort <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">ah so when is your who's coming to your oh the next barbecue is for people you work with isn't it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0441">yeah well used to work with</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">used to work with</u>
<u n="170" who="S0441">not my nurse colleagues cos that would be weird</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no no people from the pub?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="174" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I'm excited for that as well <pause dur="short"/> it was good and successful although I didn't do any of the cooking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did it all so I don't really know what's going to happen <unclear/> that one really</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">I am in <anon type="place"/> that weekend</u>
<u n="176" who="S0441">nice</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439"><anon type="place"/> it's really good I'm going <anon type="place"/> and then <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0441">that's really good actually that's that's a good week</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">I know <anon type="place"/> then back in work for three days and then off to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0441">very good</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">can't beat it bank holiday weekend hello</u>
<u n="182" who="S0441">is it is it bank holiday weekend in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">no but the French never do anything</u>
<u n="184" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">the French always have a holiday it's like bloody</u>
<u n="186" who="S0441" trans="overlap">okay true they are always closed everything everything</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439" trans="overlap">holiday <pause dur="short"/> yeah just I'm surprised they actually get any work done in France to be honest with the amount of saint's days they have</u>
<u n="188" who="S0441">that's a little bit floppy I don't think I'll be using that</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">that looks slightly <pause dur="short"/> grim</u>
<u n="190" who="S0441" trans="overlap">floppy it's okay actually the middle ones are okay</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">what are you making?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0441">just my salad for tomorrow</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439">yum <pause dur="short"/> then you're off on holiday in three weeks</u>
<u n="194" who="S0441">I'm so excited</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">I can imagine is it Dominican Republic you're going? that's I've never that's so cool never been I really would like to I've heard it's really pretty</u>
<u n="196" who="S0441">mm I'm actually very excited now that's not even I thought I'd be less excited I mean now</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">yeah but you can just it's on the horizon it's there</u>
<u n="198" who="S0441">yeah I need a break as well I'm so sick of work people are annoying</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439">have you had any holiday since? like any</u>
<u n="200" who="S0441" trans="overlap">Portugal</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439">oh yeah <trunc>Po</trunc> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0441">that was just that was really good actually that was nicely needed</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">I was going to say you kind of get to this time of year with the sun and you're just a bit like oh my god I need to have some time off I need a break</u>
<u n="204" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I'm just so over people like this woman I mean fair enough she's she's obviously really really worried about her husband but he's got a a chest infection</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0441">and I won't see him before he was admitted to hospital and I because she she she'd rung the GP and the GP was like not coming out it's probably his medication and she rang me and was like we need to change the medication and I was like that's fine so we changed the medication I went to see him and he did look he was like quite lethargic and <pause dur="short"/> sleepy sort of looking in bed but because sort of I had it in my head that it was the medication he wasn't showing any other signs really of having an infection so I just put it down to the medication anyway he's got an infection which is fine erm but I've got the feeling she's going she she she's going to be a a real dick about it</u>
<u n="207" who="S0439">because you didn't pick up the yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0441" trans="overlap">why didn't you pick it up? it's like well why didn't you pick it up as well to be quite honest?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0441">cos you know? anyway</u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">but do you know like I've had a cold for like a week over a week now and like I'm still this like sniffy and shit today</u>
<u n="212" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">and I was like and someone was like maybe it's a virus and I was like mm I'd never even thought about that like you don't know what's wrong with you and you</u>
<u n="214" who="S0441">you don't and</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439">you can't just put it down like being lethargic to an infection for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="216" who="S0441">no and so he's got I I think he's got quite a bad infection</u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0441">but it sort of it sort of happened really quickly over a couple of days</u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">where is the infection though?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0441">lung infection</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439">oh oh</u>
<u n="222" who="S0441">chest infection</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">but if he wasn't coughing or anything like that then why would you assume he's got a lung infection?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no well he was coughing she not but not when I was there she said oh he's had this cough for like months and months and I was like okay fine</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0441">but</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">also you're not a doctor so it's not your job like</u>
<u n="228" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no anyway he's in hospital now which is fine so he's getting looked after and stuff but she rang me like when he's in hospital sort of I back off because that's not really my arena he's in hospital so he's being looked after he's safe that fine so she was like I need you to change the medication again cos I think I I don't think it's helping me cos he he's hallucinating and he's really slurry and I was like okay fine I don't think they'll be making any changes whilst he's still physically unwell in hospital</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0441">because he's physically unwell</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0441">so people especially older people react with hallucinating and slurring of speech when they have an infection so I'm pretty sure it's still the infection</u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">yeah same with a urine infection as well like it can really mess you up</u>
<u n="234" who="S0441">yeah really mess you up so she's like oh but I'm I'm I'm really not sure I I thought you'd be more supportive of me on this I was like well I am but I just I'm telling you now that I don't think it's going to help him all this medication change I think he should just stick to one</u>
<u n="235" who="S0439">yeah cos like sometimes you have to get well not get over the side effects but you have to wait for it to settle down don't you?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0441">yeah but I don't really see what she wants me to do she was like if have you rang the ward yet? And I was like well no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0441">they're not going to tell me anything else from that that that they've told you because you know? I don't need to know really he's in hospital</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0441">and she's like well I I I said would you find it helpful if I liaise with the ward? and she was like well yes I would okay well I I completely forgot to do it today cos it's not it's not on my to do list at all</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah yeah if it's not part of your remit you're just yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0441">so I was like shit I forgot to do it so I rang her and it was her daughter and I was like I'm really sorry but erm I didn't get round to doing it today I'll do it tomorrow morning and give give her an update call she was like oh well her mobile number was de de de if you want to ring her mobile and I was like well I'm going home now I didn't say that but I was like it's it's it's probably just better that I just you know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439">ring her with info yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0441">ring her with an update not just babble on about that I haven't got an update god but she's just so like makes almost makes you feel guilty about it and it's like okay fine I'm really sorry that that your husband is unwell in hospital but he's in hospital</u>
<u n="245" who="S0439">yeah it's the best place for him</u>
<u n="246" who="S0441">it isn't like he's sort of wandering around the streets is it?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439">no some people when like when their like family are ill they become quite like</u>
<u n="248" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439">they lose not lose their priority but they kind of just they go a bit crazy themselves don't they?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0441">she's lost it I think I mean lost her sort of rationality a little bit</u>
<u n="251" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah just that obviously she must be a bit stressed</u>
<u n="252" who="S0441" trans="overlap">and I I I can understand that it's probably</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and it must be an awful situation</u>
<u n="254" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's probably quite scary</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439">but there's nothing you can do like</u>
<u n="256" who="S0441">I can't <trunc>ac</trunc> yeah there's nothing I can do and she was like I'm I'm going to speak to the doctor about it yeah and I was like well they won't prescribe him anything different because it's not that isn't in their remit they don't do <trunc>psych</trunc> er psychiatric drugs that for a <trunc>psy</trunc> a psychiatrist to</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0441">but she just doesn't even seem to understand that I don't know she's a bit manipulative actually</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439">I got that impression from my boss this morning not this morning when was it? one day last week she sent out an email and we were <trunc>we</trunc> <trunc>ta</trunc> basically our job has changed and we've started taking on a lot of of extra admin work because of our role change and then she sent round this email and it was just like now I've been speaking to blah blah blah the controller of erm this system we're using and she's saying that our new process is working really well and you know we've just got a few tweeks to make but it's working really well</u>
<u n="260" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439">and I messaged one of the other girls on my team I was like did she ask you if you were happy with how the new system was working? cos I'm not entirely sure who has told her that this new process is working well because it's really not</u>
<u n="262" who="S0441">so she's just lying</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she's just yeah she's just like sent round this email being like oh yeah this program is or this new process is really working well everybody's getting on board no we're not I haven't even used the new process yet because I'm avoiding it because it's so shit</u>
<u n="264" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">like</u>
<u n="266" who="S0441">what an idiot</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">it's just like who did you ask</u>
<u n="268" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439">to think that this process is working? you just want to justify giving us all this extra bureaucracy</u>
<u n="270" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">I was so annoyed and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was just like she was like yeah I hate it I've actually messed up every time I've done it I was like well</u>
<u n="272" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0441">it's that good silly woman</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh I know</u>
<u n="276" who="S0441">oh no I spoke to this man today it's really sad he's got his he's got his wife's got dementia</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0441">he's really not coping cos he's just like I guess just doesn't get out and just feels like he needs to be at home all the time looking after her and stuff</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0441">and he was just he just started crying down the phone</u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">oh don't oh that would that would that would make me cry so much</u>
<u n="282" who="S0441">ah so I'm going to see him on Thursday bless him</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="284" who="S0441">he was like he he said erm I I just want someone to come and talk to her and see what like why she's sort of being so resistive to everything cos apparently she's quite difficult to deal with</u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">it's just part of the <trunc>il</trunc> the illness isn't it?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm exactly but I think she's also got pre-morbid personality of sort of being quite difficult anyway and not like if if she doesn't like you then she won't talk to you</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0441">so that's going to be interesting but we we we have got the same name so I think that's some good good ground</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439">maybe she'll look at you and think that you're her but like her younger self</u>
<u n="290" who="S0441">that could be a bad thing</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439">that'd be weird but it could be like</u>
<u n="292" who="S0441">I hate you you're young</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">you're young and free and innocent and crazy and I'm not</u>
<u n="294" who="S0441" trans="overlap">old old and crazy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0441">but yeah we'll see how it goes down</u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">how is it only Monday?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0441">I don't know the office was absolutely dead today as well and that normally happens on Friday so it felt even weirder</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah last Friday work was really empty it's just like it's so nice when there's no one in</u>
<u n="300" who="S0441">I quite like it I mean it's very quiet but</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">I just love it I love when there's like hardly anybody in the office <pause dur="long"/> it's just so much more relaxing I know that sounds really bad but you just you feel more relaxed more just ah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439">oh I've got such it's not oh no yeah I do have sun sun burn I got sun burn all round my back cos I was out on Saturday at this at the castle and the seaside and</u>
<u n="304" who="S0441">oh yeah how was that?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">ah it was really fun it was really really good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came about half ten and picked me up and then we went on to pickup <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">erm went to the castle erm had the Knights Day and the tournament and then we went on to the beach and then went to the fish and chip shop which is apparently the best fish and chip shop in <anon type="place"/> I was like okay</u>
<u n="308" who="S0441">was it?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">yeah it was really good actually there was a massive queue outside took like twenty twenty-five minutes to queue for this fish and chips</u>
<u n="310" who="S0441">I love fish and chips</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">I know it was so worth it</u>
<u n="312" who="S0441">it's so good when it's by the sea as well</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">yeah and then we sat on the beach and ate it</u>
<u n="314" who="S0441">ah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">and then drove back here we got back here about when was it? maybe about nine</u>
<u n="316" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">and then he had to go pick up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from the train station and he were supposed to pick her up at ten to nine and he only dropped us off here at nine so</u>
<u n="318" who="S0441">what in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">no in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0441">oh god</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">so he was like he was like an hour late for her</u>
<u n="322" who="S0441">that wasn't planned very well was it?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">well he just kept being like erm shall we go to the beach? yeah okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you have to go home? he was like mm yeah not really I was erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the train station he went that's okay she can just get a drink and wait</u>
<u n="324" who="S0441" trans="overlap">bit weird isn't it? great</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="326" who="S0441">love hey</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">erm but he met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and him and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got on really well so that was good</u>
<u n="328" who="S0441">that's good</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439">yeah it was a really nice relaxing day</u>
<u n="330" who="S0441">good</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">and then I just went for the run on Sunday</u>
<u n="332" who="S0441">oh yeah how was that?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">it was really good I was really surprised I did the first ever run I did erm fourteen just over fourteen kilometres</u>
<u n="334" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">which is <trunc>betw</trunc> about nine and a half <trunc>mi</trunc> no just just a bit longer than nine and a half miles</u>
<u n="336" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">no nine and half nine miles something like that erm hour and a half's running</u>
<u n="338" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439">erm did it was good got to the end was like oh I can do this</u>
<u n="340" who="S0441" trans="overlap">great you can do it</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">so I feel much more confident about it but I got sunburnt cos it was such nice day but I did not think about putting on cream</u>
<u n="342" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">erm yeah no so I feel much more confident about this bloody run now</u>
<u n="344" who="S0441">good ow</u>
<u n="345" who="S0439">you alright?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0441">hot</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439">burning yourself</u>
<u n="348" who="S0441">burning myself with water</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">so when are you next seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0441">erm I don't know cos we're both quite busy now</u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0441">until we go on holiday so</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">no I didn't but yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0441">erm so <pause dur="long"/> probably next Friday er that spider's back</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439">yeah I know I saw the spider earlier so I was like oh yeah the weekend I'm in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0441">yeah but I'm working that day at the pub and the next day could see him the next day I suppose but then that would be a bit weird sort of</u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">Friday and then not Saturday and then yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah bit of an effort really</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">I love you but too much effort</u>
<u n="362" who="S0441">too much effort we have a whole two weeks together soon so</u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">are you going for two weeks?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0441">well ten days but ten days there and twelve it's sort of two days travelling so</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">well</u>
<u n="366" who="S0441">almost two weeks</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">yeah yeah I think I think you can get rid of him for a few weeks and then just make up for it in one massive session</u>
<u n="368" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> for two weeks</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439">for two weeks yeah not like a massive dirty session just like a bonding time</u>
<u n="370" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0439">like a <unclear/> you dirty person <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god can you imagine two week worth of sex? you're going to be knackered <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0441">I think yeah that wouldn't be a relaxing holiday at all would it?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439">you'd be like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm so tired stop it he'd be like</u>
<u n="374" who="S0441" trans="overlap">open my vagina</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">he'd be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's only day three <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0441">oh god bad times</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">yeah let's let's not break your vagina</u>
<u n="378" who="S0441">I think I need that</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">you think you need that</u>
<u n="380" who="S0441">it could be quite useful I think for the future</u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">what a broken vagina</u>
<u n="382" who="S0441">on a non broken vagina</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439">oh I see yeah I was like what?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0441">I meant I need my vagina</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439">yes yes yes you do</u>
<u n="386" who="S0441">yes I do oh I didn't make the tuna</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439">oh no is mummy <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> coming over on Thursday?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0441">er no she's taking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> grandchildren and they're going to Cornwall for the weekend</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439">oh nice</u>
<u n="390" who="S0441">they're travelling overnight on Thursday and then getting there on Friday that is really cloudy and horrible</u>
<u n="391" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah was it in the dishwasher?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439">dishwasher is really weird it keeps leaving stuff and it's like</u>
<u n="394" who="S0441">I know</u>
<u n="395" who="S0439">like dry residue or</u>
<u n="396" who="S0441">I think it's cos the water's so hard</u>
<u n="397" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0441">horrible</u>
<u n="399" who="S0439">the water here is grim</u>
<u n="400" who="S0441">it's horrible erm yeah so we're going to go to the beach and stuff</u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">that's cool</u>
<u n="402" who="S0441">get them buy them some like wet suits and just let them go <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0439">go see swim</u>
<u n="404" who="S0441">go to the sea</u>
<u n="405" who="S0439">I love going to the sea</u>
<u n="406" who="S0441">I think you she's feeling a bit like she needs children in her life at the moment so</u>
<u n="407" who="S0439">what your mum?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439">it's cos she's waiting for you to crack out some babies</u>
<u n="410" who="S0441">it's like I really can't wait for you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to have children that that that means no rush and I was like hey</u>
<u n="411" who="S0439">are you sure mum?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0441">are you sure?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">god does <trunc>li</trunc> does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like get broody or does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> think about children?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0441">he loves babies</u>
<u n="415" who="S0439">does he?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0441">absolutely loves babies more than I do I don't even like babies really</u>
<u n="417" who="S0439">that's true actually</u>
<u n="418" who="S0441">he loves them</u>
<u n="419" who="S0439">do you think do you think he wants them then?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">no but I mean like soonish?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0441" trans="overlap">not now</u>
<u n="423" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0441">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if if he stayed with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's sort of</u>
<u n="425" who="S0439">well she's just about to be a vet isn't she? so she doesn't want to have children for like a good</u>
<u n="426" who="S0441">well not for while</u>
<u n="427" who="S0439">five years four five years</u>
<u n="428" who="S0441">let's hope</u>
<u n="429" who="S0439">even longer even</u>
<u n="430" who="S0441">my granny's devastated</u>
<u n="431" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0439">but then again people just don't have children as young anymore well some people do obviously but most people are just having children young you know when they're older</u>
<u n="434" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I know I know I know</u>
<u n="435" who="S0439">but I genuinely don't think I could imagine having children before thirty</u>
<u n="436" who="S0441">well I just feel like I know this will sound really stupid but it's a lot of responsibility</u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0441">I don't think I'm old enough for that yet</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439">no like it's weird cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s twenty-eight this year <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is twenty-seven this year erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is thirty in January like a lot of the people who I actually see and like talk to and when I was round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on Friday night the girl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was thirty this year and I just I still look at them and talk to them and think that they're my age</u>
<u n="440" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439">and they're not</u>
<u n="442" who="S0441">they're not</u>
<u n="443" who="S0439">and they don't even feel ready for children and they're like thirty something or like nearly thirty late twenties early thirties so</u>
<u n="444" who="S0441" trans="overlap">exactly yeah it's weird</u>
<u n="445" who="S0439">yeah it's like you just can't imagine getting thirty and just being like let's have time to have children right now</u>
<u n="446" who="S0441">I mean say if my situation changed in a few years say if I was living with someone</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> randomly living with somebody</u>
<u n="448" who="S0441">living with someone random but say if you were like settled</u>
<u n="449" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0441">but you see I I don't want to have kids like without being being married so I'd have to get married first and then that's going to take ages so</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439" trans="overlap">married yeah like a year or so</u>
<u n="452" who="S0441">so yeah I don't see that happening any time soon but</u>
<u n="453" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="454" who="S0441">but I don't want children</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439">also you're only twenty</u>
<u n="456" who="S0441">I don't want it to happen</u>
<u n="457" who="S0439">four years old I was going to say five then</u>
<u n="458" who="S0441">I'm almost twenty-five</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439">I was going to be like you're only twenty-five you're only twenty-four</u>
<u n="460" who="S0441"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying that the other day he was like I'm twenty-five soon I can't believe it</u>
<u n="461" who="S0439">I know it's horrible isn't it?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0441">you're not even twenty-four yet</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439">well yeah but it's a horrible thought but it's like erm I went round to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yesterday I took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> shopping and then just had dinner round theirs</u>
<u n="464" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came in he was like we were talking about birthdays and stuff he goes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when are you when is your birthday? I was in a few weeks he was like erm what are you twenty-six? I was like no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm twenty-four he's like oh shit I've been telling everybody you're twenty-five I was like no no</u>
<u n="466" who="S0441">how rude</u>
<u n="467" who="S0439">he's like I've been telling you know for the last few years I've been telling people you've been twenty-five I'm like you just aged me like two years</u>
<u n="468" who="S0441">how how long have you been twenty-five for?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0439">yeah he's like I don't know I just think you always stay the same I'm like I'm not even that old how can I stay the same age when I haven't hit that age yet? he was like yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0441">how rude</u>
<u n="471" who="S0439">but then he's like he is thirty this year he's like god</u>
<u n="472" who="S0441">is he? ancient</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">practically a grandad and then he was you know I told you he was sleeping with his eighteen nineteen year old house student thing</u>
<u n="474" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh yeah awkward</u>
<u n="475" who="S0439">yeah he was like she's gone back to Poland now but he talks to her a bit I was like this is just weird you know she's nineteen</u>
<u n="476" who="S0441">weird</u>
<u n="477" who="S0439">and you're nearly thirty he's like no but she's really hot I'm like</u>
<u n="478" who="S0441">so?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0439">so? that's like an eleven year age gap it's really creepy he's like well I don't think it is I think it's fine I'm like no no no it's not</u>
<u n="480" who="S0441">oh no no</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">no no no just think when you're forty she's only going be like thirty</u>
<u n="482" who="S0441">mm sad times</u>
<u n="483" who="S0439">mm it's okay if they're like seventy and you're sixty or like they're seventy-five and you're sixty-five I think but</u>
<u n="484" who="S0441">I suppose my yeah my granny is seventy-three and my her husband's sixty-one</u>
<u n="485" who="S0439">it's like when you get older it doesn't really matter as much does it? it doesn't become like a issue but</u>
<u n="486" who="S0441">when you're young it does because it's like she's completely different like different mindset of things so</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439">yeah and also creepy as it sounds when he was like twenty she was only ten</u>
<u n="488" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0439">and that just sounds disgusting</u>
<u n="490" who="S0441">creepy</u>
<u n="491" who="S0439">I don't know I'll probably eat my words and then end up marrying a really old man and being like he's the love of my life</u>
<u n="492" who="S0441">exactly when I was ten he was thirty</u>
<u n="493" who="S0439">it's fine we're in love <pause dur="long"/> ah today at work I had to we had to do some audio recordings I had to read this story and you know when you're listening to yourself it's the weirdest thing you're like listening to your own voice and listening to erm like you try to read something in a certain way and oh god</u>
<u n="494" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that going to actually go out to to the public?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0439">no well it is but to schools it's for the demo</u>
<u n="496" who="S0441">I'm <unclear/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0439">and it's me reading this story about this rumour in the environment about this yeah these animals living by a river heard a rumour but the rumour might not be true den den de</u>
<u n="498" who="S0441">oh god</u>
<u n="499" who="S0439">I know it was sinister I tell you sinister but it was fun to read it and they're like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you put you put on you're such a nice story teller when you have children I was like what?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> pardon?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0439">when I have children do you mean if I ever ever accidently have children?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0439">did they really like the house?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0441">mm they did</u>
<u n="505" who="S0439">it was a really good day to chose to have your barbecue like really good</u>
<u n="506" who="S0441">so good we were very lucky actually it was really good timing</u>
<u n="507" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I thought that when we were at the castle like weather here is awesome it's a really good time to have a barbecue</u>
<u n="508" who="S0441">really good</u>
<u n="509" who="S0439">cos obviously you know month in advance how good it was going to be</u>
<u n="510" who="S0441">I knew it when did I arrange this? like May?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0439">yeah your psychic ability</u>
<u n="512" who="S0441">just knew it</u>
<u n="513" who="S0439">just knew <pause dur="long"/> was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> here?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0439">maybe I didn't see her</u>
<u n="516" who="S0441">I think when you came she was near the other side of the table maybe</u>
<u n="517" who="S0439">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0441">behind everyone</u>
<u n="519" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0441">probably ah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0439">what are you having for dinner?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0441">I'm having beans on toast I really fancy it</u>
<u n="523" who="S0439">I do you know I was actually looking at spaghetti hoops yesterday and was like am I at an age where spaghetti hoops is an acceptable form of dinner?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0441">course it is</u>
<u n="525" who="S0439">I know that's what I came to the conclusion as well</u>
<u n="526" who="S0441">I love spaghetti hoops</u>
<u n="527" who="S0439">I didn't have it but I came back from <anon type="place"/> and was like soon</u>
<u n="528" who="S0441">you're allowed</u>
<u n="529" who="S0439">soon I will I will do that I will bash out the spaghetti hoops</u>
<u n="530" who="S0441">they're good that's why I want eat my cream cheese that's why I'm going to cut the mould off because I've been thinking about it all day</u>
<u n="531" who="S0439">what cream cheese with baked beans?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0441">mm it's really good</u>
<u n="533" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0439"><unclear/> I did not know this what do you do with it just put it on there?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm mm put it on the bread</u>
<u n="537" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0441">it's well nice</u>
<u n="539" who="S0439">I do that with scrambled egg I put cream cheese on the bread and then put scrambled egg on top</u>
<u n="540" who="S0441">it's a bit similar</u>
<u n="541" who="S0439">yum</u>
<u n="542" who="S0441">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="543" who="S0439">it's too good</u>
<u n="544" who="S0441">it's too good</u>
<u n="545" who="S0439">guess what else is too good?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0441">erm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0439">the Great British Bake Off</u>
<u n="548" who="S0441">yes that is too good</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0441">that is way too good although I can't work out whether they've stopped doing you know when they like look at people's home lives and stuff</u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0441">have they stopped doing that or is it just cos it's too early?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no they they do it later they do it when like it comes to like the final the semi-finals and it's to get to know the finalists</u>
<u n="554" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0439">and you go into their house and stuff apparently one of the girls in this season has an Aga and they're she got loads of like abuse from people for being too posh</u>
<u n="556" who="S0441">my granny had an Aga she wasn't posh</u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">I like the Aga like quite cool</u>
<u n="558" who="S0441">Agas are good they're <unclear/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0439" trans="overlap">apparently when they like when they go wrong it's a bit annoying cos obviously you get you've got to get someone out to relight the <unclear/> and bollocks but I think they're really cool I like Agas</u>
<u n="560" who="S0441">forgotten the sweetcorn</u>
<u n="561" who="S0439">I need a haircut so badly</u>
<u n="562" who="S0441">I'm not going to bother going till I come back from holiday</u>
<u n="563" who="S0439">got loads of split ends which are so fun to pick but it's not good <pause dur="short"/> eh</u>
<u n="564" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0439">it's not really I might try and find somewhere tomorrow and ring up and book it in next week as I get paid <pause dur="short"/> and treat myself to a haircut</u>
<u n="566" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> push the boat out</u>
<u n="567" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0441">not too far</u>
<u n="569" who="S0439">I know I've got to reign it back in sometime</u>
<u n="570" who="S0441">probably get my last decent petrol thing this this month petrol allowance back</u>
<u n="571" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0441">expenses really but <pause dur="short"/> this is annoying as well there's another one of my patients that has just come out of hospital</u>
<u n="573" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0441">erm <pause dur="short"/> so he went to hospital in <anon type="place"/> which is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0441">cos that's closer probably for him cos he's in <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> but <pause dur="short"/> because we're out of area for <anon type="place"/> for <anon type="place"/> they're going to send it to <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0439">oh god</u>
<u n="578" who="S0441">send his fax stuff his discharge notice and his erm medication to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0441">and I have to go pick it up and bring it to him</u>
<u n="581" who="S0439">oh god</u>
<u n="582" who="S0441">but that's because it then it's such a big county and both hospitals are on the the other side of the county it's just like what the hell?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah Northamptonshire and Cambridgeshire and is it <trunc>Bedfordsh</trunc> no <anon type="place"/> is in</u>
<u n="584" who="S0441">Lincolnshire is just huge <anon type="place"/> is still in <anon type="place"/> er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0439">is it? okay</u>
<u n="586" who="S0441">like we just do <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="587" who="S0439">but Bedfordshire is like</u>
<u n="588" who="S0441">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0439">yeah but <anon type="place"/> is just outside of it</u>
<u n="590" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="592" who="S0441">it's just a massive county</u>
<u n="593" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0441">I mean luckily it's split up into different bits but</u>
<u n="595" who="S0439">still a pain isn't it? and it's just cos driving to <anon type="place"/> it like it in terms of like miles it's not that far but it's just a boring road to go up the A one M</u>
<u n="596" who="S0441">it's just long</u>
<u n="597" who="S0439">it takes like forty minutes doesn't it? forty minutes something like that?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0439">thirty-five minutes to get to <anon type="place"/> forty minutes</u>
<u n="600" who="S0441">I'm just going to claim for that</u>
<u n="601" who="S0439">er?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0441">I'm going to claim it back</u>
<u n="603" who="S0439">I would yeah if you can claim it back I would <pause dur="short"/> cos <trunc>pet</trunc> have you noticed now that petrol is more expensive than diesel?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0439">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0441">not good</u>
<u n="607" who="S0439">what is going on there? who hates us and why?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0441">I think it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was telling me that it's something to do with I don't know one it's it's the first time it's happened in like thirty years</u>
<u n="609" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0441">and one supermarket did it and then everyone sort of followed through or something</u>
<u n="611" who="S0439">it's just so annoying cos like</u>
<u n="612" who="S0441">really annoying</u>
<u n="613" who="S0439">yeah petrol is still like one pound sixteen seventeen eighteen and petrol's one pound fourteen what the <trunc>fu</trunc> or diesel's one pound fourteen what the hell? not impressed</u>
<u n="614" who="S0441">it's not cool is it?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0439">no all these diesel people being like ah ah ah in your face bastards bastards with their diesel cars being more economically friendly than us</u>
<u n="616" who="S0441">I think it's trying to encourage people to have diesel cars</u>
<u n="617" who="S0439">I think that's probably yeah probably is why</u>
<u n="618" who="S0441">can't be I thought is it going to be? surely it's not going to be permanent?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0439">I don't know but do you remember when petrol went up to like one pound thirty?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0441">yes</u>
<u n="621" who="S0439">I think I paid one pound thirty-two once fuming</u>
<u n="622" who="S0441">I think I have as well on on the motorway</u>
<u n="623" who="S0439" trans="overlap">on the motorway yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0441">oops</u>
<u n="625" who="S0439">well you have to if you're stuck on the motorway with no bloody petrol what else are you going to do?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0441">exactly</u>
<u n="627" who="S0439">breakdown on principle?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0441">ah I went to I went next door</u>
<u n="629" who="S0439">oh did you?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0441">to tell them that we were having a party just to make them aware</u>
<u n="631" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0441">she was like yeah she's really nice actually she's like yeah that's fine no problem like we're going to go to the cinema anyway so just that's fine with us no problem</u>
<u n="633" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0441">she was like oh by the way are you from the <anon type="place"/> area? and I was like we went to school in <anon type="place"/> she was like</u>
<u n="635" who="S0439">oh really?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0441">she went to <anon type="place"/> as well</u>
<u n="637" who="S0439">oh wow</u>
<u n="638" who="S0441">but like</u>
<u n="639" who="S0439">years ago</u>
<u n="640" who="S0441">ninety-eight she left</u>
<u n="641" who="S0439">oh how does she know?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0441">I don't know how she knew that we were from the <anon type="place"/> area it's a bit weird but</u>
<u n="643" who="S0439">it is a bit weird we don't scream <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0441">how could she? cos like I didn't really think about this before I just thought it was really cool but now thinking about that's quite strange that she knew</u>
<u n="645" who="S0439">unless maybe like one of us was in the garden one day and we might have mentioned <anon type="place"/> or something <pause dur="long"/> no <pause dur="long"/> no like I've been out in the garden maybe a few times with like when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came over a few times we sat in the garden but I don't know maybe</u>
<u n="646" who="S0441">weird</u>
<u n="647" who="S0439">weird although I met one of the girls in my team at work she went to <anon type="place"/> school</u>
<u n="648" who="S0441">really?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0439">yeah cos we were talking she said she was going home for the weekend she was in <anon type="place"/> I was like oh I live near <anon type="place"/> kinda you know</u>
<u n="650" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="651" who="S0439">near <anon type="place"/> she goes oh yeah I went to <anon type="place"/> I was like so did I</u>
<u n="652" who="S0441">weird</u>
<u n="653" who="S0439">weird she went in like I think she was six years above me</u>
<u n="654" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="655" who="S0439">five or six years above us so she was in sixth form when we just started</u>
<u n="656" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="657" who="S0439">but still I was like</u>
<u n="658" who="S0441" trans="overlap">still weird</u>
<u n="659" who="S0439">we went to the same school</u>
<u n="660" who="S0441">small world</u>
<u n="661" who="S0439">yeah it's weird when you like know the same teachers and stuff it's just like oh god</u>
<u n="662" who="S0441">yeah weirdo Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0439">oh god Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he's been there for well he was there for donkey's years</u>
<u n="665" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah he's retired now hasn't he?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0441">he has</u>
<u n="667" who="S0439">he retired quite a few years ago now</u>
<u n="668" who="S0441">yeah he did</u>
<u n="669" who="S0439">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is head of head of sixth form now isn't he?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0441">I think so he was an absolute dick</u>
<u n="671" who="S0439">yeah I hated <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so much</u>
<u n="672" who="S0441" trans="overlap">he was horrible</u>
<u n="673" who="S0439">he was a complete knob</u>
<u n="674" who="S0441"><unclear/> human being</u>
<u n="675" who="S0439" trans="overlap">horrible obnoxious and arrogant er and apparently Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is like really anorexic</u>
<u n="676" who="S0441">oh really?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0439">yeah severely anorexic</u>
<u n="678" who="S0441">not a very good role model is it?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0439">especially not for a PE teacher</u>
<u n="680" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="681" who="S0439">but oh well not very much we can do</u>
<u n="682" who="S0441">is she actually anorexic or just thin?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0439">I don't know apparently she's like really she looks really bad</u>
<u n="684" who="S0441">mm anyone actually approached her about this or just gonna talk about it?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0439">no idea probably just like everybody else talk about it behind their back and hope that she decides to eat something</u>
<u n="686" who="S0441">poor woman</u>
<u n="687" who="S0439">yeah I really liked her when she was my teacher</u>
<u n="688" who="S0441">yeah she's nice</u>
<u n="689" who="S0439">mm oh well I need a cup of tea you want a cup of tea?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0441">erm yes please</u>
<u n="691" who="S0439">I love how English people just love just love tea so much</u>
<u n="692" who="S0441">we do we do</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
