<text id="S7MU">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Washing machine, food, family, films</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking at home</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">it's so naughty that washing machine</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">it's it's it's just</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">oh but you looked it up didn't you the make?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">it's just crap isn't it? Yeah it's like a rebranded rebadged thing <pause dur="short"/> so I did that fast <pause dur="short"/> I did that perhaps too fast <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">here y'are let me do it <pause dur="short"/> let me try</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">no it's alright <pause dur="short"/> no no you've gotta <trunc>re</trunc> you've gotta turn it on and off again</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh na na</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">no no no it's stuck on the previous one it thinks it's the previous one</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh no no wait <pause dur="short"/> no no it doesn't</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115" trans="overlap">hold on hold on <pause dur="short"/> turn it off and on</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just no it doesn't</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115">hold on wait a minute wait a minute</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">that doesn't mean anything</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah like we're gonna  we're gonna  turn it off like it's like turn it off you do it and you just slowly turn it round yeah?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Cos you wouldn't do that normally <pause dur="short"/> let me try my way first</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">but that way doesn't</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037">well how d'you know?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="18" who="S0115">no no it's fixed for that isn't it it's fixed to check you just</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but it keeps deciding between the two</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">oh we've got it no there's sixty</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037" trans="overlap">this wants to be sixty</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">uh no no if you do it fast it's definitely not gonna work uh if you do it fast</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">yeah but that's the way I always do it</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">no no it doesn't</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah look</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">oh you've got it <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> uh I'm uh <pause dur="short"/> I assumed  I assumed  that you had to do it slowly</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Don't think it's about the speed</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">no it's it's the thing behind obviously isn't properly catching is it?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">well I don't know what it is <pause dur="short"/> it's just a bit idiosyncratic</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah well it's it's um</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">yeah it's just that it's got me work skirt and stuff in but I mean obviously I've got other things but I may as well wash them</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well this is is just an annoying it's just an annoying uh I think that's like</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah it's done <pause dur="short"/> it's done now</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no this is uh</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">huh?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">it's got a skin on it that mayonnaise</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">oh yeah maybe it's setting a bit</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">I'll stick it in um</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh maybe the old mayonnaise jar actually is there not?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">I threw that away yeah we we need a smaller one really</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">uh oh we'll have some <pause dur="short"/> we always have like</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">no cos I think I've chucked everything</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037">you you chucked all the jars? What about the up the top?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115">although we can nick this um horseradish</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">yeah if it's empty <pause dur="short"/> oh Matt you've left that on the side look</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and is it? Oh yeah I know  I know  what that is <pause dur="short"/> uh I'll just uh um yeah I'll check that is horseradish</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">yeah it'll probably be past its best <pause dur="short"/> you should put those in the fridge though</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">we don't have much beef do we?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">beef?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">I was supposed to make up that moose</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037">well aye you can do it tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I can come in you'll have made us a Pavlova or something</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">hmm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">I hope it's quiet at work tomorrow</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> d'you d'you think it will be?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">well I had quite a busy week last week so hopefully it'll be quieter but um I've got a few things I've carried over from last week to do so</u>
<event desc="sound of bowl"/>
<u n="56" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The uh the what?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">those those bowls are really like sonorant aren't they like a few times in the morning I've tried to get one out of the um cupboard and it's been like boong and I've thought oh that'll wake you up</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">that's a nice sound that is</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">well it's alright I mean</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115">like church bells <pause dur="short"/> there was a programme about that</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> about the order of them?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they're they're a right racket aren't they?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">can be <pause dur="short"/> yeah like at your uh your mam's it's like</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">Bell ringers</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">it's really loud on a Monday night <pause dur="short"/> I do like <anon type="place"/> though</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">uh yeah yeah I love <anon type="place"/> it's nice and um <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice sort of cheery place isn't it?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">but I don't know if <trunc>w</trunc> like we can go back on your mam's birthday I think it might be a bit like</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">no but we we're not  we're not  um planning to do that we're just uh</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037">oh the rest of her text messaging might've come I'll come I'll go and check</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115">it'll be exciting <unclear/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0037">no it hasn't</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="72" who="S0037">no just half of it <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">I think horseradish is a bit underused like <pause dur="short"/> could uh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">it's nice with salmon and stuff isn't it like with fish</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">um what we having for tea tomorrow?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">we've got  we've got  salmon as well and I've just thrown the horseradish away</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">have we got salmon really?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">we've got trout haven't we?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">no we had that last week</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">oh oh right <pause dur="short"/> well uh fair enough</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">got mackerel</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">yeah we'll have  we'll have  that then tomorrow like <pause dur="short"/> I'll get it out <pause dur="short"/> d'you wanna get it out?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">yeah sorry <pause dur="short"/> am I in the way <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> just had the other bit of your text message</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="85" who="S0037">there you go</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="86" who="S0037">okay <pause dur="short"/> the rest of your text message has arrived <pause dur="short"/> shall I read the full thing again or?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">uh yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037">okay it says Hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> how are you? Have you been able to get out in the lovely sunshine today? We've had <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">as long as there's nothing embarrassing in there</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">we've <trunc>ha</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> We've had a four mile walk along the canal at <anon type="place"/> where we went when you had an interview for bar work a few years ago <pause dur="short"/> it was lovely <pause dur="short"/> the new dog enables us to <trunc>w</trunc> malk sorry to walk much more briskly than we have been lately with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> is the PhD still coming on well? Kiss kiss kiss <pause dur="short"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="91" who="S0037">I suppose Sunday is the day for getting in touch with family</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">is it?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">no I mean like our <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="94" who="S0115" trans="overlap">easter is a possible opportunity</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">easter's a possible opportunity</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">festivals innit? You can get together with your family at Easter</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">you mean you want to or?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">you can I mean <pause dur="short"/> no I was just saying that people can <pause dur="short"/> I think what this is doing is it's congealing <pause dur="short"/> and uh creating like lumps</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">ah it'll be fine <pause dur="short"/> it was nice in the um in the sandwich</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">sort of solidified hasn't it? Yolk is very uh very sort of thick isn't it? When it hardens it doesn't sort of</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">like um quite quite a pain to get off <pause dur="short"/> but egg's a pain isn't it cos you said when you were in uh <anon type="place"/> people had to pay like hundreds of pounds if they'd  if they'd  like spilled an egg</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">if they'd like smashed an egg and like it would take masses of effort to clean it off</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">yeah no I mean it wasn't um <pause dur="short"/> I suppose that should do with some qualifying like it wasn't if you'd spilt an egg you got paid hundreds of pounds but</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah there was just threw it yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if you'd trashed your kitchen and you'd thrown eggs everywhere</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037">like there was one guy who'd thrown eggs everywhere and they'd got all in like the fire um what's it called you know the <trunc>h</trunc> the fire sensor</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they'd had like a big fight and he'd like thrown like eggs everywhere and they'd got in there</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">and like <pause dur="short"/> you know they're like it's like glue it goes so hard and crusty that you can't <pause dur="short"/> like it just had to be replaced</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037">so that was like you know some amount of money to do that</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">but if you're gonna get drunk and chuck eggs around then that's what you get really</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">yeah I mean that's kind of the problem with uh with like <pause dur="short"/> but we were talking about tuition fees that um a lot of people think that you know university's just like like a big party then</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115">it it makes it harder to justify uh funding it through the state</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well even if it is a big party like people have different ideas about <trunc>bout</trunc> what a big party means <pause dur="short"/> for me big party doesn't mean like cracking the eggs out and just scrambling them all over your flat like</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037">like <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean? There's limits isn't there like? Even I <trunc>th</trunc> I suppose even if I was totally out of me mind</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah a lot  a lot  of the youth of today <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm like an old like a granddad aren't I?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037">well a bit but that's why I like you</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you know <pause dur="short"/> today's young people</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037">no but even if I was really you know had had loads of beer or whatever I don't think I would ever I I could never entertain the idea of like smashing eggs everywhere it doesn't seem like a good plan and I don't know what I would gain from that</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">and in fact I've never really understood people who do that like who smash things and mess things up when they're</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115" trans="overlap">smashers?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037">like I can understand people who</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I am not a smasher</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">you know people get caught like going for wees in different places and stuff <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Inside washing machines?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037">but <trunc>th</trunc> there's an element of you know you need to go and okay maybe you don't choose the best place or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so I can <pause dur="short"/> I never would condone it and I would never do it meself but I can <pause dur="short"/> I have an element of sort of compassion or I can sort of see why that might happen but things like just <trunc>m</trunc> just smashing things or just throwing things out of windows or</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037">I mean I saw a lot of it</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037">when I was an assistant dean but <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">yeah I mean this was probably a lot of that sort of stuff <pause dur="short"/> there was uh in that job like you knew you could see from their point of view so</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037">of course I mean</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115">but</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037">but I think we always give like we always did give people <trunc>u</trunc> the benefit of the doubt like we always got them in and let them like explain like what they were doing</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037">or why they were doing it <pause dur="short"/> and like from time to time we did get people in who were saying who would say things like I'd been out and I'd got really drunk because my nana had died and my dad had died my <pause dur="short"/> I'd had a really bad thing and <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well that's terrible using that as an excuse isn't it?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037">and like <pause dur="short"/> no but if if it had happened and if  and if  that was why they were doing that like we did always cut them some slack but <pause dur="short"/> it's when you get idiots in going muh I just wanted to like</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah well I guess uh <pause dur="short"/> the rugby team <pause dur="short"/> the rugby team mooning the uh Chancellor <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know like it when you get people doing stuff like that it's just</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">that was a legendary you know it's like Animal House have you ever seen that?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037">I have seen Animal House</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115" trans="overlap">think I tried to show you that <pause dur="short"/> great comedy but in reality it's just a few bad apples uh is it it's good comedy but obviously you don't wanna be like that in <pause dur="short"/> yeah I <trunc>vid</trunc> yeah I videoed it and didn't have the start yet <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">you know in reality like</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what's the soup like?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I just like assumed that it was okay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0037">is it?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115">I'll taste it now when it's new</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it doesn't look as thick as normal but I'm sure it'd be nice</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">right well d'you want me to do anything to rectify that?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no no no it doesn't need to be thick</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037">oh thank you <pause dur="short"/> oh it's really good <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I think it's got quite a nice taste</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037">it's quite sort of spicy <pause dur="short"/> it's nice</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115">yeah I maybe put a little bit too much chilli in there but uh that's fine</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I don't think you did I think it's nice <pause dur="short"/> I think um with um</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">you can't go wrong with a butternut squash I think</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">it is a nice it's that sweetness is good um <pause dur="short"/> useful uh</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">you can't go very far wrong</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037">few lentils</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">yeah I</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">what you gonna do with that mackerel tomorrow?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115">put it like two two garlics and the bacon went in</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0115">uh I dunno <pause dur="short"/> um up to you really what whatever you wanna um</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037">dunno it's just</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115">uh what you would you <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's kinda nice just with</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">maybe something like um Chinesey just um</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037">I quite like mackerel just just <trunc>grill</trunc> like just cooked like by itself it's very tasty <pause dur="short"/> doesn't need much</u>
<u n="186" who="S0115" trans="overlap">noodles and that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you just grill it and then you have it like you can have it with some Chinese style noodles or something</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037">yeah that sounds nice</u>
<u n="188" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I'd like yeah like so maybe to to do a kinda curry style would be interesting to see <pause dur="short"/> or Thai like a Thai thing</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dunno it's quite it's got quite a strong taste in itself hasn't it like? I normally just put like salt and pepper on and just like <trunc>s</trunc> either shallow fry it or grill it or something it's nice</u>
<u n="190" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> thai style sauce might be interesting but uh uh that's that yeah so um</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037">you should tell your mam that you</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115" trans="overlap">did you <trunc>s</trunc> did you say what <trunc>wa</trunc> what as your favourite film? Did you say?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037">ever?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I could be pinned down to one thing like it's the same with anything like I've got different like I've my best number one sentimental film would probably be like Calamity Jane</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I um yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">but then I've got like I suppose you know films that you sort of know are good</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037">you know like <pause dur="short"/> and then maybe films that you enjoy <trunc>li</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well film <trunc>cri</trunc> critically acclaimed film yeah and then like like a guilty pleasure of like a Steven Segal film</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="204" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0037">there's a lot of those <pause dur="short"/> and there's a lot of the films</u>
<u n="206" who="S0115" trans="overlap">executive Decision</u>
<u n="207" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it depends what type of film you like because like I can see like like we were saying the other day like I can see a lot of the like why I dunno Love Actually might be a good film but it's just not a film that I like</u>
<u n="208" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0037">that doesn't mean it's a bad film it just means it's not the sort of film I like <pause dur="short"/> whereas like um</u>
<u n="210" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0037">I dunno like um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="212" who="S0037">die Hard might might not be like a cinematic masterpiece</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah I think that that was your favourite wasn't it Die Hard?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">I like Die Hard a lot and</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">it's a good one popular with the Americans isn't it?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I like <trunc>s</trunc> I like some of the um I like a James Bond and I like uh</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">D'you like Alan Rickman cos my Aunt Betty had a real fondness for Alan Rickman</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I do like Alan Rickman <pause dur="short"/> not not as much as your Auntie Betty like but uh I do like him</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">like I think she just likes evil men <pause dur="short"/> I think that's</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> each to their own</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115" trans="overlap">particularly ones with sort of posh accents and strange foreign accents</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">hello <pause dur="short"/> No</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">no he <pause dur="short"/> it was a great he he's got a great sort of voice and but him in uh Die Hard is really <trunc>f</trunc> really funny and his his accent like</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah he's good in that</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you know like uh</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">let me think what what does he say uh</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">the <trunc>w</trunc> he's got the watch on hasn't he?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">he's got his voice is really you know he's got that sort of sound the tone of voice isn't he he's very he's quite funny and uh um <pause dur="short"/> there's also is it Jeremy Irons who does like like a Disney like Disney an evil guy</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">in a <trunc>e</trunc> evil English accent like um</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">have you seen um</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">like uh</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">chariots Of Fire with Jeremy Irons?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">uh no I haven't seen Chariots Of Fire <pause dur="short"/> is he in the  is he in the  Lion King?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's set in Cambridge you know?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">was it?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">hm <pause dur="short"/> no I didn't uh uh I haven't seen that film</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you should watch it <pause dur="short"/> to get ready for the Olympics you know?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">I've seen a lot of parody like it was successful wasn't it so? I've seen a lot of parodies like it's a <trunc>par</trunc> it's a parody in uh you know National Lampoon's Vacation</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I watched that ages ago <pause dur="short"/> there's some films that I really should've like I don't haven't seen many of the um Star Wars ones</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">na <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Bit overrated that isn't it? I think</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I haven't seen any so <pause dur="short"/> I might like them I might like really like them</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh I like <trunc>s</trunc> I like science fiction particularly the idea of science fiction <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to read more uh H G Wells stuff</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">Jules Verne he's a bit more like exploration <pause dur="short"/> there was a lot of good stuff like uh like the uh Blade Runner and um</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">yeah Blade Runner's good</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">them sorts of ones where it's like it's like the idea of Blade Runner was was like getting on to the ethics of it like</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">you know like do do androids dream of um electric sheep or something?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dunno what <trunc>b</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I quite like Indian <pause dur="short"/> Philip K Dick that was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">yeah Philip K Dick yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">there's also Isaac Asimov and uh</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">I quite like uh Indiana Jones</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">yeah that's really a lot of fun like um you know racing around in the desert with Nazis chasing you and like</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">I liked their sort of silly voice <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I don't <pause dur="short"/> memento was a really good film but it's very like it's very involving like it's it's not Indiana Jones is it?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115" trans="overlap">memento's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> it's it's plot is just <trunc>tr</trunc> this crazy plot like that that style of <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah well it it's more serious and cos it's more it's ethically a bit like it's a bit of a psychological drama isn't it and uh Memento like makes you think you know you've got a narrator and the narrator <pause dur="short"/> you've you've potentially got an evil narrator haven't you so?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">like you can't really side with <pause dur="short"/> it's it's ambiguous you know like? you know it's not like a <trunc>tradi</trunc> traditional granddad's film where it's just like the goodies and the baddies are like shooting everybody</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> but I do like some of the films that I watch with me grandda as well like Zulu have you seen that?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">yeah well that's that's that's more of a granddad film innit?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">and um</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">I haven't  I haven't  actually seen it but uh</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037">watched a lot of films with me grandda like um Bridge Over The <trunc>Ri</trunc> River Kwai and um</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115">that was about the ethnic yeah the ethnic Zulus um but they lost didn't they? They they had their</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">they they had their uh they were trying to fight for their own land weren't they?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">the Eagle Has Landed and those kinda ones</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">war films really I suppose <pause dur="short"/> after his extensive military experience <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> one of those uh <pause dur="short"/> don't mention like don't mention the war with some people like he'll start talking about his war stories</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">well he wasn't even in the war he wasn't even old enough</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115">he he his story <trunc>l</trunc> he had  he had  quite a good story like like the one about the uh</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">it I mean it still must've been something like okay he wasn't in the war but it still must've been scary to go into like Malaysia and that mustn't it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it'd be pretty horrible yeah I mean I'd I'd hate to be in in that situation where you've got</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just be sent there <pause dur="short"/> and he's <trunc>chew</trunc></u>
<event desc="sound of bangs"/>
<u n="279" who="S0037">sorry <pause dur="short"/> it's my fault</u>
<u n="280" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like it was a very noisy pepper pot</u>
<u n="281" who="S0037">sorry <pause dur="short"/> it hasn't damaged that has it?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no it was  it was  um <pause dur="short"/> no it's alright <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="283" who="S0037">sorry about that</u>
<u n="284" who="S0115">no I'd hate to be in in in uh like a in the army in military combat like <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's all very well staying fit and surviving you know survival training is good</u>
<u n="285" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0115"><unclear/> like <pause dur="short"/> no it's horrible just having to <trunc>f</trunc> you know you know to put your life at risk and you you know going into places where you know that someone's trying to kill you yeah I mean that's pretty pretty</u>
<u n="287" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but it's <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty bad <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's funny that he was sure that he was in there with <trunc>M</trunc> with Michael Parkinson <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>In</trunc> inhumane isn't it? Well he claimed he was I mean we don't know for certain</u>
<u n="289" who="S0037">it's probably just one of me grandda's <trunc>tale</trunc> tall tale or uh</u>
<u n="290" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like you know I don't doubt that Michael Parkinson perhaps is a bit of a wimp</u>
<u n="291" who="S0037">me grandda said he was if it was him <pause dur="short"/> he said he was called Michael Parkinson but obviously it might not have been Michael Parkinson but they were in the same regiment</u>
<u n="292" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think you'd have  you'd have  <trunc>recogni</trunc> you'd have know wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0037">me grandda thinks it was him but</u>
<u n="294" who="S0115">quite a common name though unfortunately</u>
<u n="295" who="S0037" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> but he was from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I mean yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Big county</u>
<u n="297" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but he said he was a right wimp <pause dur="short"/> but obviously it's me grandda so <pause dur="short"/> he's probably just saying anything</u>
<u n="298" who="S0115">what part of England would you live in ideally?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0037">me well I'm a bit biased <pause dur="short"/> I like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0115" trans="overlap"> <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0037">you mean forever? I'd like to have a number of</u>
<u n="302" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just like if you could live anywhere you wanted</u>
<u n="303" who="S0037">I'd like to have like a flat in London <pause dur="short"/> a place like in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0115">the Highlands</u>
<u n="305" who="S0037">A little hidey hole in the Highlands <pause dur="short"/> Edinburgh maybe</u>
<u n="306" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like a cabin like a castle in uh like Cornwall</u>
<u n="307" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you know there's a lot of places I haven't been like I've never been to like Cornwall exactly or the Southwest I've never even been there like <pause dur="short"/> the nearest I've been's probably Bournemouth or something and that's not even very near at all</u>
<u n="308" who="S0115">no although they do have the uh rhotic accent</u>
<u n="309" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0115">in Bournemouth <pause dur="short"/> what we on?</u>
</body>
</text>
