<text id="S7NH">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:38:18</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-31</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0083 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics></topics>
		<activity>Family chatting </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0083">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Essex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0084">did you sleep alright?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0083">it is chilly isn't it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0083">well I woke up early and I I did drop off again so</u>
<u n="5" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0083">but it is annoying to do that <pause dur="short"/> and I  and I  often do <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> well there's nothing else to do</u>
<u n="7" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> the nice weather might come back next week</u>
<u n="8" who="S0083">well hopefully <pause dur="short"/> basically <pause dur="short"/> you never tell can you with these with the English weather</u>
<u n="9" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="10" who="S0083">anyway</u>
<u n="11" who="S0084">well it did say it was going to rain on Tuesday</u>
<u n="12" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="13" who="S0084">so erm are any of the groups you're in organising protests around the Jubilee or the Olympics or anything? Cos the unions have threatened to disrupt the Olympics haven't they? No <pause dur="short"/> or was it the guy who runs the tubes or something? Well they're they're threatening to have a tube</u>
<u n="14" who="S0083" trans="overlap">not that I'm aware of</u>
<u n="15" who="S0084">I can't I thought it was someone from who was a a union member but anyway he erm he was speaking and I think it was when the tube drivers were threatening to strike and he was saying <pause dur="short"/> he probably was just misquoted <pause dur="short"/> or they'd use his quote to erm make him sound worse than he actually is</u>
<u n="16" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0084">but he was saying you know the the way to get people's attention would be to strike or to protest during the Olympics <pause dur="short"/> and everyone was up in arms <pause dur="short"/> oh my God <pause dur="short"/> can't allow this <pause dur="short"/> but since then I was reading on The Guardian I think the other day that erm other protest groups were saying that they would use the Olympics as like a focal point</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="18" who="S0083">well clearly the authorities are really worried about a terrorist attack</u>
<u n="19" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh did I tell you  has got a job in counterterrorism?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0083">oh my God</u>
<u n="21" who="S0084"><trunc>Counter</trunc> well I haven't got the full full er full description but she's moving <pause dur="short"/> so it's all in the Foreign Office</u>
<u n="22" who="S0083">mhm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0084">working in the counterterrorism department erm mainly covering the Olympics <pause dur="short"/> so it would be really interesting to find out how that's going to work <pause dur="short"/> cattle prods</u>
<u n="24" who="S0083">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> as know there's a very simply solution</u>
<u n="25" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="26" who="S0084">I'm so bored with the Olympics</u>
<u n="27" who="S0083">well there there is that but we just need to get out of the Middle East</u>
<u n="28" who="S0084">oh I see what you mean yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's not going to happen <pause dur="short"/> once they invade <trunc>Ir</trunc> Iran</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="29" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="30" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> must have got the bus</u>
<u n="31" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she often does</u>
<u n="32" who="S0084">does she?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0083">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="34" who="S0083">I think she's so tired by the end of the day</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0083">cycling home is a real strain</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0083">and obviously <trunc>star</trunc> you know she's she's not really a morning person erm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="40" who="S0083">but she's she comes home absolutely exhausted</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0083">Cos she's just  she's just  standing all day <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0083">running up and down stairs all day <pause dur="short"/> well you remember what it was like</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">I've done it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084">and it is exhausting</u>
<u n="48" who="S0083">it is very very tiring yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">well I was thinking about this yesterday <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember whether I was I would come home and pass out for the entire evening <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I did <pause dur="short"/> I was tired <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I was as bad as her and I wonder if that's an iron <trunc>d</trunc> deficiency <pause dur="short"/> you know it's natural that you're going to be physically tired but</u>
<u n="50" who="S0083">to be as tired as she gets yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">at her age</u>
<u n="52" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">I suppose though <pause dur="short"/> if this was <anon type="place"/> her friends were still here and had her social life and so she would go out so it would make her carry on</u>
<u n="54" who="S0083">she didn't go out that much though</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">no but she hasn't really had the opportunity to do it here <pause dur="short"/> I think if her life was here you know she'd made friends here more than she has</u>
<u n="56" who="S0083">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">she would just go out</u>
<u n="58" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> she would go out more than she does <pause dur="short"/> that's true <pause dur="long"/> I mean the only thing is that she's managed to save a lot of money by doing this and</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">mhm <pause dur="long"/> Absolutely</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="60" who="S0083">she always did need a lot of sleep though didn't she?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0083">I mean as a kid you did but even up to her teenage years when she was at school and college and whatever she still needed about ten hours sleep a night</u>
<u n="63" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0083">and people used to joke about it</u>
<u n="65" who="S0084">yeah but as we've said before she's not very good at putting on a front for people is she <pause dur="short"/> if you're you know if everybody else is tired you just muddle on through and I I feel like I spend my whole life tired <pause dur="short"/> I don't catch up with sleep at the weekend <pause dur="short"/> I'm absolutely exhausted <pause dur="short"/> it gets to Sunday and I'm still</u>
<u n="66" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well you should <pause dur="short"/> you should try</u>
<u n="67" who="S0084">I do try</u>
<u n="68" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0084">I feel like I have a</u>
<u n="70" who="S0083">is the house very noisy at the weekend then?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0084">no I just wake up and I can't go back to sleep and then you know they do but they do get up early <pause dur="short"/> you know even so when I'm awake they don't wake me up necessarily but I'm I wake up early and I'm stirring so</u>
<u n="72" who="S0083">you're aware of them yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s up putting her washing on at half eight and and rooting about and</u>
<u n="74" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0084">every other weekend she and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will work on a Saturday</u>
<u n="76" who="S0083">oh right</u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">so it's not ideal but it does do feel good</u>
<u n="78" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I suppose you're at the front <pause dur="short"/> you hear the door go don't you?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the bikes from the bike rack from outside my window</u>
<u n="80" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0084">and all the noisy neighbours</u>
<u n="82" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084">I think there's like erm a training <pause dur="short"/> like a boot camp or something cos often at sort of half five six in the morning just before I'm getting up for work during the week a group of lads will run past shouting at each other <pause dur="short"/> happens every week</u>
<u n="84" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">it's really annoying</u>
<u n="86" who="S0083">oh lovely</u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="long"/> So I just feel tired a lot of the time and most people do I think <pause dur="short"/> like I'm looking forward to next week so next Wednesday I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I will go to <anon type="place"/> <trunc>dri</trunc> and leave at a reasonable time</u>
<u n="88" who="S0083">mhm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0084">and then Thursday I think  doesn't get in until the afternoon</u>
<u n="90" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="91" who="S0084">she's got the day off but she's got a few things to do so</u>
<u n="92" who="S0083">mhm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0084">she won't get here until about three or four o'clock in the afternoon so that's really nice <pause dur="short"/> I can have a lazy day</u>
<u n="94" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0084">and I think she'll probably just stay till Friday because she's got family stuff on</u>
<u n="96" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I can imagine</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="97" who="S0084">and then I've got Saturday Sunday Monday just to catch up with sleep and potter about</u>
<u n="98" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and come over here one day</u>
<u n="99" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0083">erm <pause dur="long"/> So you aren't able to get back to sleep after that <pause dur="short"/> cos what I do find is <pause dur="short"/> I mean if it's quiet and if I'm tired and I've taken Nytol I can sometimes sleep in <pause dur="short"/> and even if I don't I'm still sleepy enough that I can go back to sleep</u>
<u n="101" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="102" who="S0083">Cos I never used to be able to do that</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">no I can't do that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0083">but it obviously didn't help you to do that</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084">no I just lay there for about forty minutes</u>
<u n="106" who="S0083" trans="overlap">maybe take two then</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0083">I mean I think it's fine to take two <pause dur="short"/> I just thought as you weren't used to them</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0083">to start with one</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">ease yourself in yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0083">you take two and just buy a packet and have it <pause dur="short"/> actually look be careful cos there are two strengths <pause dur="short"/> erm buy a packet and take take them at weekends <pause dur="short"/> see if that helps you sleep in at the weekend</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="114" who="S0083">well it is your body clock <pause dur="short"/> cos that's what Dad was like and that's why he was always up early at weekends <pause dur="short"/> he could never sleep in</u>
<u n="115" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0083">and he was always tired and complaining and I just think for God's sake just sleep <pause dur="short"/> well he he never gave himself a <trunc>cha</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't know whether he would have been able to but he never gave himself a chance so once he was awake he was out of bed</u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">yeah I mean that's it <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="118" who="S0083">he would never lie there reading or try and go back to sleep <pause dur="short"/> he would just get up</u>
<u n="119" who="S0084">I mean I do lay in bed and I I think that's you know at least you can do that <pause dur="short"/> at least it's restful</u>
<u n="120" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">but I suppose if you know I used to remember getting up early and watching cartoons and stuff and he'd come down but I suppose because we were up even if we were being quiet</u>
<u n="122" who="S0083" trans="overlap">he was awake anyway</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084">yeah I know well it's not that we woke him up but I suppose he thought well if the kids are up I might as well get up <pause dur="short"/> there's no point lazing around</u>
<u n="124" who="S0083">he wanted a <pause dur="short"/> well when you were very young it was to keep an eye on you yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">yeah but if you think that <pause dur="short"/> sometimes I do think well you're wasting the day if you just lay around the bed when you're awake <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's nice to read or it's nice to watch a movie or read the paper or whatever but er I do think well I might as well get up</u>
<u n="126" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">have you know make the most of of the day</u>
<u n="128" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">whereas <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could sleep <pause dur="short"/> I've never known anyone like it <pause dur="short"/> she'll come home and she'll sleep in the evening then she'll sleep all night <pause dur="short"/> she'll sleep in at the weekend you know she might sleep in at one in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> it's unbelievable <pause dur="short"/> I mean she did go to the doctor to see if it was a thyroid thing because she was always always sleeping and she was having trouble shifting her weight like possibly from the thyroid</u>
<u n="130" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> how's her leg?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084">the same <pause dur="short"/> all of the bruising's gone now but it's just this lump</u>
<u n="132" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084">it's really big <pause dur="short"/> if she did say she was going to start training on it cos that's what the nurse said to do</u>
<u n="134" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">Cos they weren't going to drain it <pause dur="short"/> so either way just you know if it bursts then they'll have to do something about it and if it doesn't then at least it's still draining so</u>
<u n="136" who="S0083">hello <pause dur="long"/> It's very cute when you see cats washing their face like that <pause dur="short"/> it's very cute</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">he's sleepy <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0083">that was a fed up sigh</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">mm I've got toothache as well <pause dur="short"/> my wisdom teeth are coming through</u>
<u n="140" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">well it's this one at the moment <pause dur="short"/> this is the one that I knew was coming through and when I went to him <unclear/> One of it was for <trunc>j</trunc> before Christmas <pause dur="short"/> he said yeah it's coming through</u>
<u n="142" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">and I've got to get my</u>
<u n="144" who="S0083">and it's all okay?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">my six month coming up <pause dur="short"/> what do you mean? What coming through okay? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't hurting before <pause dur="short"/> I could just feel it whereas it's hurting now</u>
<u n="146" who="S0083">is there room for it?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm going to go and speak to my orthodontist <pause dur="short"/> I've got my six month follow up in April</u>
<u n="148" who="S0083">mhm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084">erm he might say take them out <pause dur="short"/> cos that was the question <pause dur="short"/> whether we extract them to make room for my teeth and then that would correct the over bite <pause dur="short"/> and I said no let's not bother <pause dur="short"/> at least they're straight <pause dur="short"/> if they're coming through we might have to because it sort of force the teeth out of alignment which is a bit horrendous <pause dur="short"/> I mean when people have actual operations you get sick leave from work <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether to have your teeth extracted it would be the you'd be able to do the the same thing <pause dur="short"/> they're pretty understanding</u>
<u n="150" who="S0083">I would imagine <pause dur="short"/> cos wisdom teeth is is quite a big thing</u>
<u n="151" who="S0084" trans="overlap">is pretty serious and if they're going to do all of them <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't <pause dur="short"/> they're coming through on the on both the back and I don't know but I can't feel the top</u>
<u n="152" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084">I can feel <pause dur="short"/> I well I think I can feel them but I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> if he says well I'll just whip them out <pause dur="short"/> that's going to be quite intense <pause dur="short"/> it's going to require a couple of days off work I think cos well people have <trunc>s</trunc> from what people have said it's extremely painful so</u>
<u n="154" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it is it's very painful <pause dur="short"/> it is I remember</u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">did you have all four out?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0083">no three</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084">three <pause dur="short"/> what age were you?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0083">it was after I'd had one of you <pause dur="short"/> I think it was probably after I'd had Richard <pause dur="short"/> cos it was a long time ago erm they <event desc="recording skips"/> <unclear/> which I think means they'd they'd broken up</u>
<u n="159" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="160" who="S0083">and they just <event desc="recording skips"/> <unclear/> I actually had erm I had anaesthetic cos it was really bad</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084">I thought that's what it what you mean general? Oh right</u>
<u n="162" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0083">and I was terrified at at having them out cos it was it they're huge things and it it was unbelievably painful</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what afterwards?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0083">very painful <pause dur="short"/> yeah you just keep yourself dosed up for</u>
<u n="169" who="S0084">mm Jesus</u>
<u n="170" who="S0083">a couple of days <pause dur="short"/> well I mean it's it is painful <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've had much worse so don't</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084">yeah but only childbirth <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0083">oh no no there's  It's just very painful cos anything  in your  in your head hurts very much</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0083">headaches hurt</u>
<u n="175" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0083">you know</u>
<u n="177" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think this might be the time because this hurts so <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't know if the pain is it coming up through the gum? I don't I mean  I don't  I don't understand what the pain is but it started hurting yesterday</u>
<u n="178" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I mean no wonder children cry when their teeth are coming through because it's painful</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well  if you can't  if you can't say the words</u>
<u n="180" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0084">yeah it is painful</u>
<u n="182" who="S0083">go and see <unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I'll see if I can't put up with the pain then I will but erm for the time being so I'm going to go to the orthodontist anyway</u>
<u n="184" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well no you said you've got your <trunc>ap</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> when is it?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0084">mm in mid April I think</u>
<u n="186" who="S0083">well that's not too far away</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="188" who="S0083">come on then <pause dur="short"/> come on</u>
<event desc="sound of calling a cat"/>
<u n="189" who="S0083">I know you want to come up here <pause dur="short"/> come on <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> he likes to sit with me if he can find a space cos he won't sit on laps <pause dur="short"/> don't know if he ever will <pause dur="short"/> he likes to sit next to you and sort of along side you and he actually squeezes himself into some very tight spaces now <pause dur="short"/> or he sits on the arm like that <pause dur="short"/> he makes me laugh because she often sits here and I sit there and he's on the edge or I'd sit here and she's lying where you are</u>
<u n="190" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0083">and he sits on the edge with his feet down the hole</u>
<u n="192" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0083">it's not the most comfortable place</u>
<u n="194" who="S0084">animals do surprise you where they can sleep though <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to sleep in with the <unclear/> coffee table didn't she</u>
<u n="195" who="S0083">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="196" who="S0084">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos it was</u>
<u n="197" who="S0083">well we had both of them at</u>
<u n="198" who="S0084">no we didn't <pause dur="short"/> we didn't have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> did we?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> of course we did</u>
<u n="200" who="S0084">oh yeah we did actually <pause dur="short"/> erm no it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that I remember doing it anyway</u>
<u n="201" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> they do like pillows though <pause dur="short"/> it's really peculiar because he does</u>
<u n="202" who="S0084">he likes the pink cushion doesn't he?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0083" trans="overlap">he likes the  he likes the  cushion <pause dur="short"/> and if he's on my bed  if he can  if he can do it he likes to lie near the pillow <pause dur="short"/> it's it's just having the head just that little bit up <pause dur="short"/> the same as we do</u>
<u n="204" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0083">we don't like lying completely flat do we?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="207" who="S0083">aw you're very cute <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I do like having him <pause dur="short"/> you were a good choice <pause dur="short"/> yes you were</u>
<u n="208" who="S0084">yeah he is a good choice</u>
<u n="209" who="S0083">very good nature</u>
<u n="210" who="S0084">and he doesn't sit on your lap</u>
<u n="211" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0084">which is nice</u>
<u n="213" who="S0083">it's good for you isn't it?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0084">it's good for me <pause dur="short"/> I can tolerate him</u>
<u n="215" who="S0083">I like it he he likes to lie on his back along my leg like that</u>
<u n="216" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0083">and just that' that's as close as he's comfortable with <pause dur="short"/> and he does like to do it <pause dur="short"/> cos he never used to so <pause dur="short"/> I feel he's really attached himself now</u>
<u n="218" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="219" who="S0083" trans="overlap">although he's settled ages ago <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's that kind of attachment to family to the person who owns you</u>
<u n="220" who="S0084" trans="overlap">to a degree <pause dur="short"/> I mean cats don't really have that the same as dogs do they? They don't have that unconditional love for their family the way that dogs do <pause dur="short"/> and that's what's dangerous about people who abuse pets</u>
<u n="221" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0084">because you could abuse a dog to such a degree because it will always love you</u>
<u n="223" who="S0083" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="224" who="S0084">Cos it's not in its nature to understand that</u>
<u n="225" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="226" who="S0084">but a cat will leave you if it finds a better deal</u>
<u n="227" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0084">but yeah I think he he seems very settled</u>
<u n="229" who="S0083" trans="overlap">Oscar won't will you? He does <pause dur="short"/> he likes it here <pause dur="short"/> it suits him</u>
<u n="230" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I'm sure that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought about Diesel though to be fair</u>
<u n="231" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0084">he kept running away <pause dur="short"/> and enough</u>
<u n="233" who="S0083">he's fine</u>
<u n="234" who="S0084">doesn't he try and jump through that erm fan window?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0083">no it's too high</u>
<u n="236" who="S0084">but he can get out of the bedroom ones can't he <pause dur="short"/> and the kitchen one</u>
<u n="237" who="S0083">yeah it's because there's a ledge</u>
<u n="238" who="S0084">yeah it's not quite as big a distance</u>
<u n="239" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0084">I mean from the <trunc>ro</trunc> from the chair he hasn't tried it?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0083">erm we haven't opened it because when it's been nice we've had the door open</u>
<u n="242" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0083">so we haven't just had that as it is today <pause dur="short"/> cos as soon as it was nice you know the door was open</u>
<u n="244" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="245" who="S0083">yeah we'll put it back in my room today <pause dur="short"/> I need to sort out my room a little bit <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="246" who="S0084">that forget-me-not's everywhere isn't it</u>
<u n="247" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah they do spread</u>
<u n="248" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I mean the flowers are nice</u>
<u n="249" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I mean I don't  I don't  mind some but there are too many <pause dur="short"/> I mean they they are just going crazy</u>
<u n="250" who="S0084">it flowers early in the year then</u>
<u n="251" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0084">Cos it's that</u>
<u n="253" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh no you mean these?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0084">the little blue ones at the bottom <pause dur="short"/> aren't they forget-me-not? Oh but they're violets</u>
<u n="255" who="S0083">these well they're roses they're violets</u>
<u n="256" who="S0084">yeah but they're by the buddleia as well</u>
<u n="257" who="S0083">they are <pause dur="short"/> they do spread and they're all down the sides here as well</u>
<u n="258" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0083">erm but that's fine cos they're only little <pause dur="short"/> that's fine <pause dur="short"/> erm now the forget-me-nots are the ones that are on that side</u>
<u n="260" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0083">and that will taken over</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="262" who="S0083">I wish I had some money <pause dur="short"/> I would put a fence all the way down here</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">I know</u>
<u n="264" who="S0083">I'm going to have to do it but I can only do it bit by bit <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to get</u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">how expensive is it to buy the panels?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0083">well individually it doesn't seem like much it's just you need so many of them <pause dur="short"/> and the posts <pause dur="short"/> and the concrete and the spikes to me them in and</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and how much are they on average? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> well what are you talking really for that whole side? About a hundred quid?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0083">oh God no about three or four</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">Jesus</u>
<u n="270" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's that's quite a long distance that <pause dur="short"/> well it must be <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it must be sixty feet or something <pause dur="short"/> maybe more I don't know</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084">so if you get the plans out for the house <unclear/> find out</u>
<u n="272" who="S0083">well I mean it we could just measure it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084" trans="overlap">measure it</u>
<u n="274" who="S0083">pace it out or something <pause dur="short"/> but it's yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084">blimey</u>
<u n="276" who="S0083">I'm definitely going to do the bit by the house because I want some privacy from next door</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it's so it's really when I we first moved in I quite liked the wilderness on that side but it's actually just really I don't know just not nice is it <pause dur="short"/> it's not pretty it's just ugly ugly</u>
<u n="278" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it's not <pause dur="short"/> it is ugly</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084">ugly plants <pause dur="short"/> they're just weeds essentially aren't they</u>
<u n="280" who="S0083">A lot <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Ivy <pause dur="short"/> holly <pause dur="short"/> holly's pretty but</u>
<u n="282" who="S0083">well holly is nice but it it the guy who came and trimmed it last summer said oh I'll leave the holly  cos it's  cos it's nice</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0083">fine yeah it is nice <pause dur="short"/> everyone likes holly but it grows enormously high</u>
<u n="285" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0083">if it's just left a holly tree will grow I don't know sixty feet or more</u>
<u n="287" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0083">I mean it is it's very it'll grow into a very big tree</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0083">that's why you have to be careful with it <pause dur="short"/> and it's seeded itself as well <pause dur="short"/> there's there are there's more than one</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0083">and there's a small one growing <pause dur="short"/> erm a few feet along</u>
<u n="293" who="S0084">I wonder if it's worth speaking to the tenants next door just saying can you have a word with the landlady to see if it's okay if we chop back the some wilderness <pause dur="short"/> cos it doesn't seem like the landlady gives a toss</u>
<u n="294" who="S0083">erm they paid erm to have this guy do it last year to to to to cut it so that the level wasn't blocking my light because that is an issue between neighbours</u>
<u n="295" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0083">blocking of light is something that's kind of I mean these things are not enshrined in law  but it's  but it's not you're not supposed to do that <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't know how you do get these protracted law cases of neighbours you know <pause dur="short"/> things like erm I mean the thing that really gets people is this erm is the  You know the kind of <unclear/> because they grow so big</u>
<u n="297" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0083">you're not supposed to block each other's light <pause dur="short"/> that's that's quite a major thing <pause dur="short"/> so the privacy not so important <pause dur="short"/> light obviously is</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0083">erm so I think they were told you know you're going to have to do this <pause dur="short"/> so they did <pause dur="short"/> but erm there's not the same kind of which you'd think there would be</u>
<u n="301" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0083">of emphasis on on privacy</u>
<u n="303" who="S0084">well given that everybody lives on each other's doorsteps now you'd think this would be written into the you know law</u>
<u n="304" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> because they cos they don't live actually live there they just don't care</u>
<u n="305" who="S0084">no and that's the problem <pause dur="short"/> you find that more and more because obviously lots of people have second and third homes</u>
<u n="306" who="S0083" trans="overlap">everywhere is rented out <pause dur="short"/> but why would you  why would you  rent somewhere with a? You know it's very annoying</u>
<u n="307" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0083">if you've  if you've  if you're renting somewhere and it's got a garden you're supposed to keep it tidy which basically means you cut the grass <pause dur="short"/> you don't do anything else but you're going to invest all your weekends in weeding and pruning and things are you <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="309" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>mo</trunc> well I we certainly don't <pause dur="short"/> but then thinking about it had I spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when I  when I  was looking at moving in I said who looks after the garden? And she said oh I look after it <pause dur="short"/> I mean no-one looks after that garden <pause dur="short"/> it's completely ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> we've got a bedstead half way down as the fence</u>
<u n="310" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well exactly</u>
<u n="311" who="S0084">but really there's nothing like that <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing ugly growing through</u>
<u n="312" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="313" who="S0084">they've got a couple of little <pause dur="short"/> not dissimilar to whatever that is <pause dur="short"/> I think it's honeysuckle coming over the fence</u>
<u n="314" who="S0083" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="315" who="S0084">there's that <pause dur="short"/> there's and blackberry bushes because I was picking picking blackberries when I first moved in in August September</u>
<u n="316" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0084">erm and that's about it really <pause dur="short"/> but actually we've got those <pause dur="short"/> what's that green? Like a rubber plant <pause dur="short"/> it's a rubber plant <pause dur="short"/> and they grow into trees don't they <pause dur="short"/> you know those rubber plant leaves?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0084">yeah we've got them all down that side by the conservatory on your right</u>
<u n="320" who="S0083">oh I'm I know the kind of thing that people <trunc>u</trunc> do use it as a kind of hedge yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0084">as a shield yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that's got a fence behind it</u>
<u n="322" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="323" who="S0084">but that's probably because that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s side</u>
<u n="324" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0084">so that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s put that fence in and planted those trees</u>
<u n="326" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0084">erm and it's the landlord next door who he rents it out to students who's who's got that chain link fence which would have been donkeys years old</u>
<u n="328" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the same as that yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0084">and the bedstead</u>
<u n="330" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0084">whether the landlord put the bedstead in or whether some tenants thought it would be really funny to put it in I don't know but even though either one would surprise me</u>
<u n="332" who="S0083" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0084">given that the landlord has left a a used toilet in their front garden for six months</u>
<u n="334" who="S0083">excellent <pause dur="short"/> urgh</u>
<u n="335" who="S0084">er but the <trunc>la</trunc> but the tenants don't care</u>
<u n="336" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="337" who="S0084">if I lived there I'd be horrified</u>
<u n="338" who="S0083">well I know but students don't care <pause dur="short"/> I mean a lot of people if they're renting they <trunc>ju</trunc> they don't really care about the property</u>
<u n="339" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it must be <trunc>dis</trunc> it must be absolutely disgusting inside</u>
<u n="340" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0084">I mean our house is falling down but at least we keep it clean on the inside</u>
<u n="342" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0084">I mean the bathroom needs gutting <pause dur="short"/> they've used the wrong kind of paint on the ceiling and it's all flaking</u>
<u n="344" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0084">they've obviously used like a non water resistant one</u>
<u n="346" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0084">erm and it's I mean the cleaner that comes once a week <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what she does <pause dur="short"/> I think she puts a bit of bleach in the toilet <pause dur="short"/> I don't think she properly cleans it <pause dur="short"/> hoovers and wipes the sides down</u>
<u n="348" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0084">Don't think she has anything <pause dur="short"/> oh she wipes the taps <pause dur="short"/> she wipes the sink sinks down</u>
<u n="350" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0084">she hasn't cleaned the bath <pause dur="short"/> she hasn't hoovering anything on the</u>
<u n="352" who="S0083">really?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0084">she's she's supposed to hoover around the landing and the stairs and the hall</u>
<u n="354" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0084">and she's supposed to mop the floor <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't every time <pause dur="short"/> sometimes she does</u>
<u n="356" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0084">it's really bad <pause dur="short"/> but I mean we're all quite good about washing out the bath because most of us have baths at one point like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always has a bath erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably has a bath a couple of times a week and occasionally <unclear/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0084">everyone's pretty good generally</u>
<u n="360" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's what so long as you all do it's it's when there's one that doesn't</u>
<u n="361" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> leaves her hair all over the bathroom which is a bit grim <pause dur="short"/> she's the new Spanish girl</u>
<u n="362" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0084">which I think everyone's getting a bit annoyed with and she's so so heavy footed <pause dur="short"/> I've never known anyone like it <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wears steel toe-capped boots for work because he's a labourer and he doesn't make that much noise</u>
<u n="364" who="S0083">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="365" who="S0084">are you going to paint the fence all one colour? Your fence</u>
<u n="366" who="S0083">what? I'm not particularly bothered <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="367" who="S0084">it's not an issue</u>
<u n="368" who="S0083">no not really</u>
<u n="369" who="S0084">you're going to need to put the the the stuff like the resin stuff on the wood <pause dur="short"/> the wood protector <pause dur="short"/> you're going to need to put that on</u>
<u n="370" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> it comes <pause dur="short"/> it's already treated when it when it's new <pause dur="short"/> it's when it's been there a few years do you have to put</u>
<u n="371" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no I mean on on yours</u>
<u n="372" who="S0083">oh on this?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084">I mean is that why it's wearing away in places?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0083">yeah because it it it wears off and you need to go over it again and you're supposed to do it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how often but you're supposed to do it fairly regularly</u>
<u n="377" who="S0084">I love that smell <pause dur="short"/> how many tins did they take do they take do he shed?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0083">well less than one <pause dur="short"/> there's there's some left over <pause dur="short"/> there's quite a bit leftover</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="380" who="S0084">mm you can definitely see the red coming through</u>
<u n="381" who="S0083">yeah it's it's so it's just so strong that stuff</u>
<u n="382" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0083">and  you can't  you can't paint it a lighter colour <unclear/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0083">it's it's fine don't worry <pause dur="short"/> you just have to ignore it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="386" who="S0084">I think I need some drugs</u>
<u n="387" who="S0083">what kind?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0084">brain</u>
<u n="389" who="S0083">you're just tired</u>
<u n="390" who="S0084">and my tooth is hurting a lot now</u>
<u n="391" who="S0083">well I can help with that <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't feel like doing very much</u>
<u n="392" who="S0084">how are your legs today?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0083">oh they're fine <pause dur="short"/> I was just tired last night</u>
<u n="394" who="S0084">how's your tummy?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0083">it's okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="396" who="S0084"></u>
<u n="397" who="S0083">yes</u>
<u n="398" who="S0084">are you alright?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0083">I'm alright</u>
<u n="400" who="S0084">have you been listening to the new erm any more Glen Gould?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0083">no I haven't</u>
<u n="402" who="S0084">I like the collection he's got though</u>
<u n="403" who="S0083">it is <pause dur="short"/> it's good <pause dur="short"/> oh you can put some on and listen to it</u>
<u n="404" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="405" who="S0084">my boss at work <pause dur="short"/> not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> the operations manager <pause dur="short"/> she's got chicken pox <pause dur="short"/> I know bless her she's forty <pause dur="short"/> I mean she we went out for her fortieth a couple of weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> she's got a little boy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's two</u>
<u n="406" who="S0083">and he's got it?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0084">no we don't think so but he's probably going to get it as it's a good time <pause dur="short"/> but we don't know where she's got it from <pause dur="short"/> on <trunc>ch</trunc> her feller's a chef and he's just started a new job at one of the colleges <pause dur="short"/> it's really great and he was working for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s before</u>
<u n="408" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0084">and he was working seventy hour weeks <pause dur="short"/> you know that when you're a chef they make you sign your soul away</u>
<u n="410" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0084">you have to sign a disclaimer to say I'll work whatever hours you need me to <pause dur="short"/> and he was working seventy hour weeks</u>
<u n="412" who="S0083">seventy hours</u>
<u n="413" who="S0084">he would leave at eight AM and come home at one AM</u>
<u n="414" who="S0083">that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="415" who="S0084">he would leave on a Wednesday and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would say to him okay I'll see you on Sunday <pause dur="short"/> because she would be working office hours and looking after Samuel</u>
<u n="416" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0084">and he would just <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ei</trunc> either he would come back but in the afternoon and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would be at work or he just wouldn't come back</u>
<u n="418" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="419" who="S0084">but he's just started working at the colleges so it's Monday to Friday</u>
<u n="420" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0084">Seven till two <pause dur="short"/> it's great <pause dur="short"/> and over over time if he needs at the weekend</u>
<u n="422" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0084">it's so good <pause dur="short"/> and so bank holidays he's going to have off <pause dur="short"/> easter holidays going to have off</u>
<u n="424" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0084">it's really really good but erm they don't know where she's got this from <pause dur="short"/> cos apparently she's never had chicken pox before so at least it's not shingles cos I hear shingles is much worse when you're an adult</u>
<u n="426" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it it is <pause dur="short"/> it is and it's the same virus</u>
<u n="427" who="S0084">it's the same virus yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's just sort of a stronger strength isn't it or something when you're an adult so she must not have had it when she was a kid so at least Samuel will have it now when he's young</u>
<u n="428" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely I mean that's but you assume that if if you haven't had it that that when you have kids and your kids catch it then you will get it from them</u>
<u n="429" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0083">so that's weird</u>
<u n="431" who="S0084">so it's very weird <pause dur="short"/> so at least he just</u>
<u n="432" who="S0083">very odd the way that's happened</u>
<u n="433" who="S0084">he it could be he does go to crèche a couple of days or one day a week maybe</u>
<u n="434" who="S0083">or she's perhaps she's she's picked it up from one of the children then</u>
<u n="435" who="S0084" trans="overlap">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0084">so bless her <pause dur="short"/> so she's going to be <pause dur="short"/> so she's pretty contagious right now so she</u>
<u n="438" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0084">she works from home Thursdays and Fridays anyway but she'll be off this week and off for next week <pause dur="short"/> so I my boss next week will be Sam the director</u>
<u n="440" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0084">Cos obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in in the States it doesn't really count <pause dur="short"/> she's like if you've got any problems just call me <pause dur="short"/> there's not really anything you could do from over there though <pause dur="short"/> but it's fine I never really have a have an issue</u>
<u n="442" who="S0083">Good <pause dur="short"/> that's great that you're</u>
<u n="443" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> I mean I <trunc>ma</trunc> I made a massive balls up the other day at work <pause dur="short"/> it was really annoying <pause dur="short"/> I'd proofed a supplier to <trunc>s</trunc> to send in a cover and I'd given the wrong instructions <pause dur="short"/> it's just really annoying erm but not that surprising when you think about how much work we have on</u>
<u n="444" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0084">everything is rush rush rush</u>
<u n="446" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0084">you don't really have time to sit and think you just have to push on through</u>
<u n="448" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0084">because I've got ten projects now that I'm looking after</u>
<u n="450" who="S0083">wow</u>
<u n="451" who="S0084">yeah erm there's and each one of them will have a different editor erm a different designer working on it</u>
<u n="452" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0084">they're all a different <trunc>sta</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well they're all at similar stages</u>
<u n="454" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0084">they're all <pause dur="short"/> because of the nature of the beast we have to publish everything on the exams list</u>
<u n="456" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0084">which is the list that I look after in January because that's when the schools buy the books</u>
<u n="458" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0084">so that means all of the courses have to come out together <pause dur="short"/> you can't stagger everything <pause dur="short"/> so you can't have one with you and then have another one and then have another one <pause dur="short"/> they've all got to come out</u>
<u n="460" who="S0083" trans="overlap">right okay yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0084">and at the moment they're capitalising on a  on a  segment of the market that no-one else publishes for</u>
<u n="462" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0084">which is called the For Schools market so it's you might have an adult version of this exam level because this is the kids version so they've gone absolutely mental</u>
<u n="464" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0084">basically just capitalising on the fact that they've got you know market ownership there</u>
<u n="466" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0084">so everything is the For Schools version of everything now and what ESOL do is they update the exams <pause dur="short"/> so we might be working on an <trunc>ex</trunc>  on a  on a project right now for a certain exam level</u>
<u n="468" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0084">but next year they're going to revise it and it's going to be released in twenty-fifteen so we might publish a book when everything is being published for January twenty thirteen</u>
<u n="470" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0084">but we're going to have to revise it almost immediately because the next version <pause dur="short"/> the second edition has got to come out in January fifteen</u>
<u n="472" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0084">which means the authors have to be <trunc>work</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> in the production process itself takes nine months</u>
<u n="474" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0084">so we're working backwards from January fifteen <pause dur="short"/> they'll have to hand it over in January fourteen which means the authors need to be working in two thousand and thirteen so that as soon as we're publishing the authors are starting work on the second edition</u>
<u n="476" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0084">completely ridiculous</u>
<u n="478" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0084">it just makes you feel like well you know you're never actually going to rest <pause dur="short"/> you're just constantly working on the same stuff</u>
<u n="480" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0084">you're sort of flooding the market with with its own competition</u>
<u n="482" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well you are <pause dur="short"/> why is it necessary to have a second edition so soon?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0084">because the exam is being revised <pause dur="short"/> so what we're publishing in twenty thirteen will will not be current</u>
<u n="484" who="S0083" trans="overlap">Will that have to be? Okay</u>
<u n="485" who="S0084">but we don't know <pause dur="short"/> because ESOL are just like yeah we're going to revise it but we're not going to tell you how much <pause dur="short"/> so we don't know whether it's <pause dur="short"/> if it's twenty percent new material that's fine <pause dur="short"/> well at least we've got the bare bones of what's going in</u>
<u n="486" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh God <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0084">well more than the bare bones <pause dur="short"/> we'll only change twenty percent <pause dur="short"/> but they might change <trunc>eight</trunc> eighty percent which means we have to get authors to rewrite all of that material <pause dur="short"/> new exercises new examples</u>
<u n="488" who="S0083" trans="overlap">for God's sake why would you need to constantly <trunc>re</trunc> revise <unclear/> exam?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0084" trans="overlap">er it's almost like they're just creating work for themselves for the sake of it</u>
<u n="490" who="S0083">no you wonder <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0084">you know if it's been perfectly good up till this point why do they need to keep revising it? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you know that's not <pause dur="short"/> I'm not in charge of the content <pause dur="short"/> I'm in charge of getting it out on time</u>
<u n="492" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="493" who="S0084">so</u>
<u n="494" who="S0083">I suppose it erm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="495" who="S0083">I suppose erm er what am I trying to say?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0084">well if you thinking about publishing a book <pause dur="short"/> we would bring out new editions because the material looks dated <pause dur="short"/> so current pop stars that we might include with current illustrations <pause dur="short"/> and the book dates that's that's <trunc>ou</trunc> they're</u>
<u n="497" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that's  that's only  that's only minor though isn't it?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0084">well yeah it's pretty <pause dur="short"/> it depends how long ago the last edition was published</u>
<u n="499" who="S0083">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0084">if you've got something that's not a massive seller <pause dur="short"/> your last edition might have been for seven years ago for example something that I'm working on now <pause dur="short"/> business Title <pause dur="short"/> it's a business exams title</u>
<u n="501" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0084">it was last published in twenty <pause dur="short"/> two thousand and four erm which means it wasn't even designed in the current design programme</u>
<u n="503" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="504" who="S0084">it was in Quark rather than InDesign</u>
<u n="505" who="S0083">oh right</u>
<u n="506" who="S0084">so you've got to get all the old files from <unclear/> convert them <pause dur="short"/> send them off to the type setter so that they can work from that</u>
<u n="507" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0084">but basically we're changing eighty percent of the content</u>
<u n="509" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0084">so it's it's it's massive</u>
<u n="511" who="S0083">it is isn't it</u>
<u n="512" who="S0084">and then you've got things like for that you've got two business exams and they publish a student's book for each in this project</u>
<u n="513" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0084">so you've got one for Business English it's called and then one for Business <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what the other one is <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="515" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="516" who="S0084">we've got two exams <pause dur="short"/> so you've got two student's books per level <pause dur="short"/> you've got erm a study book for the students and you've got a teacher's for the teachers</u>
<u n="517" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0084">you've also got accompanying audio for the student's book <pause dur="short"/> so for this new edition we're using some of the old edition material <pause dur="short"/> some of and then recording new material</u>
<u n="519" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0084">but there's also also authentic recordings so like this <pause dur="short"/> basically you and me just chatting or interviews that's got to be spliced into the audio recording</u>
<u n="521" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="522" who="S0084">it's it's that that makes your job quite interesting because because that's what I have to do <pause dur="short"/> I have to make sure that all of those pieces are there</u>
<u n="523" who="S0083" trans="overlap">that is a lot of work though isn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0084">er and with the right people at the right time and everything is in place</u>
<u n="525" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> well that's good</u>
<u n="526" who="S0084">massive headache but yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but you're enjoying it</u>
<u n="528" who="S0084">yeah because it's it's it's really challenging and no two days are the same really so</u>
<u n="529" who="S0083">well that's what you want <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0084">that is what you want</u>
<u n="531" who="S0083">than be doing the same thing over and over</u>
<u n="532" who="S0084">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> I mean everyday I look at Lucy who's doing my old job and er I'm very grateful that I'm not doing that job any more</u>
<u n="533" who="S0083">yeah good</u>
<u n="534" who="S0084">I mean I I think <pause dur="short"/> she says she's enjoying it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether she'd tell me the truth really because we don't really know each other that well</u>
<u n="535" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0084">we all worked in</u>
<u n="537" who="S0083">has she settled in quite well has she?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0084">she has and she and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> get on well so that's good</u>
<u n="539" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0084">erm and she already worked in the department before so you know we've met for a coffee when she was saying she was going to apply for the job but I said that she'd be great cos I know she'd be good at that <pause dur="short"/> she's very organised</u>
<u n="541" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="542" who="S0084">erm but it's one of those jobs that you probably won't ever get a good idea of it until you start</u>
<u n="543" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0084">whereas I think with production I knew what I was letting myself in for</u>
<u n="545" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0084">erm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0083">well it was a good first step wasn't it</u>
<u n="548" who="S0084">it was a good first step</u>
<u n="549" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it all worked out really well</u>
<u n="550" who="S0084">it was a good entry level job <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="551" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0084">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent me a nice email from The States saying you know thanks for all your hard work <pause dur="short"/> you're doing a great job</u>
<u n="553" who="S0083">fantastic</u>
<u n="554" who="S0084">yeah well I wrote back and said that's you know that's really sweet and you know I'm really touched but I erm I just hope I don't <trunc>le</trunc> let anybody down and she wrote back and said you know <pause dur="short"/> no thank you <pause dur="short"/> I know it's only words and it's not going to buy your holiday but you know</u>
<u n="555" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0084">you never know <pause dur="short"/> it's just the end of this financial year going into the next I know there's no budget for any new members of staff and so we don't know</u>
<u n="557" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0084">you know it's all very well you you working at the top of your level when there's no money to progress</u>
<u n="559" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="560" who="S0084">and you know that the people in your department would like to promote you but there's just no money so</u>
<u n="561" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0084">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't what's going to happen <pause dur="short"/> I really don't <pause dur="short"/> you just carry on doing what you do I suppose</u>
<u n="563" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah pretty much</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="564" who="S0084">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s finding it harder than she thought she would in The States</u>
<u n="565" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0084">well she said  she knew  she knew it was going to be hard because obviously her her husband's here</u>
<u n="567" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0084">she said they skype everyday but and she's got a miniature <trunc>schn</trunc> schnauzer her dog which she loves <pause dur="short"/> and they skype and Otto gets in on them <pause dur="short"/> in on the action <pause dur="short"/> they don't have kids <pause dur="short"/> she said</u>
<u n="569" who="S0083">no but <vocal desc="laugh"/> the couples without kids often have dogs like that yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they never wanted kids actually which is quite fortunate they were on the same page about that</u>
<u n="571" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0084">just not or they never they never wanted to be</u>
<u n="573" who="S0083">I suppose when she's back you'll feel less pressured won't you?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0084">erm well yeah cos I'm I'm doing two of her projects</u>
<u n="575" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="576" who="S0084">and even though she's supposed to</u>
<u n="577" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and when is she back?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0084">June <pause dur="short"/> so she is back in the office after the jubilee weekend but I've got that week off</u>
<u n="579" who="S0083">blimey you've got a long stretch of being on your own then <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise it was that long</u>
<u n="580" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I've got all of April and all of May</u>
<u n="581" who="S0083">gosh</u>
<u n="582" who="S0084">it's three months <pause dur="short"/> just shy of three months because she went at the beginning of March so erm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0084">that's I mean that's how much maternity leave they get <pause dur="short"/> a couple of months that's it</u>
<u n="585" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0084">so it is quite a long stretch <pause dur="short"/> cos it's it's been three weeks <pause dur="short"/> I've got another two months of it</u>
<u n="587" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="588" who="S0084">erm it's fine <pause dur="short"/> I mean there are other senior <unclear/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s level of <unclear/> that you can ask questions but everyone's busy and you don't really want to</u>
<u n="589" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0084">I mean that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> you're supposed supposed to be being trained by somebody else <pause dur="short"/> that's that's why they're getting the money</u>
<u n="591" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="592" who="S0084">they're not here <pause dur="short"/> and you know obviously she's only an email away and we speak every week on the phone but it's not the same</u>
<u n="593" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well whenever you do have a problem go to somebody because don't <unclear/> it all their busy</u>
<u n="594" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0083">I mean you know they are you know they have the position that they do erm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0084">yeah and actually they are most of them are at that position because they're a line manager <pause dur="short"/> that's how you progress so</u>
<u n="597" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I think  I think  don't don't worry about going to them and thinking they're busy <pause dur="short"/> I would definitely go to them <pause dur="short"/> don't struggle along if this you know if they can help you</u>
<u n="598" who="S0084">no no I'm I'm generally fine I mean it I've been doing it for three months now so</u>
<u n="599" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> four months</u>
<u n="601" who="S0083">yeah yeah it must be</u>
<u n="602" who="S0084">Cos I started in November</u>
<u n="603" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0084">so day to day you know I'm I'm getting a handle on things</u>
<u n="605" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0084">and the good thing is because we have so many new systems all learning all the time so that was the hardest thing about starting in November was because it <trunc>w</trunc> that was basically when we were starting a new system so they were trying to show me the old way but show me the new way and it was all very confusing so erm I think that's put me in quite a fortunate position because I've just run with the new system because there's no point learning the old one</u>
<u n="607" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0084">whereas I think the others have had a lot longer to be working the old system and they're finding it a bit difficult to move across so</u>
<u n="609" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="610" who="S0084">for example yesterday I spent time with one of the seniors showing them how to use the new scheduling system</u>
<u n="611" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="612" who="S0084">and that was quite nice because it was quite nice to be able to help rather than being the one that's helped</u>
<u n="613" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0084">so it's alright <pause dur="short"/> it's quite nice</u>
<u n="615" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0084">and it is a good team <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think anyone resents <unclear/> asking questions <pause dur="short"/> there's no attitude at all there so</u>
<u n="617" who="S0083">Good <pause dur="short"/> well there shouldn't be <pause dur="short"/> I mean you really have been thrown in at the deep end I think in this</u>
<u n="618" who="S0084">it's sink or swim <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's what they said when I went for my interview <pause dur="short"/> I mean well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my colleague that started as the trainee two years ago <pause dur="short"/> when I started my job with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he'd started a month before <pause dur="short"/> and she said you know he was quite fortunate at the time because there was fewer projects in the department going through production and he had smaller projects and he could take his time and she said you don't have that luxury you know</u>
<u n="619" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0084">you going to have a lot of work <pause dur="short"/> it's a very busy list <pause dur="short"/> and it's all projects to <unclear/> individual titles and things <pause dur="short"/> you're going to have <pause dur="short"/> it's going to be multi component multi level</u>
<u n="621" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="622" who="S0084">and it's all going to have to come out at the same time <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose you know I quite enjoy that</u>
<u n="623" who="S0083">well I think you do thrive on that</u>
<u n="624" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to be</u>
<u n="625" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well you certainly seem to you you know you</u>
<u n="626" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I don't want to be bored <pause dur="short"/> I'm more engaged with my job now that I'm</u>
<u n="627" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it's a  it's a  really pleasant surprise to see you do this <pause dur="short"/> to see you busy and loving it and challenged but thriving on it <pause dur="short"/> it's it's great to see you like this</u>
<u n="628" who="S0084">yeah I mean who would have thought it? But it definitely brings out the best in people</u>
<u n="629" who="S0083" trans="overlap">the time that I first saw it was when you were doing <pause dur="short"/> when you were in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0084">doing my MA yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was a good year</u>
<u n="631" who="S0083">you so loved doing it and getting on with it so even even the hassles about being there were were nothing <pause dur="short"/> I mean you you absolutely loved it and the busier you were <pause dur="short"/> the more deadlines you had the more you loved it and I thought I don't believe it <pause dur="short"/> this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I bet she</u>
<u n="632" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I know it's the one who just wants to get into bed</u>
<u n="633" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well I think it was then that I realised that this is  this is  what you</u>
<u n="636" who="S0084">I think that was a turning point</u>
<u n="637" who="S0083">you know given the right  given the right  subject or or world that you were in you know you absolutely thrived on it and you are</u>
<u n="638" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I think that was it you know <pause dur="short"/> it took me a few years to get there but was it's all quite crucial timing you know it's you need that time when you're finishing to just take stock and think what it is that you want to do <pause dur="short"/> it does take a while</u>
<u n="639" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0084">well certainly once I'd latched onto it or when I started the course it really felt like yeah this is it <pause dur="short"/> this is  this is  what I want to do so</u>
<u n="641" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean it it wasn't just I mean that that was clear <pause dur="short"/> that was very clear <pause dur="short"/> and I was very glad that you'd found that</u>
<u n="642" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and it's probably felt like that ever since</u>
<u n="643" who="S0083">but as you say I mean this is somebody who</u>
<u n="644" who="S0084">I didn't really like academic work</u>
<u n="645" who="S0083">when  when you  when you had a project from school <pause dur="short"/> even if it was something that you enjoyed it was like oh it's too hard <pause dur="short"/> oh it's too much work <pause dur="short"/> oh no I <pause dur="short"/> oh it's just too much</u>
<u n="646" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah complete opposite to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>in that regard <pause dur="short"/> well I think  that was  that was why <pause dur="short"/> I think it had taken me that long till my mid twenties to think <pause dur="short"/> actually I want to go to university <pause dur="short"/> I want to study</u>
<u n="647" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0084">and I think that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> when I was eighteen it was sort of well you've got <trunc>y</trunc> you go <pause dur="short"/> that's what you're supposed to do</u>
<u n="649" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0084">as opposed to a necessarily a real choice to go <pause dur="short"/> you know I wanted to go but I don't think studying was the the drive for me then at all</u>
<u n="651" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no no it absolutely wasn't</u>
<u n="652" who="S0084">and er that was apparent <pause dur="short"/> I think when I went to do my MA that was the drive that was right okay well this is my chance to prove to myself and and maybe to other people that I can do it <pause dur="short"/> I have got a brain <pause dur="short"/> I can study and I can apply myself <pause dur="short"/> and I felt like I'd been given that opportunity and not to waste it really</u>
<u n="653" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well you and that was the other thing <pause dur="short"/> it was all your choice</u>
<u n="654" who="S0084">yeah I think that was the difference <pause dur="short"/> it was my course <pause dur="short"/> it was my university <pause dur="short"/> I'd researched it <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to do it</u>
<u n="655" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="656" who="S0084">erm whereas I think I just you know with U E A <pause dur="short"/> I think said this is like a good uni <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah okay fine mum <pause dur="short"/> well this is like a good course <pause dur="short"/> yeah fine okay</u>
<u n="657" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0084">and I hadn't really engaged with any of it other than well erm I should go to uni it sounds good</u>
<u n="659" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well no I mean you you you said you wanted to do film</u>
<u n="660" who="S0084">yeah but do you remember I started doing cultural studies?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0084">and I think that was your drive <pause dur="short"/> that was your <unclear/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0083" trans="overlap">because because no <pause dur="short"/> it it I the reason I suggested that was because it was a broad canvas because  there was  there was no one field that you wanted to do</u>
<u n="664" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="665" who="S0083">and it seemed like <pause dur="short"/> well if it  if it's  if it's a sort of if it's a different bit every week or every other week that would suit you more</u>
<u n="666" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely yeah <pause dur="short"/> it seemed like a good idea and I think that's what <pause dur="short"/> you know I didn't challenge it because I thought well <unclear/> that makes sense because there wasn't anything that I wanted to do <pause dur="short"/> so what I probably should have done is wait and then gone when I was twenty-five</u>
<u n="667" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> the thing is I knew I I had this feeling and I still think it that had you worked for a year or travelled or you know</u>
<u n="668" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I wouldn't go</u>
<u n="669" who="S0083">had you worked saved travelled that at the end of it you wouldn't have gone to uni</u>
<u n="670" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and if that was the case then that would have you know well my life would have just gone in a different direction</u>
<u n="671" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and I was  I was I was  worried that that would happen to you <pause dur="short"/> yeah and you would have done and you wouldn't be where you are so</u>
<u n="672" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean if you think that I was twenty-five when I started my MA and I thought and it had taken me that long to get there and choose to do that <pause dur="short"/> I would have been behind because I would have been doing my undergraduate then as opposed to my MA so I'd only been now <pause dur="short"/> only now would I be finishing my MA</u>
<u n="673" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah you would have been way behind <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0084"><unclear/> that yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I finished my MA three years ago didn't I so yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah you might have yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0084">I would be finishing my MA now</u>
<u n="677" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0084">so erm so yeah I'd be well behind <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>f</trunc> because that's part of what you feel you know you're thirty and you're a trainee you think you know this isn't quite how what my life was planned</u>
<u n="679" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know but you've done all of the stuff that you have</u>
<u n="680" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you know I have travelled <pause dur="short"/> I have got two degrees <pause dur="short"/> I have I am in a job that I enjoy and I'm in an area a field that I enjoy so</u>
<u n="681" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you've been there for two years and you've you've you've settled and well thought of there</u>
<u n="682" who="S0084">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> I hope so</u>
<u n="683" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well you obviously are</u>
<u n="684" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> you are</u>
<u n="686" who="S0084">so it's funny <pause dur="short"/> it's funny <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>pe</trunc> yeah I mean I do <pause dur="short"/> I definitely do prefer to busy at work</u>
<u n="687" who="S0083" trans="overlap">you you do <pause dur="short"/> you do <pause dur="short"/> and it and and this is the thing <pause dur="short"/> it's like I don't recognise this confident mature capable young woman with with with the teenager who used to <pause dur="short"/> erm I don't know</u>
<u n="688" who="S0084">I'm very different to how I was when I was a teen <pause dur="short"/> I mean I still see traits of myself obviously <pause dur="short"/> you know I am still quite shy and</u>
<u n="689" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0084">I still do have a confidence issues to a degree but at the same time I'm much more self assured obviously which is what's supposed to happen</u>
<u n="691" who="S0083" trans="overlap">you are</u>
<u n="692" who="S0084">you are supposed to be more self assured when you're older but</u>
<u n="693" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know but it doesn't always happen</u>
<u n="694" who="S0084">it doesn't necessarily happen</u>
<u n="695" who="S0083">no it doesn't</u>
<u n="696" who="S0084">and everyone has you know issues about themselves</u>
<u n="697" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and you're very clear about what you want whereas when you were a teenager you you didn't know <pause dur="short"/> erm and you just liked doing the things that you liked doing</u>
<u n="698" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="699" who="S0083">and you didn't put yourself out at all</u>
<u n="700" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="701" who="S0083">whereas now you do</u>
<u n="702" who="S0084">well I suppose you know it's it's meeting people it's doing things that test who you are as a person and</u>
<u n="703" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0084">if you I suppose in every situation</u>
<u n="705" who="S0083" trans="overlap">you have pushed yourself <pause dur="short"/> you have you've I think that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> you you've you've wanted to do certain things and you've made yourself do them</u>
<u n="706" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0083">instead of thinking oh I'd really like to do that but I never could <pause dur="short"/> you thought I really want to do that <pause dur="short"/> right now erm I'm going to erm book this and save that and go there and you you've done it</u>
<u n="708" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> to a degree yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's obviously there's always more</u>
<u n="709" who="S0083" trans="overlap">you absolutely have <pause dur="short"/> you absolutely have</u>
<u n="710" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0083">and that's the difference because a teenager would have said I'd like to do that but that's not going to happen</u>
<u n="712" who="S0084">well I lived in a safety net <trunc>do</trunc> you know  when you're  when you're living at home you know it's all very easy and very safe and you're parents look after you and as soon as you move out you're on your own and that first few years is a real test</u>
<u n="713" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but that that's I think that's what made the difference  which is  which is I mean beyond anything obviously the education but I think that's what <trunc>mo</trunc>going to uni did for you</u>
<u n="714" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="715" who="S0083">it made you think you could do anything and you did</u>
<u n="716" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> and and meeting other people because obviously growing up you see the same people day in day out <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's no-one new <pause dur="short"/> there's new thought really <pause dur="short"/> everyone's doing the same thing and</u>
<u n="717" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0084">it's not until you go to uni and you meet people from all walks of life and all different backgrounds and you all think differently and you all have different challenges and they challenge your perception of yourself and the world and anything that you take for granted and it's not until you keep meeting new people and I mean it sounds really tripe but it's true</u>
<u n="719" who="S0083" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no it's absolutely true <pause dur="short"/> and it it certainly was for you</u>
<u n="720" who="S0084">I think that and that's probably why I'm more bolshy than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/><pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is very well you know take the way that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> treats her</u>
<u n="721" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0084">she doesn't feel she's able to stand up to these people and I think because I started off in my working life doing that saying actually no you're not going to take advantage</u>
<u n="723" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="724" who="S0084">you know I did <pause dur="short"/> I worked there when I was seventeen and they did take advantage</u>
<u n="725" who="S0083">they did yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0084">and that was my first working experience whereas <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s was <anon type="place"/>? Was that her first job?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0083">it wasn't her first job <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="728" who="S0084">what was her first job?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0083" trans="overlap">although that was the one that she really liked <pause dur="short"/> she'd I'd forgotten actually she reminded me <pause dur="short"/> she worked at <anon type="place"/> for about a month and then left</u>
<u n="730" who="S0084">oh that's right <pause dur="short"/> wasn't she  wasn't she  doing the sale something?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0083" trans="overlap">because she hated it</u>
<u n="732" who="S0084">yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> it was horrible</u>
<u n="733" who="S0083">it was a horrible place to work</u>
<u n="734" who="S0084">but <anon type="place"/> was easy and safe <pause dur="short"/> she liked <trunc>e</trunc> most of the people she worked with</u>
<u n="735" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0084">her bosses were I think you know bosses as bosses are but no-one took advantage</u>
<u n="737" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="738" who="S0084">and I think at that age because I'd had to stand up to <unclear/> and I'm you know I'm was red in the face <pause dur="short"/> I was sweating and wanted to cry but I was very convinced that I was right</u>
<u n="739" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="740" who="S0084">and at that point I think I thought well actually you can't can't walk over people and I don't know whether naturally we're different because I wouldn't allow it</u>
<u n="741" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> you are naturally different <pause dur="short"/> you are naturally more bolshy</u>
<u n="742" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I've got more so as I've got older which is  which is  a bad thing</u>
<u n="743" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0084">like I accidentally offended one of my colleagues the other day <pause dur="short"/> I didn't mean to obviously <pause dur="short"/> I mean no-one ever means to offend them but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I had gone for a drink at the pub on our way home and my colleague Tom had come with us <pause dur="short"/> he's bit of a wide boy <pause dur="short"/> bit of a loud mouth <pause dur="short"/> and we got into the pub and we were just having a laugh having a nice time and I can't remember how we got onto the subject</u>
<u n="745" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="746" who="S0084">and er I was saying I think because I wasn't really quality controlling what was coming out</u>
<u n="747" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0084">and I'd said oh I I think people who believe in Jesus are just a bit silly like it won't <pause dur="short"/> I don't mean to but I have a really critical opinion of people who believe in religion because I can't marry the two ideas that a logical person can also believe in God because for me I I don't think of it as a logical decision really because it's faith and whatever and</u>
<u n="749" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="750" who="S0084">our director of our financial director I found out the other day is a a is very religious and he goes to church every week and it's fine <pause dur="short"/> his choice</u>
<u n="751" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0084">but by saying this I I didn't realise I was offending Tom who is quite religious and I didn't know this and obviously why would I? It's not you know you don't need to shout about it</u>
<u n="753" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well exactly</u>
<u n="754" who="S0084">but I wasn't really thinking and obviously I'm entitled to my own opinion but  it is  it is quite offensive  if you  if you take it that way <pause dur="short"/> I didn't mean it to be</u>
<u n="755" who="S0083" trans="overlap">of course</u>
<u n="756" who="S0084">and then we were talking about the riots in London and he was getting really agitated and he was saying his cousin <pause dur="short"/> female <pause dur="short"/> very petite</u>
<u n="757" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0084">was er is in the police works for the Met and was part of the riot erm the riot troops that came out</u>
<u n="759" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="760" who="S0084">and he was saying I'm not being funny right but women you know why do they put them in these positions? And I said well she would have had training</u>
<u n="761" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="762" who="S0084">they wouldn't have let her go out if they thought that she couldn't you know look after herself and her other fellow officers</u>
<u n="763" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="764" who="S0084">and he was saying you know she's tiny <pause dur="short"/> and he got up from the table and started demonstrating but then was like gesticulating in my face <pause dur="short"/> he was like saying so you're telling me that a girl could stand up to me <pause dur="short"/> I've got a black belt in karate and he was getting really really really violent</u>
<u n="765" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="766" who="S0084">and he necked his beer and was oh look sorry whatever <pause dur="short"/> and then run for his train <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were saying to each other <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> where did that come from? That was so strange <pause dur="short"/> he really was getting really erm really irate</u>
<u n="767" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0084">and then a couple of days later <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said oh I think I know what the problem with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was <pause dur="short"/> turns out he's really religious <pause dur="short"/> I think you really offended him with your comment</u>
<u n="769" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="770" who="S0084">but he didn't say anything to me <pause dur="short"/> he didn't say oh well I'm religious</u>
<u n="771" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no he didn't no</u>
<u n="772" who="S0084">he didn't challenge me <pause dur="short"/> maybe he didn't want me to know</u>
<u n="773" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0084">which is fine <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know what it I would have done if it was the other way round <pause dur="short"/> I mean I might have fought my corner a bit and said well hang on you can't really judge people like that or fine whatever</u>
<u n="775" who="S0083" trans="overlap">or if not if if he <trunc>d</trunc> if you don't want to enter <trunc>de</trunc> the debate you just say to yourself that's their view <pause dur="short"/> I've got my view <pause dur="short"/> leave it</u>
<u n="776" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's perfectly entitled to believe in God <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? I'm not saying <pause dur="short"/> I was saying I sort of think less of these people</u>
<u n="777" who="S0083" trans="overlap">of course he is yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="778" who="S0084">I wasn't saying they're stupid <pause dur="short"/> I I was saying that it's actually my stupidity because I can't help but judge</u>
<u n="779" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0084">erm that I find it strange</u>
<u n="781" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I think it's <pause dur="short"/> I think what you said was perfectly valid to say that you you can't see the the sense because it's it's not a logical thing to do and that's all you were saying yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's not a logical thing <pause dur="short"/> it's not yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not even that <pause dur="short"/> I think they <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's not reason yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well it's it's not reason is it <pause dur="short"/> it is faith yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0084">I wasn't calling people who believe in religion stupid necessarily I was just saying that I can't marry the two ideas that if you are a logical person you would therefore believe in God</u>
<u n="785" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> no he should have said something or or if not he should have just left well alone</u>
<u n="786" who="S0084">yeah just leave it alone</u>
<u n="787" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0084">so now he's <trunc>be</trunc> he's being a bit off with me in the office which is a bit weird</u>
<u n="789" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0084">I mean we didn't know each other that well before but it's quite <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's probably a hundred <pause dur="short"/> a hundred of us that sit on the same floor but you see each other all the time you know in the coffee area or whatever and yeah he has been a bit off but</u>
<u n="791" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh it will blow over</u>
<u n="792" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I think if you're so he's but obviously he's not somebody I would really be friends with anyway because he's obviously got a bit of a women issue there</u>
<u n="793" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="794" who="S0084">erm but er yeah it was a bit strange <pause dur="short"/> I don't know really where it it came from</u>
<u n="795" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="796" who="S0084">but I think going back to what we were saying I think that's probably because I do speak without thinking often and er</u>
<u n="797" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh we all do</u>
<u n="798" who="S0084">I think I'm so convinced of my own opinions now that I'm not necessarily that bothered about other people's</u>
<u n="799" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0084">maybe that's how I've always been I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think  I think  that's something that comes with age and confidence I think <pause dur="short"/> like not necessarily being you know being open to other people's ideas but I think I am no that's not right <pause dur="short"/> this is what I think</u>
<u n="801" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0084">and I I'm aware of that <pause dur="short"/> I try not to be but I think if someone says something that I don't agree with I'd say what are you talking about? That's not the case <pause dur="short"/> it's like this and but then I think you know check yourself</u>
<u n="803" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> the more you mix with people and lots of different people with as you say different backgrounds different views erm <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of sneezing"/></u>
<u n="804" who="S0084">bless you <pause dur="short"/> bless you</u>
<u n="805" who="S0083">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> right okay <pause dur="short"/> erm I thought there was another one coming <pause dur="short"/> erm You have  you have  to deal with the fact that there are lots of different views and opinions in the world and some are obviously just wrong</u>
<u n="806" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="807" who="S0083">but it also it helps you to crystallise your own ideas you know <trunc>wh</trunc> when when you hear different views you have to take those views on board and then you you kind of you you know so you you're constantly</u>
<u n="808" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah you compare them to what you believe and and question what you believe</u>
<u n="809" who="S0083" trans="overlap">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> and it therefore makes you think about what it is you believe and so it either er confirms it or it might challenge it and you think oh well I hadn't thought of things like that so</u>
<u n="810" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah challenges it <pause dur="short"/> absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0083">so the more you mix the more you talk <pause dur="short"/> it erm I think  I think  it's it's all a help because it will  it will  it helps your thinking about your own views</u>
<u n="812" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's a good thing yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just remembering to be open to those views</u>
<u n="813" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0084">not necessarily shoot them down</u>
<u n="815" who="S0083">but not <pause dur="short"/> yes just just as a  as a  knee jerk reaction but also you know not to just take on other people's views because it's somebody else and you think oh they're much cleverer than me you know</u>
<u n="816" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="817" who="S0083">I mean which is  which is  you know the other thing that can happen so</u>
<u n="818" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="819" who="S0083">but it  but it  helps <pause dur="short"/> in some ways it doesn't help when when you're all the same and you're all thinking and doing the same thing and that's not terribly healthy I think <pause dur="short"/> it's like  it's like  living in one community where you you know there's just one world view <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's where racism starts because you are with your own kind and anyone who's different is therefore seen as dangerous or erm or a difference is seen as a threat</u>
<u n="820" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="821" who="S0083">the more we mix with you know all the differences that you know of opinion of culture of background the better for all of us I think</u>
<u n="822" who="S0084">absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0083">but I think that's the problem <pause dur="short"/> I think people do <trunc>le</trunc> live in their little enclaves you know erm and they see different difference as frightening <pause dur="short"/> as a threat</u>
<u n="824" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> a bad thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="825" who="S0083">rather than welcoming it and and enjoying it <pause dur="short"/> appreciating it <pause dur="short"/> learning from it <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't mean that you have to give up your own identity <pause dur="short"/> this is  this is  what I you know they never</u>
<u n="826" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="827" who="S0083">you know that's not what's required <pause dur="short"/> and I think they're worried that <trunc>i</trunc> that it is</u>
<u n="828" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0083">anyway <pause dur="short"/> sorry to bang on <pause dur="short"/> but I think I think just generally it's healthy er for all of us to to challenge our own views</u>
<u n="830" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="831" who="S0083">because often it will confirm them as well</u>
<u n="832" who="S0084">yeah yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="833" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I mean you know you realise that actually yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was  I was I was  on on track there because that's that's clearly the best way and the best way forward</u>
<u n="834" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I think that's right yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0083">but we do get very stuck in our ways of thinking</u>
<u n="836" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's it if you spend all of your time with one type of person <pause dur="short"/> one group of people then yeah you do</u>
<u n="837" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> or just in your own head all the time you know you're not challenging it <pause dur="short"/> you know you're not having else coming in</u>
<u n="838" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="839" who="S0083">erm no other views <pause dur="short"/> no other input from anywhere <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's why we read and we talk and we listen and we you know because that's it isn't it I mean</u>
<u n="840" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="841" who="S0083">the discussion of ideas the the the the free flow of ideas between people is is what has made us and and what will continue to make us a good society</u>
<u n="842" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> like The Enlightenment</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="843" who="S0083">well that was I mean that just reminds me of mum because it was it's like she decided this is what she believed and that was that and she wasn't interested in anything <pause dur="short"/> yep a lot of people are like that <pause dur="short"/> a lot of right wing are terribly this is their view of the world and you're not going to move them</u>
<u n="844" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah well it's it's putting up barriers to other thoughts <pause dur="short"/> it's it's some sort of patronising erm way of speaking to people</u>
<u n="845" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it is</u>
<u n="846" who="S0084">erm no dear that's not what we think this is what we think <pause dur="short"/> parrot fashion</u>
<u n="847" who="S0083" trans="overlap">because it's it's it's their sense of superiority</u>
<u n="848" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0083">and it's it's a  it's a  putting down of erm you know other classes other cultures as as being inferior to theirs</u>
<u n="850" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="851" who="S0083">and and not allowing anything to challenge that because if you challenge that you will see weaknesses in that and you have to accept other things as being important or right</u>
<u n="852" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="853" who="S0083">and they you know it's it's it's not wanting to allow that to happen I think</u>
<u n="854" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0083">so you cling on to your view and you don't  you don't  allow any anything to challenge that <pause dur="short"/> and you're not like that <pause dur="short"/> you are you you just you have strong views in the same  in the same  way that a lot of us do about what's important <pause dur="short"/> about what's right</u>
<u n="856" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0083">I don't think you're closed <pause dur="short"/> I don't think you're</u>
<u n="858" who="S0084">I don't think I'm closed I think I'm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0083">I think you just I think you know at having got to the age that you have and done the things that you've done I think you realise certain things are important and and you you're not shy about saying that</u>
<u n="860" who="S0084">yeah I'm I'm aware of my own values and and my core values and what I think is important</u>
<u n="861" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well that's fine</u>
<u n="862" who="S0084">yeah but I try not to  I try not to  judge too quickly but I guess we're all a bit guilty of that</u>
<u n="863" who="S0083">well exactly we <trunc>ca</trunc> we can all do that</u>
<u n="864" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="865" who="S0083">oh you're beating yourself up a bit this morning <pause dur="short"/> don't do that</u>
<u n="866" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no no no it's sort of just self reflection isn't it?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> well again that's an incredibly important thing to do <pause dur="short"/> it I mean we all can take it too far</u>
<u n="868" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0083">but it's a very important thing to <pause dur="short"/> people who don't that I think are people you just don't want to be with <pause dur="short"/> you don't want to be around them</u>
<u n="870" who="S0084">well I think people that don't have got something to hide from themselves haven't they because why don't they want to look inside</u>
<u n="871" who="S0083" trans="overlap">if people <pause dur="short"/> it's too dangerous <pause dur="short"/> it's too scary</u>
<u n="872" who="S0084">it's yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's something buried there</u>
<u n="873" who="S0083">and you might</u>
<u n="874" who="S0084">might not like what you see</u>
<u n="875" who="S0083">it it allows doubt <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's the thing you know <pause dur="short"/> you can't allow <pause dur="short"/> if you've got very strict erm er very rigid views</u>
<u n="876" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="877" who="S0083">you can't allow doubt in because then it will upset that</u>
<u n="878" who="S0084"><event desc="sound of yawning"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> like the right wingers</u>
<u n="879" who="S0083">I mean I I think that's a very  a very  good saying erm no let me get it right <pause dur="short"/> the most dangerous person in the world is is the person who knows that they're right</u>
<u n="880" who="S0084">oh that's interesting</u>
<u n="881" who="S0083">I think that's that's because if you know you're right if you have no doubt at all knowing you are right <pause dur="short"/> I mean that makes you dangerous because you are capable of doing anything because you know you are right</u>
<u n="882" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="883" who="S0083">erm Hitler knew he was right</u>
<u n="884" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="885" who="S0083">didn't he?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="887" who="S0083">and Stalin</u>
<u n="888" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="889" who="S0083">these mad dictators they know they're right</u>
<u n="890" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="891" who="S0083">and they will do anything in the cause of that</u>
<u n="892" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="893" who="S0083">that about which they know they are right</u>
<u n="894" who="S0084">I mean I don't want to you know compare Blair to Hitler but Blair thought Blair knew he was right</u>
<u n="895" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> absolutely and that made him very dangerous because he would do anything</u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="897" who="S0083">and Bush <pause dur="short"/> they know they're right</u>
<u n="898" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="899" who="S0083">no <trunc>br</trunc> no opposition</u>
<u n="900" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="901" who="S0083">and it makes them very dangerous because they're prepared to go to war because they are right</u>
<u n="902" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="903" who="S0083">so beware of anyone who knows that they're right</u>
<u n="904" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="905" who="S0084">yes indeedy</u>
<u n="906" who="S0083">ah you're so cute <pause dur="short"/> all curled up</u>
<u n="907" who="S0084">he looks pretty pleased with himself</u>
<u n="908" who="S0083">he's very relaxed</u>
<u n="909" who="S0084">is that your perfume on the book here still?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0083">it is <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> I haven't opened it yet <pause dur="short"/> well I I use it very sparingly because it and it lasts me for years because it has to</u>
<u n="911" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0083">I don't wear it obviously everyday but I <trunc>m</trunc> I I don't wear it very often but but it means that I really really appreciate it when I do <pause dur="short"/> and I'm very</u>
<u n="913" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0083">I <trunc>re</trunc> I was really pleased because obviously I can't afford it and you obviously remembered so you're a lovely daughter you you've you've spoiled me terribly over the last couple of weekends and it was really lovely <pause dur="short"/> it meant a lot to me</u>
<u n="915" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh good well you deserve it</u>
<u n="916" who="S0083">oh thank you <pause dur="short"/> it really did mean a lot</u>
<u n="917" who="S0084">oh I'm glad you had a nice time <pause dur="short"/> it was very very you <pause dur="short"/> all about you</u>
<u n="918" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it was a bit busy <pause dur="short"/> it was a little full on <pause dur="short"/> well it was about me and I'm not used to that <pause dur="short"/> I don't really like it</u>
<u n="919" who="S0084">I know but it was good that's for that reason</u>
<u n="920" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="921" who="S0084">it was nice that Steve could make it up as well it sort of put the icing on the cake</u>
<u n="922" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it was I mean it's the first time I've seen him on my birthday for years</u>
<u n="923" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> good timing really</u>
<u n="924" who="S0083">and he <trunc>s</trunc> he said that he really enjoyed so I mean I I thought it might be a bit quiet for him but maybe he likes it</u>
<u n="925" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Good</u>
<u n="926" who="S0083">he loves being around you lot so</u>
<u n="927" who="S0084">does he?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0084">I'm always wondering whether it just hard work <pause dur="short"/> not hard work but you know</u>
<u n="930" who="S0083">no he likes it <pause dur="short"/> when you were younger he found it difficult <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he's <pause dur="short"/> I mean no he was very  he was very  good with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0084">he was very good with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0083">but erm he's kind of oo all these kids erm yes well it's nice being an uncle but I don't really know what to do with them all</u>
<u n="933" who="S0084">can can you take them please?</u>
<u n="934" who="S0083">but as soon as you all grew up erm you know</u>
<u n="935" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you think he would ever have wanted to have kids?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0083">I think he would have done <pause dur="short"/> not when he was younger but erm I think <unclear/> always wanted them it's just they've they've never had a penny so it's just <pause dur="short"/> you know they just couldn't</u>
<u n="937" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> good job they didn't</u>
<u n="938" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0084">I mean at least they were sensible about it though <pause dur="short"/> you know we can't afford to have kids so let's not entertain the thought</u>
<u n="940" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it is <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="941" who="S0084">not let's just have kids anyway</u>
<u n="942" who="S0083">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> where I think that even she saw the sense in that</u>
<u n="943" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0083">and I know she did want them</u>
<u n="945" who="S0084">well she's young enough but there's time <pause dur="short"/> she's what only in her thirties isn't she?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah she's</u>
<u n="947" who="S0084">late thirties</u>
<u n="948" who="S0083">yeah late thirties I think yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah she must be</u>
<u n="949" who="S0084">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had <unclear/> when she was thirty-eight</u>
<u n="950" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="951" who="S0084">first baby</u>
<u n="952" who="S0083">I mean it <pause dur="short"/> you obviously you can it just gets more difficult</u>
<u n="953" who="S0084">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> they sound like the war planes don't they <pause dur="short"/> or is it the props?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0083">it's the props <pause dur="short"/> it's it's what we used to hear <pause dur="short"/> actually I I don't hear it here very much <pause dur="short"/> you when I owned <anon type="place"/> Road we used to hear it more</u>
<u n="955" who="S0084">well it's that low drone that makes me think it's of it as a big plane <pause dur="short"/> you know one of the carrier planes or something</u>
<u n="956" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no I think it's when they're testing engines</u>
<u n="957" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="958" who="S0083">it's not something flying <pause dur="short"/> it's when they're testing them</u>
<u n="959" who="S0084">right okay</u>
<u n="960" who="S0083">I think because it goes on and on</u>
<u n="961" who="S0084">because the prop  the prop  planes make a sort of more sort of buzzing <pause dur="short"/> they're not high pitched</u>
<u n="962" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah that's a different  that's a different  sound isn't it</u>
<u n="963" who="S0084">is a different sound yeah</u>
<u n="964" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no it is an engine but it's a oh I don't know what what you call it anyway</u>
<u n="965" who="S0084">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="966" who="S0083">erm so is it going to be dry do you think?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0084">I think so <pause dur="short"/> think it is <pause dur="short"/> consult the oracle</u>
<u n="968" who="S0083">just realised erm</u>
<u n="969" who="S0084">your washing's still in the machine</u>
<u n="970" who="S0083">I could hang the washing out because it would be <trunc>re</trunc> it's it's so much nicer drying it outside</u>
<u n="971" who="S0084">yeah I mean it</u>
<u n="972" who="S0083">so I think I could so long as it's not damp</u>
<u n="973" who="S0084">I don't know</u>
<u n="974" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it's greyer than it was yesterday</u>
<u n="975" who="S0084">it's grey <pause dur="short"/> I'll try and find out information</u>
<u n="976" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it's even more grey than yesterday</u>
<u n="977" who="S0084">I don't know what these mean <pause dur="short"/> sunrise was at six thirty-five <pause dur="short"/> sun will set at seven thirty-three</u>
<u n="978" who="S0083">oh it's so nice when they say that <pause dur="short"/> seven thirty-three</u>
<u n="979" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><trunc>Tw</trunc> <trunc>twent</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I know it's good isn't it <pause dur="short"/> twenty percent <trunc>rai</trunc> chance of rain I think that's what that means</u>
<u n="980" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0084">Good visibility <pause dur="short"/> winds seventeen miles an hour <pause dur="short"/> low UV <pause dur="short"/> ten degrees <pause dur="short"/> medium level cloud <pause dur="short"/> feels like seven</u>
<u n="982" who="S0083">well that's really not very warm is it</u>
<u n="983" who="S0084">no not when during the week it was nineteen</u>
<u n="984" who="S0083">I know <pause dur="short"/> what a change</u>
<u n="985" who="S0084">I know so it's going to be wind <pause dur="short"/> it's good good clothes drying weather because it's it's windy</u>
<u n="986" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it is actually <pause dur="short"/> so I think I will put it out then I'll just keep an eye on it</u>
<u n="987" who="S0084" trans="overlap">just put them out this morning</u>
<u n="988" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="989" who="S0084">then it's got a good sort of six hours till you'll have to bring it in</u>
<u n="990" who="S0083">oh yeah yeah yeah I think I'll do that</u>
<u n="991" who="S0084">tomorrow it'll have sunny intervals <pause dur="short"/> feels like ten</u>
<u n="992" who="S0083">slightly better then <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="993" who="S0084">it's April Fool's Day tomorrow</u>
<u n="994" who="S0083">oh so it is</u>
<u n="995" who="S0084">charge my phone <pause dur="short"/> does your phone battery run down within a day?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0083" trans="overlap">quite quickly yeah <pause dur="short"/> not within a day but every er much more than it erm the other one used to</u>
<u n="997" who="S0084">well I think cos you don't use the background data do you <pause dur="short"/> you don't don't have your emails coming through and stuff like that</u>
<u n="998" who="S0083">no I don't</u>
<u n="999" who="S0084">which runs down the battery</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0083">no I don't check emails on it <pause dur="short"/> but I do do you know everything else</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> these were only five pounds <pause dur="short"/> five whole English pounds</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0083">wow</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0084">three pounds and two pounds</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0083">and they look nice together</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0084">well they look a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> they're <unclear/> together but you know</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no they look nice <pause dur="short"/> I'm just going to have a quick look at the <unclear/> then we'll all just have to get out there <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> quickly <unclear/></u>
<u n="1007" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0083"><unclear/> the kettle's just boiled</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0084">okay</u>
<event desc="0083 leaves"/>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1010" who="S0083">and I don't know why</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0083">she wanted to watch Strangers on a Train <pause dur="short"/> and I put it on and she slept all the way through it</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0084">is that Gregory Peck?</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0083">no it's not</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0084">it's Clark?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it's it's <pause dur="short"/> no it's not it's</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0084">Cary <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0083">it's one of those films erm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0084" trans="overlap">where you think it's someone famous and it's not</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0083">and it's not</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0083">I mean I've seen it many times so I know I I can't think of <pause dur="short"/> they're not household names anyway <pause dur="short"/> put it that way</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0083">erm I think both of them made films at the time but erm and it's a good film but I have seen it many times</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0083">erm but she slept through it <pause dur="short"/> now now where did she get the idea <pause dur="short"/> it's very old <pause dur="short"/> it's black and white</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's from a <trunc>mo</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> it's from another film isn't it or it's it's referenced in a song cos we were talking about Strangers on a Train</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0083">oh no that's why she's</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0084">and it was referenced and we I couldn't tell you what it was <pause dur="short"/> it was but either we were talking about it or she'd <trunc>men</trunc> someone had mentioned it in class or something <pause dur="short"/> someone had mentioned it for her to get the idea and I can't remember whether it <trunc>w</trunc> where the idea had come from</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh right <pause dur="short"/> but somebody gave her the idea <pause dur="short"/> cos if I'd said it she wouldn't</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0084">the thing is there's there's <trunc>gre</trunc> like you know if you watch Rope it's completely different to anything you've ever seen before</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0083">absolutely</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0084">it's like watching a play <pause dur="short"/> and if if she doesn't</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and all Hitchcock films although you can tell they're Hitchcock</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0083">they are all different form each other</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0084">yeah well it's because he's making films for forty years</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0084">you know his early films were influenced by German cinema which is a bit weird</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0084">which is why his early films are a bit peculiar</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0084">then he moves to Hollywood and makes Hollywood blockbusters and then he makes yeah some interesting arty films <pause dur="short"/> I think you can see how he develops</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0083">yeah of course</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0084">Cos obviously he makes them for such a long time but naturally within that <trunc>p</trunc> within that forty years you are going to find a film that you quite like</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0084">I mean it's brilliant</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0083">I would think so</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0084">apart from The Birds</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0083">and different ones like like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> that was very different</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> has she seen that? She'd like that</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0083">I don't know whether <trunc>sh</trunc> because I used to have it on video so maybe she remembers but</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah but we we've <trunc>def</trunc> we've definitely watched it <pause dur="short"/> I've seen it a couple of times but erm</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0084">she'd watch that</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0083">but she's very odd about the things that she will and won't watch</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0084">yeah it's difficult to predict</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0083">I I can't predict <pause dur="short"/> I can't second guess her at all</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1059" who="S0084">it's amazing what a small surface area you can get all four paws on</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> it always amazes me</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0083">and actually and turn around on it as well</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0084">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a funny one</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0083">it's very strange I mean that you know they can do that</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0084">and he's sleeping</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I mean and almost literally walk on a tightrope <pause dur="short"/> I mean they're they're so agile</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0083">it's so funny <pause dur="short"/> well though the wobbly bit down there now has thrown him cos he goes urgh</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1070" who="S0083"><unclear/> that post has to be replaced</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0083"><trunc>Th</trunc> but that's that's <unclear/> I'll get Steve here to just to do you know two panels there so that will be pleasant for the summer to for us to sit out there and then we'll just gradually</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh we'll just see how we go <pause dur="short"/> see how the money goes <pause dur="short"/> I've got other things I want to do as well</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> bloody money</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I don't like this not having any money <pause dur="short"/> it's not nice</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0084">rubbish</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0083">it's absolute poo <pause dur="short"/> I don't like it <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> anyway we'll see <pause dur="short"/> we'll see how how things go</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0083">I'm not not going to look too far ahead I think that's the</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0084">probably for the best</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0083">it seems to work the best <pause dur="short"/> I just  I just  go yeah from week to week and that's</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0084">well that's what the most people do</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0083">it's well yeah but you you do have to look a bit forward but not too much <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm I'm quite looking forward to having have the summer</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well it's nice to have an idea of something</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0083">I mean I look forward to growing things and</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0083">you know nice times sitting <pause dur="short"/> I was <trunc>spe</trunc> it was so lovely you know having breakfast out there in the mornings last week <pause dur="short"/> it was just really nice</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0083">I enjoy things <pause dur="short"/> you know just things like that just pleasant times</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0084">yeah yeah I know</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0083">er I think  I think  I need to have people round more</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0083">in the summer</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0084">probably good</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah would be nice <pause dur="short"/> and if you want to you know you're always welcome <pause dur="short"/> and if you want to come and sit in the garden in on a sunny afternoon just do</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0083">just come round</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0083">any time <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know that you've got a little garden to sit in but you know</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0084">mm with our installation art</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0083">oh you can ignore that <pause dur="short"/> just sit out there with a cup of tea and a book</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0083">and a bikini</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0084">Cook me <pause dur="short"/> I don't really do that any more <pause dur="short"/> I like to be brown but I also don't want I don't want the cancer so</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0083" trans="overlap">you do <pause dur="short"/> if you're just sensible</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0084">I'll just try and be a bit sensible</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0083">slap on the old er SPF</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0083">and you'll be alright</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0084">actually that's a point I might go and dig that out of the garage cos it's in one of the boxes with my summer clothes</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0083">is it?</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0084">yeah I packed it away in the depths of winter because I thought I wouldn't need it</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0083">of course <pause dur="short"/> well you will at some point</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0084">yeah I'll go and dig it out a bit later</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0083">you'll want your summer clothes as well won't you</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> I might just bring them in and air them a little bit because they probably all need to go in the wash</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> well you've got I mean you've got things that you can use in summer haven't you</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0084">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> it's fine <pause dur="short"/> I mean that stuff is really sort of not just beach wear but you know</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0084">cotton dresses and things that really are just when it's hot</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0083">when it's very hot so</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0084">sort of like three days a year that if you're in the UK you can wear them</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes exactly</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0084">and I won't be having a summer holiday this year <pause dur="short"/> you know if we if I go away it will be New York</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> well you've got a garden to come and sunbathe in that's fine</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I'm going to be getting around I think I'm going to try and get over to <anon type="place"/> again in July</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0083">mhm</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0084">you know they have  you know they have  the <anon type="place"/> parade's in July</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0083">oh my God</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0084">but there's a bank holiday so it means <unclear/></u>
<u n="1134" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah but you don't really want to be there though</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0084">well it <trunc>w</trunc> I was there when I got back from travelling so four years ago that was when  met her future husband <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because he came round to the house</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0084">was a friend of her sister's</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0084">that was the night they met and I was there</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0083">ah</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0084">and we had a house party because her parents because it's a long weekend her parents bought a caravan on the coast</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0084">so I think I'd gone on the Saturday <pause dur="short"/> was I working at <anon type="place"/> Assessment then? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I'd gone <pause dur="short"/> I'd taken the Friday off <pause dur="short"/> so flown Friday</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0084">and was it in the party was a Friday night</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0084">and on the Saturday we drove to the coast and that's when we went to <anon type="place"/> and we went to the beach and it was all very beautiful and</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0083">lovely</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0084">has got the same weekend off again this year so she said why don't you come over?</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0084">twelfth <pause dur="short"/> twelfth of July I think but it's a Thursday so I've booked the Thursday and Friday off work so</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0083">twelfth of July that rings a bell for me</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah she said it was really funny because obviously she was working at <anon type="place"/> then and Americans would in and they'd say happy twelfth <pause dur="short"/> have a nice day <pause dur="short"/> like as if it's the fourth of July <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they really understand</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0084">they thought it was like a big everyone would be celebrating and they didn't really understand all the troubles <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0083">americans <pause dur="short"/> thick really</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0084">well I mean it is complicated</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0083">of course it is</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0084">er but yeah so I might go over then</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0084">obviously no-one assumes it will be nice weather but erm in terms of sort of getting about and having little breaks</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that will be nice</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0084">so I've got next week the Jubilee week</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0083">mhm</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0084">and I think erm we might go <anon type="place"/> for a few days</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0083">well when is the Jubilee week?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0084">at the beginning of June <pause dur="short"/> fourth and fifth of June or third and fourth of June</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0083" trans="overlap">is it? I think so that's in June and the Olympics are July <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0084">end of July</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0083">Good grief</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no escaping it</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0083">no <pause dur="short"/> so this is sixty years isn't it</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0083">yeah she's catching up on Victoria</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0083">Cos how long cos? Wait a minute I do know</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0084">I don't know when she was crowned but she died in nineteen O one</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0083">that's right <pause dur="short"/> sixty-four years she was</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0083">yeah sixty-four</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0084">and she is the longest serving monarch?</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I think Lizzie's going to overtake her</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0084">well if she's going to be like her mum then yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0084">she could live for another twenty years</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0083">she could</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0084"><unclear/> how old is she? Wait how old was she when she was crowned?</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0083">well she was  she was  young <pause dur="short"/> she was in her twenties <pause dur="short"/> she was young</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0084" trans="overlap">was she twenty? So she probably eighty</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0083" trans="overlap">whereas Victoria was a  was a  I think she was actually a teenager wasn't she? About eighteen or something when she became queen?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0083">erm I I think she was born I I erm I think she was born in twenty-six because mum was born in thirty-six and I just remember</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0083">twenty years before <pause dur="short"/> erm so what does that make her? <unclear/> six <unclear/></u>
<u n="1195" who="S0084">eighty-six</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0083">God <pause dur="short"/> oh is she really?</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0084">well she must be</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah cos the Duke's ninety isn't he <pause dur="short"/> ninety-one</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0084">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> ninety-one this year <pause dur="short"/> but he's got to be senile hasn't he? I mean I know granddad kept all of his faculties until he was <trunc>n</trunc> you know when he died</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0084">he just you know his body was giving up on him</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0084">so it happens but you'd think that by the time you get to ninety you're brain it would just be mush</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well not necessarily <pause dur="short"/> I mean really not necessarily I mean I don't know I don't know how</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it depends how active you keep it I suppose <pause dur="short"/> and they live a life of luxury so</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0083" trans="overlap">they do yeah</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0084">it's not like he'd be using his brain an awful lot</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/> If he ever did</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0084">if he ever did <pause dur="short"/> he certainly never had any quality control did he with what came out</u>
<event desc="sound of cat"/>
<u n="1210" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0084">has he been fed?</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> where is he?</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> probably twice <pause dur="short"/> he's out in the garden</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0083">what's he meowing for? Oh</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0084">so she's eighty-six <pause dur="short"/> so erm Queen Mum was what? Hundred and two</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0084">so she's potentially she's got another sixteen years</u>
<event desc="sound of cat"/>
<u n="1218" who="S0083">yes? What are you complaining about? What are you complaining about? Are there birds out there?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0084" trans="overlap">at which point Charles <pause dur="short"/> cos isn't Charles a couple of years younger than dad? So he's sixties</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0083" trans="overlap">he's a year younger I think <pause dur="short"/> he was born in forty-eight</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0084">right so in which case this year he's fifty-sixty-four</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> god <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0084">erm and in sixteen years he'd be <trunc>sev</trunc> eighty <pause dur="short"/> my maths is bad</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0083" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1225" who="S0084">he'd be eighty so he might be senile</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0084">in which case maybe it would go <pause dur="short"/> skip him altogether and go to William</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and people have often said that <pause dur="short"/> people have often suggested that <pause dur="short"/> I mean years twenty years ago they were saying</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0083">you know the queen the queen's obviously going to live a very long time and he might never be king and wouldn't it be better just to give it to William?</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he's held out for <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> yes it will <pause dur="short"/> it depends how he <trunc>fe</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> like if he's really desperate to be king then he's going to want it whether he's senile or not</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but he wouldn't be king for very long <pause dur="short"/> it will be like Edward the Seventh</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it was  and it was  more the frustration you know that he I mean that that is true <pause dur="short"/> you know when the only job you have is waiting for someone to die so you can do their job</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0083">what do you do with your life?</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0083">and I think that's always been his frustration <pause dur="short"/> what to do with his life <pause dur="short"/> and and it must be <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's in that way it's not his fault it's it's the  it's the  structure of the  of the  monarchy isn't it?</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0084">well I suppose but you can still you know the princes certainly er are busy enough and they go out their <trunc>th</trunc> two young princes</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0083" trans="overlap">he's certainly tried to do things</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0084">I mean they're out and about meeting people <pause dur="short"/> you know supporting <unclear/> And and that's what he does <pause dur="short"/> well <unclear/> been doing it for sixty-five years hasn't he but yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh that's what Charles has always done <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's only so much of that you can do <pause dur="short"/> I mean they have to be so boring <pause dur="short"/> so boring just meeting people <pause dur="short"/> oh long have you been doing this? Oh yes <pause dur="short"/> do you enjoy doing that? Oh yes</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0084">he's quite into the all green way of life as well isn't he <pause dur="short"/> he's quite a champion <pause dur="short"/> you know erm all about climate change and</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0083" trans="overlap">he has been <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's had  he's had  various projects I mean he made erm</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0084">he formed the Princes Trust</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0083">he did <pause dur="short"/> he did <pause dur="short"/> I mean he has done he's I think he's someone who would like to have a project and he would throw himself into something like that</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0083">and I think he does done</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> get's very passionate about things</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0083">erm his house is it Highgrove? I think that's what it's called</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0084">the one on The Mall?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0083">highgrove House <pause dur="short"/> no where <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's I think it's where he and Diana lived <pause dur="short"/> and I presume it's where he lives</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0084">well there's one that belongs to him ext to the palace isn't there? <trunc>Cla</trunc> <trunc>Clar</trunc> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1254" who="S0083">Clarence House</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0084">Clarence House yeah</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0083">yeah I think I think they've got that as well maybe <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that's his isn't it?</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0083">anyway he turned it into a a you know a completely kind of sustainable house <pause dur="short"/> I mean even even things like cos I mean cos people were horrified at the time but it's it's really good way of doing it</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0084" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0083">erm the waste systems <pause dur="short"/> you know all the plumbing and the waste from the house erm rather than go into the the main sewerage system erm they they built a series of reed beds which filter and cleans water <pause dur="short"/> it's a completely natural way of</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> sewers <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0083">I mean and there was a big programme about all of that <pause dur="short"/> and he grows all his own stuff and you know it's all very green and sustainable and he he was really into the whole thing</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0084" trans="overlap">wow <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0083">and I thought well that's really good <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously you need the money to do it but</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0084">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0083">but at least he's doing so fair enough</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0084">it's a good model for <unclear/></u>
<u n="1268" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and that was a big project for a long time</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I can imagine</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0084">I think I remember reading in the paper that Blair at the time was quite would get frustrated with him because he would try and get involved in politics and it's all like that's a bit of  bit of  a no no in this day and age but to have someone take an interest in the monarchy is is important I think you know they are supposed to be the head of our  of our  country whether that's in name only which it essentially is</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0084">but they should be <pause dur="short"/> they should know what's going on <pause dur="short"/> they should be involved in the policy making <pause dur="short"/> you know this is completely ridiculous if they've got to go and ask the Queen if they can form a government but actually she's go no say in what the laws are</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well that's pretty much how it is</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0084">well absolutely and and there's reasons for that I mean look at our history but still if you're going to have a monarchy have them involved or don't have one</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0084">this whole pretence it's very very strange</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it is pretence yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0084">this black rod knocking on the House of Commons and</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know and that's why it gets frustrating because you think well what are we paying them to do? And it's it's billions</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0084">well <pause dur="short"/> tourism</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0083">you know</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0084">oh absolutely <pause dur="short"/> but the country wouldn't be without them <pause dur="short"/> there's more pro monarchists than there are anti</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I think that's it <pause dur="short"/> I think people just like it</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0084">it's it's historic you know</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0083">I I don't know what it is <pause dur="short"/> erm because  was trying to work this out and and she just came to the conclusion that it's it's just something people like <pause dur="short"/> it's nice</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0084">it's nice</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0083">it has no no real value</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0084">tourism is the value</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but but oh well that's what people say I mean I don't know</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0084">well look at the wedding last year <pause dur="short"/> look at the Jubilee <pause dur="short"/> people flood to the UK <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>m</trunc> particularly er you know countries in the Commonwealth</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0083">but why do they? It doesn't make any sense <pause dur="short"/> but why do they like it?</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0084" trans="overlap">they love it <pause dur="short"/> I suppose they <trunc>wa</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>pe</trunc> people got quite fascinated by that sense of tradition aren't they</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it is weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0084">I mean if you look at countries that are obsessed with British culture <pause dur="short"/> you know in Japan they've got erm they've got their own Globe built <pause dur="short"/> they've got their own mini Stratford-upon-Avon built <pause dur="short"/> you know they love <pause dur="short"/> they go <trunc>ma</trunc> mad for it and in terms of money that's it's very lucrative</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it's so strange isn't it</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0084">it's a big it's big money spinner for the UK</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0083">I suppose that's that's how</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0084">and that's part of the reason for having the Olympics here <pause dur="short"/> it's bringing people here <pause dur="short"/> it's making people aware of what's going on and it's providing jobs for people this year you know providing work for people</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0084">obviously by September they'll be out of work but at a time when there are few jobs then</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0084">I don't understand it <pause dur="short"/> I mean it is billions is it almost a billion pounds isn't it</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but it's I think more than that it's it's the money that's being poured into an area of London that that needed it but it's not the people who actually live there that will benefit from it</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>abso</trunc> well it's the rich people who will come in and buy all the houses and up the rent</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0083">yeah and that's what they're that's what's happening</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0084">it will drive people out into into the slums because that's the area that people could afford to live in</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and it's and and the the new building  the new building  is is expensive building so</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0084">it's not affordable housing</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0083">no</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1311" who="S0083">just seems very wrong</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it is</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0083">but it was like you know the rich have always lived in the West and then the North and then the South and now they're moving into the East of London so what area of London is there for ordinary working class people to live in?</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> nowhere</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1315" who="S0084">it does look like it's going to rain doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0083">it's windy as well <pause dur="short"/> it's it's it's not actually</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0084">and that's quite a grey cloud coming over</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0083">it is <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether to put the washing out or not now</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0084">I mean we might we're usually just on the edge of it aren't we?</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0083">we are</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0084">I mean it will be good <pause dur="short"/> the garden needs the rain</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0083">it does <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's the other thing</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0084">it's very dry</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0083">Richard always goes ah you're always saying this <pause dur="short"/> you always jinx the weather <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is we do have very dry weather here and we need rain</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mother Earth is so dry</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0083">it does dry out and and we need it</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1328" who="S0083">in the summer we're going to need it <pause dur="short"/> we've got a hosepipe ban it's going to be really hard watering all the vegetables <pause dur="short"/> it will be very hard</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> They're going to have to <pause dur="short"/> I mean you're going to have to just decide what the priorities are and some of them</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0083">well everything needs water</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0084">I know I know I know but in terms of whether you keeps the roses alive or whether you keep the veg alive</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well the roses are okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1333" who="S0084">did you say that there are they quite temperamental? The roses?</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0083">no <pause dur="short"/> no they're they're roses are pretty hardy</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0084" trans="overlap">once they're in they're okay <pause dur="short"/> are they?</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they can put up with most <pause dur="short"/> they don't like absolute drought</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> have they got quite deep roots though?</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes they do have very deep roots and obviously the longer they're in</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0083">I mean these these have only right these four have been in two years now <pause dur="short"/> obviously I'm going to have to be careful with the new one and I'll water that regularly</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0083">but I mean every summer I've been able to water it as much as I liked</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0084">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1344" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and the roses don't like being very dry <pause dur="short"/> they can tolerate a certain amount</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0084">it's difficult isn't it because they're they're the ones that need all the sun</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0084">so they would dry out</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0084">I wonder what they're going to do the botanics?</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0083"><unclear/> one thing I must do then erm if you fancy a trip to the garden centre</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0084">mhm <pause dur="short"/> oh with you need to get that little piece</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0083">we need to get the thing to to to erm feed in the er water butt so that I can use that <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1353" who="S0084" trans="overlap">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> well why don't you <trunc>dri</trunc>have a cycle over to during the week and if they don't have it then we'll drive down there?</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0083">they don't have that <pause dur="short"/> no I mean it's it's it's quite a specialist</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh have you looked?</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0083">it's not just like <pause dur="short"/> I mean  only have like the the hose bit and and that kind of thing so so it's erm</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0084">that's fine we can drive out there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1358" who="S0083">oh  was telling me there's another er garden centre that's much much nicer</u>
</body>
</text>
