<text id="S7QU">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:58</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0114 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home of ANON, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Plants and gardening</topics>
		<activity>Mum and son talking about plants and gardening</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0114">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Eccleshall, Staffordshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">right so um</u>
<u n="2" who="S0114" trans="overlap">so did we decide that those bigger seeds were were pumpkin seeds on the bread?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh no uh I dunno actually they were some funny colour they were like um they were like browny green or or almost but uh I didn't know what that was um but uh I've</u>
<u n="4" who="S0114">I've eaten them often yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115">actually I've seen pumpkin seeds that when we took them out at Halloween</u>
<u n="6" who="S0114">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh had the <trunc>th</trunc> you know take out the seeds and sort of throw most of them away <pause dur="short"/> we kept a few of them and toasted them but uh <pause dur="short"/> they actually white those ones so</u>
<u n="8" who="S0114" trans="overlap">they may turn green of course <pause dur="short"/> they may go a different colour</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">I dunno so I don't I I dunno but um</u>
<u n="10" who="S0114">I've seen them many times but I've eaten them many times but I don't know what they are</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so I never thought of growing a pumpkin but uh I guess they'd be good <pause dur="short"/> cos you can make soups can't you?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0114" trans="overlap">I think I might <pause dur="short"/> oh did I did we tell you we've made some absolutely wonderful compost</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> uh</u>
<u n="14" who="S0114" trans="overlap">we've been cultivating it for years <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um and it's finally</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right you actually put sort of like a</u>
<u n="16" who="S0114" trans="overlap">it's turned into the most wonderful soft light soil <pause dur="short"/> so um</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115" trans="overlap">alright so it does work then it's not just a  not just a  joke</u>
<u n="18" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah it works yeah <pause dur="short"/> and what's really lovely about it is that Dad pulled out this long piece of wool and um he said <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="20" who="S0114"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought that was really nice because if you <trunc>sh</trunc> if you shouldn't put something into the composter it tells you cos it doesn't break down</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it sort of <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's just there <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> it's a good thing to have isn't it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0114" trans="overlap">so we've got this wonderful light really soft light soil cos it's full of worms if you look in it it's disgusting <pause dur="short"/> it's got all these worms in</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah well I'm I'm sure it's disgusting I mean I would expect compost to cos they they smell quite bad don't they <trunc>e</trunc> for a while <pause dur="short"/> that's why you have to put them at the end of the garden don't you? Away from uh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Away from yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they smell bad <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> is that where we're going wrong? <vocal desc="laugh"/> So</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">because uh I suppose they attract they do attract sort of flies and things and uh maybe uh wasps or something but uh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0114" trans="overlap">they attract flies yeah they do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">but but when but it is a way of <trunc>mak</trunc> saving yourself money isn't it because if you wanted to grow uh you know if you wanted to grow plants then you'd need to buy soil so how much what sort of volume d'you think it?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh masses <pause dur="short"/> a whole barrel <trunc>f</trunc> a really quite a large two <trunc>f</trunc> uh three foot high barrel uh of it</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah so sort of a substantial <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0114">and um so what I'm going to do is when the weather's a bit warmer I'm going to um dig it into those two the terrace beds at the bottom and uh for my veg</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115">oh yeah right so you're gonna <pause dur="short"/> a sort of self-sufficient or you know moving towards slowly towards self-sufficiency</u>
<u n="32" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm digging out the raspberry canes cos they completely failed <pause dur="short"/> and then I'm going to grow  I'm going to grow  runner beans this year <pause dur="short"/> d'you remember when we grew them at Langleys Road? You grew some and they were really successful <pause dur="short"/> very successful</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> uh I remember having when the canes were we haven't done any here cos we don't really have um</u>
<u n="34" who="S0114" trans="overlap">no we haven't <pause dur="short"/> but we uh we're going to do that this time</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose we don't eat that many of them but</u>
<u n="36" who="S0114" trans="overlap">you would if you grew them</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">the yeah I mean it's one of those things we have to think about uh what is sort what's gonna save us money what what will we actually cos it's all very well growing you know ten um <trunc>y</trunc> you know uh gooseberry plants or something but well we don't  we don't  eat gooseberries ever so we wouldn't have any use for that but</u>
<u n="38" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">well we had a cucumber one that saved us sort of you know fifty P each cucumber you know so</u>
<u n="40" who="S0114" trans="overlap">at least</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">but um</u>
<u n="42" who="S0114" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115">and things we we eat a lot of uh carrots and potatoes but</u>
<u n="44" who="S0114">yes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">well there is a problem cos of course you you can't really match the kinds of demand that you have you know you buy a bag of potatoes every week uh but it'd be hard to grow that many <pause dur="short"/> but uh it'd be</u>
<u n="46" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can grow a lot out of one plant in a tub <pause dur="short"/> so that's another thing we're going to do <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to waste valuable ground space on potatoes cos you can grow a lot on a plant <pause dur="short"/> I saw Jamie Oliver doing it <pause dur="short"/> um but I'm going to grow some carrots <pause dur="short"/> we're going to have the beans just in front of the terrace to give a better view <pause dur="short"/> um and a bit of privacy as well in that corner</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I see yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0114">so and then in that bed I'm going to grow onions red onions <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0114">um and white onions <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to grow some garlics <pause dur="short"/> lettuce with a cloche</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that'll be good <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's it's a question of can you uh you gotta use the space haven't you I mean? Cos how much space have you got? You've got about <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how to judge space by the way into square metres <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0114" trans="overlap">we we might we're getting a greenhouse as well <pause dur="short"/> um in that if we use those just those terraces we've got um we're about six feet wide by <pause dur="short"/> six by three <pause dur="short"/> two of them six by three</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">oh so sort of six by six so <pause dur="short"/> in feet translating that to metres</u>
<u n="54" who="S0114">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> see it's never enough for your vegetables but um</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115" trans="overlap">two by  two by  two metres? No <trunc>i</trunc> it would probably be more <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="56" who="S0114">Cos you then you need a big space between each of them <pause dur="short"/> the broccolis <pause dur="short"/> we're go we're getting a greenhouse so we'll probably put the lettuces in there <pause dur="short"/> um because um last year we grew those cauliflowers and they started off with a a fist-size ball and they were so healthy white <pause dur="short"/> and we'd got all these slug pellets round them but we didn't realize that the danger came from overhead <pause dur="short"/> the caterpillars the cabbage whites lay their eggs all over it and they were totally ruined <pause dur="short"/> cauliflowers broccolis the lot went into the bin</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it? Oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> moths and things? The little moth things yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah um <pause dur="short"/> well they're really they are hard to grow those ones cos we had  we had  some some <trunc>broco</trunc> you gave us a broccoli and uh they they just grew into these really hideous uh things where the the individual  the individual  yeah uh Frankencabbage</u>
<u n="58" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's terrible <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> Day Of The Triffid <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0115">uh the the um the individual tree sprouted the whatever they call them the individual sprouts of it were sort of growing at different rates so you'd have bits sticking out uh certain clumps sticking out and other bits holding back and then it was going off and also it was getting eaten by a variety of things <trunc>u</trunc> so that I think that sort of broccoli and cauliflower are perhaps you know amongst the  amongst the  harder things to grow <pause dur="short"/> are they do do they need more heat? Yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I know <pause dur="short"/> ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> for the greenhouse <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> beetroot's <trunc>b</trunc> I tell you <pause dur="short"/> uh you get good ideas going round um garden centres round the um the kitchen gardens <pause dur="short"/> you get lots of tips then <pause dur="short"/> cos you can see that you can grow beetroots and then in between them you can put a carrot <pause dur="short"/> uh you can put something in between them that doesn't need as much space <pause dur="short"/> you get loads of good ideas by going round those <pause dur="short"/> um the Women's Institute often do a garden and you get uh you can get ideas for growing all sorts of things</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah you gotta do that <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot of um <pause dur="short"/> you need to  need to  read <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there's an allotment down here <pause dur="short"/> but I was thinking you know obviously the internet is a real good source isn't it cos I know yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115">remember that that programme you know with the <pause dur="short"/> when Jamie Oliver had his you know he's got his gardener I'm sure he's got all his everything has been planned out so I assume there's loads of knowledge that that you can get about it uh</u>
<u n="64" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> monty Don as well <pause dur="short"/> you can get lots of ideas</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it's a question of <pause dur="short"/> you have to learn a lot <pause dur="short"/> yeah you have to learn a lot quite quickly uh is the hard part I suppose</u>
<u n="66" who="S0114">about shooting and getting them in the pots to start with <pause dur="short"/> but we've got some <pause dur="short"/> uh we're gonna start little things off in egg trays <pause dur="short"/> well when we get the greenhouse that'll make a huge difference <pause dur="short"/> um cos we can <trunc>mov</trunc> put the tomatoes and lettuces and things like that that are slug prone into there</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> you know yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh how big the how big are the lettuce gonna be? Sorry the the greenhouse gonna be</u>
<u n="68" who="S0114" trans="overlap">uh eight by <pause dur="short"/> eight by six <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>si</trunc> or yeah or six by four</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0114">pends how much space there is</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so you can then you can get lemons cos I've got a load of lemons over there but they they seem to have uh</u>
<u n="72" who="S0114" trans="overlap">grape vine</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah we'll we've got one in the cemetery isn't there?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0114">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we're <trunc>go</trunc> yes what you do is you plant you take a piece of window out of the bottom out of the corner of it and stick it and poke the root into the ground <pause dur="short"/> so that it gets watered <pause dur="short"/> and then the rest of it grows round your greenhouse</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mind you in in where you are you may be able to grow it outside but yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0114">um yes you get a lot of concentrated sun in that one corner <pause dur="short"/> I grow tomatoes in that corner <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you could've <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> could've as well actually cos he was in  he was in  <anon type="place"/> he might've been able to <pause dur="short"/> partly just to <pause dur="short"/> red them I'd think</u>
<u n="78" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> white? White and red? I'd grow red</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well there's two <pause dur="short"/> there's there's one in the cemetery which is an old and it's an established sort of old plant and then there's one in the um <pause dur="short"/> there's one uh <pause dur="short"/> there's one in a pub down there it sort of goes round the on a trellis on the side of the house</u>
<u n="80" who="S0114">can anybody pick it? Are they <trunc>pri</trunc> is it <trunc>pri</trunc> it's not for everyone to pick <pause dur="short"/> really? mm <pause dur="short"/> oh I'd love to do that <pause dur="short"/> I'd love to do that</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but yeah so I don't know if it has to go inside but I suppose it doesn't matter I mean</u>
<u n="82" who="S0114">if you've got plenty of sun on it <pause dur="short"/> constant sun <pause dur="short"/> cos there or the maximum sun <pause dur="short"/> cos there's a the you know the way our gardens are <pause dur="short"/> the way our gardens are <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's um areas where you get um a lot of sun concentrated sun for all day <pause dur="short"/> and in our garden it's in the bottom right hand corner</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah the the south  the south  facing bit isn't it the uh <pause dur="short"/> you your garden though is actually <trunc>nor</trunc> you've got a north facing garden haven't you? Or have you?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0114">the south <pause dur="short"/> yes that's right <pause dur="short"/> actually no the the um <pause dur="short"/> yes but it gets um <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't matter because it comes over the <trunc>roo</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> because the garden slopes at a certain angle it gets the sun on that spot <pause dur="short"/> and then our neighbour gets the sun the other side of the fence in that corner so they've got a bench there <pause dur="short"/> and we've got we but we grow plants in ours cos um</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean it's not just about the direction as well I mean obviously if you had the south facing you you can't have <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to chop trees down at the bottom if you had a south facing one you'd have to chop trees at the bottom <pause dur="short"/> otherwise you'd have to yeah I suppose you'd have to chop all your trees to maximize your light I suppose wouldn't you? Well yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0114" trans="overlap">we could <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes but we wouldn't do that <pause dur="short"/> cos uh there's this particular area that gets um a lot of sun <pause dur="short"/> uh it gets the sun um from about eleven onwards <pause dur="short"/> from eleven till</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's there there's been <pause dur="short"/> your your garden gets quite hot actually uh I mean I didn't go <pause dur="short"/> I don't normally go in the sun very often but uh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0114" trans="overlap">it does get very hot yeah <pause dur="short"/> but um <pause dur="short"/> but the good thing about our garden is when you're in the front garden it's absolutely boiling hot <pause dur="short"/> you've got your sun hat your sun glasses and it's torture</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah you'd probably do better at planting in your your front garden that's really hot</u>
<u n="90" who="S0114" trans="overlap">so what we could do we could put some tomatoes there if they were or we could put um sweet peas or something</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0114">but um if it's far too hot in the front garden which it quite often is you you can go to the back because after eleven o'clock you get the shade from the house <pause dur="short"/> you get the shade from the house so you can sit on the patio <pause dur="short"/> and of course the sun moves round the shade moves round <pause dur="short"/> but there's an almost always a little patch of the garden where you can be in shade <pause dur="short"/> which is really handy <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean <trunc>all</trunc> it's a small garden but it's not tiny <pause dur="short"/> by any means you can do quite a lot with it <pause dur="short"/> uh it's got</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah for uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah well it's what you  it's what you  make of the space isn't it I mean people that</u>
<u n="94" who="S0114" trans="overlap">of the space yes</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">you know in I saw a thing in uh central London where they they have all kinds of innovative sort of garden techniques you know there there was mushroom growers you see um <pause dur="short"/> they don't mushroom doesn't need light so</u>
<u n="96" who="S0114" trans="overlap">outdoors?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">they they do <pause dur="short"/> yeah they they had a sort of a kinda indoor garden sort of thing</u>
<u n="98" who="S0114" trans="overlap">Peter and Ann used to make them in the  in the  cellar</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">Peter and Ann?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0114">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">oh Mott? Yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> um the cellar yeah yeah we we should um <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's quite a good trick actually I I think I'd like to do that I mean <pause dur="short"/> I've got a lot of aspirations that don't have you know necessarily time or experience to um</u>
<u n="102" who="S0114" trans="overlap">so you could make them <pause dur="short"/> you can <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> or space <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot of things you can grow that don't need much space</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like I don't like like brewing <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'd always like always wanted to brew or um <trunc>ci</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> wine or cider beer <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wine <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to make some wine <pause dur="short"/> I've got an <trunc>abs</trunc> I've got two big cartons of um damsons in the freezer from last winter and I haven't done a thing with them <pause dur="short"/> yet</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0114">so I mean I I uh I'll make a pie I'll make a tart that'll be nice and uh I might um make some damson wine or something <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't got uh the facilities</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">I was just thinking actually some some of the things uh back to um your fungus again um some types of fungus are very um valuable aren't they? Famously truffles are valuable aren't they?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0114">truffles? Are they the ones that grow on the tree?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115">no truffles don't grow on trees <pause dur="short"/> they're the ones that the pigs  the pigs  come and um</u>
<u n="110" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh there's a stake <pause dur="short"/> oh sorry <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking of mushrooms <pause dur="short"/> um yeah <pause dur="short"/> those are <trunc>st</trunc> the stake <pause dur="short"/> the stake mushrooms they were they called it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah you mean fungus that grows on the side of a tree? Uh yeah no um <pause dur="short"/> no I'm thinking of things like truffles and similar I mean I was I think there's a bit of a you know it's a bit like champagne with truffles I think it matters where the you know where the region is that they come from</u>
<u n="112" who="S0114" trans="overlap">I don't think I've ever eaten them actually <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115">with you need to I think they're they're supposed to get Italian truffles and specifically the greatest most expensive truffles presumably come from a particular region of Italy like I dunno um uh <trunc>Mon</trunc> yeah the place that's at the foot of the mountain uh I can't remember <trunc>Pied</trunc> Piedmont or something?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">um it's this region in north of Italy anyway um <pause dur="short"/> cos I saw a programme about it <pause dur="short"/> anyway um there were them two Italian chefs uh that went and <pause dur="short"/> there's they take truffles very seriously in in Italy and um very <trunc>ex</trunc> very valuable</u>
<u n="116" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes they do</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">but anyway yeah so if you had a cellar or someone had a cellar you can just turn uh a boring cellar into you know somewhere that you could <trunc>p</trunc> possibly produce something valuable if if you could grow something like that or or um you know the <trunc>ty</trunc> other type of things like brewing or <pause dur="short"/> you you can  you can  use space that way I mean <pause dur="short"/> there must be a lot of um <pause dur="short"/> a lot of tricks to to make extra <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> make the most of the same money yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0114" trans="overlap">it'd be good <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> there are <pause dur="short"/> and the the apple trees that <trunc>gr</trunc> and the fruit trees that grow along the wall <pause dur="short"/> um they're a very good idea because I mean we've got these apple trees and they're very intermittent in what they produce <pause dur="short"/> um most of our apples this year are from um were from the tree that's on the right which is golden delicious <pause dur="short"/> but um the quality for for a golden delicious apple it's not the quality wasn't very good uh but there were hardly any on the um the James Grieves which are good <trunc>qual</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> when you get those those are superb quality <pause dur="short"/> very big <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> it's a matter of timing the picking before um before the birds and the <trunc>s</trunc> grubs get in it <pause dur="short"/> uh and before it falls off but allowing them to ripen <pause dur="short"/> I mean we had a superb um crop of apples last year cooking apples last year and we gave loads of them away and uh you had a lot didn't you? Um but um but this year we had hardly any from that tree</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh yeah quite a <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> um we we didn't make any cider though</u>
<u n="120" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh I tell you why <pause dur="short"/> we cropped it <pause dur="short"/> we cut it back</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0114">cut the tree right back <pause dur="short"/> pruned it <pause dur="short"/> I didn't think it would leaf even <pause dur="short"/> I mean the way dad cut it it was so big and ugly <pause dur="short"/> um and the way dad cut it back uh I didn't think it would ever grow again but um <pause dur="short"/> we had lots of leaves and a few apples so I mean we'll probably get a good crop this year <pause dur="short"/> but I yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah well that's good I mean I think if we prepare for that actually we should be able should get uh a press or something to press the <trunc>a</trunc> to filter the apples</u>
<u n="124" who="S0114">yes</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">um cos that's the hard part uh well one of the hard parts of making um cider from apples is is um is that you need to filter to press them and filter them</u>
<u n="126" who="S0114" trans="overlap">is to <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yes to get the pulp</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> uh not not the pulp the to get rid of the pulp to get the juice</u>
<u n="128" who="S0114">get juice yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="130" who="S0114" trans="overlap">D'you peel them?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean <pause dur="short"/> so you peel them and that'll take a long time <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="132" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">although uh yeah I think so because I think the sometimes the skin doesn't have <pause dur="short"/> well it has sort of <pause dur="short"/> I suppose you don't have to I suppose you could put them in the press with the skin on as well uh but I'm not sure if the skin has the right sort of things in it but uh</u>
<u n="134" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes I'm not sure what they do <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">we made a little bit of cider uh</u>
<u n="136" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh the skin has the healthy bits in it the the um <pause dur="short"/> the skin of the apple <pause dur="short"/> but for the cider yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh no I mean the the bits for the cider <pause dur="short"/> the the you want the sugars <pause dur="short"/> uh the water and sugar</u>
<u n="138" who="S0114" trans="overlap">I would make cider vinegar if I was doing it <pause dur="short"/> I love cider vinegar</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">yeah well we did cos we left it too long you see cos it starts off as cider and then if you leave it it turns into vinegar</u>
<u n="140" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> did you have some usable?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">we made cider vinegar yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0114">did you? I didn't know about that</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's quite easy actually <pause dur="short"/> we pretty much just did it with uh what are those cloths that you squeeze the uh like a <trunc>clo</trunc></u>
<u n="144" who="S0114" trans="overlap">sieve <pause dur="short"/> uh <trunc>s</trunc> muslin <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">yeah we basically um sort of uh blended them or chopped them</u>
<u n="146" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115">A blender would be very useful or some kind of big blender</u>
<u n="148" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes and then you you can leave it to <trunc>s</trunc> to drip through</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah you gotta peel and core them yeah peel and core them blend them or yeah some way find some way of blending them then then this is the hard bit you've gotta press and filter it you know you've got the <pause dur="short"/> so we did the <trunc>m</trunc> the muslin thing and just squeezed out the uh the juice of it and then uh um</u>
<u n="150" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> the juice <pause dur="short"/> cos you can leave them overnight <pause dur="short"/> to drip but it was</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">we left it in a bottle with a sort of we tied some muslin over the top of it <pause dur="short"/> I think and then left it</u>
<u n="152" who="S0114" trans="overlap"><trunc>Y</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh I didn't know</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">Cos the the yeast is in the um air</u>
<u n="154" who="S0114">oh</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">we didn't add any yeast <pause dur="short"/> um yeast just settles on it and uh and it turns it starts to fizz <pause dur="short"/> it turns into cider but them it it if you leave it the alcohol sort of evaporates and you're left with um well the alcohol gets turned by some other <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what the science of it but you end up with cider vinegar if you leave it too long so you have to know when to <pause dur="short"/> also I think it gets stronger so I think if you <pause dur="short"/> if you started uh it goes through a phase of of initially it would just have a bit of alcohol then then I guess it would get stronger <pause dur="short"/> um and then presumably it would get weaker again as it was starting to turn into vinegar so <pause dur="short"/> but we didn't know much about it <pause dur="short"/> so we hadn't  we hadn't  done what you should do which is to properly read instructions first and make sure you've uh followed it um according to  according to  those so uh um yeah d'you want any any coffee or?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0114" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> cider <trunc>v</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh yes please yeah <pause dur="short"/> cider vinegar's got uh loads of health properties <pause dur="short"/> you know that don't you? All vinegars have <pause dur="short"/> um not they don't just go on fish and chips <pause dur="short"/> you knew that didn't you? You can use it for cleaning um medicinal <pause dur="short"/> and but um but for medicinal <trunc>h</trunc> healing <pause dur="short"/> like aloe</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh well uh what um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah with yeah cleaning yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0114">our aloe's grown really well <pause dur="short"/> uh that little plant <pause dur="short"/> it's grown all through the winter actually <pause dur="short"/> um it had when you gave it to us it had two big stems and one little stem and that stem's grown big and there's another one half-grown as well <pause dur="short"/> it's grown ever since you gave it to us <pause dur="short"/> that's a good one</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah the <pause dur="short"/> I think they um <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yeah um we've we've got a sort of extra <trunc>s</trunc> um bit come out you know the the the little  the little  one on the side <pause dur="short"/> uh that's <pause dur="short"/> we had <trunc>an</trunc> yeah we had another</u>
<u n="160" who="S0114" trans="overlap"><trunc>Y</trunc> yours is <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> oh a baby <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">that's connected to it <pause dur="short"/> we had uh two of them but actually the other one died and it it was suffering for a while but uh I put it on the uh windowsill it seems to have improved but I think they're quite uh those ones are quite hardy uh you know whatever</u>
<u n="162" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> they're very um <pause dur="short"/> those uh I printed off um I looked on the internet the <trunc>p</trunc> uh healing <trunc>pro</trunc> medicinal properties healing properties of um aloe um and it's not just burns <pause dur="short"/> there was a whole page of it <pause dur="short"/> same as tea <pause dur="short"/> you look at um tea um <trunc>y</trunc> ordinary black tea as well not <trunc>j</trunc> it doesn't have to be green tea <pause dur="short"/> and then there's um</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah I've seen that on uh Wikipedia yeah there's loads of uh loads of chemicals in there isn't there? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean there's all these different things some of them are controversial aren't they?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0114" trans="overlap">A garlic loads of them <pause dur="short"/> some of them are controversial but <pause dur="short"/> you see our our forebears knew all this <pause dur="short"/> hundred years hundred well hundred and fifty years ago uh you know the people with their cottage gardens they knew all about uh the healing properties of herbs <pause dur="short"/> and we are realizing</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah based on <pause dur="short"/> well yeah I mean ancient in ancient as well and things like uh like the <trunc>f</trunc> the the <trunc>f</trunc> um penicillin yeah the mould the you know I think aboriginal uh people were using um mould from bark or something to um to to as an antibiotic <trunc>a</trunc> you know as an ancient thing yeah something like that</u>
<u n="166" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> and they found during <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they found during the war that um during um the First World War I suppose it would've been that the soldiers that were injured they cos it took time to catch up with the soldiers that were injured <trunc>w</trunc> you know after battles <pause dur="short"/> um and when they went to them they found that maggots had got into some of the wounds uh which is a bit disgusting but then they realized that the ones whose wounds had been um eaten by um maggots were were healed where um they'd eaten all the the germs the bacteria out of it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah on yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> the the <trunc>di</trunc> the <trunc>discov</trunc> the bacteria yeah <pause dur="short"/> the dead uh the dead um the dead flesh which had bacteria in it um leaving only the um leaving only the good <pause dur="short"/> leaving behind the good flesh</u>
<u n="168" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> amazing isn't it? Yes <pause dur="short"/> enabling the good flesh to heal</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>get</trunc> getting rid of the bacteria I suppose uh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0114" trans="overlap">getting as oh that's amazing <pause dur="short"/> but plants have got terrific</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's an accidental discovery isn't it uh as opposed to um</u>
<u n="172" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like um penicillin <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>h</trunc> we we've turned our back on um on herbal <vocal desc="laugh"/> on herbal remedies for an awfully long time and uh people are realizing you know by analysing these these foods</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I dunno I mean different yeah <pause dur="short"/> some of it um is uh some it's sort of disputed I mean things like the uh anti-oxidants um I think the they you know they get in uh berries and things and yeah yeah uh tea I think and you know</u>
<u n="174" who="S0114" trans="overlap">everything <pause dur="short"/> oranges applies it</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">but it has sometimes in some ways it's good because uh it's got the <trunc>m</trunc> the the you know the free radicals you know the um it it can reduce um</u>
<u n="176" who="S0114">yes</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">uh it has an effect of getting rid of um you know the dangerous free radicals in the blood but also uh it has certain other <trunc>m</trunc> may have certain negative effects as well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0114">yes</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">depending on you know various things but</u>
<u n="180" who="S0114">overconsumption uh like they say</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I think yeah for some things like tea I think prevent uh absorption of some tea prevents absorption of some other stuff like iron but it depends on a lot uh I guess it's complicated though so</u>
<u n="182" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh does it? Yes</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">I mean um</u>
<u n="184" who="S0114">I hadn't read that</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">I mean I uh yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0114" trans="overlap">it has got anti-oxidants to <trunc>pr</trunc> that's protective against quite a few illnesses</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and yeah and some some it's like with the cancer studies often you get you say that this some study will say that it's that it helps against cancer but another study will say that it can actually make can actually have no effect or can actually increase the chance of cancer and there's a lot of complicated uh things about that and these sorts of things take a long time cos you have to do loads and loads of experiments I suppose</u>
<u n="188" who="S0114" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> there are yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">um it <pause dur="short"/> oh there was  there was  one substance for cos it was aspirin wasn't it uh aspirin was supposed to to help against cancer wasn't it um?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0114" trans="overlap">oh well that's the one that's uh <pause dur="short"/> oh well aspirin is the one that <trunc>go</trunc> you know that becomes the um the the you know the ultimate remedy and then they  then they  suddenly announce Oh no it's um it's it's terrible <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> don't take it at all <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well no I mean the I I think it's <trunc>f</trunc> it's good in smallish doses actually but I I have heard cos you sometimes you have it and you don't realize like it's in um it's in like that Bonjela stuff you know that for you to put over mouth ulcers um so it's in that <pause dur="short"/> but it is natural isn't it it's from the willow uh so it is a naturally occurring you know</u>
<u n="192" who="S0114" trans="overlap">it's just <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> in small dose yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> it's natural yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it I think most of things I've read is is its good <pause dur="short"/> its good outweighs its bad um you don't know you know you have to take it with a pinch of salt don't you?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah I think the <trunc>mo</trunc> most of the bad of aspirin is involves um stomach damage or something it damages your stomach but <trunc>or</trunc> uh it I think it has a lot of positive stuff including yeah like <trunc>ca</trunc> cancer benefits something to do with that it compared with paracetamol it sort of it kills it stops processes rather than merely pausing <pause dur="short"/> whereas you know paracetamol would pause a process and then when it wears off the process starts again but uh aspirin I think um just kills the stops the process</u>
<u n="194" who="S0114" trans="overlap">stomach bleeding yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh hair <pause dur="short"/> but um <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's more powerful <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">and that <trunc>hel</trunc> translates to somehow to it actually inhibiting cancer growth but I don't know exactly uh exactly how that happens but oh yeah so I was wondering d'you want any uh coffee? Um yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0114" trans="overlap">we don't know <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yes please yeah <pause dur="short"/> shall we have a cup of coffee then? I think dad's ready for some coffee as well</u>
</body>
</text>
