<text id="S7QY">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:40:28</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0264 S0265</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Dinner at participants' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Work, new technology</topics>
		<activity>New technology</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0264">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crickhowell</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Wales/Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>tutorial fellow</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Dutch -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0265">
				<exactage>56</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harworth, Nottinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>e_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>technical analyst</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0264">have you had pepper?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0265">yes thank you yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0264">and er we need to decide about that Tuesday about getting there for I I'll already I'll already be there</u>
<u n="4" who="S0265">oh right</u>
<u n="5" who="S0264">I'm having lunch there and and then there's the dentist at four o'clock</u>
<u n="6" who="S0265">right well that's that's fine I can I can get there easily</u>
<u n="7" who="S0264" trans="overlap">do you think these vegetables are overdone?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0265">erm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0264" trans="overlap">mm?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0265">no I think they're fine</u>
<u n="11" who="S0264">I think they're a bit overdone <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0265">I think they're just right actually</u>
<u n="13" who="S0264">no <pause dur="short"/> the cauliflower is too soft <pause dur="long"/> you're what about eating?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0265">erm <pause dur="short"/> well I haven't thought about it really but erm I'm assuming I can erm eat at lunchtime and then just take sandwiches for <trunc>th</trunc> for <trunc>th</trunc> for the evening</u>
<u n="15" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="16" who="S0265">how do would you prefer to eat out somewhere?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0264">well I'd I wouldn't in a way because <pause dur="short"/> it's it's gonna be very inconvenient er finding anywhere that's decent and erm we need to find somewhere serving pre theatre dinners</u>
<u n="18" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="19" who="S0264">and then I suppose it would be sensible to find somewhere locally well because you wouldn't want a Tube delay or something</u>
<u n="20" who="S0265">no <pause dur="long"/> no being a prom concert it's it's likely that everywhere is going to be very busy</u>
<u n="21" who="S0264">yeah I've seen erm but erm <pause dur="short"/> well any anywhere that's any <trunc>u</trunc> any good but on the other hand sandwiches would be horrible because they might get spilled or crumbs everywhere <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0265">well we can just erm if it's nice weather we can just go out and find a bench somewhere and eat them</u>
<u n="23" who="S0264">it'll be dark by that time at that time of year won't it?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0265">second of September? no not not at seven thirty I don't think surely <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0264">well there's the Polish place on Exhibition Road but but I notice they've taken the carpets away and it was the food was never any good anyway</u>
<u n="26" who="S0265">no I don't erm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0264">mm?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0265">yes I I remember that er Polish place and I didn't think the food was particularly interesting <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0264">there's a German place next door</u>
<u n="30" who="S0265">oh is there?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0264">yes the Goethe Institute or something I'm not sure if it's open in the evening anyway and it's nothing special <pause dur="long"/> I wonder whether the best thing wouldn't be a hotel somewhere <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0265">mm expensive though probably <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0264">er well there's that erm <pause dur="short"/> there's that bistro place that erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well when went to in near in Piccadilly <pause dur="short"/> in the basement but that could be quite noisy but they're quite efficient</u>
<u n="34" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/> well if they're efficient that might <pause dur="short"/> make up for the erm for the noisiness cos we won't be there quite so long <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0264">and it's very popular well I'll check erm <pause dur="long"/> I'll check that then because it's sort of on the right line isn't it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0264">er?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0265">on the right what?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0264">line</u>
<u n="40" who="S0265">on the right line <pause dur="long"/> you mean right Underground right I don't know I don't know which <trunc>wh</trunc> do are are you talking about the one that erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to oh that was an Italian restaurant wasn't it?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0264">you haven't been there</u>
<u n="42" who="S0265" trans="overlap">no right oh okay so I don't know where it is</u>
<u n="43" who="S0264">it's just off Piccadilly Circus</u>
<u n="44" who="S0265">oh right <pause dur="long"/> actually I don't know what Tube you get to the Royal Albert Hall is it the Circle line? Piccadilly line?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0264">or Victoria</u>
<u n="46" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="47" who="S0264">I think erm or erm <pause dur="short"/> or Piccadilly</u>
<u n="48" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0264">hang on it's not Victoria it's Circle or Piccadilly so actually it's quite good</u>
<u n="50" who="S0265">yeah that's right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0264">I suppose we could eat at the Barbican but <pause dur="short"/> I don't like I don't I don't think the food's any any use there particularly</u>
<u n="52" who="S0265">no it's it's out of the way as well it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's not near is it? <pause dur="long"/> so we'd have to eat early</u>
<u n="53" who="S0264" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> er yeah because you could take the Circle line but it would take ages and also it's very dangerous because if you change er if you get the wrong <pause dur="short"/> you could end up you could end up in Kensington High Street by mistake because some of the Circle lines do the strange things</u>
<u n="54" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0264">they don't all and they also they're quite slow I think going around</u>
<u n="56" who="S0265">yeah <pause dur="long"/> so what sort of a day have you had?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0264">I don't know erm <pause dur="short"/> just nonstop as usual what about you?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0265">yeah it was erm I managed to catch up on on my emails and erm I did quite a few admin type tasks</u>
<u n="59" who="S0264">Tuesday</u>
<u n="60" who="S0265">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0264">your meeting day</u>
<u n="62" who="S0265">it wasn't too bad for meetings it was quite quiet today but we had erm what we call erm a town hall which is erm supposed to be an hour and a half but is only and hour</u>
<u n="63" who="S0264">where?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0265">this <trunc>after</trunc> it was this afternoon it was via <trunc>tele</trunc> it telephone conference</u>
<u n="65" who="S0264">what from your desk?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0265">I asked I I dialled in from my desk but erm you had the option of going to erm a a large room <pause dur="short"/> erm and listening to it</u>
<u n="67" who="S0264">I thought the whole point was to go somewhere</u>
<u n="68" who="S0265">well this it's <trunc>w</trunc> it could it's run from the States you see so the presenter was in the in New York and it was just erm it was just going through a slide a a Powerpoint deck and erm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0264">are there any are they really any ever any good?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0265">yes they I mean it's just sort of information sharing and an opportunity to ask questions <pause dur="long"/> I mean we do it we do also have erm one by meeting by video conference <pause dur="short"/> where the presenter is actually up on large and you couldn't actually see them up on a large screen</u>
<u n="71" who="S0264">er it wasn't this one?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0265">as I said it was just a telephone</u>
<u n="73" who="S0264">telephone audio?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0264">why? are they trying to save money on video cameras or something?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0265">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> it's the it's the format that our particular <pause dur="short"/> boss prefers I suppose <pause dur="short"/> cos he's not he's <trunc>n</trunc> it wasn't erm a company wide one it was specifically for our area which is more urgent</u>
<u n="77" who="S0264" trans="overlap">maybe the <trunc>qua</trunc> maybe the technical quality is actually better than the video conferencing <pause dur="long"/> I mean nowadays there's no excuse for not getting a very good special phone line like broadcasting you know when you have a <trunc>stu</trunc> a broadcast from a studio?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0264">they have special lines so they don't sound like telephones <pause dur="short"/> and when they do sound like telephones it's because somebody's using an ordinary BT phone or even worse a mobile or</u>
<u n="80" who="S0265" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0264">even worse that one of those Skype things</u>
<u n="82" who="S0265">mm well I think they're just ordinary BT lines</u>
<u n="83" who="S0264">well that's not very good cos</u>
<u n="84" who="S0265" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="85" who="S0264">they could afford better than that couldn't they? <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0265">they could do but</u>
<u n="87" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0265">I I'm not complaining because erm <pause dur="short"/> I can usually hear quite clearly <pause dur="short"/> I can hear better listening to someone down the telephone than I can sitting in a room where</u>
<u n="89" who="S0264" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0265" trans="overlap">the the sound is coming out of speakers even though I can see them talking on a video screen</u>
<u n="91" who="S0264">yeah but supposing they had a broadcast quality phone line whatever that's called <trunc>y</trunc>you you might be able to hear better still</u>
<u n="92" who="S0265">yeah maybe <pause dur="long"/> but I mean we we do have erm <pause dur="short"/> we do have some a very high quality video conference facility but it's it's in quite a small room so you can only have</u>
<u n="93" who="S0264" trans="overlap">Google Plus</u>
<u n="94" who="S0265">can only have that with erm small groups</u>
<u n="95" who="S0264">how many?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0265">erm you could probably get about twenty people in that in that room</u>
<u n="97" who="S0264">you mean they can all be seen?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0265">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like one side of the room you can actually see <pause dur="short"/> erm a group of people er er on your the end of the line <pause dur="short"/> and see if they are sitting on the opposite side of the table and they can see you</u>
<u n="99" who="S0264">but are they really on the opposite side of the table?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0265">no</u>
<u n="101" who="S0264" trans="overlap">I mean <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0265">no of course not but they they</u>
<u n="103" who="S0264" trans="overlap">no but I mean are they sitting in a line?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0264">then why don't they sit in a semicircle?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0265">well it is a semicircle actually yes you're right <pause dur="short"/> and I think there are about three cameras which er are trained on you but</u>
<u n="107" who="S0264" trans="overlap">operated automatically or by a human?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0265">I think it's just automatic but what what's strange about them is that when someone's looking at you they tend to look at you on the screen <pause dur="short"/> and not in the camera so when they're looking at you they appear not to be looking at you so that that's a bit <pause dur="short"/> confusing sometimes cos you're not quite sure if they're talking to you personally</u>
<u n="109" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah well</u>
<u n="110" who="S0265" trans="overlap">or</u>
<u n="111" who="S0264">one of the students did something like that last week because they went to find a different classroom and then they phoned up from a room that they'd found and one of them must have been holding the phone as a camera so you could see the face of the other one it wasn't possible that the person making the call was holding <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it wouldn't have been possible would it?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0265">I don't know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0264">do you think the person making the call cos I saw their face the face of the person speaking and I assumed the phone was being held by the other person because there were two of them</u>
<u n="114" who="S0265">mm <trunc>probab</trunc> possibly cos I think it must be difficult to speak and think about what you're saying and and and and hold it steady at the same time</u>
<u n="115" who="S0264">and how did he know also how did he know that he was in the picture?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0264">in the frame?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0265">I don't know cos</u>
<u n="119" who="S0264" trans="overlap">and then and then and then well cos he must have been erm the er <trunc>ca</trunc> the mirror image of erm of my situation where one of the students in in the room where we were was holding his <pause dur="short"/> holding the phone <pause dur="short"/> for me to see so presumably that was on camera as well</u>
<u n="120" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0264">so I could <trunc>o</trunc> I couldn't see myself obviously I could only see erm this person in the other building</u>
<u n="122" who="S0265">well we we've done some meetings where we've used some application like Skype where where you actually <pause dur="short"/> in the corner of the screen you get a <trunc>li</trunc> a small picture which shows you what</u>
<u n="123" who="S0264">yeah we do that</u>
<u n="124" who="S0265" trans="overlap">people the other end can see</u>
<u n="125" who="S0264">what? for</u>
<u n="126" who="S0265">it <trunc>sho</trunc> it shows you what the people at the other end can actually see of it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0264">well we have erm split screens for erm the speaker and any Powerpoint that they're using <pause dur="short"/> so that when it's when it's broadcast or recorded but and played back later you can see both the speaker and the <pause dur="short"/> slides</u>
<u n="128" who="S0265">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0264">but that means the speaker is often minute <pause dur="short"/> doesn't though</u>
<u n="130" who="S0265" trans="overlap">you</u>
<u n="131" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it shouldn't have to be minute but they are in one in the one I used today anyway the er this morning</u>
<u n="132" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> well we have erm <pause dur="short"/> we've had meetings where you where the presenter is going through slides and <pause dur="short"/> they tend to switch between him and the slides</u>
<u n="133" who="S0264">yeah but that must be a that's the whole point that's what I suppose our system tries to avoid because that could be quite irritating because you're not in control of when you switch from the from the slide to the speaker are you? or vice versa</u>
<u n="134" who="S0265">no we're not in control of it no but it's like when you</u>
<u n="135" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah so what if you're looking at something and you haven't finished interpreting?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah that yeah well that's it exactly <trunc>s</trunc> it's like when you're watching the news</u>
<u n="137" who="S0264">yeah well the answer is not to watch it they <trunc>d</trunc> you know it</u>
<u n="138" who="S0265" trans="overlap">that is quite difficult</u>
<u n="139" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it</u>
<u n="140" who="S0265">trying to read something anyway while they're speaking <pause dur="short"/> cos I can't I can't read and take it in and listen at the same time anyway</u>
<u n="141" who="S0264">well I doubt whether a lot of people can't I think <pause dur="short"/> cos the speakers are probably they don't stop <pause dur="short"/> long enough to let people take things in</u>
<u n="142" who="S0265">no they don't no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0264">so is it next week that your mother's coming?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0265">no it's it's the week of the proms concert</u>
<u n="145" who="S0264">so it's not next week it's the week after is it?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0265">it must be <pause dur="short"/> well let's work it out</u>
<u n="147" who="S0264">I I don't need to work it out I've got my diary right here and it and so I don't need to I can just look it up if I wanted to <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0265">well the concert's three weeks today <pause dur="long"/> shall I shut this window now?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0264">yes please probably midges or insects that will come <pause dur="long"/> oh <pause dur="long"/> actually they're not coming <trunc>f</trunc> it's nearly three weeks</u>
<u n="150" who="S0265">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's three weeks <pause dur="short"/> or just over three weeks</u>
<u n="151" who="S0264">well thank goodness I'll be on leave that week sort of <pause dur="long"/> but I don't know whether I'll feel like eating much after a luncheon oh no that er the other thing about these trousers I really I I don't think I'm I can be bothered to to either to take I I don't think the iron will iron out those things because they're probably steamed or manufactured in <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't say anything I I looked</u>
<u n="152" who="S0265">mm you you could be right <pause dur="short"/> the they've obviously been done like that but for effect and</u>
<u n="153" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0265" trans="overlap">they're meant to to be <trunc>r</trunc><trunc>r</trunc>rucked apart like</u>
<u n="155" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it's really annoying and I could take them back she said I could anyway er the the the assistant but <pause dur="short"/> but I needed a I need a new pair of trousers anyway</u>
<u n="156" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0264">the trouble is they're not really suitable for work are they? they're alright in the summer I suppose</u>
<u n="158" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0264" trans="overlap">but may but maybe not</u>
<u n="160" who="S0265" trans="overlap">though I think that makes them look a bit <trunc>inf</trunc> too too informal</u>
<u n="161" who="S0264">maybe I should take them back then</u>
<u n="162" who="S0265">I think <trunc>s</trunc> well</u>
<u n="163" who="S0264">it's just a gigantic waste of time <pause dur="short"/> I only</u>
<u n="164" who="S0265">you've got to take the other one back anyway aren't you? the top are you taking that back?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0264">I don't know do you do you want it?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0265">no no thank you</u>
<u n="167" who="S0264">erm because I'm not even sure about the quality though I when I when I undid the buttons they didn't undo very easily I don't think it's been made with great care the buttons and the button holes are</u>
<u n="168" who="S0265" trans="overlap">well it's probably cheap clothing</u>
<u n="169" who="S0264">yeah and that's what annoys me because if you can get it the same thing or similar from Primark for a couple of quid <pause dur="long"/> I only went to get a a a a a card er a congratulations card</u>
<u n="170" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0264">and then we didn't need anything else and so but then I thought oh yeah I'd use that coupon erm and I found out I could use it on clothing so I thought I'll have a look and see if there's anything on sale and so that's what I <trunc>fou</trunc> I noticed those two things but obviously really I would have bought erm a long sleeved shirt if I if there'd been one on sale but there wasn't</u>
<u n="172" who="S0265">mm yes so have you tried those trousers on?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0264">in the shop</u>
<u n="174" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="175" who="S0264">they're not not a particularly good fit</u>
<u n="176" who="S0265">no</u>
<u n="177" who="S0264">they're a bit big actually oddly around the waist</u>
<u n="178" who="S0265">really?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0264">well they must make them bigger than they say</u>
<u n="180" who="S0265">well a thirty-two aren't they around the waist and it's</u>
<u n="181" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="182" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> maybe they shrink maybe they're <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc> <trunc>sor</trunc> the sort of cotton that shrinks</u>
<u n="183" who="S0264">yeah but then they won't be no it's more likely that they're like Marks and Spencer's they just make everything bigger than the than the size that they say they are <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I just wanted to go home early to carry on with this other work stuff anyway I just I want to get that's my task for tonight I want to get all of that done and dusted and then that's out of the way</u>
<u n="184" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0264">and so I'd er you know I I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I just thought it would be a quick trip on the way home but <pause dur="short"/> that's why when it when it mushrooms into something complicated</u>
<u n="186" who="S0265">I just put them by the door and then or keep them in the car and just remember to return them next time you go to</u>
<u n="187" who="S0264" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="188" who="S0265">Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="189" who="S0264">I think I would forget it if I put them in the car boot cos I don't open it <trunc>somet</trunc> well <pause dur="long"/> it's still full of junk from when the house was tidied</u>
<u n="190" who="S0265">oh right <pause dur="long"/> is that books?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0264">I don't know just general rubbish whatever <pause dur="short"/> couldn't go anywhere else <pause dur="long"/> have you been checking Zoopla?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0265">not not since I've got back</u>
<u n="193" who="S0264">well you ought to look and then you could see that house that I've that erm that I mentioned and see what</u>
<u n="194" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah I'll have a look for it yes</u>
<u n="195" who="S0264">I know where it is it's where it's that one where you road where you go under the railway bridge and you can't turn right <pause dur="short"/> and I think it's there of course they've photographed it so it looks as if it's semi secluded and in a quiet road</u>
<u n="196" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/> yes well well</u>
<u n="197" who="S0264">but you wouldn't do anyway it's too late now because it's been sold</u>
<u n="198" who="S0265">it's sold right that's</u>
<u n="199" who="S0264">and I'm not and like I said I'm not even sure that I want to go to the hassle of all and all the expense of moving some somewhere further into this place I'm not even sure I like particularly like and the only that's the and these seagulls have been driving me mad this year</u>
<u n="200" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> I've not noticed them since I've been back particularly</u>
<u n="201" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah they've quietened down a bit <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0265">yes I think <pause dur="short"/> I think really it's it's time something was done about them because they seem to be getting worse year after year and so it can't just keep going on can it?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0264">well it did it did in was it <anon type="place"/> where they tried to shoot them and then there was a big fuss about it?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0265">mm well perhaps there are <pause dur="short"/> other ways of controlling them like erm breaking their eggs</u>
<u n="205" who="S0264" trans="overlap">poison <pause dur="short"/> putting some foxes up on the roof</u>
<u n="206" who="S0265"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay you'll end up with foxes as well</u>
<u n="207" who="S0264">what's your evidence?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0265">I think well I just think I see I see them a lot</u>
<u n="209" who="S0264">where?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0265">here</u>
<u n="211" who="S0264" trans="overlap">when?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0265" trans="overlap">around and about I see them quite often well not not recently because I've not been walking at dusk but when it does get dark I've quite often see one walking across the the <anon type="place"/> road and there's some that live in that little island</u>
<u n="213" who="S0264">are there?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0265" trans="overlap">or well they go in there</u>
<u n="215" who="S0264">really?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0265">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I've seen them up erm up the driveway as well <pause dur="short"/> up the drive is it the drive?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="217" who="S0264">well that reminds me I've got this <unclear>aisles</unclear> thing to do and then oh yeah I've got to find another companion piece for that and then any day in fact I thought I might come home and find this this other thing waiting and then that'll be quite stressful and that's why I want to get this out of the way because if one of those comes through the letterbox then that'd be that's it that's another thing on top of work</u>
<u n="218" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0264">and it means you you know when it's a <trunc>n</trunc> a nice evening well you can't go out anyway unless you go for a run and then it's all over in thirty minutes or so</u>
<u n="220" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0264">erm <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said something erm nice today er she found erm apparently erm you know that did I told you about that erm <trunc>w</trunc>write up for erm <anon type="place"/> didn't I? that they used the paper in where was it? that didn't go this year <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0265">I don't know I can't remember you even <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="223" who="S0264" trans="overlap">they used it they used it as a an example of of er how to write up a report of your presentation</u>
<u n="224" who="S0265">right</u>
<u n="225" who="S0264">so <pause dur="short"/> they and and it's er and they put it online</u>
<u n="226" who="S0265">oh this is your example?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0265">oh that's good</u>
<u n="229" who="S0264">er but even better <pause dur="short"/> they've done all the all the work of putting in little boxes and things saying <pause dur="short"/> er this is <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc>this is this achieves the purpose of X or this is good because it's so they've labelled it all anyway and put little comments all around and it's on it's as a PDF I'll show you later</u>
<u n="230" who="S0265">oh right yes</u>
<u n="231" who="S0264">but I don't know where erm well presumably there's a link to it from the main site</u>
<u n="232" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0264">and that and that explains why I've been getting these emails from these people overseas cos I thought I I just assumed well I guessed it was to do with that write up because of the subject cos the topic <pause dur="short"/> erm and so I assumed that they'd been been present at the at the workshop</u>
<u n="234" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0264">but obviously <pause dur="short"/> well more probably they've they've just they weren't there at all but they they've found or seen it online</u>
<u n="236" who="S0265">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0264">so it just makes you realise it's important <pause dur="short"/> but that blog I don't think a single person's looked at it</u>
<u n="238" who="S0265">is that where that thing is?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0264" trans="overlap"><trunc>sc</trunc> <trunc>blo</trunc></u>
<u n="240" who="S0265">where it's is that where it is on a blog?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0264">no of course it's not I'm talking about my blog</u>
<u n="242" who="S0265">right oh your</u>
<u n="243" who="S0264" trans="overlap">nobody's</u>
<u n="244" who="S0265" trans="overlap">oh right and the other one you were writing a few weeks ago</u>
<u n="245" who="S0264">yes you've got to</u>
<u n="246" who="S0265" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0264" trans="overlap">do it every week really and you've got to like link it and have Twitter and all this stuff and oh I think it would drive me mad you'd <trunc>ha</trunc> you'd always having you'd always have to be <pause dur="short"/> engaging and</u>
<u n="248" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="249" who="S0264">messing around and you'd probably have car accidents and things</u>
<u n="250" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> I can imagine yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0264">and <pause dur="short"/> the other thing I can imagine is that you'd engineer situations to write about</u>
<u n="252" who="S0265">in order to keep the momentum</u>
<u n="253" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0265">going and?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0264" trans="overlap">that wouldn't be very ethical would it?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0265">no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0264">or erm at least erm you'd have to have your antennae out and be noticing <trunc>s</trunc> things all the time and perhaps you <vocal desc="laugh"/> if you had the mm luxury of reflection and time to reflect on stuff maybe you could think back over your day and you'd <trunc>th</trunc> and you'd pick out a few interesting things to write about but if normally you didn't <pause dur="short"/> have time and you just go from one thing to the other then</u>
<u n="258" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> well if there's if there's no activity on a on a blog people will quickly lose interest I mean I</u>
<u n="259" who="S0264" trans="overlap">but why would they they wouldn't why would they see it in the first place?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0265">erm I don't know the</u>
<u n="261" who="S0264" trans="overlap">you have to put a link</u>
<u n="262" who="S0265" trans="overlap">it yeah the they would be looking for something in particular they would be looking for something so they may do a hash search for something so</u>
<u n="263" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="264" who="S0265" trans="overlap">you need to make sure that when you create your <pause dur="short"/> blog on Twitter or whatever it is</u>
<u n="265" who="S0264">it</u>
<u n="266" who="S0265" trans="overlap">it needs to have hashtag doesn't it or something like that?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0264">I did put a hash thing I think but erm it's probably a meaningless one cos I didn't think about the consequences <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0265">cos I er I <pause dur="short"/> yes you do or because you have to <trunc>s</trunc> you use it as a search thing so your <trunc>hasht</trunc> your hash the</u>
<u n="269" who="S0264">but that's Twitter isn't it?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0265">that's Twitter yes I've only used Twitter</u>
<u n="271" who="S0264">yeah but do you think the same applies to blogs perhaps?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0265">I don't know</u>
<u n="273" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't understand it's all too it's all a bit I don't even <trunc>kn</trunc> I think Google have done it on purpose because <pause dur="short"/> I have never succeeded yet in erm signing out of that page</u>
<u n="274" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0264">I don't even know properly how to sign in I just have to mess around and suddenly it appears</u>
<u n="276" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0264">and then and then I have to crash out I just</u>
<u n="278" who="S0265">so where where is the site? is it erm is it an internal?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0264">it's no it's Blogger it's Google Google Blogger or whatever</u>
<u n="280" who="S0265">oh right well</u>
<u n="281" who="S0264">but I think they've made it like that on purpose so you can't escape so once you're in there you just stay there all day or</u>
<u n="282" who="S0265">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0264">or have it open on your screen somewhere all the time</u>
<u n="284" who="S0265">mm I don't know</u>
<u n="285" who="S0264" trans="overlap">you know cos <trunc>y</trunc>you that that Hotmail was doing that at one time if you remember the the thing to log out was suddenly disappeared or was made tiny and it was right up in the top it was where you don't didn't look well they made it almost invisible</u>
<u n="286" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0264">no I <trunc>th</trunc> I think it must ruin people's eyes cos they they make the screen so busy <trunc>wi</trunc>with different banners and colours and little bits and then they say oh you can always enlarge it and in fact of course there's a legislative requirement that you should be able to do things like enlarge and turn volume up because of disabilities</u>
<u n="288" who="S0265">yes of course</u>
<u n="289" who="S0264" trans="overlap">but you can't you still <trunc>co</trunc> it doesn't work because if you're trying to read script if you're trying to read text on er on the <trunc>p</trunc> on the screen</u>
<u n="290" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0264">if you enlarge it a great deal then you lose you've always gotta be moving the the page around</u>
<u n="292" who="S0265">yes you're gonna use more</u>
<u n="293" who="S0264" trans="overlap">from left to right</u>
<u n="294" who="S0265">it's more it's more awkward yes</u>
<u n="295" who="S0264" trans="overlap">in fact and and that isn't the way that your eye would work with hard copy because you might be jumping around with your eye I mean and then they'll stops you jumping around the screen</u>
<u n="296" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0264">I don't think and there was this er we we watched this erm <unclear/> dot com presentation today which turned out to be <trunc>m</trunc> far too long it erm I hadn't erm I hadn't noticed and it was all on and there was a this speaker had a photograph of er her daughter and her friend in the kitchen of course it was it was north America and erm they were perched on these stools it must have been north America and erm they were all erm hunched over their mobile phones and texting somebody else so their body language they they're all they all had their backs to each other and they just <trunc>m</trunc> might as well have been on Mars or somewhere</u>
<u n="298" who="S0265">yes <pause dur="short"/> someone was saying the other day that erm <pause dur="short"/> he said <trunc>wi</trunc><trunc>wi</trunc>with all the technology we've got you you can go you can go a day without talking to anyone</u>
<u n="299" who="S0264">yeah because you're busy texting</u>
<u n="300" who="S0265">you're busy texting and it's you don't need to go into a bank anymore and you've got the ATMs and you do your shopping erm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0264">yeah but when you do go into a bank you've gotta make sure that you erm adhere to the the the <trunc>cond</trunc> <trunc>con</trunc> scraping have you cut those plants?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0265">yes why?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0264">because I told you there's er something on the windowpane especially when it was windy over the weekend</u>
<u n="304" who="S0265">oh could you still hear something blowing?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0264">scraping across the glass</u>
<u n="306" who="S0265">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh maybe it's grown back again but I cut it I did cut it right back</u>
<u n="307" who="S0264" trans="overlap">well maybe it's not that window maybe I can hear maybe it's that one</u>
<u n="308" who="S0265">mm I'll have to have a look</u>
<u n="309" who="S0264">have you noticed next door hasn't put anything out in front of the window?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0265">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0264">they must have they must have did they put a concrete on where you know where we've got a flowerbed there?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0265">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0264">and they've got concrete</u>
<u n="314" who="S0265">yes it's always been like that I</u>
<u n="315" who="S0264" trans="overlap">what it ever <trunc>sin</trunc> well in before they got there?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0265">oh no not not before they got there I don't remember what was there before they got there but they er I think it's more than likely that they redid it or they</u>
<u n="317" who="S0264" trans="overlap">what when they had the drive done you think?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0265">no I think it was before then</u>
<u n="319" who="S0264">one of their little schemes</u>
<u n="320" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's <trunc>be</trunc></u>
<u n="321" who="S0264" trans="overlap"><trunc>anyw</trunc></u>
<u n="322" who="S0265" trans="overlap">it's been it's been luck like that for some time why what what's the point you're trying to make?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0264">that there's nothing there they're just being left</u>
<u n="324" who="S0265">oh yeah cos they took all their pots or most of them</u>
<u n="325" who="S0264">most you mean they left some?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0265">they left they've left some things haven't they?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0264">I don't know I haven't looked I haven't wanted to look</u>
<u n="328" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yes I mean next door she's not done anything has she yet?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0264">no well thank <trunc>good</trunc> it's good in a way <pause dur="short"/> but in another way it's a bad omen I think cos</u>
<u n="330" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it means that things are just going to slide and get worse</u>
<u n="332" who="S0265">well she's not cutting the grass cos there are a couple of fellas came round last Tuesday was it last Tuesday when I was working from home? erm a couple of <trunc>f</trunc> fellas and I think one of them is her father or uncle or something</u>
<u n="333" who="S0264">do you mean she's not even employing anybody <pause dur="short"/> to do it?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0265">no I think she <trunc>ye</trunc> I think her family's doing it for her</u>
<u n="335" who="S0264">why?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0265">well she's working all the time</u>
<u n="337" who="S0264">yeah but why but nag but er if she can afford why can't she afford to get one of the many many local landscape?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0265" trans="overlap">well presumably because her family have offered to do it for her for free</u>
<u n="339" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> it's a bit well a bit weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0265">not necessarily no <pause dur="short"/> that's what <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="341" who="S0264">I think it's weird because it looks the whole house and just one person</u>
<u n="342" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0264">but that on the other hand it just shows you how small these houses are <pause dur="short"/> they were never meant for children for a start</u>
<u n="344" who="S0265">no not for children no</u>
<u n="345" who="S0264">no because they're not they're not large enough and that's why <pause dur="short"/> erm very there have been very very few <pause dur="short"/> in this place</u>
<u n="346" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0264">in fact it was a bit it's maybe that's why they've gone from the erm corner</u>
<u n="348" who="S0265">mm probably <pause dur="short"/> but cos they're getting quite old probably those those children they're both teenagers now</u>
<u n="349" who="S0264">probably</u>
<u n="350" who="S0265">they did but they they created two rooms out of the <pause dur="short"/> out of your room they they created</u>
<u n="351" who="S0264" trans="overlap">did they? how do you know?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0265">because I think we went she showed us didn't she?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0264">no but no the bathroom are you not getting confused with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because that's what they did with their daughter's</u>
<u n="354" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah they I know they did but I've not seen theirs</u>
<u n="355" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="356" who="S0265">but it's we've we've seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="357" who="S0264">but I don't</u>
<u n="358" who="S0265" trans="overlap">it's it's when she took us round the house</u>
<u n="359" who="S0264">yes I but I that <trunc>c</trunc> I I don't I don't remember what they looked like er but I remember I think I remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="360" who="S0265">well I've never been inside <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s so</u>
<u n="361" who="S0264" trans="overlap">cos that was quite cleverly done well I I mm I don't think I'm confusing the two houses <pause dur="short"/> are you sure that you're not thinking about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s upstairs? cos they did it very neatly with making wardrobes from those erm places under the roof</u>
<u n="362" who="S0265">well maybe it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0264">she showed us</u>
<u n="364" who="S0265" trans="overlap">no I'm I'm I'm pretty sure it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0264">but I don't think she gave us a tour of the whole house she showed us the bathroom and the kitchen I think but <pause dur="short"/> that I don't</u>
<u n="366" who="S0265" trans="overlap">and and she she used used <trunc>s</trunc> she used that space under the</u>
<u n="367" who="S0264"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="368" who="S0265" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s as well</u>
<u n="369" who="S0264">for what?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0265">cupboards</u>
<u n="371" who="S0264">oh <pause dur="long"/> anyway it's a disaster because when <trunc>sl</trunc> eventually people are going to you know this er environmental categories what is it? D or E or F or something?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0265">mm don't know <pause dur="short"/> d or E I think</u>
<u n="373" who="S0264">so <pause dur="short"/> if you you know like <pause dur="short"/> if you had the choice if I had the choice I'd go for I'd go for a brand new <pause dur="short"/> in fact the the best thing would be to have one designed <pause dur="short"/> properly from scratch <pause dur="short"/> and built from nothing you just buy buy some</u>
<u n="374" who="S0265" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="375" who="S0264">land build it properly like the one that I saw in <anon type="place"/> near near <anon type="place"/> park they use wood nowadays you know cherry wood and things and they have the solar panelling and everything new and <pause dur="short"/> and clean and so on and erm none none of this horrible asbestos stuff and badly designed roofs and wasted space you <trunc>d</trunc> have it done properly from scratch I think that's the best thing and then okay so that would be an A presumably</u>
<u n="376" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0264">and then why would you expect anybody to buy this place <pause dur="short"/> when it's a D or E or something?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0265">mm if they're environmentally conscious <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>cons</trunc>conscientious then yes I quite agree</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
