<text id="S7RM">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:15:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Birthdays, plants, baby names, computers</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking while making tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1" who="S0115">so the the pie had um quite a lot of spices in it</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">uh flavours like the uh garlic the carrot onion like the flavours had some extract in them</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037" trans="overlap">tasted quite peppery</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115">yeah they it had like black pepper extract <pause dur="short"/> they also had thyme and clove <pause dur="short"/> um and like the concentrated you know vegetables um</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">and yeast extract went in there <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit like Marmite innit?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and with tomato paste so they did <trunc>th</trunc> this is typical I think that you do with it being these sorts of things they do have a lot of different flavours uh at the same time</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm just getting me scissors</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> I mean more than you'd you'd always think of putting in <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">have you had any thoughts about what we should buy your mam for her birthday?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">D'you think she's like some jewellery or something or?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <trunc>s</trunc> I wasn't hold on I was  I was  gonna ask her wasn't I and then um I imagine it would probably have something to do with the garden or a plant or some sort um</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or you not planning on spending? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> although we've got her those the <trunc>plas</trunc> past two times I mean I do like a bit of plant action but I just wonder if she might want something more</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> more?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">should <trunc>cup</trunc> her cook her a cake or something if she's coming round</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037">with seventy candles</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115">um yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037">well I can just get one of those number sevens cos I've got a number zero from when you were thirty</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037">you know? That's in there somewhere I'm sure I saw it the other day</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">it sounds sounds like a great idea</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">ah she'd like that wouldn't she? She like a bit fuss <pause dur="short"/> everyone likes a bit fuss <pause dur="short"/> well I like a bit fuss</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115" trans="overlap">something um</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">doesn't <trunc>don</trunc> does she?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">I think so I mean</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or would she be embarrassed?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> maybe a bit but you know you you always get</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what's that for?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">I was gonna grill this</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037">ah put it in the grill pan <pause dur="short"/> in the <trunc>mist</trunc> this one</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh the the the um <pause dur="short"/> um alright yeah yeah cool</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="36" who="S0115">uh yeah so I dunno if um what she'd want but I thought it would be <pause dur="short"/> uh she doesn't normally ask for much does she?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">she normally asks for some socks from Marks and Spencer's</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah she does</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">I feel like we should probably buy something slightly better if it's like her seventieth <pause dur="short"/> and people ask her Ooh what did you get from your son? and if she's like Um some socks <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">well I think that</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">I know she's a woman of simple means</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">in the um in traditionally um I've asked her and she's not asked for like spectacular things so um that's why you know</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037">well that's why I was thinking maybe don't ask her and just buy her</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you know she's she wouldn't be expecting</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">but then again she might not like it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um yeah I wouldn't uh I would definitely wanna ask her first uh to make sure cos otherwise it you know could get could make her really <pause dur="short"/> well if you were doing it as a surprise well what would you you know what would you get?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">well she's funny cos she doesn't really like the sort of things that I would like</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's like uh one of the main reasons why</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">why what?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">just have to sort of</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037">ask her?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">wouldn't wanna surprise her cos we don't really like the same things she does</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> or similar things that I would buy for like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or me mam I would kind of know what I would buy them</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">I wouldn't really know what to buy</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">your mam <pause dur="short"/> I quite like any sort of smellies and</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">stuff like stuff from from Boot's</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037" trans="overlap">vanity items <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0115" trans="overlap">A lot of stuff from <trunc>B</trunc> yeah you're you're quite a vain person aren't you?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">well I'm not really but I do like cosmetics quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> I don't say I'm I wouldn't say I'm vain</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no neither would I</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">you're mean</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">no I was saying it's just a joke I mean</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">I like  I like  quite like nice bath things and like um hair products and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I like that sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>co</trunc> and cosmetics</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah sort of like Boot's things yeah like similar to what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">uh and probably <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and I also like sweets and I also like booze</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115">yes</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so I think a bottle of wine box of sweets that you can't go far wrong with that for me <pause dur="short"/> uh flowers are always nice you should get your mam some flowers cos she'd really appreciate that</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115">yeast extract</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037">lovely <pause dur="short"/> d'you not think?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">eh?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">she would really appreciate some flowers?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">uh yeah I think she likes flowers yeah um and plant she like likes a lot of plants</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> could <pause dur="short"/> we could go <pause dur="short"/> but where we could get her something that would last like why don't we buy? Has she got  has she got  herbs and stuff? I mean I know we gave her some cuttings but did they all survive?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115" trans="overlap">A tree or something like that <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037">Cos we could buy her like um a sage bush or a <pause dur="short"/> what about like you know have you seen those little bay trees? Does she cook like that though? Would she use it?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">yeah probably a bay tree yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037">they're about twenty quid aren't they?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037">that's a great present I'd like one of them</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">maybe they've if they've got them on two for one I'd be over the moon</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">wonder if they have</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">quote of the day</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">eh?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">quote of the day</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">if they've got them on two for one I'll be over the moon? No it's true I would be</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">in fact I'm tempted to just look on Homebase Dot Com and see if they have <pause dur="short"/> that would be really good</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">oh yeah so these these things take ages to uh</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">that's why I was thinking we should put them in <pause dur="short"/> I was telling some people at work about my knitted hanging bag things and they said they thought it was a nice idea <pause dur="short"/> not you're mental was what which is what you said</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">sorry did I say? When did I? I didn't say that</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037">that was a paraphrase but yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">what when was this the oh the the plant thing?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">I saw them this morning and they <trunc>m</trunc> like they made us smile so I think that they should definitely stay <pause dur="short"/> just for the craziness of them</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">oh yeah no I <trunc>l</trunc> I mean I never  I never  said that they didn't look good uh <pause dur="short"/> I was just thinking that it was more than what was necessary</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">yeah but I'm <trunc>tr</trunc> it's just like free time isn't it?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">I it's not like I've got loads of stuff to do <pause dur="short"/> and I'm instead I'm knitting crazy things</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">I have got a lot of time on me hands now <pause dur="short"/> don't think I've ever really adjusted since finishing the thing</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">well it is big big thing to do isn't it?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">and when I was working as well like</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh to do that to do them two things at the same time</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">um a lot of work <pause dur="short"/> you already had quite a lot of it done uh before in terms of uh the data and everything</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true <pause dur="short"/> d'you think we should put the what's in that pan in that  in that  bigger <trunc>pa</trunc> like that pan with the lid?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what's gonna happen</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">alright <pause dur="short"/> you've got it under control</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">it's uh that'll go over there and then <pause dur="short"/> these um <pause dur="short"/> go on <unclear/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">or you could get the griddle pan out and do the fish on that <pause dur="short"/> cos you'll need to boil some pasta won't you?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115">that will that'll be free after</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037">yeah but what you gonna boil the pasta in if that's in there?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean there's there's the big one but uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah let's just <pause dur="short"/> I can use the griddle one yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> is there a space?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">need a bigger kitchen <pause dur="short"/> it gets frustrating for me</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">yeah it is a bit on the small side</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">need a bigger kitchen and a bigger garden <pause dur="short"/> the rest of the stuff I don't care about <pause dur="short"/> I don't <pause dur="short"/> oh a bath would be nice but I don't really mind the shower is fine</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="122" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037">D'you think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> though? D'you think that sounds weird?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="125" who="S0115"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">no not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> georgie <pause dur="short"/> girl</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">but the kid's gonna be weird if it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s baby anyway like</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> suppose there's a <trunc>ch</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I I have no <trunc>i</trunc> there's no way of um can't easily imagine what um</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I'm only joking</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">I think it's often different from what you expect</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">um but my cousin <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't think his kids are that much like him and I  and I  don't think</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">but you haven't seen them for years though</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">and I don't like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but but with um with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't think  I don't think  his kids are that like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> either</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> ahh sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">I'm getting in the way</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">I'll move this out the way <pause dur="short"/> did we get any post?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">um no we didn't</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">not even any flyers</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">no nothing</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">we didn't even get any flyers <pause dur="short"/> aw devastated</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">disappointed</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="145" who="S0115">I'm gonna look and see if they have got any <trunc>e</trunc> offers on on  If they have I'll be round there like a shot tomorrow</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="147" who="S0115">have the read the uh read any <trunc>n</trunc> news today then?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">I didn't actually I was quite busy <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">what did I read?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">no <trunc>n</trunc> not really</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">uh I'll just uh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah was a there was a bit about <trunc>a</trunc> <trunc>the</trunc> Aung San Suu Kyi <pause dur="short"/> suu Kyi</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">yeah?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">that she'd like supposedly won the election</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">she has?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">I uh think so <pause dur="short"/> then um <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah then there was that resigning uh thesis stealing guy <pause dur="short"/> and then um <pause dur="short"/> there wasn't loads of big stuff but um</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">oh your Dad's liked my my status on Facebook</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">what is that?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">I love Brno that one</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">weird</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's a weird guy</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">well he's alright <pause dur="short"/> I dunno if he understands Facebook sometimes like he does weird things <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0115">that applies to many things that he does</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> we're all a bit weird underneath though aren't we? Some people hide it better than others</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">guess so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">so did you say you were using Opera on on <trunc>y</trunc> as your browser your main browser now?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">I was trying to um <pause dur="short"/> if that  if that  doesn't work I'd use Chrome</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is it like is it any good? Do you not use? Why don't you use um <trunc>Fire</trunc> um</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but Opera's okay though it does  it does  suffer from some of the same problems</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">why don't you use Fast Stone?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">that's not great for um</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">oh look it's your thing from yesterday</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">I've had that on quite high actually <pause dur="short"/> so uh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">it's alright</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">might be smelling smoke in a minute</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">it's alright just let it out a bit at a time</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115"><unclear/> over yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> I might have some um <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten what I was gonna say there <pause dur="short"/> yeah no I had um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah Google uh Chrome I could try uh just <pause dur="short"/> but I think I I need to get a new laptop anyway</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos it's uh</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">be nice to have a new one</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">not as fast as it should be</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037"><trunc>W</trunc> you've had it a long time <pause dur="short"/> mine didn't even last half the time yours lasted <pause dur="short"/> it's exploded</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">that was a shock you know that was like I was kinda sad that the laptop died</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I was kinda sad given the timing</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">well you know <pause dur="short"/> thought that that that was the better of the two <pause dur="short"/> so I expected it to last longer</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">maybe it can be repaired</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="189" who="S0037">ooh half price fourteen ninety-nine bay tree <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> better uh snap it up then</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037">and you can get a planter for twenty pounds <pause dur="short"/> or a big one <pause dur="short"/> think we should get one?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115">it's worth  it's worth  um considering</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do they deliver? No they don't deliver <pause dur="short"/> how am I gonna get a bay tree back from the shops? I'll look like a right idiot like with a massive tree in the bag <vocal desc="laugh"/> on the front of my basket</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">I dunno I mean depends how how big the one that you're getting is I mean</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037">forty-one centimetres <pause dur="short"/> that's not too bad is it?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115">Don't think so</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037">half price <pause dur="short"/> ah should I go tomorrow?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115">uh yeah if you want</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">Will she like that or will am I just buying it for meself?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115">well just wait wait and uh you know hang fire</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037">could just buy it and then give it to her if I have to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0115">um wait wait and see like what she wants and then <pause dur="short"/> cos she might want something totally different</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like what? We should take a punt</u>
<u n="204" who="S0115">no no she might want something <trunc>mor</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> no no we shouldn't take a punt cos I don't think she's a punter</u>
<u n="205" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I mean like on <trunc>gue</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> noo I mean on guessing what she'll like</u>
<u n="206" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="207" who="S0037">D'you wanna draft an email to her? Like d'you wanna invite her? Have you done that yet?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0115">no I haven't written that yet but um</u>
<u n="209" who="S0037">I can help you if you want</u>
<u n="210" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I'd like to</u>
<u n="211" who="S0037">okay <pause dur="short"/> shall I  shall I  draft something?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0115">yeah um on the  on the  smartphone? Yeah that'll be uh that'll be good <pause dur="short"/> thanks</u>
<u n="213" who="S0037">alright <pause dur="short"/> hi Mum and Dad <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> what d'you wanna say next?</u>
<event desc="sound of something landing in the frying pan"/>
<u n="214" who="S0037">whoaahh</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">have you put salt and pepper on the skin?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">oh you don't have to <pause dur="short"/> they'll be fine without it <pause dur="short"/> put it on its insides</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh that'll be <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'll put that on the other side</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah don't worry about it it'll be fine <pause dur="short"/> it's lovely anyway <pause dur="short"/> we won't need very much cos it's quite a salty fish like</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">was it been salted what is it was it cured?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">no but I mean it's quite like oily and sort of</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's a rich fish isn't it?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">aww <pause dur="short"/> no leave it up quite high it'll be nice</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">yeah I'll <trunc>g</trunc> I did yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">um d'you wanna?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115" trans="overlap">hey your your um your parser assumes does a lot of assuming about the intentions of the person</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">here</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">um d'you wanna boil some pasta?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">yeah just uh I'll put this over here</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">D'you need the big pan then?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">how you gonna boil the <trunc>pa</trunc>? Ah you're gonna put that in there?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I'll have that in there</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">oh okay</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">just uh leave it to me</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if you boil the kettle and then you'll it'll it'll take less time for the water to heat <pause dur="short"/> sometimes do that</u>
</body>
</text>
