<text id="S7RW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:31:27</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0540 S0541</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Marin’s flat, London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Studies, hair, staying in Marin’s flat, Airbnb, mutual friends, utilities, internet, tea, Japanese wedding attire, family wedding, honeymoon, Hawaii, holiday activities, hairstyles, family memories, food, Indian restaurants, guests, staying out of London with friends, neighbour noise, pets, spiders, Bishop’s Stortford, moving out of London, job-seeking, renewing visas, health, friends, stress, finances, work methods, winter, family, cultural differences, charity work, managing difficulty, religion, research groups, exhibition, social media</topics>
		<activity>Friends’ pre-holiday catch-up</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, inviting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements, apologising, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0540">
				<exactage>38</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Japanese</nat>
				<birthplace>Fukuri</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Japan</birthcountry>
				<l1>Japanese</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>more than 10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0541">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bradford, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Writer</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; Italian -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0540">you know two more deadlines I <trunc>sudden</trunc> handed in my thesis erm the end of <pause dur="short"/> well you er I handed in the first no second of November I had to work through that weekend the the last weekend of October hand it on the second although <trunc>m</trunc> I it was due on the thirty-first but thirty-first was Saturday so I submitted it on the Monday which was the second <pause dur="short"/> and then after that I had to finish this paper for the scientific journal article journal article that was also about three four thousand words that we had been working on as a team but I had been hoarding it because I my priority was the thesis so after that I er went back to this manuscript and then finished it off done a few edits over a few days and then after that I had then had to deal with this another paper <pause dur="short"/> another journal</u>
<u n="2" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="3" who="S0540">which was really important because I'm the I I'm this is where I am <unclear/> author and it's a <trunc>d</trunc>design journal <vocal desc="sigh"/> and it's almost you know <pause dur="short"/> certain to be published because I <trunc>m</trunc> I was invited by the editor of the journal</u>
<u n="4" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="5" who="S0540">so it's you know it's one of those peer reviewed articles erm in academic system so but it's very good to have these papers published as a researcher</u>
<u n="6" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0540">especially you know based on <trunc>res</trunc> PhD research it's quite good <pause dur="short"/> so I was you know because I wanted to apply for a research fellowship after this or you know any any other the publication you know would be you know plus <pause dur="short"/> ah and I finished that paper yesterday <pause dur="short"/> it took me like three three more weeks</u>
<u n="8" who="S0541">wow</u>
<u n="9" who="S0540">and I realise now tomorrow is my flight day now</u>
<u n="10" who="S0541">you're flying tomorrow?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0540">I'm flying on Wednesday</u>
<u n="12" who="S0541">Wednesday</u>
<u n="13" who="S0540">that's it and then I have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thing at the <anon type="place"/> just for one-day event but they're putting up my installation there in the science museum</u>
<u n="14" who="S0541">oh nice</u>
<u n="15" who="S0540">I know so that's</u>
<u n="16" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I might go and see it</u>
<u n="17" who="S0540">yeah so that's the</u>
<u n="18" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0540" trans="overlap">fifteenth of <trunc>Augu</trunc> or December</u>
<u n="20" who="S0541">cor yeah I'll have to go and see it how amazing</u>
<u n="21" who="S0540" trans="overlap">but er it's a one-day event</u>
<u n="22" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="23" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0541">oh wow how exciting</u>
<u n="25" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I know so that's that so that's you know I've evolved now it's it it needs a bit of preparation and then I you know again I need to set up my work which means you know <unclear>claiming the best walls</unclear> that arrived from the <anon type="place"/> science centre in <anon type="place"/> so it the whole thing takes about a week or two</u>
<u n="26" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="27" who="S0540">you know just and then I have to start looking <pause dur="short"/> not start looking actually I have to actually <trunc>com</trunc> you know I sort of er <trunc>assemb</trunc> compose <vocal desc="sigh"/> a short summary of my work and send it to the <anon type="place"/> centre which is like half a year late to respond terrible but I've got to now</u>
<u n="28" who="S0541">busy</u>
<u n="29" who="S0540">yeah this is endless endless and I have a <anon type="place"/> next er January the fourteenth</u>
<u n="30" who="S0541">do you have to prepare for it?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0540">I do I really do yeah otherwise I will forget <pause dur="short"/> but it's okay I have Christmas</u>
<u n="32" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0540">I will be here</u>
<u n="34" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0540"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0541">you look a little bit kind of exhausted</u>
<u n="37" who="S0540">I'm a little bit exhausted because <pause dur="long"/> yeah I just want to have a week or two off</u>
<u n="38" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0540" trans="overlap">but then you know going home isn't that easy er either</u>
<u n="40" who="S0541">it's quite a long flight as well isn't it?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0540" trans="overlap">long flight you know long journey and then again quite hectic because of the wedding wedding is quite hectic it's a formal thing and we'll be all staying in a hotel in Kyoto we live in we don't live there so again and a <trunc>lit</trunc> a little bit of travelling and then you know you you know and I see my relatives there as well</u>
<u n="42" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0540">so that's another pressure to tell what I have been doing all all over the last five six years</u>
<u n="44" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0540">you know</u>
<u n="46" who="S0541">that'll be nice though it'll be beautiful</u>
<u n="47" who="S0540">it will be beautiful</u>
<u n="48" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you'll have a good time</u>
<u n="49" who="S0540" trans="overlap">and my brother came last no no yeah stayed here a couple of days</u>
<u n="50" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0540" trans="overlap">this weekend so suddenly I had to cook I tried lasagne which failed</u>
<u n="52" who="S0541">oh no</u>
<u n="53" who="S0540">I know the pasta stuck</u>
<u n="54" who="S0541">to the bottom?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0540">yeah no there was I boiled the pasta er the sheets but they all stuck together this is the second <unclear>anyway I have been</unclear></u>
<u n="56" who="S0541">you know how you can avoid that? you just put like a drop of oil in the thing</u>
<u n="57" who="S0540">yeah I did that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0541">did you?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0540">yeah I I succeeded once <unclear/> er but erm that was just my you know <unclear/> trial er and then I anyway I'm just testing you know there with the lasagne recipe <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> anyway oh</u>
<u n="60" who="S0541">oh here's my hat oh wow</u>
<u n="61" who="S0540">I know I and I went to see and then so last night anyway I had a free time like I normally do er but I was er exhausted like I always am you know went to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0540" trans="overlap">and erm again you know exhausted cos we prayed <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was good oh she told me the psalm ninety-one which is a really lovely psalm lovely and the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there and er she had a friend from church</u>
<u n="64" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="65" who="S0540" trans="overlap">a Spanish lady with two kids so there were like about <trunc>f</trunc><trunc>f</trunc><trunc>f</trunc>four kids running around</u>
<u n="66" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0540">it's quite nice you know quite nice</u>
<u n="68" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0540" trans="overlap">to have that sort of noise erm anyway and then I didn't see your text till I got home</u>
<u n="70" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="71" who="S0540">oh but I was hoping maybe you are around and and I would you know you come <unclear>over</unclear> and I go over yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah I I didn't erm I got back about in the afternoon and er <vocal desc="yawn"/> and then I was just tidying up and er left my phone in my handbag really and then I kind of</u>
<u n="73" who="S0540">oh did you?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0541" trans="overlap">fished it out and I was like oh</u>
<u n="75" who="S0540">oh that's</u>
<u n="76" who="S0541" trans="overlap">but I was really tired anyway yesterday</u>
<u n="77" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0541">I was a bit kind of washed out so</u>
<u n="79" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah I understand</u>
<u n="80" who="S0541">so I had a nice little watched a movie and</u>
<u n="81" who="S0540">what did you watch?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0541">I just watched anything on Netflix I watched Donnie Brasco which is quite good timing</u>
<u n="83" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0541">because Johnny Depp is in that film which I wish I'd seen the other day</u>
<u n="85" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0541">and I didn't I saw something crap so I got The Lady in the Van which is really dreadful</u>
<u n="87" who="S0540">oh did you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0541">oh god it was so bad</u>
<u n="89" who="S0540">it's got er not bad review though</u>
<u n="90" who="S0541">oh god it's so boring <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="91" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>j</trunc> really <trunc>dra</trunc> I'm not really I I'm not that keen on Alan Bennett actually which is</u>
<u n="93" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0541">you know and it's all about Alan Bennett obviously cos it's his story anyway blah blah blah so I watched er</u>
<u n="95" who="S0540" trans="overlap">what about?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0541" trans="overlap">Donnie Brasco which was really entertaining with Robert</u>
<u n="97" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0541">De Niro and Johnny Depp a young Johnny Depp which apparently was his best role ever</u>
<u n="99" who="S0540">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0541">so it was good I just watch it on Netflix</u>
<u n="101" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="102" who="S0541">I keep <trunc>fi</trunc> I keep finding things to watch on there</u>
<u n="103" who="S0540">I really want to watch erm you know the new film</u>
<u n="104" who="S0541">which one?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0540">featuring your favourite actor</u>
<u n="106" who="S0541">Macbeth?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0540">no like</u>
<u n="108" who="S0541" trans="overlap">Fassbender?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0541">in Macbeth?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0540">no this Apple</u>
<u n="112" who="S0541">oh I know I wish I'd seen that actually I didn't I it was either that or The Lady in the Van and I I felt like something kind of lightweight even though I did feel like a bit of Michael Fassbender but anyway</u>
<u n="113" who="S0540">yeah no then I just realised oh he's er oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s favourite actor</u>
<u n="114" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah he was in the Men in Black on telly the other night so I I</u>
<u n="115" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0541">I watched a little bit of him there</u>
<u n="117" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0541">I can dream</u>
<u n="119" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right I need a new hairdo I mean this is awful this is like I mean it from world war two I mean it's it's</u>
<u n="120" who="S0541"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0540"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I need I need</u>
<u n="122" who="S0541">come back with a Mohican have it done for the wedding that would be quite funny</u>
<u n="123" who="S0540">I have actually I might I <trunc>ha</trunc> <unclear/> I have a Mohican like hairstyle</u>
<u n="124" who="S0541">I know you told me that's why I said it</u>
<u n="125" who="S0540">with erm shiny blue Diesel trousers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0541">the foils of youth</u>
<u n="127" who="S0540">yeah god that's before my you know psychedelic flower power costume in my first year at university <vocal desc="laugh"/> matched with Adidas <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was before wow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean you know now I'm just really subdued very urban boring <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0541">mm me too</u>
<u n="131" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I'm really tired but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc>you will be staying here?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0541">I don't know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0540">oh you don't know okay</u>
<u n="134" who="S0541">if I get a booking</u>
<u n="135" who="S0540">oh oh okay oh</u>
<u n="136" who="S0541">why?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0540">well I had an email from er it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="139" who="S0540">er and er <trunc>sh</trunc>she's been contacted by someone</u>
<u n="140" who="S0541">who needs somewhere to stay?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0540">yeah but doing er the <trunc>th</trunc>the thirtieth of November to the fourth</u>
<u n="142" who="S0541">okay <pause dur="short"/> well we'll go for it</u>
<u n="143" who="S0540">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0541">well I don't yeah cos erm it's all a bit last minute with Airbnb I've had two bookings</u>
<u n="145" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0541">and it's always a bit kind of like erm no I did have some notice on the last one actually but the first one I hadn't like hardly any notice two days one day so it's kind of hard to know</u>
<u n="147" who="S0540">oh I see but anyway I mean it otherwise you know I mean it's all you know it's free anyway so you know but you know I wanted to show you how to use this</u>
<u n="148" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="149" who="S0540" trans="overlap">place</u>
<u n="150" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and I'd like to see</u>
<u n="151" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah because just in case you know if you</u>
<u n="152" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0540" trans="overlap">do you know</u>
<u n="154" who="S0541">cos it is on I mean it is on there</u>
<u n="155" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and it is active</u>
<u n="157" who="S0540">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0541">so I might I mean and it</u>
<u n="159" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="160" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it tends to be weekends actually that people book for</u>
<u n="161" who="S0540">oh I see</u>
<u n="162" who="S0541">so erm but if this person is in dire need of somewhere to stay then I I I feel bad really I</u>
<u n="163" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no no you don't have to feel bad because you know she can stay at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s place</u>
<u n="164" who="S0541">oh that's fine then</u>
<u n="165" who="S0540">you know</u>
<u n="166" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0540" trans="overlap">upstairs because erm and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s now gone to <unclear>Iceland</unclear> from today so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="169" who="S0540">maybe it suits her yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0541" trans="overlap">okay yeah you'll have to show me how to do things</u>
<u n="171" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I thought</u>
<u n="172" who="S0541">because I may well I mean I've had two</u>
<u n="173" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0541">so far erm and yeah so I've kind of been up to <anon type="place"/> and I got <unclear/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="176" who="S0541">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0540" trans="overlap">sorry I'll just make sure that that tea tea is on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0541">so is there anything what do I need to know then? is the heating's just on <trunc>d</trunc> is that on a timer? or is it a?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0540">well the timer is a bit er erm messed up</u>
<u n="180" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0540">because I haven't been able to erm <pause dur="short"/> reconfigure</u>
<u n="182" who="S0541">what is there to know?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0540">so usually</u>
<u n="184" who="S0541" trans="overlap">what have I got to know?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I just do it manually</u>
<u n="186" who="S0541">oh you do it you so you just</u>
<u n="187" who="S0540" trans="overlap">so now</u>
<u n="188" who="S0541" trans="overlap">switch it on when you want it?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0540">now the heating is on</u>
<u n="190" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0540" trans="overlap">because I just did that the now it's set to</u>
<u n="192" who="S0541">what does that say?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0540" trans="overlap">twenty-one</u>
<u n="194" who="S0541" trans="overlap">set?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0540">yeah set twenty-one degree</u>
<u n="196" who="S0541">oh okay</u>
<u n="197" who="S0540" trans="overlap">so the the heating will be on until it reaches the twenty-one degree</u>
<u n="198" who="S0541">yeah okay</u>
<u n="199" who="S0540">but usually</u>
<u n="200" who="S0541">I mean how do I switch it off then? where do I switch it off?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0540">I just switch the main thing the main switch which is here <pause dur="long"/> yeah and there is a <unclear>spider</unclear> I have to get rid of</u>
<u n="202" who="S0541">where's the switch?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0540">and the switch is here</u>
<u n="204" who="S0541">I see just this one? and that's just on and off?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0541">right got you got you got you okay okay</u>
<u n="207" who="S0540">yes</u>
<u n="208" who="S0541">so I meant to bring the keys but I forgot</u>
<u n="209" who="S0540">oh don't worry you can keep the keys of course</u>
<u n="210" who="S0541">so what is there this <trunc>le</trunc> thing I mean it's just the heating right?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh god and then the lights the lights I don't have a ceiling light at the moment</u>
<u n="212" who="S0541" trans="overlap">no right</u>
<u n="213" who="S0540" trans="overlap">you know so all the lights you know</u>
<u n="214" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0540">and er</u>
<u n="216" who="S0541" trans="overlap">just your wi-fi password</u>
<u n="217" who="S0540">oh and then er I've got the form the you know BT <pause dur="short"/> bT erm hotspot</u>
<u n="218" who="S0541">can I use that or is it?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0540" trans="overlap">you can use it but it expires er er no but then I have to renew it so yeah but it expires as I leave</u>
<u n="220" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="223" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0541" trans="overlap">okay okay okay</u>
<u n="225" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah I know yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0541" trans="overlap">okay so there won't be</u>
<u n="227" who="S0540">no I I think I I going <trunc>t</trunc> I I just need to renew it</u>
<u n="228" who="S0541">oh well don't renew it for me <trunc>d</trunc> you're got to wait until you get back and have two weeks off</u>
<u n="229" who="S0540">no it's only ten days</u>
<u n="230" who="S0541">oh is it ten days?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0540">yeah it's only ten days it doesn't make much difference</u>
<u n="232" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="233" who="S0540">it</u>
<u n="234" who="S0541">well up to you I can live without it</u>
<u n="235" who="S0540">no</u>
<u n="236" who="S0541" trans="overlap">she said <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no no no no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm telling you you won't</u>
<u n="238" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> terrified</u>
<u n="239" who="S0540">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos I don't have a TV <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0541">even though I've got it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no no you won't be able to survive here I'll leave er the Bible for for you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0540" trans="overlap">but even still you know you might want to online to <vocal desc="laugh"/> to read the Bible these days er</u>
<u n="244" who="S0541">I have my phone but</u>
<u n="245" who="S0540">oh the reception's not very good here</u>
<u n="246" who="S0541">is it not?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0540">I never really had a reliable sort of a streaming</u>
<u n="248" who="S0541" trans="overlap">really? how strange</u>
<u n="249" who="S0540">I mean of course it's good enough for checking sort of the news on BBC app</u>
<u n="250" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0540" trans="overlap">but er nothing more</u>
<u n="252" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="253" who="S0540">what do you think of this tea?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0541">I quite like it <pause dur="short"/> kind of berry thing</u>
<u n="255" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0541">is it what is it? oh</u>
<u n="257" who="S0540">it's mulled fruit</u>
<u n="258" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mulled <trunc>fr</trunc>fruit</u>
<u n="259" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm from M and S</u>
<u n="260" who="S0541">it's kind of wintery isn't it?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's good for December</u>
<u n="263" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0541">so have you got your kimono and everything did you sort it all out?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0540">yeah it's sorted out I'm going to have to wear the er my mother's kimono</u>
<u n="266" who="S0541">okay that's cool</u>
<u n="267" who="S0540">yeah yeah yeah yeah that pink one and then borrow the accessories rent rent rent accessories</u>
<u n="268" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="269" who="S0540">shoes and bag and everything</u>
<u n="270" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="271" who="S0540">and then <trunc>h</trunc></u>
<u n="272" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you can rent the shoes and everything?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0541">wow</u>
<u n="275" who="S0540">but we might buy a pair of shoes for me actually it's not that expensive erm but I you know otherwise I can rent from the company who are going to dress us all up</u>
<u n="276" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm what kind of shoes then go with it?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0540">erm it's kind of flip flops</u>
<u n="278" who="S0541">oh okay</u>
<u n="279" who="S0540" trans="overlap">but much cos they're heeled</u>
<u n="280" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="281" who="S0540" trans="overlap">er flip flops I might be able to bring back a pair or so</u>
<u n="282" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="283" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I don't know but you might like it</u>
<u n="284" who="S0541">that would be quite elaborate or</u>
<u n="285" who="S0540">quite elaborate yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0540">elaborate flip flop with heels</u>
<u n="288" who="S0541">how do are they hard to walk in?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="291" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0541">I mean you won't be walking very far right?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0540">mm I have no idea probably not probably taxi</u>
<u n="294" who="S0541">mm mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0540" trans="overlap">just you know between rooms and entrances</u>
<u n="296" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I look forward to seeing your photos amazing</u>
<u n="299" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah that's why I haven't had my hair cut because you know I wanted to because I was thinking of having a little bit of you know er layers</u>
<u n="300" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="301" who="S0540">and have slightly more modernised hair kind of cut recently and then I thought oh my god</u>
<u n="302" who="S0541">not for the wedding</u>
<u n="303" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><unclear>that's too modern</unclear></u>
<u n="304" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0540">you know <pause dur="short"/> after that probably I should have my hair cut there in Japan cos you get better</u>
<u n="306" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0540">stylist</u>
<u n="308" who="S0541">well yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0541">and it's something fun to do while you're there so when is the wedding?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0540">twenty-ninth</u>
<u n="312" who="S0541">and when do you get there? oh really? so that's next week?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0541">oh wow oh that's good because then after you can just relax and hang out</u>
<u n="315" who="S0540">I can then relax and hang out but not so long and then catch a flight on the seventh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="317" who="S0540">yeah it's not like London I have to travel quite a bit to get to the airport</u>
<u n="318" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0540">cos we only have well in my area there is only <pause dur="short"/> well it takes about three or four hours to get to the airport</u>
<u n="320" who="S0541">really?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0540">that's why well maybe four is a bit exaggerating like three</u>
<u n="322" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0540">door to door</u>
<u n="324" who="S0541">uhu</u>
<u n="325" who="S0540">it's quite exhausting <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc>maybe no maybe two and a half hours</u>
<u n="326" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="327" who="S0540">yeah but anyway I never really like travelling <pause dur="short"/> to the airport</u>
<u n="328" who="S0541">it's better travelling there than travelling back <pause dur="short"/> you just wanna get home</u>
<u n="329" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you've had your fun thinking oh oh I wanna go home</u>
<u n="331" who="S0540">also I'm quite tired these days you know I just want to rest and</u>
<u n="332" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0540" trans="overlap">have you know like you know the spa</u>
<u n="334" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was dreaming of the spa session</u>
<u n="336" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="337" who="S0540">but now oh I'm I think I'm gonna have to do it some at some point somewhere</u>
<u n="338" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0540">maybe in Japan I have to go to <unclear/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah do it do it do it</u>
<u n="341" who="S0540"><vocal desc="sigh"/> but I just you know <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't have a car and my friend's not there and my mother doesn't drive and my father works in Ireland you know I'm very immobile when I go home that's why I don't I'm not really looking forward <pause dur="short"/> although my brother's gonna be around although they're going to get married but he's going to stay at home for one month to write a book</u>
<u n="342" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="343" who="S0540">because now he's got a book deal</u>
<u n="344" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="345" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="346" who="S0541">a medical book?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0540">er but for the general public</u>
<u n="348" who="S0541">oh okay</u>
<u n="349" who="S0540">it's quite good yeah it's a quite a famous author mm but he's going to be the one writing it <pause dur="short"/> so that's kind of the deal is now erm <pause dur="short"/> concrete</u>
<u n="350" who="S0541">oh that's good</u>
<u n="351" who="S0540">mm so he said he had to actually concentrate on writing and</u>
<u n="352" who="S0541">so not going on honeymoon?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0540">not yet after to Hawaii</u>
<u n="354" who="S0541">mm gorgeous</u>
<u n="355" who="S0540">Hawaii <pause dur="short"/> it's a quite you know popular place to go <pause dur="short"/> for Japanese people</u>
<u n="356" who="S0541">it is Japanese and Americans</u>
<u n="357" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0541" trans="overlap">love Hawaii</u>
<u n="359" who="S0540">but they decided that that's the kind of place they want to really hang out and enjoy is it's just it's it's really almost <trunc>Jap</trunc>Japan</u>
<u n="360" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0540" trans="overlap">an extension of Japan <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0541">yeah yeah cos the Americans love Hawaii</u>
<u n="363" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0541" trans="overlap">they're crazy about it</u>
<u n="365" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah yeah well it's very Japanised very very</u>
<u n="366" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0541">maybe different islands have got different erm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0540">yeah that's true I think they are just going to the main</u>
<u n="370" who="S0541">appeal to different</u>
<u n="371" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0541">nationalities</u>
<u n="373" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah possibly</u>
<u n="374" who="S0541" trans="overlap">the American love Maui they always go to Maui</u>
<u n="375" who="S0540">okay</u>
<u n="376" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0540">I don't know which er which island they're going to but anyway they'll they'll have a great time <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0540">I mean I should really you know enjoy a holiday like that <pause dur="short"/> to be honest but I have to really find a job <vocal desc="laugh"/> and get my visa sorted out <pause dur="short"/> you know and these things <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what I am really looking forward to probably is fine food fine food and also</u>
<u n="380" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0540">and maybe <pause dur="short"/> get some clothes <pause dur="short"/> shoes</u>
<u n="382" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm a haircut <pause dur="short"/> bit of revamp</u>
<u n="384" who="S0541">you'll come back I won't recognise you</u>
<u n="385" who="S0540">you will</u>
<u n="386" who="S0541" trans="overlap">go who is this? who is this person?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0540">I I haven't changed since I'm like twelve <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0541">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I have not changed <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0541">you'll come back with a gamine Audrey Hepburn crop</u>
<u n="391" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I know I dunno</u>
<u n="393" who="S0540">oh recently I saw Marion Cotillard</u>
<u n="394" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah quite nice</u>
<u n="396" who="S0541">what's she got?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0540">she's got a bob little wavy</u>
<u n="398" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="399" who="S0540">no fringe</u>
<u n="400" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0540">but I think I should go something that she has <pause dur="short"/> because her face is round</u>
<u n="402" who="S0541">what a short thing?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0540">mm?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0541">short?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0540">well not short but <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of the similar style</u>
<u n="406" who="S0541">like a bob?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0540">a <trunc>w</trunc>wavy bob</u>
<u n="408" who="S0541">but you've got straight hair</u>
<u n="409" who="S0540">yeah I have to have a permed</u>
<u n="410" who="S0541">really? that would be awful <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't it look a bit weird when it grows out?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0541">cos you have very straight hair</u>
<u n="413" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0541">well</u>
<u n="415" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no I need to consult my hair stylist <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what to do but I had <pause dur="short"/> I had all sorts of hairstyles <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've been you know <pause dur="short"/> you don't know <pause dur="short"/> but I have <pause dur="long"/> I think here I may have something it's er yeah ah but I'm looking forward to cos my brother was compiling er photos</u>
<u n="416" who="S0541">uhu</u>
<u n="417" who="S0540">from the past</u>
<u n="418" who="S0541">uhu</u>
<u n="419" who="S0540">and there were some really you know I mean unforgettable pictures from the past <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0541">from your childhood?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0540">yeah well yes so when he was maybe five and I was seven when I was that's where the only time when I was taller than him</u>
<u n="422" who="S0541">uhu</u>
<u n="423" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> er so it's going to be very mm moving <pause dur="short"/> I used to have funny passport</u>
<u n="424" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0540">photos <pause dur="short"/> er I don't know what I've done mm I used to have something quite interesting to look at <pause dur="long"/> oh and I wanted to show you if I I I thought I had very fun pictures of me</u>
<u n="426" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0540">but I don't</u>
<u n="428" who="S0541">mm oh no</u>
<u n="429" who="S0540"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I keep forgetting to cash cheques</u>
<u n="430" who="S0541">that's nice it's is it out of date now?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0540">absolutely out of date I suppose how long does it last?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0541">three months</u>
<u n="433" who="S0540">no it's out of date stupid</u>
<u n="434" who="S0541">might be able to issue you another one</u>
<u n="435" who="S0540">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0541">if you send it to them</u>
<u n="437" who="S0540">yeah I really should do these things <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> Paris <vocal desc="sigh"/> I was so shocked</u>
<u n="438" who="S0541">I think everybody was</u>
<u n="439" who="S0540">yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0541">I know I saw it on the news I'd just switched on the news before I went to bed on a Friday and I was up</u>
<u n="441" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah me too I was just</u>
<u n="442" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> up to about three four in the morning</u>
<u n="443" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0541">watching it yeah I was er really wide awake then</u>
<u n="445" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you know it was kind of so horrible and it was frightening</u>
<u n="447" who="S0540">I mean</u>
<u n="448" who="S0541">it's frightening absolutely frightening</u>
<u n="449" who="S0540">yes and so I asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know what I should do with the fear and the speed of fear <vocal desc="sigh"/> because it doesn't come from god <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so according to psalm ninety-one because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if you feel frightened and scared you need to know this because this is really helpful <pause dur="short"/> mm so it says I mean I've been really frightened to take public transport or</u>
<u n="450" who="S0541" trans="overlap">what here?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0540">here even here I feel like I saw that erm <pause dur="short"/> that <unclear/> on on run that</u>
<u n="452" who="S0541" trans="overlap">what you</u>
<u n="453" who="S0540">Salah Salah <unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0540">I felt like a saw him on the tube</u>
<u n="456" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0540">anyway so psalm ninety-one says it it you know he's god's word is the truth <pause dur="short"/> so if you know the character <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't feel so scared because you'd be so assured by it <pause dur="short"/> anyway it says oh if you make the most high your dwelling even the lord who is my refuge then no harm will befall you no disaster will come near your tent for he will command his entrance concerning you to guard you in all your ways they will lift you up in your hands so that you will not strike your foot against a stone mm <pause dur="short"/> the interesting thing is here you will not fear the terror of night nor the arrow that flies by day nor the pestilence that stalks in the darkness nor the plague that destroyed at midday a thousand may fall at your side ten thousand at your right hand but it will not come near you <pause dur="short"/> you will only observe with your eyes and see the punishment of the wicked obviously if I'm on the wicked side I would be <pause dur="short"/> I dunno but however <vocal desc="sigh"/> if you really really really live the word by word the end result would be no fear I mean you know it's difficult I mean I'm absolutely frightened by the spiders in the kitchen but I have to because I cannot keep living in fear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> so it's a really stressful time <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0541">because of the Paris thing?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0540">no just mm you know just in general <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I thought I had mm my strange passport photos</u>
<u n="460" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0540">there ah <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0540">I'm really hungry</u>
<u n="464" who="S0541">you should eat something</u>
<u n="465" who="S0540">I try that Indian takeaway for the first time</u>
<u n="466" who="S0541">which one?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0540">here the one on <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0541">oh the <anon type="place"/> or whatever?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="gasp"/> it's really good</u>
<u n="470" who="S0541">is that the good one? because there were two that were recommended on there were two on here has one closed?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0540">probably one closed because</u>
<u n="472" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I think maybe it's now the fish place that</u>
<u n="473" who="S0540">oh yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0541" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="475" who="S0540">yeah that fish place</u>
<u n="476" who="S0541" trans="overlap">there was another one and I never knew which one was good because someone had recommended one and I couldn't remember</u>
<u n="477" who="S0540">okay</u>
<u n="478" who="S0541">so it is good?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0540">it's really it was really good</u>
<u n="480" who="S0541">really?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0540">mm and I wouldn't I think once six every six months might be enough for me</u>
<u n="482" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah and like swimming in like</u>
<u n="483" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0541" trans="overlap">ghee</u>
<u n="485" who="S0540">mm it's it's quite salty</u>
<u n="486" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="487" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I can just taste all sorts of flavours in in curries and and naan and rice and poppadum you know with the whole set</u>
<u n="488" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0540">it's really filling</u>
<u n="490" who="S0541">yeah it's very high fat I do love it I had one a few weeks ago</u>
<u n="491" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0541">and they erm in that <anon type="place"/> place you know there are a few of them in town? they've got like a pink exterior there's one on</u>
<u n="493" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="494" who="S0541">kind of off <anon type="place"/> street</u>
<u n="495" who="S0540">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0541" trans="overlap">very much</u>
<u n="497" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0541" trans="overlap">they're they're kind of a little bit</u>
<u n="499" who="S0540" trans="overlap">is it still the <trunc>ve</trunc>vegan places vegan curry places?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0541" trans="overlap">no they're not actually they're they do everything</u>
<u n="501" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh you mean on <anon type="place"/> street cos there is a</u>
<u n="502" who="S0541" trans="overlap">the</u>
<u n="503" who="S0540" trans="overlap">famous Indian fish restaurant on</u>
<u n="504" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="505" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> street</u>
<u n="506" who="S0541" trans="overlap">no no I went</u>
<u n="507" who="S0540" trans="overlap">just</u>
<u n="508" who="S0541" trans="overlap">somewhere kind of off erm <anon type="place"/> street</u>
<u n="509" who="S0540">but I have been I have been to a few</u>
<u n="510" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0540">you know</u>
<u n="512" who="S0541">I do I do like curries but erm er always a bit conscious of erm er <pause dur="short"/> I like to make my own curries to be honest cos then I can control the amount of oil and</u>
<u n="513" who="S0540">mm and all the other things</u>
<u n="514" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you know sometimes they're really oily</u>
<u n="515" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="516" who="S0541">well it's it's not oil but it's ghee</u>
<u n="517" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0541" trans="overlap">butter</u>
<u n="519" who="S0540" trans="overlap">butter mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0541">but they are good oh well that's good good to if I ever feel like having a take out Indian then erm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0540">yeah the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0541" trans="overlap">the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0540">I had</u>
<u n="524" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0540">okra in tomato curry</u>
<u n="526" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0540">and prawns</u>
<u n="528" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0540">both of them</u>
<u n="530" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yummy</u>
<u n="531" who="S0540">were just really good</u>
<u n="532" who="S0541">really?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0540">and then had er <vocal desc="sigh"/> sort of extra vegetable curry for free</u>
<u n="534" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="535" who="S0540">plus er ten percent off for picking up</u>
<u n="536" who="S0541">that's good</u>
<u n="537" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><trunc>collectio</trunc></u>
<u n="538" who="S0541">that's good</u>
<u n="539" who="S0540" trans="overlap">you know collection in person</u>
<u n="540" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="541" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="542" who="S0541">but I haven't cooked for ages then like when I was away I cooked on my last night I'm I just made some tagliatelle with like chilli prawns which are really like and er it's just the easiest thing to make and it's just so delicious</u>
<u n="543" who="S0540">what is this?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0541">it's just basically it's just tagliatelle and I just sautéed the prawns in garlic and chilli chopped</u>
<u n="545" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0541" trans="overlap">with chilli that's it and er</u>
<u n="547" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0541">just literally for like three minutes in a little bit of olive oil and then just put salt and pepper and a bit of parmesan and it was really good there was big tiger prawns and that was really yummy but I haven't cooked for ages</u>
<u n="549" who="S0540" trans="overlap">where did you get the tiger prawns from? frozen?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0541" trans="overlap">just M and S or Waitrose or somewhere</u>
<u n="551" who="S0540">yeah I need to <pause dur="short"/> I you know I I cooked a lasagne without the pasta sheets <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I wonder why they were sticking</u>
<u n="553" who="S0540">I don't know my lasagne sheets from Waitrose are not very good quality ones</u>
<u n="554" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah maybe you should get the <unclear/> ones which are better</u>
<u n="555" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm erm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0541" trans="overlap">did you put too many in the pan?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0540">well you need to though you need a sort of six sheets and they all have to go into the thing the pan</u>
<u n="558" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you got big big enough pan?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0540">maybe I don't have a big enough pan</u>
<u n="560" who="S0541" trans="overlap">maybe you need to do it in batches so you do some and you put them out and do some and put them out</u>
<u n="561" who="S0540">oh no</u>
<u n="562" who="S0541" trans="overlap">that might be a better way of doing it</u>
<u n="563" who="S0540">anyway yeah I need to figure out how to</u>
<u n="564" who="S0541" trans="overlap">my mum used to do it all the time</u>
<u n="565" who="S0540">how did she do it?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0541">she just put them in boiling water and then put them out but I think she did it in batches I think you have to if you're doing quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I can't remember she used to make her own pasta as well which is all very elaborate</u>
<u n="567" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0541">but er it can't be that complicated I mean there's no reason</u>
<u n="569" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no it can't be</u>
<u n="570" who="S0541" trans="overlap">why they should stick together unless you've got too many in maybe the water's not hot enough or something or</u>
<u n="571" who="S0540">I don't know there must be</u>
<u n="572" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I mean are you not rinsing</u>
<u n="573" who="S0540" trans="overlap">a way</u>
<u n="574" who="S0541" trans="overlap">them in</u>
<u n="575" who="S0540">rinsing? do you rinse pasta?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0541">some <trunc>peo</trunc> no actually I don't rinse pasta</u>
<u n="577" who="S0540">no</u>
<u n="578" who="S0541">I dunno</u>
<u n="579" who="S0540">that's the the only problem I have</u>
<u n="580" who="S0541" trans="overlap">well just google it</u>
<u n="581" who="S0540">yeah I should do shouldn't I? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah cos I'm sure you'd find about a million kind of similar it's it's amazing now I've just realise that nobody's had an original thought ever because you can just put anything in there and the chances are someone's had the same problem</u>
<u n="583" who="S0540"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's true</u>
<u n="585" who="S0540">that's how I actually you know verified the originality of my research like</u>
<u n="586" who="S0541">what googling it?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0540">yeah I put</u>
<u n="588" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0540" trans="overlap">after printing okay the digital printing <unclear/> you don't see anything</u>
<u n="590" who="S0541">no</u>
<u n="591" who="S0540">just my work</u>
<u n="592" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0541">well maybe you are the only one</u>
<u n="595" who="S0540">yeah it's not that amazing I mean you know it's not that innovative well anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's er <vocal desc="laugh"/> anyway it's just I'm just saying it's <vocal desc="laugh"/> innovative in a sense that no one else actually even bothered to put it up on the website or something</u>
<u n="596" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah maybe someone's done it in some corner of the world in some</u>
<u n="597" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0541" trans="overlap">language that you don't understand you know</u>
<u n="599" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but I came across two people who actually contacted me saying that they had the idea as well but they didn't manage to do it or something</u>
<u n="600" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="601" who="S0540">but those ones are working in my field so they kind of told me in person you know</u>
<u n="602" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0540">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I also had the idea and I check it a little but it never worked or the other one was oh we were gonna do it but we just saw you doing it or my published work so they just decide not to do it sort of like that</u>
<u n="604" who="S0541">you are <unclear/> in the world of</u>
<u n="605" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0541" trans="overlap">digital <unclear/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's so true I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean imagine you know if you you know write you hear I don't know put up something erm online someone else did <pause dur="short"/> and that became in demand <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know <unclear>what that is</unclear> er <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know so how did you find Airbnb?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0541">erm it's been fine actually</u>
<u n="609" who="S0540">oh yes?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah I had two my first one <pause dur="short"/> was a guy who who's like an <trunc>Engli</trunc> he was an English Arab and so I <vocal desc="laugh"/> saw his picture obviously he just looked like a kind of he didn't have a beard or anything but his name was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> something or other</u>
<u n="611" who="S0540">yeah <trunc>diff</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="612" who="S0541">and er this <trunc>w</trunc> obviously it's before Paris so</u>
<u n="613" who="S0540">oh okay</u>
<u n="614" who="S0541">and I was a bit like oh and then but he seemed fine and</u>
<u n="615" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0541">and then his friend turned up</u>
<u n="617" who="S0540">oh yes?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0541">rather than him like he was</u>
<u n="619" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0541">you know cos I have to hand over the keys</u>
<u n="621" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah oh right</u>
<u n="622" who="S0541">and so kind of a woman in her forties so I was kind of reassured by that</u>
<u n="623" who="S0540">oh good</u>
<u n="624" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and I came back and the flat was perfect</u>
<u n="625" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0541" trans="overlap">the only thing was they'd used a lot of towels for some strange reason and they'd left behind a lot of erm <pause dur="short"/> beer bottles</u>
<u n="627" who="S0540">oh yeah? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0541" trans="overlap">like the you know the big ones?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0541">and there were like twelve of those and they'd</u>
<u n="631" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0541">they were there for two nights</u>
<u n="633" who="S0540">wow</u>
<u n="634" who="S0541" trans="overlap">so twelve of those and some tonic water so she must have had some vodka or gin or something</u>
<u n="635" who="S0540">they must have had a party</u>
<u n="636" who="S0541">well this is what I think and then when I opened the recycling bin I saw an airbed erm box</u>
<u n="637" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="638" who="S0541">which if they'd got smuggled somebody and which would explain the towels</u>
<u n="639" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0541">but if they'd smuggled someone in that's naughty because they have to pay extra</u>
<u n="641" who="S0540">yeah they must have been that</u>
<u n="642" who="S0541">I think so</u>
<u n="643" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0541">and then the woman I had last weekend I had well she came on Thursday actually <pause dur="short"/> and she was an American woman from New York</u>
<u n="645" who="S0540">okay</u>
<u n="646" who="S0541">so she was fine and I kind of</u>
<u n="647" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0541" trans="overlap">went home yesterday and it's kind of it's quite funny going back into your home because it's like people have got different patterns of</u>
<u n="649" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0541">kind of behaviour</u>
<u n="651" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0541">so yeah whereas the the other guy <trunc>le</trunc> I mean everything was absolutely immaculate I mean I'm not joking it was literally</u>
<u n="653" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0541">absolutely immaculate she'd left like crumbs on the table kind of like big fingerprints all over the stuff like the stove was dirty and erm <pause dur="short"/> and that was it really I mean nothing else it was only the kitchen she said that she cooked a lot <pause dur="short"/> and she kind of er kind of decimated my butter cos she used loads of stuff and anyway whatever but I mean do you know on the whole kind of absolutely fine</u>
<u n="655" who="S0540">yeah and do you actually make money?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0541">I have made money yeah otherwise</u>
<u n="657" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah you yeah okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0541">I wouldn't do it yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="660" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I just vacate my flat and</u>
<u n="661" who="S0540">no I <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0541" trans="overlap">take my poor little cat <pause dur="short"/> all the way</u>
<u n="663" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0541" trans="overlap">to <anon type="place"/> in a box in the freezing cold</u>
<u n="665" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no I was I <trunc>wa</trunc> no I <trunc>wa</trunc> no I don't know I just wondered</u>
<u n="666" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah no no</u>
<u n="667" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I mean you do? you do?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I mean it's well it's er it's been a kind of life saver for me</u>
<u n="669" who="S0540">oh yes? oh okay I just wondered</u>
<u n="670" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I just wondered yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0541">well it's it cost me quite a lot to go to <anon type="place"/> cos I have to get a taxi to</u>
<u n="673" who="S0540" trans="overlap">do you?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0541"><anon type="place"/> and cos I've got my little cat</u>
<u n="675" who="S0540" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0541">but it's been fine I've got the journey down to about an hour and a quarter</u>
<u n="677" who="S0540">yeah oh right</u>
<u n="678" who="S0541" trans="overlap">cos where my friend lives so I go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="680" who="S0541">in the cab and then I go from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0541">which erm is about anything between twenty-three and thirty-five minutes</u>
<u n="683" who="S0540">that's nice yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0541">and then his flat is like literally two minutes walk from the station</u>
<u n="685" who="S0540">oh okay and</u>
<u n="686" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's</u>
<u n="687" who="S0540">you can just have the spare room?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0541">well I mean he yeah <pause dur="short"/> kind of he's been away cos he's kind of like he's he was away <pause dur="short"/> when I was there two weeks ago</u>
<u n="689" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="690" who="S0541">he was away in Brazil that was it</u>
<u n="691" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0541">and then his parents are quite elderly and they live</u>
<u n="693" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0541">about five miles away so he spends the weekend with his parents</u>
<u n="695" who="S0540">oh I see</u>
<u n="696" who="S0541">his mother's got cancer</u>
<u n="697" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="698" who="S0541" trans="overlap">or <trunc>ki</trunc> recovering actually but anyway so he's kind of in and out and he's away now he's off to New York again</u>
<u n="699" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0541">and and he's got a spare room which is his office that he works from</u>
<u n="701" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="702" who="S0541">so I mean he's kind of said that I can kind of like basically he's there until the end of December and then</u>
<u n="703" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0541">he's gonna go and live in Lisbon</u>
<u n="705" who="S0540">oh right</u>
<u n="706" who="S0541">so in theory although around Christmas obviously I won't go <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so in theory erm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh you can come here</u>
<u n="708" who="S0541">well aren't you gonna be here? <pause dur="short"/> I thought you were here for Christmas</u>
<u n="709" who="S0540">yeah but you know my brother's been sleeping on that <vocal desc="laugh"/> so like</u>
<u n="710" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="711" who="S0540">I'm joking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0541">just <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah don't worry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you we we need our privacy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0541">well you know I'm kind of getting less er and less erm <pause dur="short"/> it's funny I mean I I actually kind of the first time I stayed there I was really relieved cos like you know this nightmare with the people upstairs</u>
<u n="715" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0541">and anyway which has got a lot better since I complained to the freeholder</u>
<u n="717" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0541" trans="overlap">but it's still they've been waking up in the night still like</u>
<u n="719" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0541" trans="overlap">twice a week you know</u>
<u n="721" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="722" who="S0541">so I was really tired and when I went to this place it was really quiet and</u>
<u n="723" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0541">I slept through the night</u>
<u n="725" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="726" who="S0541">you know and it's really quiet it's like a new build so it's all</u>
<u n="727" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="728" who="S0541">hermetically sealed like it's really</u>
<u n="729" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="730" who="S0541" trans="overlap">super quiet</u>
<u n="731" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="732" who="S0541">and warm and I mean it's just so calm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="734" who="S0541">it's just so calm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and there's no like noise there's no door banging or like other people's noise and yeah I just kind of like rested I had a really nice restful weekend and I</u>
<u n="735" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="736" who="S0541" trans="overlap">slept all the way through the night and the cat was like just</u>
<u n="737" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="738" who="S0541">the cat was super happy she just</u>
<u n="739" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0541">I took her little bed and she was like in her bed</u>
<u n="741" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0541">putting <anon type="place"/> so it was</u>
<u n="743" who="S0540" trans="overlap">well that's nice that's nice</u>
<u n="744" who="S0541" trans="overlap">so it was actually really nice</u>
<u n="745" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it's worked out yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0541">yeah so it's really nice</u>
<u n="747" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it's amazing that the cat you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was happy in the you know</u>
<u n="748" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I I I don't I think she's a bit stressed out by it actually cos when when I got home yesterday she went and sat in her litter tray which is a classic sign of stress apparently</u>
<u n="749" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0541">but she</u>
<u n="751" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="752" who="S0541" trans="overlap">seems okay I put her on the train and</u>
<u n="753" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="754" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and in her little <trunc>bas</trunc> in her little carry thing</u>
<u n="755" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and you know she seems find</u>
<u n="757" who="S0540">oh okay</u>
<u n="758" who="S0541">but I think maybe it's a bit much for her</u>
<u n="759" who="S0540">mm would you mind if I boil a a noodle?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0541">oh no go for it</u>
<u n="761" who="S0540" trans="overlap">quickly</u>
<u n="762" who="S0541">go for it</u>
<u n="763" who="S0540"><vocal desc="cough"/> oh but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I I do have a spider problem I have to say</u>
<u n="764" who="S0541" trans="overlap">do you want me to kill them?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0540">er no not really</u>
<u n="766" who="S0541">do you want me to throw them out the window?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0540">well well I don't know not exactly the window</u>
<u n="768" who="S0541">are they really big? are they the big ones or the little ones?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0540">well they these are the famous er er false widow spiders</u>
<u n="770" who="S0541">oh you're joking?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0540">I'm not joking</u>
<u n="772" who="S0541">but they're really dangerous <pause dur="short"/> are you joking?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0540">well that's why I'm telling you or <unclear/> I had along here and didn't realise that was that like all the one over there which is kind of curled up er you know it's not dangerous because it's there all the time</u>
<u n="774" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="775" who="S0540">in <unclear/> and er come here this way <pause dur="short"/> there's one just by the <unclear/> here</u>
<u n="776" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="777" who="S0540">a little one</u>
<u n="778" who="S0541">oh that one</u>
<u n="779" who="S0540">that's a little one</u>
<u n="780" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="781" who="S0540">and there's a big one over there in the corner</u>
<u n="782" who="S0541">oh I'll just leave it</u>
<u n="783" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0541">I'd leave it I mean I I can quite happily catch them and throw them out if you want</u>
<u n="785" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0541">I don't mind I don't I don't like them myself to be honest they make me a bit</u>
<u n="787" who="S0540">but er yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I don't like the thought of them crawling over me at night</u>
<u n="789" who="S0540">yeah they won't move that's that's why I haven't caught them they've been there for a long long time mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0541">so my Airbnb thing the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0541">something er something quite funny is that I got a request from er this woman for <unclear/> can I come and stay and I've got like a five-year-old and a baby</u>
<u n="793" who="S0540">what?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="795" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="796" who="S0541">and I was like oh I don't know if my sofa cos I've got this new sofa and I don't know if it's gonna survive a five-year-old which</u>
<u n="797" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0541">you know</u>
<u n="799" who="S0540">that's fair enough</u>
<u n="800" who="S0541">and fair enough and then she said oh by the way I live opposite you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0540">what?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0541">she said we live at number seventy-one</u>
<u n="803" who="S0540">on my god</u>
<u n="804" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and then how freaky is that? so now I've and I haven't heard from her since actually</u>
<u n="805" who="S0540">well that's a very strange contact</u>
<u n="806" who="S0541">isn't it weird?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and she said no we're between flats and erm we need somewhere to stay and then she came back to me and said actually we need it for thirteen days and I was like oh I don't know I I've</u>
<u n="809" who="S0540" trans="overlap">thirteen?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0541"><trunc>thir</trunc> yeah I know</u>
<u n="811" who="S0540" trans="overlap">when? when?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0541"><trunc>d</trunc> well December</u>
<u n="813" who="S0540">which December?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0541">now</u>
<u n="815" who="S0540">but December which date?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0541">from the sixth</u>
<u n="817" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="818" who="S0541">but then I haven't heard from her so <trunc>sh</trunc> I think maybe she found somewhere else which I was quite relieved about cos I just thought oh and I thirteen days is too long</u>
<u n="819" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0541">it's too long and I just thought a baby and like</u>
<u n="821" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0541" trans="overlap">a kid and</u>
<u n="823" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="824" who="S0541">no</u>
<u n="825" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="826" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's too much isn't it?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0540">yeah it is a little bit too much</u>
<u n="828" who="S0541">mm <pause dur="short"/> what's this? oh is it a de-fluffer?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0540">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="830" who="S0541">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> so have you heard your neighbour?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0540">yeah so would you like to sit over here or there?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0541">I'll sit here</u>
<u n="833" who="S0540" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="834" who="S0541">I'll join you with my tea</u>
<u n="835" who="S0540">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's a bit dark in this flat because I don't really have erm a ceiling light mm</u>
<u n="836" who="S0541">so my little trips away have been a bit of an insight into the life beyond <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="837" who="S0540">oh that sounds like er you've been just so spoiled <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0541">no life out of town</u>
<u n="839" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="840" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0540">yeah but you know you are thinking of you know living outside now though</u>
<u n="842" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0540">plus it's</u>
<u n="844" who="S0541">obviously there hasn't been the commuting but erm</u>
<u n="845" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="846" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="847" who="S0540">oh so did you like the <trunc>com</trunc> I mean do you like outside?</u>
<u n="848" who="S0541">erm yeah I mean the it's this place is is it's okay I mean it's a nice little kind of market town and erm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0540" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="850" who="S0541">there's a river and everything's very compact erm</u>
<u n="851" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="852" who="S0541">it's very clean and they are not very not chavvy</u>
<u n="853" who="S0540">oh sounds like a quite <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="854" who="S0541">it's kind of</u>
<u n="855" who="S0540" trans="overlap">posh town or is it?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm no it's very <trunc>or</trunc> it's very kind of ordinary actually I mean it's</u>
<u n="857" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="858" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's just ordinary people and it's not you know exciting I mean it's quite pleasant it's got everything you need like an M and S and a Waitrose</u>
<u n="859" who="S0540">oh perfect</u>
<u n="860" who="S0541" trans="overlap">Caffè Nero</u>
<u n="861" who="S0540">really?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0541">a Carluccio</u>
<u n="863" who="S0540" trans="overlap">in the village?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0541">it's like a market town</u>
<u n="865" who="S0540"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0541" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="867" who="S0540">oh like a okay so the</u>
<u n="868" who="S0541" trans="overlap">so a small</u>
<u n="869" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it's er like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0541" trans="overlap">town</u>
<u n="871" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="872" who="S0541">it's small it's probably smaller than that</u>
<u n="873" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh pretty oh that sounds perfect for me actually</u>
<u n="874" who="S0541">it's okay it's okay yeah I don't know it's been a bit kind of erm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0541">it's kind of cheap there you know if I wanted to buy a little house there it's very cheap and it's in a <unclear/></u>
<u n="877" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh it's <trunc>y</trunc>yeah I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're not now a woman of you know desperate er you're not poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're not poor</u>
<u n="878" who="S0541">I'm getting poorer now <unclear>anyway</unclear> believe me</u>
<u n="879" who="S0540">oh yeah but you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> let let's get it right you're not poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm because you can actually buy a place</u>
<u n="880" who="S0541">yeah in the middle of nowhere</u>
<u n="881" who="S0540" trans="overlap">in a place like that</u>
<u n="882" who="S0541">it's okay I mean I I don't know I I I need to I need to do a bit more exploring but anyway if things you know it was kind of like</u>
<u n="883" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="884" who="S0541">you could live there you know you could live there</u>
<u n="885" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="886" who="S0541">I mean</u>
<u n="887" who="S0540">and commute to London</u>
<u n="888" who="S0541">it's yeah the trains go to <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0541">and erm I don't know I mean I didn't kind of like feel massively drawn to it but I was</u>
<u n="891" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0541" trans="overlap">quite you know it's it's not kind of</u>
<u n="893" who="S0540" trans="overlap">of course not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0541">no you know but I'm always quite kind of you know if things get really you know if I kind of have to kind of do the the deed which is sell my flat</u>
<u n="895" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="896" who="S0541">then erm you know <pause dur="short"/> it was quite a <trunc>q</trunc>quite reassuring</u>
<u n="897" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="898" who="S0541">that you know <pause dur="short"/> it's quite reassuring that it is possible to kind of even on my very small budget it would be fine somewhere if I have to</u>
<u n="899" who="S0540">really?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0541">if I have to which I might have to so anyway so that was good</u>
<u n="901" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="902" who="S0541">so it was kind of a bit quite positive in terms of you know</u>
<u n="903" who="S0540">I'm really worried I'm not that worried but I do really have to</u>
<u n="904" who="S0541">find a job</u>
<u n="905" who="S0540">mm yeah visa and everything oh</u>
<u n="906" who="S0541">and what sorry?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0540">and and visa and everything you know</u>
<u n="908" who="S0541">oh you're on a visa</u>
<u n="909" who="S0540">a <trunc>vi</trunc><trunc>vi</trunc> you know I have to er extend my visa apply for a visa to stay</u>
<u n="910" who="S0541">oh cos you've been on a student visa</u>
<u n="911" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="912" who="S0541">when does that expire?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0540">at the end of February</u>
<u n="914" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="915" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0541">so do you have to get a job before then? <pause dur="short"/> or you just have to know that you are gonna or can you extend it anyway?</u>
<u n="917" who="S0540">mm there are a few a few ways in anyway it's quite hard</u>
<u n="918" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="919" who="S0540">I need to have a job I think</u>
<u n="920" who="S0541">have you started looking?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0540">no because I need a job as in you know I need to look for research fellowship</u>
<u n="922" who="S0541">yeah I know that's what I mean</u>
<u n="923" who="S0540">no</u>
<u n="924" who="S0541">do they coincide with the academic year or not? or do they open or they open?</u>
<u n="925" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I just missed the one that er in September</u>
<u n="926" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="927" who="S0540"><anon type="place"/> college junior fellowship</u>
<u n="928" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="929" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="930" who="S0541">how annoying</u>
<u n="931" who="S0540">but I couldn't have applied <pause dur="short"/> in September</u>
<u n="932" who="S0541">because you haven't got your PhD?</u>
<u n="933" who="S0540">mm impossible impossible</u>
<u n="934" who="S0541">maybe you can get some other work <pause dur="short"/> welcome to my world <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="935" who="S0540" trans="overlap">but but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't worry I'm <trunc>u</trunc></u>
<u n="936" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="937" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I'm used to it I'm used to it anyway <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah anyway <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0541" trans="overlap">do do lots of them come up?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0540">mm?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0541">do lots of them come up?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no I don't think so but I I do think I need to start talking to people I <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> about you know possibilities <pause dur="long"/> yeah er <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's that's what you know that will hit me in December yeah gosh <pause dur="short"/> erm <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's really good to have a I think a security but how can you? <pause dur="short"/> oh it's so oh oh oh oh but anyway</u>
<u n="942" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0540">hopefully there is something <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0541">something will come up</u>
<u n="945" who="S0540">yeah and mm otherwise yeah I'm I should really have health checks you know</u>
<u n="946" who="S0541">have what sorry?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0540">health</u>
<u n="948" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><trunc>hea</trunc></u>
<u n="949" who="S0540">health check</u>
<u n="950" who="S0541">why?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0540">I don't know haven't had it for a long time</u>
<u n="952" who="S0541">do you feel okay?</u>
<u n="953" who="S0540">when I'm really stressed out I feel I'm really ill do you think it's normal?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0541">yeah cos I've been feeling like that for a year</u>
<u n="955" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0541">my stress levels are just they've been so high they've been like up here</u>
<u n="957" who="S0540">me too</u>
<u n="958" who="S0541">just a nightmare and then I sorted out a few bits and pieces and <pause dur="short"/> I kind of sorted a few things out and you know I got a <unclear/> Airbnb things which kind of helped</u>
<u n="959" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah that's so well done <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="960" who="S0541">I know but</u>
<u n="961" who="S0540" trans="overlap">that's so great but you were I mean</u>
<u n="962" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I could do with more I mean I could do with now I'm into the kind of the making the sacrifice and you know cos when I first thought about it I was like</u>
<u n="963" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="964" who="S0541" trans="overlap">wow this is really like a massive disruption</u>
<u n="965" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="966" who="S0541">and really it quite quite upset me</u>
<u n="967" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="968" who="S0541">and now I've done it I'm I'm kind of like a bit more kind of open and flexible which I have to be in my position I can't I can't not be flexible</u>
<u n="969" who="S0540">well you seem to enjoy it in a way</u>
<u n="970" who="S0541">well you know I guess</u>
<u n="971" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="972" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I guess I mean I guess I was lucky because you know I was lucky my friend is not really around and he's a he's a really old friend of mine I mean he's</u>
<u n="973" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="974" who="S0541" trans="overlap">from my university friend</u>
<u n="975" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="976" who="S0541">and erm he's <trunc>ab</trunc>absolutely lovely as well he's just so lovely and</u>
<u n="977" who="S0540">ah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0541">he's just been kind of like you know just a source of good practical kind of practical assistance and just said oh you know I mean he he planned it the whole Airbnb thing in my head</u>
<u n="979" who="S0540">oh that's so good I mean you know yeah your friends you know</u>
<u n="980" who="S0541">ah I just really needed that kind of you know and you've been so sweet as well to offer your flat and it's just things like that you know</u>
<u n="981" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh no fine</u>
<u n="982" who="S0541" trans="overlap">just kind of really helpful but anyway but erm</u>
<u n="983" who="S0540" trans="overlap">erm <trunc>any</trunc> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know if you could ever bear you know sleep in here I could just sleep on that er</u>
<u n="984" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="985" who="S0540" trans="overlap">bed mm</u>
<u n="986" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's fine it's just my little my little cat you know</u>
<u n="987" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="988" who="S0541">it's just my little cat so but erm</u>
<u n="989" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="990" who="S0541">but yeah my stress levels like and when I first went there and I got in the door with the cat the first time like I got a key that we cut that doesn't work properly in the door</u>
<u n="991" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh yeah oh typical yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and it took me ages to get in and I was like panicking cos I couldn't get either of the locks open cos it's</u>
<u n="993" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="994" who="S0541">the bloody key wouldn't work</u>
<u n="995" who="S0540">oh yeah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0541">and I got in and I was so relieved and he had like ten this is what I had a fag cos he had like ten Marlboro Lights and I was just like went out on the balcony I was like so</u>
<u n="997" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0541" trans="overlap">stressed oh</u>
<u n="999" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1000" who="S0541">so I literally had so much like adrenalin running through my body <pause dur="short"/> it's crazy</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0541">I do get very stressed</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0541">but now my stress levels have kind of come down cos now I've kind of faced the worst situation</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0541">you know the worst</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I know I know the I realise</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0541" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I know yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0541">I now I know that you know I can might have to sell my flat I might have to and I'm I'm kind of fine with it now and just kind of</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0540">you seem calm</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0541">yeah I feel I feel better I mean obviously it's a bit kind of desperate it's</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0541" trans="overlap">kind of it's just desperate</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0540" trans="overlap">you're not the only one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> being desperate <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0541">well</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0540">but</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0541">I I don't I yeah I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't know I mean <trunc>y</trunc> I I don't think you can compare everyone's got their own <pause dur="short"/> everyone's got their own problems and their own kind of issues but I think to lose your home out of financial</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0540" trans="overlap">that is so true</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0541">problems is pretty much one of the worst things that can you know happen</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0541">but anyway but I've kind of</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah but yeah no I agree</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0541" trans="overlap">faced the fear</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0540">yeah I think you in your case it's the yeah the the changes you're facing are so big</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0541">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0541">anyway whatever so erm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0541">but anyway but I kind of feel a I feel a bit better at the moment I've just kind of like I've come down from the really high stress place and I I just feel a bit like resigned now <pause dur="short"/> what will be will be right?</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0540">yeah you can watch your couple of friends on Netflix it can't be too bad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0541">oh I've had a terrible time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've had the worst time you should know I've been whingeing to you for months</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0541">but anyway</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0540">but I do know I mean you know</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1039" who="S0540">I mean I've been you know living like you you know a zombie</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0541">yeah I've heard that yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0541" trans="overlap">just working and working</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0540">I just it was never ending never ending oh my gosh <pause dur="short"/> I don't it was so hard for me to wake up in the morning cos I <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't wake up in the morning because <pause dur="short"/> I I cannot write in the morning <pause dur="short"/> I I I write best in the early morning you know between twelve and five</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0541">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I never really I was you know un-stressed to write and edit and all of these things <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't quite work in the morning so I would get up you know so I would simply come er and <unclear>at night or</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> for like three four you know five months I mean you know <pause dur="short"/> it's quite a much you know I feel like I've missed an entire summer</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1047" who="S0540">I missed a complete autumn <pause dur="short"/> erm and and now erm and realise that the winter <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0541">yeah that's the worst time to wake up</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0540">I know</u>
<u n="1050" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't think of anything worse</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1053" who="S0541">having loads of</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1055" who="S0541">free time in the winter</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's so grim already</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0540">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1059" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I can't bear it you know I was swimming in the pond up until last week I was still in there</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yes I just have two or three recollections of that and that's it my summer was gone mm</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0541">I don't know what I've done with my year I've had so much</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0541">I've got the opposite problem I've had so much time and and like so little of it has been productive</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0541">I'm really not looking forward to the winter</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0540">ah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0541">with no travel and <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0540">I know</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0541">god</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0540">but I don't know</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1072" who="S0540" trans="overlap">quite happy not to travel <pause dur="short"/> mm quite happy <pause dur="short"/> I get really stressed out when I travel</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0541">really? I love it</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0540">I never used to <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm these days I'm just stressed out</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0541">but that's only cos of your PhD you won't be you should relax now a little bit if you can</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0540"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1077" who="S0541">get into <unclear>just</unclear> worrying about</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah I should</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0541" trans="overlap">a job</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0540">yeah I should do <pause dur="short"/> it's just hard</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you might feel better when you come back from Japan and like sometimes it's good to have like a physical <pause dur="short"/> geographical</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0540" trans="overlap">the yeah</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0541">displacement you know</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0540"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the thing is I'm dreading to go home every time I go home I have <pause dur="short"/> such a <pause dur="short"/> difficult time <pause dur="short"/> it's not that I don't get on with my family but it's always quite intense because I haven't seen them for a long time</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0540">so it's a lot of catching up to do <pause dur="short"/> or not catching up to do because I'm so exhausted</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0541" trans="overlap">are you not in contact with them a lot on the phone?</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0540">no <pause dur="short"/> but I of course you know I see my brother a lot</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0541">but your parents?</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0540">no I don't really</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0541">really?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0540">no</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0541">you don't ring them?</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0541">why not?</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0540">I never did</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0541">how strange</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0540">I never did</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0541">and they don't ring you?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0540">not necessarily</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0541">that's interesting</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0540">but I see them when I go home</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0541">oh okay</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0540">I mean of course you know we talk occasionally about things very rare maybe you know every half a year three months</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0541">wow that's amazing</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0540">I don't talk to my father these days because you know he's he he works in Ireland and usually I don't just you know I usually talk call my mother and then talk to my father <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I dunno but still you know they never change that much so <pause dur="short"/> I haven't and I'm old you know I'm not like a teenager I mean I think in Japan we have this kind of culture where once you grow up you don't contact them that much</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0541">really?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0540">mm <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's not so strong here but in Japan it's not that unknown</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0540">mm and I think it's an ageing thing</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0540"><vocal desc="sigh"/> but I'm close to my you know brother in a way a family member and then you know and then my news gets circulated through him in a way</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0540">so there is kind of you know indirect</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0540">contact with the rest of my family <pause dur="short"/> I just see my brother or I'm talking to my younger sister</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0540">yeah I'm terrible I'm terrible in keeping in touch that's the thing I'm terrible <pause dur="short"/> I never really call up call my parents on weekends I should do though I feel like time is short</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0540">I'm really not very good with long distant kind of erm relationships</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0541">mm I'm amazed you don't use Skype and all that stuff that is around now that makes it so easy</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0540">no it's we no</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0541" trans="overlap">video calls</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and stuff</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it doesn't make it easy because you know my father doesn't use Skype my mother uses Skype or we er a little bit er</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0540" trans="overlap">not that technically savvy so we just end up talking on the phone</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0540">which is fine somehow because landline's cheap now these days to call landlines</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0541">oh is it?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0540">mm oh but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean <pause dur="short"/> I do I do think that you know because I've been living you know abroad for so long this is the norm <pause dur="short"/> but it's not healthy I don't think <pause dur="short"/> could be better for sure it's it they're so difficult to change I mean it's been like this for a long time</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0541">I mean yeah I guess so if there's a pattern but you know well I mean it's fine if they don't mind</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0540">but I do feel a bit awkward you know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> and so I you know I feel like er just a bit tired when I go home I can't quite relax entirely there's a bit of catching up at the beginning <pause dur="short"/> then relax after that but because I'm only there for two days I mean there's not much of being a couch potato and then completely relaxing</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0540" trans="overlap">and there's not much we can you know I mean I will probably have a couple of days with my mother cos he has to go back to this Ireland and I will probably <unclear>more contact</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> oh er you know</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0541">I'm sure it will be nice to go</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it will be nice to go but I'm just <pause dur="short"/> yeah you know</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0541">you're probably just tired</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0540">just think of the journey to Heathrow <pause dur="short"/> six o'clock in the morning <pause dur="short"/> I'm flying with Finnair so go to Helsinki</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0541">okay</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0540">I usually fly with Finnair</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0541">really?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0540">mm somehow quite like it</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0541">how long is the flight?</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0540">mm <pause dur="short"/> they go together like twenty-two hours</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0541">oh my</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0540" trans="overlap">no fifteen</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0541">oh fifteen</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0540" trans="overlap">fifteen yeah sorry</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0541">so is it so do you stop at all anywhere?</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0540">yeah Helsinki</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0541">is that it? and then it's one leg</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0541">from Helsinki</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0541">all the way</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0540" trans="overlap">to all the way to Kansai not Tokyo to Kansai</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0541">and that's what? nine hours?</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0540">I don't know maybe mm something like that</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0540">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1163" who="S0541">uhu mm I love plane travel but <trunc>mayb</trunc></u>
<u n="1164" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it's I suppose so</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0541" trans="overlap">maybe not so much at the moment but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1166" who="S0540">I mean my brother came back for two days you know this weekend he arrived <pause dur="short"/> and he flew with Cathay Pacific and he <trunc>ca</trunc> flew from Kansai airport to London Heathrow</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0540">arrived at six o'clock in the or seven o'clock in the morning on Friday attended this ceremony something to do with with Japanese society of <trunc>doc</trunc> medical doctors in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1169" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0540">and then stayed here on Friday and Saturday and then flew back to Japan again</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0541">you're joking</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0540">no and I said are you crazy?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0541"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1174" who="S0540">he said no I wanted to attend this ceremony it's really important for the future</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0541">oh right</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0540" trans="overlap">of Japanese medical system so I mean it's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh well</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I was like oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0541"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1180" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like he didn't do anything he just slept ate I cooked</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0541">but er</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0540">and then left again <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1183" who="S0541">oh my god</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0540">but I would be like that a bit <pause dur="short"/> I will come home and my mother will be cooking and I will so be fortunate to I mean you know to just you know be able to and do nothing but</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0540">it'll be just like that I'll be home sleeping most of the time</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0541">well it's good you can regress to being a teenager</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0540">I always do when I go home</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0541">everybody does</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0540">where's my washing?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0540" trans="overlap">have you got my laundry? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1193" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it'll be good I think it's good timing</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0540">erm</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0541">it's good timing and you'll then you'll have a bit of a blast of kind of Japanese culture which will be interesting and a beautiful wedding which will be lovely and emotional and then like you know then you'll come back for Christmas</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0540">yeah I'm glad I'm coming back and doing this science museum thing on the fifteenth but I could have stayed for longer if I'd known</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0540">that my <unclear/> was in January</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0540"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0541">cos you thought it was December?</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0540">mm I thought it was gonna be around the fifteenth</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0541" trans="overlap">how annoying</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0540">so I'm quite annoyed</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0541">can you not change it? or now you've got your <anon type="place"/> thing you can't right?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh no it's all no I can't</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0541">how annoying</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0540">yeah but at the same time it's a bit more relaxing in a way cos I can just relaxing as in you know like in my usual kind of you know super way but I have plenty of time to go over my thesis</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0541">oh okay</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0540">and research for my application and positions I can't do that at home <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm and and Christmas you know it's not that merry back home <pause dur="short"/> because a lot of us are not around <pause dur="short"/> and my father works also <unclear/> at Christmas at the hospital</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0540">and my mother you know a student doing the homework so <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> but I can't wait <pause dur="short"/> to go home and just live like I used to live</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0540">it probably won't be changed very much where I live</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0541">what's that sorry?</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0540">I don't think much has changed in my area</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0541">where?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0541" trans="overlap">where your mum is?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0541">when did you when were you there last? last year?</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0540">no I was there about two years ago</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0541">two years ago</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0540">very briefly cos that time we you know we it was the new year so we all spent time in er our father's place in</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0540" trans="overlap">in Ireland where he works</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0540">and and that was bizarre because just so cold</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0541">oh no</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0540">er oh <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0541">oh well listen we should celebrate the end of your <pause dur="short"/> when you get back</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0541">we should celebrate the putting to bed of the thesis the dawn of a new era</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0540">are you still recording?</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0541">I think so</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0540">oh good</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0541">I think so</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0540">fantastic</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I haven't sent anything in yet they were emailed me about it and I said I was gonna do it and then I and then I didn't I started preparing it all</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0540">oh yes?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0541">and then I got sidetracked by some other pointless activity of like applying applying for some pointless job which obviously I would never get</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1245" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/> which is kind of how I spend weeks of my life these days</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0541" trans="overlap">and it's <trunc>p</trunc>pointless applications but erm</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0540">you'll get somewhere <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1249" who="S0541">I don't think so I failed another thing you know I failed a erm I found another thing and I applied for it</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0540">oh yes?</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0541">yeah it was like another <trunc>ed</trunc>editorial thing and I I applied for it you know the working from home thing?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0540">oh</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0541">and I applied for it and I got past the first test and then</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0541">they were like we want you to do another test so the second test was two hours long and I did the second test and I waited to hear and then they said you failed it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1256" who="S0540">wow</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0541">and erm they said you had too many errors and erm <pause dur="short"/> and it was quite funny like you had to kind of like edit these three pieces and then and then you had to give erm some feedback to the writers and then you had to give some feedback to the client well that was a separate exercise</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0540">that sounds like a really hard task</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0541">it was quite a lot to do in er like time was short so on the feedback to the writers obviously I had I just picked like a couple of points each I was like oh well you know cos obviously like I'm gonna run out of time right so I'm not gonna this is not the exercise the <trunc>e</trunc> the exercise is doing the editing and then they came back and they said oh I wasn't erm I was too abrupt with the writers in my feedback and like you you you know you didn't kind of or I didn't massage my comments enough for them they were kind of like too direct I was like for god's sake like what <trunc>wor</trunc></u>
<u n="1260" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0541" trans="overlap">what world do we live in? you know what world do we live in? you know when you're giving feedback to someone like you're straight and to the point you're not like oh oh oh ah oh oh oh</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0540">yeah <trunc>exact</trunc></u>
<u n="1263" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh oh</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0541">it was so ridiculous but anyway they just said oh well so you failed that but we'd erm we'd be delighted if you'd join our network of writers</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0540">wow well that's something</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0541">not really because I because it's gonna pay even worse than the editors which was quite bad but better than the last one erm it'll it'll pay really really badly and erm so then of course I I went to the website to kind of launch this <trunc>applica</trunc> this thing register and there's another test <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm like you know it's like I haven't done it yet because obviously I lost the will to live because that was like two days of my life you know doing all this crap just another waste of time</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0540">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> why don't you just forget about the online thing and?</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0541">well what am I gonna do?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0540">you know</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0541">no I'm I've I've applied for all sorts of stuff</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0541">and it's you know why are we <trunc>li</trunc> anyway whatever I dunno</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0540">mm oh I see</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0541">it's it's kind of you know it's quite difficult to get work that is not something you've done before</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0540">yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0541" trans="overlap">cos that's what people recruit for</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0541">so even if it's like a low job I have a harder time with the low jobs</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0541">because I you just look at my CV and like you've gotta be joking so it's a bit of a problem <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it really is</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0541">kind of finding something that is just like a you know just something to do which will pay some kind of you know basic money but I don't know what you're gonna be looking for but it's it's really difficult you know unless you go and work in a shop which I'm not gonna do sorry not because I feel I'm above it but I'm just like you know so it's really hard it's just really difficult</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0541">it's just very difficult to find I've applied for <trunc>every</trunc> for everything so it's really hard I I dunno I dunno I haven't got a solution and I can't seem to find one unfortunately no matter how hard I look and how hard I try</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0540">what about this <anon type="place"/> thing cos that sounded really good?</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0541">yeah I I am gonna do that but</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0541" trans="overlap">the exams aren't till I've got to I need to redo my CV so I need to completely rework it</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0540" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0541">in a new way and I wanted to find like a charity editing thing like</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0541" trans="overlap">to do as a project</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0541">so so I wanted to kind of be engaged on that</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0540">mm mm</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0541" trans="overlap">when I was doing my application</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0540">mm mm</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0541">cos I thought it would give me like <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1300" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0541">some er additional kind of necessary</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0540">yeah experience</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0541">gravitas</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0540">gravitas</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0541" trans="overlap">you know cos I'm coming from a consumer background</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0541">recently anyway so and I haven't kind of like and I asked somebody about it who's running like a charity project but I haven't heard back from him and I don't think he wants to share any of it with me so I kind of need to find something so that in itself is quite difficult because or obviously a lot of the kind of global organisations employ people</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0541">or they have interns or they er so volunteering and something like that is quite I haven't found anything yet I need to keep looking I was looking today actually</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0541">so I've had an issue with that so I really wanted to apply for that before Christmas</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0541">but then the exams aren't until July</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0541">so even if I passed the written exam in July there's then an aural <trunc>e</trunc> an aural <pause dur="short"/> exam <pause dur="short"/> after that so then presumably September would be the earliest point if I passed all of those things which at the moment my track record is just I'm not passing anything which is quite worrying</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0541">so then if I passed all of those then I'd be eligible to apply for stuff from September</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0540">oh my <trunc>g</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1319" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah so I've got to kind of get from here to there</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah I know I have the same <unclear/></u>
<u n="1321" who="S0541" trans="overlap">so nine months ten months</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0541">and then I might not even and even if I fail it's not a disaster it just means that I lose another year so anyway it's quite difficult you know it's quite difficult</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0540" trans="overlap">especially if you are just you know er having to you know live the moment I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know survive the <trunc>mo</trunc></u>
<u n="1325" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's just a nightmare</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0540" trans="overlap"><unclear/> tomorrow yeah mm</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's just I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I feel like I'm kind of walking through treacle like I'm never getting anywhere I keep you know</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0540" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0541">everything everything falls through</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0541">it's been the theme of the year it's just been the theme like everything has fallen through</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0540">you will come out of it very strong <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0541">I don't know if I will</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0540">you will come out</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0540" trans="overlap">you will</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I'll come out of it a broken woman</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0540">no er you know when I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know going really mad I thought oh my god that's really really sad cos she's I think come out strong yet she's saying that</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0541">really?</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0540">you will find out you know if you if you catch up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I think she must have gone through such hell she must have such hell</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0541">but what hell?</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0540">you know</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1344" who="S0540" trans="overlap">she had to give birth you know when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't around remember when we went to see her?</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0541">but he turned up for the birth didn't he?</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0540">in a in a extremely awkward kind of you know er it er <pause dur="short"/> er <unclear/> cos you know he didn't know er his sister found out about it on Facebook etcetera etcetera you know it just goes basically you know everything was falling apart and she was just really really you know <pause dur="short"/> off basically because of that and now I think it she's fine I mean I have really been having a very hard time you know besides you know my work and everything you know <vocal desc="sigh"/> but I think we are here to just go through this and come out stronger</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0541">I dunno I'm looking forward to kind of closing the door on twenty fifteen</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1349" who="S0541">it's been like annus horribulis it really has</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0540">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1351" who="S0541">it has like it's been a really bad year but anyway</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0540">you will survive <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because you already have</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0541">yeah it's just that kind of like really basic component of kind of making a living which is alluding me at the moment</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0540">yes</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0541">it's kind of quite worrying</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0540">oh but I think I mean I'm so you know the you're cos you're keeping at it you just you're doing so well</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0541">I didn't today I just couldn't do anything I'm so demoralised I just you know</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0541">I was just really demoralised that</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0540" trans="overlap">but I have those days when I was writing the thesis you know for you know for <trunc>th</trunc> one day I just so so proactive and then trying just you know not really not making any difference to it so it's</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0540">but eventually the deadline comes you know you've got to do it you know <pause dur="short"/> and somehow er the bad days you know <pause dur="short"/> they're terrible but good days are great and <pause dur="short"/> I managed to pull it off but oh but I do think you know we all need help you know had a lot of er support for proofreading and <pause dur="short"/> think in these difficult time we all just need help <pause dur="short"/> and support</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0541">that's true</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0540">and just that just makes it you know just that's how we survive <pause dur="short"/> in a way and I can tell maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was really you know getting support from the church</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0541">mm</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0540">probably yeah</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0541" trans="overlap">mm because I think that's how she survived yeah and god cos she yeah I think she she was looking after some <unclear/> some you know ladies with with single mothers mm mm</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0540" trans="overlap">okay so how's his hotel thing going? was it good?</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I think it's good yes</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0540">that's good</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0541">yeah I mean you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean <pause dur="long"/> I mean <unclear/> you know <trunc>de</trunc>denouncing his faith now he's he's not Christian anymore <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1372" who="S0540">he's said that?</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0541">yeah</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0540">well you know</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0541" trans="overlap">in in front of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and they all fine about it nowadays</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0540">yeah you've gotta be honest</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1378" who="S0540">can't live a lie</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0541">that is so but you know that's how it is yeah</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0540" trans="overlap">he was just pretending all along</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I don't know how it is how it is</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0540" trans="overlap">he was just pretending all along oh my god</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0541" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0540">I knew it all along</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0540">well you know</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0541">I I guess he tried you know and I said he's still you know <unclear>baby</unclear> Christian he's</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it's not for everybody</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0541">but he's still a <unclear>baby</unclear> Christian you know he's baptised you know he said the Lord's Prayer he's still a Christian he just hasn't grown <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has grown so much</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0540">maybe he's growing in another way</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1392" who="S0540">in a financial way <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1393" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1394" who="S0540">or in a business way</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0541">yeah yeah so that's how it works <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1396" who="S0540" trans="overlap">you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1397" who="S0541">oh</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0540">yeah I think he's more</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0540" trans="overlap">kind of a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1401" who="S0541" trans="overlap">he realised that's where <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's how he feels very <unclear/></u>
<u n="1402" who="S0540"><unclear>he's through to the universe</unclear> er</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I I think in a way I think in a way erm yeah he had to be honest maybe he you know maybe</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0540" trans="overlap">he can't carry on for a whole lifetime pretending</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0541">but er you know that's the way you know it's a good beginning that is and he'll probably you know he wouldn't be able to ignore it because you know he's part of the you know he's part of it even if he did you know denounces it I mean you know it <unclear>through his wife</unclear> he is you know saved lucky anyway <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0540">is that the time?</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0541"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1408" who="S0540">I need to go actually</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0540" trans="overlap">because I erm I have a I have to get up early</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0541">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0540">I have a research I'm doing a research group tomorrow</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0541">oh yes?</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0540">yeah I'm maximising all my avenues of passive income I'm not actually managing to generate any income from work but I'm doing erm I've joined like a research thing so I have to go and do a research session tomorrow morning</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0541">oh how</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it's only an hour</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0541">how exciting</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0540">it's only an hour in <anon type="place"/> but it starts at eight forty so</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0541"><vocal desc="gasp"/> my god</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I need to get up at six six forty-five and get down there</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0541" trans="overlap">yeah you have to go oh yeah</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0540" trans="overlap">it's very easy I'm just doing something on arts and culture so</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh okay you are you know you have a natural flair</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0540">mm I'm just being like a little research person and I just ask questions like asking people who do arts and culture so</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0541"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1426" who="S0540">just a little thing</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0541">yeah I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1428" who="S0540" trans="overlap">fifty pounds an hour <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1429" who="S0541">you must be joking</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0540">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1431" who="S0541"><vocal desc="gasp"/> they do like lots of for all this stuff all this market research</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0540">oh maybe I should do it</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0541">I'll send you the link</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0540" trans="overlap">in hard time I was gonna do it's</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0541">well you'll only it's only it's a bit random erm but they send you an email about what they're looking into and then you fill out like a</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0540">yeah I actually it's probably not for me because I'm not very language person</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0541">it's not language though</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0541">it's just a random research thing</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0540">oh I see</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0541">anyway so I have to do that</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah but I mean I er yes I I need to you know because I can actually work part time as a student so now I have some time on hand I should</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0541" trans="overlap">there are loads of university kind of er which unfortunately I can't do cos I'm not a student but erm there are generally loads and loads of kind of positions</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0540">yeah</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0541" trans="overlap">temporary and</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0540">I yeah I'm actually turning to some scientist I mean because now I've got involved this the <anon type="place"/> museum thing I just wonder if I could be paid for you know doing some preparation I dunno now I'm involved as an artist so they must think that you know I got a chance to exhibit in the <anon type="place"/> museum so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1447" who="S0541">exciting what day is it?</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0540">the fifteenth</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0541">what day though? is it a weekend or a week?</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0540">no no</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0541" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0540">a Tuesday I think it's a Tuesday yeah</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0541" trans="overlap">why is it only a day?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0540">I dunno it's just very temporary it's nothing major probably the one section of the museum it's nothing major</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0541">mm mm</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0540" trans="overlap">right just the one</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0541">exciting if you had an Instagram account you could do loads of pictures of it and put them up there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1458" who="S0540">I should really get social media savvy but I it's just so</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0541" trans="overlap">no it's so boring who can be bothered?</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I know I mean you know I <trunc>kee</trunc> I only realised that there are celebrities from Youtube and Instagram I didn't know</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0541">oh yeah it's a big <trunc>thi</trunc> it's a whole parallel universe</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I I did not know yeah</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0541">of people who don't do anything apart from feed their social media</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0541" trans="overlap">all day that's so boring if I see any other picture of somebody with like <trunc>h</trunc> there are so many of these photos have you seen them?</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0540">mm</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0541">they are always of someone with like in their underwear you know kind of like sucking in there and going and they're all taking a picture of it's so I can't bear to look at it anymore</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1469" who="S0541">men and women</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0540">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0541" trans="overlap">just who are these people? just</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0540" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0541" trans="overlap">it's kind of empty</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I think it's it's it's not our generations definitely</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0541">it's a millennial thing</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0540">yeah it's really</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0541" trans="overlap">but it's so dreadful like all these</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0540" trans="overlap">I'm so glad</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0541" trans="overlap">people doing this</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0540">I'm so glad I'm not that generation</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0541" trans="overlap">oh god they're so vapid</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0540">but they do look good like</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0541">well everybody looks good when they're young</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1485" who="S0541">know what I mean? <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's only when you get old that you look shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1486" who="S0540"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1487" who="S0541">you know?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0540">oh I see</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0541" trans="overlap">I mean they're</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
