<text id="S7S7">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:45:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>The “Axis of Evil”, Middle East, Music, Easter, shops</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking at home</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, apologizing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">never get them off</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">that's my fault</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">is it on?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">yeah I think I'd</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115">just not pressed it <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit funny actually cos it's the sort of thing that you might humorously leave it on when you didn't realize and uh</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">well I might've done</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">and uh take it  take it  with you everywhere and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">I'm sorry about that <pause dur="short"/> it's my</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">no that's that's fine uh</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I just saw it blinking out the corner of me eye and I was like whoops</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah so it's like I'm gonna  I'm gonna  find some stuff about uh about Easter but uh first of all I was just going through the Axis Of Evil and uh uh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">we found out that uh I found out that there wasn't just three in the Axis Of Evil</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">ah I haven't heard this song for ages</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115">well the the <trunc>f</trunc> original Axis Of Evil was three but there actually were Beyond The Axis Of Evil that's another three and there was <trunc>out</trunc> Outposts of Tyranny um</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's like an it's <pause dur="short"/> oh my goodness</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115">and uh so they <trunc>orig</trunc></u>
<u n="18" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like Yemen? Was Yemen an outpost of?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no it's not  it's not  part of the nine <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037">I'm surprised</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the Axis Of  The Axis Of  Evil described by George Bush was Iran Iraq and North Korea uh <pause dur="short"/> this article's placed Iraq</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but Iran haven't done anything <pause dur="short"/> what's Iran done?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's placed <trunc>I</trunc> Iraq first <pause dur="short"/> north Korea second and Iran third like they're all in order like</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037">what's Iran done though?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">uh it's it annoys Israel a lot by by funding um groups like Hezbollah which attacks Israel</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">um it uh it <trunc>defe</trunc> the the main the official excuse is that it uh <pause dur="short"/> the the the official excuse that the government uses is that it's uh it's developing nuclear weapons</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037">but they don't know that though surely?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and uh it has some nuclear facilities in there I think it <trunc>h</trunc> already has some um <pause dur="short"/> it already  it already  has nuclear power I think</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it but it's uh you know people like America and Israel were saying that it was gonna develop nuclear nuclear weapons but I personally don't think even if it had them it would use them uh other than as a  as a as a  a <trunc>d</trunc> a deterrent sort of thing</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037" trans="overlap">bombs? Yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115">um so personally no I I'm not a</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but you can't tell other people</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">I'm quite anti-war so I'm not in favour of</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you can't tell other people not to have nuclear weapons if you have nuclear weapons like that's just obvious</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">well yeah I mean obviously America has a very large number of nuclear weapons uh Isreal has a lot of nuclear weapons <pause dur="short"/> uh Pakistan has a <trunc>n</trunc> has some nuclear weapons <pause dur="short"/> india has as well I mean so there's there's quite a few of them in the  in the  sort of Middle-Eastern area</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">they have them I mean but <trunc>f</trunc> if you look at Iran you've gotta understand it's uh it's geography actually</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115">it's a very big country <pause dur="short"/> it's actually bigger than um <pause dur="short"/> I think it's bigger then England France and Italy combined</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">really?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">and and its landmass is very large</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">I never really thought about</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's it's yeah cos you've gotta look at it geostrategically like um</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">it's a  it's a  strategically quite an important place <pause dur="short"/> um it it's</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">I just wish it wasn't so war-torn and like <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously Iran's not</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that that that area's in a terrible mess isn't it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I mean the area I mean <pause dur="short"/> it would be so nice to go there there's so much stuff there</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">well it's it's it's one of the world's oldest continuously inhabited areas isn't it it's part of the cradle of civilization</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> gulf of the cradle of <pause dur="short"/> that's right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">crescent <pause dur="short"/> whatever it is</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">crescent that's what I was trying to say</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> sounds like a good version of the uh the Axis Of Evil it they should've it should've been like <pause dur="short"/> they could have used the word crescent as well because has a really islamophobia in it as well <pause dur="short"/> so it could be like the the crescent of sin or something or</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115">the uh the crescent of of destruction or something</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">no I like the crescent of destruction</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> so yeah if you <pause dur="short"/> iran is a massive country and also it's got quite a big economy which is forecast to grow <pause dur="short"/> like a lot of people reckon that it's gonna become uh one of the bigger new economies like uh bit like Turkey and Mexico and stuff</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115">um that area's really in a big problem with tribal conflict and uh opium in Afghanistan um</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115"><trunc>I</trunc> areas like that where there's that much sort of tribal problems tend to have dictators in them who who um like Saddam Hussain</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">um Assad from Syria <pause dur="short"/> uh Syria instead were are in the Beyond The Axis Of Evil trio alongside Cuba and Libya</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's like the  that's like the  Championship <pause dur="short"/> not the Premier League</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115" trans="overlap">this is like the Championship <pause dur="short"/> the Championship is Cuba Libya and Syria <pause dur="short"/> uh obviously Libya's now gonna be changed uh it's got a different flag and everything uh <pause dur="short"/> then and the the Division One was uh Third Third Division</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115">was Outposts of Tyranny</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">outposts of Tyranny that sounds like a cocktail</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">that's um <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to have it uh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What would be in a outpost of tyranny</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's it's <trunc>Belaru</trunc> <trunc>Belaru</trunc> it's it's it's one part Belarus two parts Zimbabwe and three parts uh Myanmar or Burma <pause dur="short"/> um so um they're</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">maybe we should put something on that's a bit more like us</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">what what's wrong with? This is Rui Da Silva</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">touch Me from the album Touch Me</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you know what it's <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> touch me in the morning that one <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Last thing at night <pause dur="short"/> d'you know it?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">it's from like when I was at school</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> um so</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">it reminds us of like going to like Chambers it's this nightclub in Sunderland</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">like they just actively encouraged underaged people to go in <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously anyone who could get in anywhere else wouldn't go there cos it was horrible</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">there's some horrible places in Sunderland aren't there?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and they used to sell <pause dur="short"/> they <trunc>us</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> they used to sell bottles of Red Pig</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">mind you</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">this drink called Red Pig for seventy P</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">oh and it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> they just got everywhere <pause dur="short"/> then there'd just be like purple splats of vomit outside on the pavement like</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">oh right uh yeah I mean well well I think I suppose that that's just something that that that you know kids do isn't it though they they go through that that phase you know maybe when they're at college or something and they uh they just sort of go round you know <trunc>go</trunc> going mad and discovering uh discovering alcohol and um uh</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">and sort of but they're throwing up because <trunc>th</trunc> because the stomachs like aren't used to the alcohol so they just throw up everything</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but like all of the <pause dur="short"/> all of the boys used to have like loads of <trunc>a</trunc> horrible aftershave on and like</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">those Ben Sherman shirts and</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well that's part of the whole like as as you get from watching Inbetweeners isn't it?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">and like I would go out full-on dressed up not like now when I just wander down the pub in whatever I happen to be wearing you know</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah we we we're quite sort of casual</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037" trans="overlap">cardigans and <trunc>trainer</trunc> little shoes and that</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">how did we get from Axis Of Evil to uh to drinks?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037" trans="overlap">sorry I just  I just  asked about</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no yeah it was cocktails you said  you said  Axis Of Evil? That reminds me of a cocktail</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">no I said it should be a cocktail <pause dur="short"/> and then no then I was talking about this</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115" trans="overlap">outposts of Tyranny</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">I'll turn it <pause dur="short"/> d'you want us to put like Kerrang on or something?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115">um whatever you want</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or should we just leave it? No we're alright we'll just leave it <pause dur="short"/> it's like a Saturday party</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well uh yeah um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah so about so about so Iran I was saying like it's really mountainous and apparently although a lot of people are talking about invading it a lot of American uh hawkish people</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115">uh are talking about invading it uh</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh excuse me</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">apparently it's it's not um</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">invadable?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">it's not a place that you could feasibly conquer and hold um you just couldn't couldn't hold it because of the  because of the  mountainousness it was it's really difficult to invade um only a few people have successfully conquered Iran I think</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh and it <trunc>w</trunc> to hold it you you wouldn't really be able to to um to hold it because there'd just be too many people who'd come come out from the mountains and and</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah tribes</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">yeah I think uh it's similar to Afghanistan and I think <trunc>i</trunc> Afghanistan has pretty much demonstrated the problems of of fighting in that tribal mountainous environment like uh</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">you you really don't have the <trunc>popul</trunc> you don't have the can't please the people in the  in the in the  <trunc>countrys</trunc> in the  in the  mountains</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">you might be able to please the city people in Kabul but you can't uh can't you can't tame the uh the tribes very easily</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">they just just don't like um</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you can't reach them can you I mean?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">yeah it's very <trunc>d</trunc> it's a very difficult environment to fight in I mean  I mean  the all the sort of um the militias that are going around and</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> D'you remember this one?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> 9pm Till I Come</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know it goes <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">is it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">it's like a different remix of that though isn't it?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">it's like from nineteen ninety-five or something</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">oh right well I think this is a different remix isn't it? What does that say? Viva <pause dur="short"/> channel Viva <pause dur="short"/> freddie</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">listen</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> feddie Le Grand</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">this really reminds us it's it's Freddie Le Grand who apparently</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">it says Feddie in this though</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">yeah Feddie that's what I mean</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">Feddie Le Grand's top fifty dance number ones</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's a Dutch  he's a Dutch  dance DJ <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">well that's that's just <pause dur="short"/> I can imagine him sort of uh <pause dur="short"/> holland is really the centre of Europop I suppose isn't it?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">I dunno if this really classifies as Europop but yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no yeah yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">um but yes I agree</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">euro Euro club</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">but uh</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">you've been to a Euro club haven't you in Switzerland?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">I have been to a Euro club it was very unusual</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">oh really? Well uh I I I feel in some ways perhaps I'm too old but I would like to go to a Euro club and uh</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037" trans="overlap">would you? With a white suit?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah is it  is it is it  it hasn't died has it?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">no no <pause dur="short"/> ooh <pause dur="short"/> no it's fine <pause dur="short"/> and wear like a white suit?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah so that <pause dur="short"/> we don't wanna be going on for like half an hour and find that that's</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well we'd just be talking anyway let's be honest</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">yeah I mean uh you know May as well just yeah <pause dur="short"/> what were you saying a white suit? Were a lot of <trunc>peop</trunc> a lot of people wearing white suits were there?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">there were a number of people in like a white like jeans and like a white jacket</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">ah like Miami Vice sort of style?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">exactly like Miami Vice sort of style</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">kinda that's just like fresh off  fresh off  the yacht</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037" trans="overlap">in fact that sums up that sums it up very well</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115">come off the yacht <pause dur="short"/> were you in a place near a lake that might've had like yachts on it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">um actually yes I mean it was in Austria so it was very near Lake Constance you know</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">oh right so you actually went across the border?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037">well it was just like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">went to the club <trunc>l</trunc> in a different country and then drove back?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">that's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> to go clubbing in another country and then come back</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">yeah but it wasn't really it was like it's like us just going down the bottom of the road like</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">did he drive</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">you back?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">that's a bit strange though <pause dur="short"/> it feels weird going to a club and then sort of driving home across the border on the way back</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I thought that as well <pause dur="short"/> everyone did <pause dur="short"/> the club was in the middle of nowhere</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">but like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">it was like off a junction off a motorway</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">but</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037">like you couldn't get there unless you'd driven</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">can you not even you can't even have like more than one drink or something?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">no no</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">I don't think I could do that sort of thing personally</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">well I did I had more drinks <pause dur="short"/> obviously</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">have to get a taxi but like through through through the Alps</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no no you could like <pause dur="short"/> it was yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> exactly</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">alpine Taxis</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ski home or something <pause dur="short"/> no it was uh</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">just walk home</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">no it wasn't next to anything <pause dur="short"/> it literally was like on a industrial estate</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">it would be a great place to uh to go I think we'd have to go to Austria some time</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">yeah well I mean I didn't really see very much of it I only saw that tiny like tiny bottom corner like that</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">I remember my school saying that they they had their skiing trips to Austria cos they were the friendliest of the uh the nations that uh yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> skiing countries? Well there's a lot of newer ones though isn't there like you can ski in Bulgaria and stuff now</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">has it gone I think of um as I was saying about Austria and um Austria and Czech Republic is that  is that  you've gotta think of them kind of as Southeast Germany yeah like</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Croatia <pause dur="short"/> uh Czech Republic and stuff</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">like they are they really are kind of parts of Germany like</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">there were loads of German people in in those you know Course Germany wasn't originally like one single country was it?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">look Feddie whoever he is</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">but yeah there were loads of German people in there in <trunc>B</trunc> in Bohemia and places</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh this is a good one</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">oh yeah this is Bonkers uh by</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">this reminds me of when we first moved into our flat in Lancaster</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">yeah I remember you had I know I originally started listening to it actually uh even earlier than that before like it before it was released I think because uh <pause dur="short"/> uh so it was on YouTube but I wasn't listening to uh <pause dur="short"/>Uh I searched for him on YouTube um for some reason <pause dur="short"/> I think it was because I heard I found out that there was this type of music that I'd never heard of that was called grime and uh</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah it was cos we went to that thing in Furness</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">I'd never heard of Grime and then there was all sorts of different types like grimecore uh</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's because we went to that thing in Furness d'you remember?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">yeah yeah it was like a drum and bass party <pause dur="short"/> I really didn't know much about</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and grime grime party</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">so grime is basically a cross between rap and uh rap and drum and bass I suppose <pause dur="short"/> it's like a London urban sort of thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mr Rascal <pause dur="short"/> that always reminds me of that</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115" trans="overlap">this this this isn't grime though this is  this is  really kind of poppy dance isn't it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">it reminds me of that like <trunc>re</trunc> Jeremy Paxman interview</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">oh yeah when he interviewed yeah Jeremy Paxman interviewed Dizzee Rascal and and addressed him as Mr Rascal which was uh extremely funny I thought uh but it was quite a nice interview I mean I think it went <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>Di</trunc> Dizzee wasn't uh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">being too naughty?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">like wasn't that offended by the fact that Paxman was maybe talking down to him <pause dur="short"/> but yeah addressing him as Mister I mean that it's just it's very funny <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> mean this reminds me of the summer and uh sort of</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> quite good effect you've got like a three hundred and sixty degree camera thing going on there <pause dur="short"/> one of those cameras that's sort of like a total panorama</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah I like this bit <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> right so I was what I was doing about uh supposed to be about Easter wasn't it?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">I love those uh Mini Eggs <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'll buy some at the shop</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>c</trunc> Cadbury's uh Mini Eggs are they're sort of shiny on the outside chocolatey on the inside</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well the Aldi ones are um the Aldi ones are like half-price</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I've got  I've got  a <trunc>pic</trunc> gone to Wikipedia page of Easter and uh perhaps unsurprisingly there's a picture of Jesus uh he's also holding holding a stick with a flag and then like a red cross on it that looks a bit like an England flag <pause dur="short"/> it's supposed to be depicting his resurrection</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">Jesee Cresee?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">yeah so he's he's got robes on</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">uh the ones I think he was buried in that sort of shroud he's got like a big golden globe around his head</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">where's the shroud of Turin has he cast that aside? Is it on the picture?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he's he's wearing it he's wearing like a shroudy</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's wearing it? No but a shroud's like a bag isn't it like is it not the the cloth that they're wrapped in?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well he's he's he's wearing a cloth yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">ah right yes he is <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">what else has he got on his? There'll be loads of symbolism won't there in that?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">yeah there's a  there's a  sort of angel with wings uh holding um what looks like uh a palm branch</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">thought you were gonna say a pie there <pause dur="short"/> that'd be really good</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">no they they didn't really have pies in uh</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh Palm Sunday what's that about in it?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">ah well all all all of the time I've just uh <pause dur="short"/> it's uh it's coming up obviously the eighth of April for us but for the Eastern Church it will be the fifteenth the the Sunday after</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> they say religious services um it it they have you have like a festival family meals <pause dur="short"/> family meals uh Easter egg hunts and gift giving <pause dur="short"/> um and you're supposed to have like all-night vigils and sunrise services</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know I saw on that leaflet that came through the door from the church that there's like a five AM thing <pause dur="short"/> lighting the Easter fire or something</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>he</trunc> here's something that I was interested in it's the sort of comparative religions uh <pause dur="short"/> it's related to Passover</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">it's considered the uh Christian equivalent of Passover <pause dur="short"/> it's also related to a whole load of other stuff uh including Septuagesima Sexagesima <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>Septu</trunc> Septuagesima and another one called Sexagemina and then one called Quinquagesima</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">what what are these gesima ones?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um Shrove Tuesday Ash Wednesday Clean Monday Lent Great Lent</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">greater Lent?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">there's a Great Lent as well as the ordinary Lent</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">ah it's obviously better than normal Lent</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">what's <pause dur="short"/> it's like I can see they're counting quinque five sexa septua that's seven</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> ow <pause dur="short"/> ah me little toe's hurting that I've bashed</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so if I look at Quinquegesima is um the Sunday before Ash Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> um also called Shrove Sunday <pause dur="short"/> uh and then <trunc>S</trunc> Sexagesima is like the um the second Sunday before Ash Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> oh right fair enough</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037">so when's Ash Wednesday?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well simply simply put it's after Pancake Day isn't it?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">alright so we've had it</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">lent follows doesn't it and then Lent ends um at Easter doesn't it?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">easter Sunday?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115">Great Lent is um and just to clear up we've got Palm Sunday so if Lent ends at Palm Sunday or if Lent ends at Easter</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's what's the difference?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">well between what?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">are they not the same thing?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115">no Palm Sunday's the Sunday before</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">easter Sunday</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">ah right <pause dur="short"/> this Sunday tomorrow?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah so tomorrow will be  will be  Palm Sunday</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">uh it's the day it commemorates when Jesus uh rode in rode into Jerusalem on a donkey which didn't have a cross shaved in its back</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what went down the palm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> yes it did</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115">uh like with uh</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">what are the palms about then?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he got he rides in he rides into Jerusalem on a donkey</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah do they put it down on his feet cos he's tired?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they put palm palms um to welcome him in <pause dur="short"/> they put palms and their clothes on the ground for him to for his donkey to walk over</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">why is the donkey tired?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">I think it's just a sign of respect <pause dur="short"/> like like a path like a bit like a red carpet</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">ah <trunc>ro</trunc> red carpet yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">hold on um I'll I'll read that cos I might be totally wrong but uh <pause dur="short"/> great Lent <pause dur="short"/> ooh there's a picture of a Czech Republic church there</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037">which one? Peter and Paul?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's just inside <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> uh Great Lent or the Great Fast is the most important fasting season in the church year in Eastern Christianity <pause dur="short"/> they prey as Christians for the greatest feast of the church year which is Pascha <pause dur="short"/> easter <pause dur="short"/> it's similar to the Western Lent <pause dur="short"/> I think Great Lent is merely an Eastern version of</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">I see</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">our Lent <pause dur="short"/> western Lent</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">but better <pause dur="short"/><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> they have some differences of time in um um <pause dur="short"/> right so yeah Lent I think it starts on Ash Wednesday doesn't it?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh Lent is called Quadragesima meaning fortieth <pause dur="short"/> uh is uh it's about six weeks leading up to Easter <pause dur="short"/> runs from Ash Wednesday to Maundy Thursday</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">aha</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">in um Western most Western uh denominations <pause dur="short"/> or to Easter Eve which presumably is Easter Saturday <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> it's a penitential preparation <pause dur="short"/> well it's uh <pause dur="short"/> okay so you've got  you've got  Shrove Tuesday Ash Wednesday Lent Maundy Thursday</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">leading up to um</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">what does it say about?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115" trans="overlap">easter <pause dur="short"/> so what I was interested in was the the comparative religion of it <pause dur="short"/> oh I like this one</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">it's a bit stupid <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">easter comes from</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">maybe we should turn it down a bit</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">I think it's alright <pause dur="short"/> uh Jesus rose from the dead obviously</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="306" who="S0115">some say he resurrected in AD twenty-six <pause dur="short"/> some say AD thirty-six <pause dur="short"/> and some say in-between</u>
<u n="307" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hang on <pause dur="short"/> jesus?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0037">I thought it was the next day</u>
<u n="310" who="S0115">no AD <trunc>thir</trunc> twenty-six the year <pause dur="short"/> talking about the year that it happened</u>
<u n="311" who="S0037" trans="overlap">how old he was you mean?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0115">I'm talking about what year it was supposed to have happened</u>
<u n="313" who="S0037">like how old he is?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0115">well not not his age but the the year it occurred he</u>
<u n="315" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but it is if we're starting from BC</u>
<u n="316" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah but you see if they say  if they say  twenty-six then</u>
<u n="317" who="S0037">that means he's twenty-six?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0115">I don't know if it does I</u>
<u n="319" who="S0037">well what else can it mean?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0115">not sure <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> you're assuming that he was definitely born in AD?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0037">well that's</u>
<u n="322" who="S0115">but not every church maybe believes that he was born in what we call in AD zero you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0037">well I don't even believe he was born full-stop so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0115" trans="overlap">aD <pause dur="short"/> we we might say like there was no year zero was there but? It was like it went from B <trunc>s</trunc> one BC to one AD and then the AD the BC AD changeover as uh Eddie Izzard called it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0115">but <trunc>w</trunc> obviously that was written <trunc>behi</trunc> you know after the fact wasn't it so?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> so uh well anyway um <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> the last week of Lent is Holy Week <pause dur="short"/> that's the one <pause dur="short"/> that's the week that we're gonna get next week <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> it's followed by a fifty-day period called Easter Tide</u>
<u n="329" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0115">ending with Pentecost Sunday <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> obviously it moves <pause dur="short"/> first Council of Nicaea three twenty-five established it as being the first Sunday after the full moon</u>
<u n="331" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="332" who="S0115">following the Northern</u>
<u n="333" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is that why Easter changes then?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0115" trans="overlap">following the Northern Hemisphere's vernal equinox which is twenty-first of March</u>
<u n="335" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's that's why Easter changes its day then?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0115">yeah it's the first Sunday after the full moon following the equinox which is the twenty-first of March</u>
<u n="337" who="S0037" trans="overlap">clocks forward yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="339" who="S0037"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0115">yeah so it it was actually twentieth of March this year <pause dur="short"/> and at precisely five fourteen AM uh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0037">right <pause dur="short"/> think I was asleep <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="343" who="S0037">nevermind</u>
<u n="344" who="S0115">it's the  it's the  tilt of the Earth's access is inclined</u>
<u n="345" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you think I've made that wide enough?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0115">it's when we're aligned like we're neither tilting towards or away from the Sun we're like perfectly</u>
<u n="347" who="S0037">facing it?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0115">um level</u>
<u n="349" who="S0037">D'you think these are gonna look stupid?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0115">it's possibly bigger than I thought <pause dur="short"/> uh I thought you were just <trunc>t</trunc> tying a piece of string with some holes in the side</u>
<u n="351" who="S0037">no it's a pot warmer</u>
<u n="352" who="S0115">ah um</u>
<u n="353" who="S0037">it's a pot warmer and then it has a loop at the top <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like that</u>
<u n="354" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like I'd have thought like you'd probably just drill a couple of holes in the side of the pot and then tie a string and hang that from a hook</u>
<u n="355" who="S0037">but where's the bonniness in that?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0115">Bonny?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0037">where's the beauty in that?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0115">yeah but like it's just it's a <trunc>pl</trunc> it's a functional plant man</u>
<u n="359" who="S0037">no no no</u>
<u n="360" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it isn't beauty</u>
<u n="361" who="S0037">but you've gotta make things look</u>
<u n="362" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um I'm I'm a bit functional you know?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0037">well yeah I'm about function too but it may as well <pause dur="short"/> if you've just got like a crappy pot and you just drill a hole in and tie a twine round that's no fun like it just looks like</u>
<u n="364" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="365" who="S0037">there's gotta be something about making it look nice <pause dur="short"/> isn't there? Or are you not bothered?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0115" trans="overlap">fair enough</u>
<u n="367" who="S0037">ah no but I <trunc>rememb</trunc> <trunc>appea</trunc></u>
<u n="368" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh because if that's what you <trunc>l</trunc> you know it's a hobby isn't it so?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0037" trans="overlap">appearances aren't important</u>
<u n="370" who="S0115">oh yeah I said that didn't I?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> um <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="372" who="S0115" trans="overlap">particularly when choosing girlfriends</u>
<u n="373" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but it's at least <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> but at least it's um</u>
<u n="374" who="S0115">appearances don't <pause dur="short"/> no I didn't say that you you should pay um zero <trunc>a</trunc> attention to appearance I was just saying that like you can't go solely on <trunc>appea</trunc> you got if you go only on appearance then you you you're not gonna be happy are you so?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I'm only <trunc>t</trunc> I'm only teasing you</u>
<u n="376" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you  if you  go only on appearance then you you you're not gonna be happy are you so? Like</u>
<u n="377" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you're an idiot yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> I'm only teasing you <pause dur="short"/> what I'm saying is</u>
<u n="378" who="S0115" trans="overlap">unless unless unless they're really rich and you just go for money and so that's uh slightly different but then once again that's not appearance that's you've gotta put something you know like money or you know</u>
<u n="379" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0115">family ties or uh</u>
<u n="381" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Money's a <trunc>t</trunc> bad one</u>
<u n="382" who="S0115">some some other factor like appearance on on its own is is not a great</u>
<u n="383" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="384" who="S0115">although it does work I suppose it does work for some people like some people they might think yeah I'm gonna go with this  with this  good person and I'm gonna get children</u>
<u n="385" who="S0037">yeah but that's like</u>
<u n="386" who="S0115">you know he's got a  he's got a  great pair of eyebrows</u>
<u n="387" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0115">my children when they're born they're gonna have those black eyebrows <pause dur="short"/> soon as they're  soon as they're  born they're gonna have the same black eyebrows</u>
<u n="389" who="S0037">but the thing is</u>
<u n="390" who="S0115">it's gonna be  it's gonna be  great</u>
<u n="391" who="S0037">people who do that are stupid aren't they?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0115">well uh I mean you know there's a always a there's there's always an element of uh</u>
<u n="393" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well of course they are you've gotta live your whole <trunc>l</trunc> uh whole life like you've gotta live your own life and why would you? It just seems weird to me <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> no I was only winding you up</u>
<u n="394" who="S0115" trans="overlap">some people just like you know just like um <pause dur="short"/> remember if you think about all these like donor you know sperm donors and that like if you go round looking for a <pause dur="short"/> if you  if you  want to to to um to take you know from a  from a  donor</u>
<u n="395" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Will you do it? Be a sperm donor?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so because I think uh um <pause dur="short"/> I think I I um I like you you know um I'm a bit sort of I don't <trunc>th</trunc> know if I'm good enough but uh</u>
<u n="397" who="S0037">ah don't be silly</u>
<u n="398" who="S0115">that's just</u>
<u n="399" who="S0037">I think it's a bit <trunc>w</trunc> of a weird thing but I think it's a good thing that people do it I mean if they want to but</u>
<u n="400" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no I think it's it's it's great I mean if if people want to but but yeah if you look at the way that that sort of culture works I mean it is very appearance and also mental um features as well isn't it? Like they they do the the the the fact of the matter is it's there are a lot of genetic factors in in life aren't there so?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh you mean choosing a sperm donor? Yeah but also you just don't know what which ones are gonna be expressed like it's all very well saying I want someone who's tall dark and handsome and and <trunc>s</trunc> brain surgeon and a triathlete <pause dur="short"/> but equally they could have genes for like stupidness or like laziness or <pause dur="short"/> you just don't know <pause dur="short"/> not all the ones that they have are will be expressed</u>
<u n="402" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it it at the  at the  moment it's very hard to predict isn't it? Um</u>
<u n="403" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well the</u>
<u n="404" who="S0115">success of uh <pause dur="short"/> you know it's very hard to <trunc>pr</trunc> to predict that you know if someone has <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> if you have a successful father or mother you know it really doesn't  it really doesn't  guarantee that you'll be successful but neither is it a guarantee <pause dur="short"/> I think if you have good looking parents I mean even then it's still not totally guaranteed that that they way that their jeans will merge together will create a good looking child</u>
<u n="405" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I had a friend when I played netball called Hayley who was really like she was a model you know like stupidly good looking</u>
<u n="406" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0037">and her mom and dad were both like funny looking people <pause dur="short"/> her dad looked like Max from</u>
<u n="408" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah you're referring to the the Nigella Lawson phenomenon?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> her dad looked like Max from Guess Who <pause dur="short"/> you know Guess Who?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0115">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> No I don't know all the characters of Guess Who</u>
<u n="411" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> max from Guess Who had like a black <trunc>s</trunc> black sort of bushy hair and a big massive bush moustache he looked a bit Italian</u>
<u n="412" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0037">D'you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0115">well I can imagine like sort of um thinking of Mario from Super Mario</u>
<u n="415" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you? A a bit like that style <pause dur="short"/> so her dad looked like that and her mam looked a bit weasley <pause dur="short"/> like a weasel <pause dur="short"/> but she was  she was  like a model this girl</u>
<u n="416" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> d'you d'you? What what precise features? Small nose? Whiskers?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah small and sort of ferrety <pause dur="short"/> she had like big like fluffy hair that</u>
<u n="418" who="S0115">like very very tilted back forehead</u>
<u n="419" who="S0037">like pointy sort of she was a bit pointy in the face <pause dur="short"/> but this girl was like</u>
<u n="420" who="S0115">big big upper lip?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0037">um don't know</u>
<u n="422" who="S0115">tiny chin yeah?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0037">I can't exactly remember it was a long time ago</u>
<u n="424" who="S0115">with whiskers coming out of her cheeks?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no she didn't have whiskers <pause dur="short"/> that's not what I mean by ferrety</u>
<u n="426" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> upturned but very small nose uh?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0037">what? Fir? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="429" who="S0037">silly</u>
<u n="430" who="S0115">hold on <pause dur="short"/> so where was I on this? Um</u>
<u n="431" who="S0037">I sort of like can't remember what it was like when before we had a smartphone like</u>
<u n="432" who="S0115">ecclesiastically they reckon March twenty-first is the equinox <pause dur="short"/> even though astronomically speaking it's actually the twentieth of March <pause dur="short"/> and the full moon isn't necessarily the correct date either <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="433" who="S0115">uh but it Easter varies between uh March twenty-second</u>
<u n="434" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0115">uh it can't be on March twenty-first cos it has to be the first it has to be Sunday after</u>
<u n="436" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0115">the full</u>
<u n="438" who="S0037">so you gonna get your mam to come over on her birthday?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it's gonna be it has to be <trunc>S</trunc> it has to be Sunday after a full moon following the equinox <pause dur="short"/> I guess that means it's impossible for it to occur on the twenty-first it has to occur at least the twenty-second <pause dur="short"/> till could be as late as uh April twenty-fifth um</u>
<u n="440" who="S0037">is your mam gonna come on her birthday? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0115">but in the Eastern Church <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah maybe uh we'll have to get in touch um get in touch and um</u>
<u n="442" who="S0037">I don't mind you know she can come whenever</u>
<u n="443" who="S0115">but uh we'll do some more recordings with them <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="444" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0115">could record them again</u>
<u n="446" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> eastern Christianity puts a slightly different date um so they they go between April the fifth and May the eighth</u>
<u n="448" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> it's linked to Passover this is quite interesting uh <pause dur="short"/> while much of the symbolism as well as its calendar position</u>
<u n="450" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0115">uh a lot of them have similar words to Passover in these <unclear/> languages uh <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="452" who="S0037">I really like the Cadbury's Creme Eggs as well like <pause dur="short"/> and I think I still would like a really big one of those just filled with all that goo</u>
<u n="453" who="S0115">you what? A big? A massive? A giant Creme Egg?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0037">the size of my face <pause dur="short"/> in fact of my face <pause dur="short"/> like chocolate moulded to it so it looked like my face <pause dur="short"/> and then when you <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="455" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that really would be quite bit <pause dur="short"/> that would be big</u>
<u n="456" who="S0037">and then when you cracked it <trunc>op</trunc> head open and you bit like the ear off like it would just be Cadbury's Creme Egg insides</u>
<u n="457" who="S0115">would you want it to look like your face then?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0037">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0115">I find that a bit disturbing</u>
<u n="460" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'd get <pause dur="short"/> I'd get a um</u>
<u n="461" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just eat your face?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0037">I'd get <pause dur="short"/> You know those bandages that you see? Those bandages? And I'd make a mould of me face <pause dur="short"/> then I'd fill it with chocolate and then it would be the shape of me face <pause dur="short"/> then I'd make another half like with the back of me head and then yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that's a good idea</u>
<u n="463" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And the the creme inside what what will that be made of?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0037">yeah Cadbury's Creme Egg cream</u>
<u n="465" who="S0115">basically sort of icing sugar?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0037">it's like a fondant isn't it?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0115" trans="overlap">bit of vanilla and?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0115">boiled with water</u>
<u n="470" who="S0037">with yellow colouring</u>
<u n="471" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah for the yolk?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0037">maybe with some chocolate chunks in for like brain pieces <pause dur="short"/> or some jelly sweets</u>
<u n="473" who="S0115">oh right so now you're going to into the horror <trunc>g</trunc> sweets genre?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0037">horror sort of sweets are popular anyway those <trunc>l</trunc> those ones that like Bursting Bugs? Have you had those before?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> I don't really haven't had much horror horror sweets really</u>
<u n="476" who="S0037">bursting Bugs <pause dur="short"/> bursting Bugs are nice <pause dur="short"/> they're like you know those jelly sweets that I like?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0037">D'you know which ones I mean?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0115">um no</u>
<u n="480" who="S0037">like Haribo type sweets</u>
<u n="481" who="S0115">I don't really know them so</u>
<u n="482" who="S0037">ah that's from the Inbetweeners film isn't it?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah doing his his his robot dance or something</u>
<u n="484" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you see him like <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen that film <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="485" who="S0037">it's like a black and white style look <pause dur="short"/> I mean like a silent movie style</u>
<u n="486" who="S0115">yeah um sort of Italian an old Italian movie</u>
<u n="487" who="S0037">like I quite fancied seeing The Artist</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="488" who="S0115">yeah yeah we should</u>
<u n="489" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0115">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0037">I don't think its on in the cinema any more</u>
<u n="492" who="S0115">obviously we've got an Italian song in the you know in the back</u>
<u n="493" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what the song <pause dur="short"/> cos they've just like remixed it haven't they?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="495" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I like they're doing the comedy slow run</u>
<u n="496" who="S0115">it's a funny style of running <pause dur="short"/> they're sort of jumping</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="497" who="S0037">this song's a bit annoying</u>
<u n="498" who="S0115">it's Yolanda B Cool and</u>
<u n="499" who="S0037">D Cup?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0115">D Cup</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="501" who="S0037">yeah it's like an Italian film he's eating the spaghetti at the end isn't he?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And there's a <unclear/> Um <pause dur="short"/> it says here that God has given Christians into a living hope through the Resurrection</u>
<u n="503" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> little fly <pause dur="short"/> I don't want all the Christian <trunc>u</trunc> things</u>
<u n="504" who="S0115">oh no I'm just  I'm just  reading you know</u>
<u n="505" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I hate all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="506" who="S0115">it's linked to Passover and Exodus from Egypt um <pause dur="short"/> through the Last Supper and Crucifixion <pause dur="short"/> according to New Testament Jesus gave the Passover meal a new meaning um <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="507" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="508" who="S0037">what's she doing carrying that massive heart around?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="509" who="S0115">um they have unleavened bread don't they?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0037">at the Passover?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0115">yeah and also um at the Communion</u>
<u n="512" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> are they not like wafers at the Communion thing?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0115">yeah well it's not  it's not  got yeast in it has it?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="515" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> jesus is compared to the Passover lamb uh we were gonna get a leg of lamb actually</u>
<u n="516" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh One day I'll get that leg of lamb</u>
<u n="517" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0037">the one that I had before was really nice but was really unappreciated</u>
<u n="519" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and <trunc>th</trunc> they slay the lambs in the temple <pause dur="short"/> they like to slay a lamb don't they in the Mediterranean we saw that on uh</u>
<u n="520" who="S0037">oh yeah that was a <pause dur="short"/> was that not a goat?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there was a it was a programme where you you you take a fat person and send them over to uh</u>
<u n="522" who="S0037">even fatter people?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0115">to to some other fat people in in um it's Cyprus I think it was actually or Crete</u>
<u n="524" who="S0037">was it? Oh that's right</u>
<u n="525" who="S0115">was it Cyprus or Crete?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was Crete</u>
<u n="527" who="S0115">and um which is very near Jerusalem actually and uh Israel isn't uh?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="529" who="S0115">and in <trunc>Cr</trunc> in Crete you know and in a lot of the Mediterranean like whey they have a visitor they slaughter one of the lambs</u>
<u n="530" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0115">um in the traditional cut throat style <pause dur="short"/> and then cook that and uh</u>
<u n="532" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0115">that's something that I think they do at Passover um in the temple</u>
<u n="534" who="S0037">Lamb is tasty <pause dur="short"/> I'd much like I obviously we don't have it very often but I like it better than like turkey and that</u>
<u n="535" who="S0115">the scriptural instructions say the lamb is to be slain between the two evenings</u>
<u n="536" who="S0037">like at Christmas I'd much rather have lamb than have  than have  turkey</u>
<u n="537" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> ah right well you know we'll have to get some uh a leg</u>
<u n="538" who="S0037">I know your mam always wants all the trimmings in</u>
<u n="539" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you can get a leg for if you get a leg for twelve quid in Aldi</u>
<u n="540" who="S0037">all the trimmings <pause dur="short"/> that's what she wants</u>
<u n="541" who="S0115">twelve twelve quid in Aldi you can get a leg of lamb</u>
<u n="542" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0115">then you gotta  you gotta  do it right though you know you can't just like</u>
<u n="544" who="S0037">I know you slow cook it</u>
<u n="545" who="S0115" trans="overlap">can't just stuff it in the oven and uh hope for the best you know you've gotta like</u>
<u n="546" who="S0037">give it some loving care yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0115">I mean you've gotta prepare them and I mean depending on what sort of thing you would do I suppose <pause dur="short"/> obviously if it's a leg of lamb we're presumably gonna be roasting it aren't you so?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0037">yeah with like</u>
<u n="549" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="550" who="S0037">well that <trunc>o</trunc> that one we did last time was really nice like <pause dur="short"/> it was just a bit unappreciated I thought <pause dur="short"/> a Moroccan sort of one</u>
<u n="551" who="S0115">um it's just I'm thinking difficult to like  to like  actually slaughter a lamb I thought it</u>
<u n="552" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ignoring us <pause dur="short"/> no it wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> same as anything</u>
<u n="553" who="S0115">depends how you do it I suppose doesn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0037">do you not just like?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0115">Cos <trunc>i</trunc> if you do it like in a you know like a  like a  pellet in in in the head</u>
<u n="556" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no they just cut their throat</u>
<u n="557" who="S0115">well yeah no I'm saying that would be harder for me than than than a pellet based you know</u>
<u n="558" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0115">pellet based method</u>
<u n="560" who="S0037">yeah but if you breed lamb</u>
<u n="561" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sorry I ignored <unclear/> the</u>
<u n="562" who="S0037">you did yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0115">what did you say?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> who what did I say? Uh oh I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> mustn't have been important</u>
<u n="565" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="566" who="S0037">um something about lambs I can't remember</u>
<u n="567" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="568" who="S0115">right so yeah I was just saying <trunc>n</trunc> no I think it would be  would be  fairly hard to to to like slaughter an animal in that  in that  way but um but I guess everyone it's very popular in uh</u>
<u n="569" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ooh <pause dur="short"/> wonder what that was</u>
<u n="570" who="S0115">it's very popular in uh sort of <trunc>Medi</trunc> you know mid eastern Mediterranean</u>
<u n="571" who="S0037">is there some post?</u>
<event desc="sound of door opening"/>
<u n="572" who="S0115">it's a paper</u>
<u n="573" who="S0037">ooh what is it?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0115">it is the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0037">oh what's been happening in the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0115" trans="overlap">which is the  which is the  uh Liberal Democrat</u>
<u n="577" who="S0037">aw</u>
<u n="578" who="S0115">uh the Liberal Democrat newspaper</u>
<u n="579" who="S0037">thought it was gonna be like</u>
<u n="580" who="S0115">there's a picture of uh  of uh  our MP <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0115"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is that his name?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0037">oh what's he doing?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0115">is the recorder still going? Is it working?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0115">I'll probably uh probably go to the shop in a you know in a bit</u>
<u n="587" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll just finish this piece</u>
<u n="588" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> hold on you see quite a big beard there uh <pause dur="short"/> there's a guy with a beard saying save our libraries</u>
<u n="589" who="S0037">which bit? Like is it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="590" who="S0115">hold on so the main headline is Libdems deliver <anon type="place"/> Railway Station</u>
<u n="591" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> one?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0115">um good benefits but yeah <anon type="place"/>  sidings <pause dur="short"/> Action is needed to make sure the access road is up to scratch <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah it's in <trunc>te</trunc> it's in ten years time or something though it's not like next week</u>
<u n="594" who="S0115">I was wandering if the Liberal Democrats gonna get quite badly punished in uh the elections</u>
<u n="595" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> the local elections are they this week or next week or?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> d'you? I suspect Liberal I suspect there may be a swing  a swing  from Libdem to to Labour but um</u>
<u n="597" who="S0037">I think I asked a postal vote for both of us so</u>
<u n="598" who="S0115">alright fair enough <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="599" who="S0037">although I can't really remember</u>
<u n="600" who="S0115">ooh there's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looking very serious</u>
<u n="601" who="S0037">oh <pause dur="short"/> what's he doing now?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0115">with his he's holding up a little flyer saying worst bus cuts in the country <pause dur="short"/> exclamation mark</u>
<u n="603" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0115">put <pause dur="short"/> it says put a hundred K into helping youth into work</u>
<u n="605" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0115">liberals want to spend the councillors' pay rise money on free youth transport to address the council cuts last year <pause dur="short"/> Uh they've called for uh the hundred grand that uh Tories were planning to use  planning to use  hundred grand as pay rise for themselves</u>
<u n="607" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but a hundred grand's not gonna go very far is it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0115">to be spent in on transport to get young people into work <pause dur="short"/> um to provide free public transport to help young people aged sixteen to nineteen</u>
<u n="609" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0115">sounds quite a good idea to make it free uh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="611" who="S0115">they've got a list of proposals that Labour didn't support uh</u>
<u n="612" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0115">including eighty grand a year investment in youth and community engagement officers <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what uh community engagement officers are <pause dur="short"/> forty-six grand to improve recycling rates</u>
<u n="614" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="615" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and sixteen grand a year to support <anon type="place"/> Road</u>
<u n="616" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what that they didn't improve? I don't understand like <pause dur="short"/> so Labour didn't support it and then they were done anyway or what?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0115">I dunno</u>
<u n="618" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="619" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> doesn't say whether it actually happened or not <pause dur="short"/> uh when it says supporting <anon type="place"/> Road I mean are they  are they are they  sort of how are they?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0037">does it mean the commerce?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0115">are they subsidizing um some businesses or or? Cos they were talking about you know Politics is always annoying isn't it cos it's often like</u>
<u n="622" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0115"><trunc>al</trunc> <trunc>al</trunc> there's often sort of two sides to everything and then it becomes hard to to decide what to do because you cos you tend to get two sides and you tend to get the people grouping themselves in two sides and you tend to get like a a one group of saying I want a big Tesco in this road</u>
<u n="624" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0115">another group of people saying um I don't well I don't  I don't  because um I'm a small business and I'm gonna get I'm gonna be put out of business by this big Tesco so you've got like one group of people saying one thing another group of people saying another and it's basically like politics is essentially sort of somehow mediating</u>
<u n="626" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0115">between them where it is effectively taking sides uh</u>
<u n="628" who="S0037">I've nearly finished me uh</u>
<u n="629" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um maybe compromise uh you know making a compromise but</u>
<u n="630" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0115">Cos obviously there's certain advantages you know if you have a big Tesco you know whatever that uh has an advantage that um you may get cheaper prices than the smaller local ones</u>
<u n="632" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I don't think Tesco's that cheap</u>
<u n="633" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> well I mean or Sainsbury's whatever but they they do have some of the I think some of the own brand uh stuff is cheap but</u>
<u n="634" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> apprentices a <anon type="place"/> success story it says uh um city council's celebrating the uh success of its apprenticeship scheme which uh</u>
<u n="636" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aha?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0115">uh eight young people achieved qualifications</u>
<u n="638" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what are they doing? What type of apprenticeships?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0115">there's the Halfords picture of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> uh in Halfords there um</u>
<u n="640" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uhh <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose it's <trunc>n</trunc> it's like he it's obvious his face is gonna be on there if that's the Libdem thing</u>
<u n="641" who="S0115">his face is everywhere <pause dur="short"/> he's in almost every picture</u>
<u n="642" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0115">in a variety of different poses different looks <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0037">oh dear</u>
<u n="645" who="S0115">there's one on the bottom where he looks really sort of proud <pause dur="short"/> he's proudly holding a piece of paper</u>
<u n="646" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="647" who="S0115">in a crowd who are also holding pieces of paper <pause dur="short"/> the headline for that one is county Tories put new council tax up brackets and stash away some for themselves</u>
<u n="648" who="S0037">uhuh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> Conservatives on the county council have put your council tax up and set aside a hundred thousand of it as a pay rise for themselves?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh for their? Yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0115">um Libdems running the city council have frozen council tax <pause dur="short"/> That was actually because of uh like Conservatives wanted to give it yeah wanted to take some more money and give it to the party</u>
<u n="652" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0115">whereas the Democrats didn't want to take an um um hold on <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="654" who="S0037">this song's quite recent I think</u>
<u n="655" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's so the <trunc>ci</trunc> so we've got like the city council says one thing um</u>
<u n="656" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0115">which is Liberal Democrat and we have like we have the county council's Conservative um uh frozen council tax apparently but you were saying that our council tax has in fact gone up</u>
<u n="658" who="S0037">yeah I know like they said</u>
<u n="659" who="S0115">or is that in the inflation?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0037">on the thing it said like oh it's gone down by so many percent and then but then on the but then the payment's more so how can it be? Cos like last year they were paying a hundred and twenty-eight and this year we're paying a hundred and thirty-five first and then a hundred and thirty <pause dur="short"/> unless I paid more at the start last year or something</u>
<u n="661" who="S0115">libdems on the county council launched a campaign against pay rise for the council <pause dur="short"/> the petition which was like they were holding um gained three thousand signatures um</u>
<u n="662" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they shouldn't be having any pay rises <pause dur="short"/> although actually do county <trunc>coun</trunc> do county councillors have other jobs?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0115">the county council actually is is opposite the Castle Hill isn't it?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0037">yeah but do the councillors have like day jobs? Or are they full time councillors?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it depends like a lot of <trunc>ci</trunc> civil servants and might be the management</u>
<u n="666" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I just</u>
<u n="667" who="S0115">I dunno it depends <pause dur="short"/> like some of them might simply be party members of</u>
<u n="668" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0115">interfering in uh</u>
<u n="670" who="S0037">no I was just wondering</u>
<u n="671" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> um it looks like our campaign to freeze allowances has won out <pause dur="short"/> this serves the Tories right says <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> county councillor</u>
<u n="672" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aha <pause dur="short"/> killian <pause dur="short"/> that's a funny name</u>
<u n="673" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> uh</u>
<u n="674" who="S0037">hey d'you think we should go to the shop then before it gets too late?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah we we should <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> tried to give themselves a twenty percent</u>
<u n="676" who="S0037">okay well I'll just</u>
<u n="677" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you'd think I I don't think in in in a time of cuts you can't really have a pay rise can you cos?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'll just finish this bit and then <pause dur="short"/> not really <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="679" who="S0115" trans="overlap">everyone else is feeling the pinch <pause dur="short"/> can you turn it off? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
</body>
</text>
