<text id="S7SU">
<header>
		<rec_length>2:04:38</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0046 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Food, relationships</topics>
		<activity>Friends eating dinner, chatting.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0046">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Labourer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0084">philistine that he is he doesn't like red wine</u>
<u n="2" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0084">what a weirdo</u>
<u n="4" who="S0041">what is</u>
<u n="5" who="S0084">so he drank it and he says yeah it's alright and I was like never mind it's a good enough pinot <pause dur="short"/> I was like uh</u>
<u n="6" who="S0041"></u>
<u n="7" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what could have gone wrong?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0041">you've gone wrong in the head I'm afraid</u>
<u n="9" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well last week he was like uh what wine do you like? I said well I like pinot I like a sauvignon blanc but if it's a really good one</u>
<u n="10" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0084">and he went to the shop and he ordered one and he's like oh yeah yeah let's take one and he drank it and was like ugh that's disgusting I only like good wine and I said oh you buy good wine and he said well I haven't got any <pause dur="short"/> so I said</u>
<u n="12" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0084">oh I thought he had a really refined pallet when it came to wine and I think it was all bollocks</u>
<u n="14" who="S0041">maybe <pause dur="short"/> do you know what it might be? That it was chosen a wine that he likes</u>
<u n="15" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0041">he has been told that it's a good wine not because it's a good wine <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't like it because it's a good wine you know he just likes it cos that's the only one he likes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0041">which tends to happen which is to be fair frankly enough that you're an alcoholic</u>
<u n="19" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0041">I couldn't quite get bothered</u>
<u n="21" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0041">I'm about I am going to sieve this spaghetti bolognaise</u>
<u n="23" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="24" who="S0041">because it's quite runny</u>
<u n="25" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="26" who="S0041">add lots of sausage</u>
<u n="27" who="S0084">sausage</u>
<u n="28" who="S0041">sausage</u>
<u n="29" who="S0084">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll put sausage in it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0041">sausages</u>
<u n="31" who="S0084">I'm so attuned to the word sausage</u>
<u n="32" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0084">sausage <pause dur="short"/> is it sausage?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0041">um I haven't heard back from that uh guy after the threesome thing comment</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">interesting for three years and playing every ten minutes</u>
<u n="38" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">cheers</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041">and all last night</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0041">I mean <pause dur="short"/> ooh that is good</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084">isn't it?  isn't it?  I thought</u>
<u n="44" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">it's normally over a tenner and it was a eight <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0041">it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> oh it's just peppery</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like it's not vinegary at all is it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">it's just really smooth and I love it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0041">what is the? A good cheap wine is the Ernest Gallo</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">oh is it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0041">the merlot</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">oh okay that's interesting</u>
<u n="54" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the <unclear/> isn't bad either but</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">well it's just</u>
<u n="56" who="S0041">as far a cheap bottle of red goes</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0041">it's actually quite good</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">ah that's a good it's good top tip there <pause dur="short"/> can you just visit in on a normal day? Just cos then you're not spending any more than a fiver on? But you can't get anything for that now</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and I used to do which makes it sound awful</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041">but um we over Christmas when we had a bottle of port uh</u>
<u n="63" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0041">in the house</u>
<u n="65" who="S0084">as you do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0041">not extremely not like great port it's just like</u>
<u n="67" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0041">you know room stuff <pause dur="short"/> um I don't know why I want to what I want to do with this <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'll sieve it into another thing in case we need to put some of the sauce back in</u>
<u n="69" who="S0084">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="70" who="S0041">um yeah so we had this bottle of port and we got a bottle of wine and it just tasted like vinegar wine and I don't know if it's expensive or not</u>
<u n="71" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0041">but it tasted like vinegar wine</u>
<u n="73" who="S0084">oh dear</u>
<u n="74" who="S0041">uh and we put a drop of port in it</u>
<u n="75" who="S0084">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0041">freaking awesome saves any wine</u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="78" who="S0041">yes that's what we just started doing <pause dur="short"/> every time I got bought a bottle of red that was a bit on the vinegar side</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0041">drop a port in <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0084">yeah cos it's fortified wine isn't it port?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084">it's just really strong wine</u>
<u n="84" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it went down a treat</u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">it's a good top tip</u>
<u n="88" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we don't mind doing</u>
<u n="91" who="S0084">yeah well that sounds good</u>
<u n="92" who="S0041">hmm so that was a a good top tip <pause dur="short"/> accidental top tip</u>
<u n="93" who="S0084">uh hmm bunch of alcoholics</u>
<u n="94" who="S0041">yeah I mean really we should have thought about it with it being fortified wine <pause dur="short"/> that would be a way to go but</u>
<u n="95" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0041">I just think it's vinegar wine don't you? You just have to</u>
<u n="97" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0041">cook with it</u>
<u n="99" who="S0084">I mean um obviously we can you know you can buy you can bulk buy can you? It actually brings the price right down</u>
<u n="100" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0084">but then you do have like a million bottles of wine in the house that you will all just drink</u>
<u n="102" who="S0041">all drink yeah cos they're there</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">especially when <unclear/> and I did the first Christmas this year was in the house <pause dur="short"/> like I said we brought in six bottles of wine with our Sainsbury's shopping before that it was a week nearly after Christmas and then we drank them all ourselves <vocal desc="laugh"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can  I can  see why that would happen with the wine</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it <unclear/> happened so <pause dur="short"/> ugh <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/>so over you<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0041">yeah <trunc>J</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <trunc>mu</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum last year for Christmas I was around <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> did you see them? Don't know if you were there? Um she had like on the stairs boxes and boxes of wine <pause dur="short"/> she had like boxes and bottles I mean</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0041">as in</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084">so</u>
<u n="110" who="S0041">boxes of twelve</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0041">I took two of them</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="114" who="S0041">yeah I mean there's three of them drinking in the house</u>
<u n="115" who="S0084">and they're animals</u>
<u n="116" who="S0041">and they're animals</u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0041">uh but yeah that's what I thought they not going to make it till Christmas</u>
<u n="119" who="S0084">that is the way forward isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0041">and also a <unclear/> had a very expensive wine</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0041">and provided you can keep it like that's what I was going to do with the <unclear/> but I thought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you won't keep it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084">no and you'll just drink lots and lots of wine</u>
<u n="124" who="S0041">and become a heifer</u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">well or</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">take some over to A and A <pause dur="short"/> a and A? Or A and A</u>
<u n="128" who="S0041">or A A or A and E <pause dur="short"/> all of that</u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">A and E <pause dur="short"/> all of that <pause dur="short"/> all of the things</u>
<u n="130" who="S0041">of all of the places to check in</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084">uh hmm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="132" who="S0041">oh so it sounds like your evening went really well then?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084">it was nice <pause dur="short"/> it was really nice actually <pause dur="short"/> uh I'll say <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I'm potentially seeing him tomorrow for the gym so I'm looking forward to it actually</u>
<u n="134" who="S0041">aww</u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">it'll be  it'll be  like having a personal trainer</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">yes so I was saying if you could report back</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="138" who="S0041">or if you do become good friends with him</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">he could help me with with the navy</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">well exactly <pause dur="short"/> this is it <pause dur="short"/> well he was in the army that's another thing</u>
<u n="142" who="S0041">oh my God</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">he was in the army</u>
<u n="144" who="S0041">this girl is so fun</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">I know</u>
<u n="146" who="S0041">you just keep looking up all these different things</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084">ah he was in the army <pause dur="short"/> um so remember he was <trunc>h</trunc> he also is a bit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> cos he's got the mental ex girlfriend who swapped her son for a Blackberry <pause dur="short"/> so that's normal behaviour</u>
<u n="148" who="S0041">this is  this is great <pause dur="short"/> this is the greatest way of living through you I've even seen in my life</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0041">this is fantastic</u>
<u n="151" who="S0084">so he's a  he's a  top character <pause dur="short"/> so he was in the army and uh because <trunc>tod</trunc> so today we were watching The Big Question and they were <trunc>talk</trunc> one of the questions was</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">oh he likes The Big Question?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he likes The Big Question</u>
<u n="154" who="S0041">that is such a great thing</u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">I know it's good isn't it? Um although we differ on a lot of things and I <unclear/> Um</u>
<u n="156" who="S0041">porridge <pause dur="short"/> porridge</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084">yeah it's good <pause dur="short"/> I need to get that early <pause dur="short"/> um one of the questions was is Iran a great threat? And uh half the people were saying yes and half the people were saying no obviously <pause dur="short"/> um and he was saying what they need to do right is like go over into all the countries and like round up all the bad people and just shoot them and I was like right you see</u>
<u n="158" who="S0041">uh</u>
<u n="159" who="S0084">the thing is</u>
<u n="160" who="S0041">pretty strong</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like</u>
<u n="162" who="S0041">I mean I'm well I'm actually agreeing with him however</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084" trans="overlap">you are going to join the navy so essentially that is going to be a part of your re thought <pause dur="short"/> um but the <trunc>thin</trunc> over day we have intelligence agencies <pause dur="short"/> we have the CIA <pause dur="short"/> we have The Secret Service that is sort of their job</u>
<u n="164" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="166" who="S0041">they shouldn't get to the point where they're bad people in actual fact</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="168" who="S0041">if they were doing their job properly <pause dur="short"/> they shouldn't</u>
<u n="169" who="S0084">exactly</u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">need to be shot because they should never be able to get to where they are</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084">yeah but basically that's their <trunc>ide</trunc> that's their job is to like round up as much information about these people as possible to stop any actions being taken against the country you know or externally <pause dur="short"/> that's their job <pause dur="short"/> he said yeah but they need to like go out of the country like kill them but then they can't kill them I said well I can't sign off on that cos I'm a pacifist I don't believe in the that no matter how bad a person is I don't they don't deserve to be killed for it <pause dur="short"/> he's like you know like if I was going to kill if I was going to walk down on the street with a gun and like killing kill ten people what would you do? And I was like fucking run away <vocal desc="laugh"/> you maniac <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0041">fucking cut you right out</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">yeah he said <pause dur="short"/> I was like I wouldn't have a gun you know <pause dur="short"/> how I'm I going to tackle you? He said what if  what if  you had a gun what would you do? I was like I'm not fucking Rambo I'm not what going to tackle you to the ground bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> and I was like I'll call the police and he was like there's no police <pause dur="short"/> I was like right so we're living in some sort of guerrilla state where there's no police or authority? He said yeah what are you gonna do? I said oh well I'll probably still run away I mean even if I had a gun because if we're talking about me as I am now I couldn't do it but I did qualify the statement with the uh if I did do with the idea that I did it I've never had anyone close to me hurt <pause dur="short"/> I've never</u>
<u n="174" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0084">you know I mean my sister hasn't been</u>
<u n="176" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0084">hurt or my <trunc>m</trunc> mum hasn't been raped or</u>
<u n="178" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084">I don't know anyone that has been killed and</u>
<u n="180" who="S0041">for you to have that anger</u>
<u n="181" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="182" who="S0041">perhaps where <trunc>m</trunc> maybe you never will even if you had it but</u>
<u n="183" who="S0084">yeah you just</u>
<u n="184" who="S0041">you never know if you would capitalise it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0084">don't know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">you can't make that call really <pause dur="short"/> I mean ideologically I would say I don't agree with anybody being killed it's not our right to take away someone's life no matter how heinous the crime but I've never experienced something that bad</u>
<u n="188" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0084">so um maybe I would think differently <pause dur="short"/> oh smells delicious <unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">the potatoes are well they look like perfect potatoes mum</u>
<u n="191" who="S0084">well I hope so <pause dur="short"/> the secret is power boiling</u>
<u n="192" who="S0041"><unclear/> hobs</u>
<u n="193" who="S0084">yeah and <unclear/> I got in the shower and I put garlic in with them which is why it smells a bit of a burn in here because I <trunc>wh</trunc> whisked them out turned them over another five minutes they were done <pause dur="short"/> probably been in the oven for about twenty minutes</u>
<u n="194" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I mean they were soft put a knife through them</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="197" who="S0084">so they should be okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah so he is a bit mental <pause dur="short"/> so we have quite a lot of discussion</u>
<u n="198" who="S0041">which is good</u>
<u n="199" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> which is good <pause dur="short"/> I know and it's quite nice cos I think <pause dur="short"/> I this sounds really bad <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I take anything away from what he his opinions <pause dur="short"/> I think he comes around to what I think more</u>
<u n="200" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0084">than I can come around to what he thinks cos whenever he says stuff like that I think you've gone wrong</u>
<u n="202" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0084">just a little bit <pause dur="short"/> but I think you know I've got to stop patronizing cos he was on the right lines</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">I just think um so stuff like stuff that he will never change his mind on</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">you know killing bad people cos he was in the army and ultimately I think that's</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="208" who="S0041">I hope I haven't taken like too much out of it</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084">no it will be grand just put the good stuff</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041">hot</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084">do you want to shovel shovel shovel?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>shovel<shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I mean really I think it depends on how set you are with your views as well <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0041">if you're if you really feel strongly about something no matter how much you debate it you're not going to take anything away from it are you?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="216" who="S0041">maybe you should relinquish it</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think with something like that</u>
<u n="218" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">that is basically your condimental ideology like</u>
<u n="220" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084">he's not going to change his mind on that and</u>
<u n="222" who="S0041">how old is he?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084">thirty-six</u>
<u n="224" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084">right obviously he he's had kids young <pause dur="short"/> cos the oldest is thirteen so</u>
<u n="226" who="S0041">oh right okay</u>
<u n="227" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> it's all a little bit <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0041">we don't care</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">that's fine</u>
<u n="230" who="S0041">it entertainment isn't it? It's the entertainment factor</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">it really is <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's not a point where we don't have anything to say to each other <pause dur="short"/> it's quite nice</u>
<u n="232" who="S0041">that's good</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">so yeah um it's fine <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's fine</u>
<u n="234" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> uh how much would you give him on the scale of one to ten hotness?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0084">um probably seven point five <pause dur="short"/> eight</u>
<u n="236" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084">cute</u>
<u n="238" who="S0041">wow that's quite good</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084">I mean he's not someone that you would look at and think god he's hot</u>
<u n="240" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0084">I think because he he's got that cheeky chappy</u>
<u n="242" who="S0041">do you think I need to make some more spag ball?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">we can always come back and do a second sitting</u>
<u n="244" who="S0041">yeah we could do that</u>
<u n="245" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0041">or shall we just do it at one go in?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0084">oh yeah maybe we should just do it</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041">just chop it in</u>
<u n="249" who="S0084">yeah and I <trunc>m</trunc> mean we have got more potatoes that we can do</u>
<u n="250" who="S0041">I thought  I thought  there was a lot of it cos obviously lot of it is liquid</u>
<u n="251" who="S0084">hmm yummy <pause dur="short"/> it is quite liquid isn't it?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="253" who="S0084">I guess that happens with the tomato</u>
<u n="254" who="S0041">hmm and I think as well the mince wasn't very good that I used</u>
<u n="255" who="S0084">oh yeah they were a bit of uh seepage</u>
<u n="256" who="S0041">seepage</u>
<u n="257" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="258" who="S0041">let's burn you up in there</u>
<u n="259" who="S0084">how can it be Sunday night already? I feel like it has been a busy weekend isn't it? Yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0041">I feel like uh <pause dur="short"/> I've lost</u>
<u n="261" who="S0084"></u>
<u n="262" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">lost two days of your life</u>
<u n="264" who="S0041">yeah but it's such a pain cos you look forward to the weekend don't you?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="266" who="S0041">and we haven't seen much of it <pause dur="short"/> although yesterday was really nice</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084">hmm and it sounds like you had a really nice time</u>
<u n="268" who="S0041">I need another day <pause dur="short"/> the weekend should just be one more day more</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that would be pretty sweet wouldn't it? Friday's</u>
<u n="270" who="S0041">Friday's should be a weekend or even</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084">or Monday's</u>
<u n="272" who="S0041">if it should just be a half day on Friday <pause dur="short"/> everyone should just have a half day</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0041">so then you can get all your shopping done or washing done or whatever you wanted to do if everyone left work on midday on Friday</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084">that would be pretty nice wouldn't it? When I worked at <anon type="place"/> cos that's <unclear/> we used to finish earlier in fact you used to work there didn't you?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0041">I can't remember there I was only there for three days</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084">I think at the time we did um <pause dur="short"/> three days</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084">um shift was supposed to be nine till five but because that we worked as temps in the summer it was really busy <pause dur="short"/> so we often I often start at seven thirty then when we would  we would  normally work eight yeah eight thirty actually till five and on a five day we can do four uh <unclear/> thereabout</u>
<u n="282" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084">it was really good and then yeah we did overtime</u>
<u n="284" who="S0041">so I never really understood this about our company especially like  you know they say that we really want you to find a really healthy work life balance</u>
<u n="285" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0041">but nobody we don't take phone calls in our department usually</u>
<u n="287" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="288" who="S0041">and uh on a Friday afternoon <pause dur="short"/> there's nobody there</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0041">because nobody wants to call <pause dur="short"/> so actually if we left the office at about three on Friday</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0041">I don't really think business wise it won't make that much of a difference</u>
<u n="293" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0041">and also because we've got a full time reception twenty-four hours that can take messages so</u>
<u n="295" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0041">it's also their job <pause dur="short"/> um right let's give you ah that's not <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> so really they might have because compared to everyone else in the hotel we in our office are the only ones that will tend to spend over the odds time wise at work because we're the only ones that are salaried everybody else is on apart from <trunc>man</trunc> managers are on like hourly</u>
<u n="297" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0041">wages</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084">that's weird isn't it? How the departments could be that different</u>
<u n="300" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose how that can be <unclear/> like on the bar we don't know what hours</u>
<u n="301" who="S0084">that's just shit</u>
<u n="302" who="S0041">we're going to need to</u>
<u n="303" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0041">it depends on which business we've got as to how many hours that they get and stuff <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="305" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="306" who="S0041">but if they really wanted us to have a healthy work life balance given that we'll come in on stupid days for events or or stay longer or and nobody else does that <pause dur="short"/> cos they just</u>
<u n="307" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0041">they finish their shifts somebody else takes over from them and that's that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0041">you think they would say okay you can <unclear/> the office on Friday cos on a Friday at three cos we're not going to make any <trunc>m</trunc> we're not going to lose any money from it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">and given the hours and the stress that you're under generally</u>
<u n="313" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0041">you just do it</u>
<u n="315" who="S0084">as a little courtesy</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0084">A little thank you</u>
<u n="318" who="S0041">and then maybe the managers could take that time if they wanted to</u>
<u n="319" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0041">to prep for the next week <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="321" who="S0084">? Uh what is it?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041">it's uh garlic</u>
<u n="323" who="S0084">wow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0084">do you like a bit of garlic?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0041">oh garlic yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0084">the garlic's disappeared isn't it? Uh <pause dur="short"/> so you don't answer the phone on Friday as a way of catching up with yourself?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> we do answer the phone if it rings but generally it doesn't ring</u>
<u n="329" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="330" who="S0041">yeah cos not many people call and or if they do they call for things like generic things like what's the parking like</u>
<u n="331" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0041">cos we arriving in <trunc>weeken</trunc> at the weekend</u>
<u n="333" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0041">but the reception should deal with them they're just not  <unclear/> by themselves</u>
<u n="335" who="S0084">Good <pause dur="short"/> good <vocal desc="yawn"/> I texted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="337" who="S0084">yeah <unclear/> this afternoon about next weekend</u>
<u n="338" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0084">about what to do but I don't know  I don't know  if she's actually made plans cos she's she suggested this Saturday so I don't know whether she seemed <unclear/> on a Friday</u>
<u n="340" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="341" who="S0084">well I'll let you know if she comes back with anything <pause dur="short"/> it does sound quite good <pause dur="short"/> so it's free entry and then free canopies? I <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0041">uh yes <pause dur="short"/> I think so <pause dur="short"/> it's definitely free canopies and cocktails</u>
<u n="343" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0041">I can't remember if it was free entry <pause dur="short"/> I think it might be <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'll um I'll find out <pause dur="short"/> I've got the little flier on my desk at work</u>
<u n="345" who="S0084">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="346" who="S0041">so that's pretty good</u>
<u n="347" who="S0084">yup</u>
<u n="348" who="S0041">hmm done</u>
<u n="349" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> I'm so tired <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> woke up at six</u>
<u n="350" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="351" who="S0084">to go for a pee and he came back and he never wanted to <unclear/> again and then we kissed and cuddled and uh he was like I'll I'll go downstairs cos uh you know if you need to sleep I said well I'm not going to be able I'm not going to sleep now</u>
<u n="352" who="S0041">poor you <pause dur="short"/> do you want to eat at the table</u>
<u n="353" who="S0084">thank you</u>
<u n="354" who="S0041">or the boudoir?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0084">um clear the table</u>
<u n="356" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0084">that's where we'll be eating isn't it?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0084">thank you</u>
<u n="360" who="S0041">I suppose <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="361" who="S0084">not a problem <pause dur="short"/> tatties are easy</u>
<u n="362" who="S0041">you say that they're the one thing I can't cook you know</u>
<u n="363" who="S0084">are they?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0041">I can't cook potatoes <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="365" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> well I hope they're alright</u>
<u n="366" who="S0041">I suppose cos I'll try not to eat them cos I can't cook potatoes <pause dur="short"/> I can't cook rice</u>
<u n="367" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> rice is quite hard actually cos it's always either half a cup of rice with a cup of water that you're supposed to and they never actually cos it's all supposed to boil away so you're just left with the rice um</u>
<u n="368" who="S0041">it never does</u>
<u n="369" who="S0084">it never works <pause dur="short"/> cos it's too little or too too much <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>oh<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0041">hmm oh this is standard  this is standard</u>
<u n="373" who="S0084">standard didn't go there</u>
<u n="374" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084">did you say you saw toothless <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on Friday?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0041">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> he's the one</u>
<u n="378" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> he said to me um oh uh did you hear what I did to Liz?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right</u>
<u n="380" who="S0041">and he caught me really off guard</u>
<u n="381" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="382" who="S0041">so I thought cos I thought he wouldn't say anything cos he would be embarrassed about it you know</u>
<u n="383" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">and so I thought what do I say? Do I say yes I know?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084">we'd be gossiping about you</u>
<u n="386" who="S0041">hmm?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0041">or do I say no I haven't got a clue and then he tells me and</u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so I thought on my feet and laughed</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">and said oh yeah that was really funny <pause dur="short"/> um I got in and I had a really crap day and I saw it on the top of the fridge um and I thought was absolutely brilliant like</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0041">really great like really funny thing to do</u>
<u n="395" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0041">and he was like yeah when I got home the next day I put my coat on and in but in my pocket I have the flower head and a load of leaves</u>
<u n="397" who="S0084">oh no</u>
<u n="398" who="S0041">and no stem</u>
<u n="399" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="400" who="S0041">and I said to him yeah you know I had a really good really fun night and um you know so <trunc>k</trunc> you know Liz seemed to have a laugh as well so</u>
<u n="401" who="S0084">oh bless him <pause dur="short"/> he's really sweet yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0041">I just thought I'd and I said yeah I said well it's not it's so I said I've no she had a nice time <pause dur="short"/> so I said it's nice we you come to see somebody that you don't know isn't it? And that when you feel comfortable</u>
<u n="403" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0041">uh hmm <pause dur="short"/> he was like yeah yeah it just seemed like she had fun <pause dur="short"/> I said well I mean I'm guessing from what I saw it wasn't serious like but you know just so you know <trunc>L</trunc> Liz would not be looking for anything out of that you know that don't ya?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0084">uh hmm hmm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">and he was like yeah of cos he does <pause dur="short"/> I mean not that</u>
<u n="407" who="S0084">you're not</u>
<u n="408" who="S0041">just you anybody in the world</u>
<u n="409" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> nice good one  good one</u>
<u n="410" who="S0041">anybody in the world <pause dur="short"/> she's just not she doesn't want a boyfriend she doesn't really want <trunc>th</trunc> she wouldn't she just felt comfortable with me but she certainly wouldn't cos he said well no I thought maybe we could go for a drink</u>
<u n="411" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0041">hmm you know maybe next time she's here um and I said  I said  oh well you know yeah definitely the next time she comes here with me</u>
<u n="413" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="414" who="S0041">I'll let you know if we're coming out</u>
<u n="415" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="416" who="S0041">umm I said but certainly one on one she wouldn't feel comfortable in</u>
<u n="417" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0041">doing that <pause dur="short"/> I said you know <pause dur="short"/> he said oh no no yeah I just thought you know and then he said you know even if you weren't coming out and she wanted to come <trunc>f</trunc> out for a drink with us lot</u>
<u n="419" who="S0084">oh God</u>
<u n="420" who="S0041">just so she felt she knew she was welcome <pause dur="short"/> I said oh no I'm sure she does know she's welcome but you know what it's like I know you and she doesn't really know <unclear/> very well <pause dur="short"/> I don't really think that would be an option but she certainly could she certainly would come with me and we can you know I'll let everyone know if we decide to come come round</u>
<u n="421" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0041">what was that?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0084">who can say?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0084">who can say? Well thanks mate <pause dur="short"/> sounds like I really owe you</u>
<u n="426" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0084">you really sort of laid the ground work cos I've been there it would have all been really awkward</u>
<u n="428" who="S0041">wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0041">hmm and I</u>
<u n="431" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0041">I can't I don't think they I don't think I made a joke about the cat card</u>
<u n="433" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="434" who="S0041">I hope I didn't</u>
<u n="435" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> it sounds like it went well <pause dur="short"/> it sounds like he reacted quite well to whatever you were doing even though you laughed at him</u>
<u n="436" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I couldn't really  I couldn't really  gauge if he was agreeing with me to save face</u>
<u n="437" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0041">or whether he actually thought that you know he actually thought of it as a friend thing and as a bit of a joke</u>
<u n="439" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0041">I think it was probably a bit of half and half</u>
<u n="441" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> by the way it was a really really sweet thing to do</u>
<u n="442" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0084">and it was thought and effort it was really nice</u>
<u n="444" who="S0041">bless</u>
<u n="445" who="S0084">he's a nice guy</u>
<u n="446" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> turns out I think he has got teeth</u>
<u n="447" who="S0084">just not all of them</u>
<u n="448" who="S0041">well</u>
<u n="449" who="S0084">just not all the teeth <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0041">I was trying to eye up a little bit</u>
<u n="451" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0041">see what teeth he had got missing and I couldn't notice any of them missing</u>
<u n="453" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0041">I mean they're black and fucked but</u>
<u n="455" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0084">would you reckon kissing that guy?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0041">hmm?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0084">Christ</u>
<u n="460" who="S0041">Jesus</u>
<u n="461" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0041">so maybe he has got teeth and they're just fucked but I couldn't see back far enough to see if they have got holes <pause dur="short"/> I mean I couldn't say anything cos I've got a hole cos I didn't have any adult teeth</u>
<u n="463" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0041">and my teeth didn't fall out till I was my baby teeth didn't fall out until I was nineteen</u>
<u n="465" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="466" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I've got a massive gap right just there</u>
<u n="467" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0041">you see?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0084">you'd never notice</u>
<u n="470" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not as big as a tooth like you couldn't get a tooth in it</u>
<u n="471" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0041">Cos as I've grown it's kinda pushed together a bit <pause dur="short"/> look</u>
<u n="473" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0041">had there was it was a big enough for a tooth in it when it started</u>
<u n="475" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0041">but I have one one tooth two less</u>
<u n="477" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0041">on both sides</u>
<u n="479" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="480" who="S0041">I don't know why</u>
<u n="481" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0041">so I can't really you know prey on poor old toothless <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but uh he I don't even how can you uh</u>
<u n="483" who="S0084">doesn't he?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0041">hmm  I've noticed that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s teeth are quite bad</u>
<u n="485" who="S0084">are they?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> like quite black <pause dur="short"/> not not black as in all of them black but I'm sure like behind</u>
<u n="487" who="S0084"><vocal desc="cough"/> hmm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0041">that bit</u>
<u n="489" who="S0084">that's fillings isn't it? Like if you don't have a white <trunc>fi</trunc> like it's more expensive to have a white filling</u>
<u n="490" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="491" who="S0084">Cos it's for cosmetic reasons <pause dur="short"/> so usually if you've just got a mercury filling like the one they did for mine at the back which actually is starting to be a bit painful sometimes when I <unclear/> back hmm if you can't see it they just do a mercury filling which is cheaper</u>
<u n="492" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="493" who="S0084"><trunc>S</trunc> so if he'd had a hole on the front of his teeth like for example</u>
<u n="494" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0084">they would have done a white cap on it <pause dur="short"/> they would have fixed it</u>
<u n="496" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0084">with a white filling but because it's the back he would have made that decision where you can't really see or just have a mercury filling probably</u>
<u n="498" who="S0041">ooh</u>
<u n="499" who="S0084">but the thing is you can obviously notice</u>
<u n="500" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know I just pay for mine white</u>
<u n="501" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0041">but plus I've got quite a few fillings <pause dur="short"/> I think I've got about seven</u>
<u n="503" who="S0084">I think you've just got to make the call about where it is like even if it was at the back of my front teeth I would have white</u>
<u n="504" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0084">because you</u>
<u n="506" who="S0041">at the front teeth</u>
<u n="507" who="S0084">know yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0084">but like this one was the second from the back and so I just thought</u>
<u n="510" who="S0041">oh God</u>
<u n="511" who="S0084">no it's everybody like a dentist that's it <pause dur="short"/> even if you do like a little  tennis</u>
<u n="512" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0084">it's not if they were looking down there</u>
<u n="514" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well before I went abroad  before I went abroad  cos I didn't think I was going to come back <pause dur="short"/> I went to the dentist and said just look at if there's anything that needs doing do it now</u>
<u n="515" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="516" who="S0041">um cos I didn't know when the the next time I would go to a dentist would be</u>
<u n="517" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0041">uh and he gave me seven fillings in one go</u>
<u n="519" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="520" who="S0041">yeah and at the time I thought that's like that's extreme he said no it's nothing they're just little ones <pause dur="short"/> but still</u>
<u n="521" who="S0084">I don't know if you can actually do that <pause dur="short"/> can you legally?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I don't know  I don't know  um</u>
<u n="523" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="524" who="S0041">but since the other dentist I went to after that was like holy fuck why have you got all these fillings?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0041">yeah and <trunc>par</trunc> most of them I didn't need</u>
<u n="527" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0041">and they were just a just in case</u>
<u n="529" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="530" who="S0041">yeah and they were like five at the time</u>
<u n="531" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0041">I didn't pay for it but</u>
<u n="533" who="S0084">such <unclear/> isn't it? I mean we had um like those pre emptive fillings when we were kids <pause dur="short"/> we had um in the back two teeth and the bottom back two teeth and the top we had white fillers but not fillings but they're fillers to stop you getting cavities in the back and now</u>
<u n="534" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="535" who="S0084">they're white and they did it to all of our teeth <pause dur="short"/> so it was me and my brother and my sister and then my sister she was a little bit older</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="537" who="S0084">I was probably about seven or eight and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would have been five</u>
<u n="538" who="S0041">I didn't even have my adult teeth by then <pause dur="short"/> no adult teeth</u>
<u n="539" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I didn't start getting adult teeth till I was about I probably started getting them at about seven or eight</u>
<u n="541" who="S0084">I think I'm remembering it wrong then cos that sounds young doesn't it?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="543" who="S0084">maybe it was when I was at secondary school but I just remember feeling very young</u>
<u n="544" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0084">isn't it? I can't remember I thought it was when I was in primary school</u>
<u n="546" who="S0041">Cos I remember in year six mum was gonna pay for me to have all my teeth painted like coated</u>
<u n="547" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0041">which might be the same type of thing</u>
<u n="549" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0041">all of them and he said we can't do it until you've got your adult teeth <pause dur="short"/> so I know I didn't have them by then</u>
<u n="551" who="S0084">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah maybe I was a bit older? hmm <pause dur="short"/> I can't even remember <pause dur="short"/> it was  it was  it seemed like a good idea I suppose to my parents because</u>
<u n="552" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0084">sort of pre empting I think</u>
<u n="554" who="S0041">protecting</u>
<u n="555" who="S0084">yeah they had you know they didn't have you know a good dental care when they were kids and I suppose they got <trunc>h</trunc> had a lot of work later in life which must have been painful and expensive so</u>
<u n="556" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0084">I guess they were really into us like brush your teeth you know twice a day um look after your teeth cos once they're gone it's you're fucked</u>
<u n="558" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> that was awesome</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">they are awesome <unclear/> potatoes</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you like them?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041">they're actual perfect <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084">they're a bit more soggy than I wanted but there was a bit of a crunch there</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">I like them soggy</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041">hmm hmm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">they probably sat in the uh oven for a while longer</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> I really need to</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">no I don't</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084">Good for you</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041">I was going to say I really need to learn how to cook them</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084">it's dangerous</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">then I thought no I don't <pause dur="short"/> I'll just live on them</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084">when I'm at my mum's <trunc>s</trunc> she's got a <unclear/> garden so I'll go and pick rosemary and then put rosemary and thyme and put rosemary  put rosemary  and thyme and garlic</u>
<u n="576" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084">for a nice little flavour and then olive oil</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041">yum</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084">so that wasn't bad really</u>
<u n="580" who="S0041">awesome <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't too bad for you was it?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> I think Dan's regime is going to be high protein if that's what it's going to be about <pause dur="short"/> which is fine</u>
<u n="582" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">like he tried to make me a protein shake earlier and I was like I don't really like drinking <unclear/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0084">just bare that in mind when you're creating this diet plan for me and he said no we'll sit down and you can tell me your favourite food and I was like it consists of any sandwiches <vocal desc="laugh"/> If you can make me a diet out of fish fingers and sandwiches</u>
<u n="586" who="S0041">fish fingers and sandwiches</u>
<u n="587" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that would be fab I'm not feeling very confident</u>
<u n="588" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm going to start my protein shakes again <pause dur="short"/> I've still got loads of them <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084">I suppose and they are really good to have before the gym aren't they? Cos they do give you that energy boost and then you just</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">you just hammer it</u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084">it's really what you want</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">he said you've got to do it until you feel sick and I was like ha ha ha</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">do the gym?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0084">yeah and then I looked at him</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0084">I realised he wasn't joking</u>
<u n="600" who="S0041">yeah I know I do <pause dur="short"/> I do it until I'm going to be sick but I think that's probably cos my threshold isn't very good like I'll run until I'm gonna I feel like I'm gonna vomit and then</u>
<u n="601" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0041">when I go on the weights like the one that you push this way</u>
<u n="603" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0041">I do</u>
<u n="605" who="S0084">well like</u>
<u n="606" who="S0041">until I feel like woozy <pause dur="short"/> the leg ones I never feel sick on that</u>
<u n="607" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="608" who="S0041">but I pull down I never feel sick on that but the one that I have to push up</u>
<u n="609" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="610" who="S0041">literally my head's spinning but I have to just I just finish the three sets and that's it <vocal desc="laugh"/> when I'm like</u>
<u n="611" who="S0084">keep doing that <pause dur="short"/> but the ones  the ones  I do are the ones that I started doing at the gym when I first joined my well preliminary it's been like many moons ago and um I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about it and he said that you've got to do the flump fly or something? Like that's the one that goes all up which is <unclear/> wings?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0041">oh yeah I've seen one of those at my gym</u>
<u n="613" who="S0084">I don't know if you've got one of those there?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0041">but if you have a look</u>
<u n="615" who="S0084" trans="overlap">like bench presses</u>
<u n="616" who="S0041">or probably I'll show you <pause dur="short"/> they are other ones you can do if you've been going <pause dur="short"/> cos on our</u>
<u n="617" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0041">on our gym they have pictures in the corner</u>
<u n="619" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="620" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and it shows you what muscle groups you work</u>
<u n="621" who="S0084">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0041">so I always make sure I get <trunc>t</trunc> this one and this one</u>
<u n="623" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0041">and the back one</u>
<u n="625" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0041">but <trunc>freakin</trunc> do you know right? I've sat here with crazy horse</u>
<u n="627" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0041">and he's actually not well he is a crazy horse but he's actually not as freaky as I thought he was <pause dur="short"/> he's <trunc>weir</trunc> he's weird as far that goes and all</u>
<u n="629" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0041">jaws of life <pause dur="short"/> you know he wouldn't ordinarily go out with him</u>
<u n="631" who="S0084">you wouldn't trust him</u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="634" who="S0041">um but he's actually quite cleared up</u>
<u n="635" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0041">he's not I thought he was I thought  I thought  he was really really thick <pause dur="short"/> he's not that thick <pause dur="short"/> um he definitely definitely says things that are a little bit say in front of a boy but he doesn't say it in front of me</u>
<u n="637" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0041">which is never never wonderful <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="639" who="S0084">it's never that line</u>
<u n="640" who="S0041" trans="overlap">he used to be in the cadets</u>
<u n="641" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="642" who="S0041">uh training to be in the RAF</u>
<u n="643" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0041">um and was training to be in the marines <pause dur="short"/> he wanted to be a marine but fucked his wrist and now can't do it</u>
<u n="645" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="646" who="S0041">and now he's</u>
<u n="647" who="S0084">that's a shame</u>
<u n="648" who="S0041">yeah and he doesn't want to go in as uh entry level</u>
<u n="649" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0041">in the army or in the RAF but he's not bright enough to get in as an officer</u>
<u n="651" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0041">he's you're not going to say I'm not brave enough I can't do that type of thing</u>
<u n="653" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0041">um he was saying there's this thing right? Cos obviously he he's quite built I don't know how cos he looks so  and I thought <vocal desc="laugh"/> but um the thing on the gym have you got this with the <trunc>par</trunc> like the wires that come off and the handles and you get it and you're supposed to do this or something or?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0084">oh yeah you can add we've got loads of attachments yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0041">yeah what is? So I just thought well I'm not going anywhere near that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what the hell it does</u>
<u n="657" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0041">Cos it looks like a frame isn't it? With the two like leads that come off it</u>
<u n="659" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="660" who="S0041">but apparently if you do that it's supposed to work every single core muscle</u>
<u n="661" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he was like we were told to just do that even if you're just going for a run do that</u>
<u n="663" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="664" who="S0041">and he saying to do to <trunc>pu</trunc> to pull it up and up and under <pause dur="short"/> I think it was up and under?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="668" who="S0041">I need to get  I need to get  on that <pause dur="short"/> I need to find out what that's all about</u>
<u n="669" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0041">Cos you have to use everything to pull it <pause dur="short"/> cos you stood up you faced up  you faced up</u>
<u n="671" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="672" who="S0041">so you're not sat on anything</u>
<u n="673" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="674" who="S0041">and I think he said that apparently <pause dur="short"/> they were told when he was training for the marines to do that cos it uses all your core muscles <pause dur="short"/> so you've got to keep yourself stood up</u>
<u n="675" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0041">keep yourself in the same position and then move the muscles that the thing is supposed to work</u>
<u n="677" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="678" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> I think we need to get on that I think I need to ask</u>
<u n="679" who="S0084">you need to find out <pause dur="short"/> ask him about that</u>
<u n="680" who="S0041">ask him about the the lead thing</u>
<u n="681" who="S0084">uh there are amazing amount of ways I supposed that <unclear/> and how it all works <pause dur="short"/> I've have to see what they've got that sounds pretty good <pause dur="short"/> there's just loads like I was looking at it the other day and there's loads of benches I could do like bench presses <pause dur="short"/> there's like three different ones <pause dur="short"/> there's one you've got to lie down with your feet up and do it that way</u>
<u n="682" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0084">there's one where you've got uh</u>
<u n="684" who="S0041">have you got one of the lap?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0084">lie down <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0041"></u>
<u n="687" who="S0084">like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0041">you know what that's supposed to be for? Doing sit ups but put your head in the bottom</u>
<u n="689" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="690" who="S0041">awkward like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0084">because I was talking to Dan about this</u>
<u n="692" who="S0041">fuck that</u>
<u n="693" who="S0084" trans="overlap">obviously he's in the army and he was like you're better off doing the little ones</u>
<u n="694" who="S0041">the crunches</u>
<u n="695" who="S0084">like they're keeping you taunt the whole time</u>
<u n="696" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like eight minute abs</u>
<u n="697" who="S0084">I haven't told him all that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly I have told him about that and how I nearly died and he was like don't worry you're  with me you'll be fine and I was like a bit scared <trunc>mo</trunc> actually more than a bit scared but I'm not a bum I <trunc>neve</trunc> cos I never push myself with the weights <pause dur="short"/> it's I could do with the <trunc>sit</trunc> with the cardio but I never um I could never do it with the weights so</u>
<u n="698" who="S0041">I don't think it's as bad as the cardio <pause dur="short"/> it just makes your head spin a bit <pause dur="short"/> makes my head spin</u>
<u n="699" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="700" who="S0041">a bit sometimes <pause dur="short"/> but you sat down so</u>
<u n="701" who="S0084">I think I don't push myself the same way I do with the cardio <pause dur="short"/> if I'm running and I get you know I get umm out of breath or whatever I push myself a bit more than I would if I do weights hmm I'd feel a pain in my arms</u>
<u n="702" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0084">I'd stop that</u>
<u n="704" who="S0041">I only push myself till I'm set when I've when I first start on a thing <pause dur="short"/> I'll pick it up and see how much I can comfortably do this with</u>
<u n="705" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0041">or whatever it is</u>
<u n="707" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="708" who="S0041">and if I can do it then I'll just put the peg in that one</u>
<u n="709" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0041">and if I can finish the ten by the  by the  time I push up on the nine</u>
<u n="711" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="712" who="S0041">it should be really hard</u>
<u n="713" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="714" who="S0041">and that means by the time I'm in the third lap by the time I get to five I think I can't do anymore</u>
<u n="715" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0041">so it's not  it's not  too much of a push but I think that it's different with the weights isn't it? Cos you can't push yourself <trunc>fa</trunc> so far your arms just can't do it <pause dur="short"/> they're just</u>
<u n="717" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0041" trans="overlap">your body physically can't make it <pause dur="short"/> whereas on cardio I think no matter how hard I push myself if you're if there's a gun to my head I could push a bit more</u>
<u n="719" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="720" who="S0041">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0041">like your body is capable of doing more than your mind let's you use</u>
<u n="723" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0041">whereas if you can't push with your arm you can't just</u>
<u n="725" who="S0084">it's not going to happen</u>
<u n="726" who="S0041">it's not going to happen</u>
<u n="727" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="728" who="S0041">oh I'm quite excited to try my new shoes out</u>
<u n="729" who="S0084">new shoes</u>
<u n="730" who="S0041">new shoes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0084">sounds like <unclear/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0041">I haven't quite got it yet <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it happened all day</u>
<u n="733" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> this is ridiculous isn't it?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0041">I wanted to go to for a run by the river and then I thought well I'll only  I'll only  make it as far as the river and need to turn back again because I can't run that far</u>
<u n="735" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> so then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like why don't you drive down</u>
<u n="737" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0041">just around the corner down to the church is and park your car there and then you'd start near the bridge <pause dur="short"/> I thought yeah I could do that</u>
<u n="739" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0041">but it seems a bit ridiculous for me to have to drive around the corner</u>
<u n="741" who="S0084">it's a bit of waste of your time and petrol</u>
<u n="742" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="743" who="S0084">besides you'd be stuck in traffic jam <pause dur="short"/> you know you could just</u>
<u n="744" who="S0041">no I just go down to the bottom of the street turn left turn right and park</u>
<u n="745" who="S0084">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> well you might  you might  as well just walk back <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? You might as well walk down to the river and run up and down and then walk back</u>
<u n="746" who="S0041">walk back</u>
<u n="747" who="S0084">Cos that's <trunc>y</trunc> your warming up and your cooling down</u>
<u n="748" who="S0041">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="749" who="S0084">and then</u>
<u n="750" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="751" who="S0084">and then you'd be able to tell how much more you can run with each one you do if you run a bigger distance</u>
<u n="752" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="753" who="S0084">um if you're planning to do</u>
<u n="754" who="S0041">I need to do this  I need to do this</u>
<u n="755" who="S0084">yeah even though it's snowing stroke raining</u>
<u n="756" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="757" who="S0084">and the good thing is the night's are getting shorter uh longer</u>
<u n="758" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="759" who="S0084">in fact actually that's just the end of March isn't it the clocks go forward?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh we're nearly there <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="761" who="S0084">we're nearly there <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice sleep but it's light <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="762" who="S0041">aw</u>
<u n="763" who="S0084">I'm a light sleeper obviously</u>
<u n="764" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can do it for that <pause dur="short"/> I can do it</u>
<u n="765" who="S0084">more potatoes?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0041">oh I'd love some more potatoes</u>
<u n="767" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0041">we used to do this after Sunday dinner</u>
<u n="769" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0041">come and have cold roast potatoes</u>
<u n="771" who="S0084">with a bit of a cold gravy</u>
<u n="772" who="S0041">yup <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0084">amazing</u>
<u n="774" who="S0041">thanks  <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0084">oh oh oh you had to dig in <pause dur="short"/> had you?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0041">thanks</u>
<u n="777" who="S0084">thanks great <pause dur="short"/> get out you <pause dur="short"/> get in my belly</u>
<u n="778" who="S0041">hmm hmm hmm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0084">yummy</u>
<u n="780" who="S0041">oh yum</u>
<u n="781" who="S0084">they're a little bit crispy that's good <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="782" who="S0041">winner <pause dur="short"/> actually I think this is how my salt intake started</u>
<u n="783" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0041">because on a Sunday we used to I don't know where I got it from <pause dur="short"/> I don't know who I saw do it but I've done it here you know put a pot pile of salt and dip the whole potatoes in the salt</u>
<u n="785" who="S0084">yeah it's pretty nice <pause dur="short"/> it's a good tip actually <pause dur="short"/> if you're doing the potatoes in the microwave cos you do you can't actually spend two hours <unclear/> the potatoes you can cook them in the microwave or have the oven on til it gets hot so you can cook for ten minutes wrap them in um <trunc>pape</trunc> in a paper towel with olive oil and then um add salt and it crisps it up and you just wrap it in the oven for five minutes and then just makes it a little bit harder rather than having a soft skin <pause dur="short"/> it's a good tip</u>
<u n="786" who="S0041">so you'd cut it up like this?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no you just cook the jacket potato as normal in the microwave however long it takes to cook in the inside then when it's cooked wrap it in um kitchen towel</u>
<u n="788" who="S0041">still whole?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0084" trans="overlap">still whole and then sprinkle <trunc>ol</trunc> um salt and olive oil over it and then wrap it in the oven for five or ten minutes <pause dur="short"/> it just crisps it up</u>
<u n="790" who="S0041">with the paper towel under it?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0084">hmm well that's just to keep the olive oil from running everywhere</u>
<u n="792" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="793" who="S0084">Good tip</u>
<u n="794" who="S0041">rub it on</u>
<u n="795" who="S0084">rub it on</u>
<u n="796" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="797" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> that's the only thing about cooking with the microwave the skins pretty soft</u>
<u n="798" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> just remind me again why potatoes are good for ya?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> carbolicious</u>
<u n="800" who="S0041">such a shame</u>
<u n="801" who="S0084">they're the most addictive carbolicious</u>
<u n="802" who="S0041">are they?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="804" who="S0041">in my head they are <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="805" who="S0084">I think roast potatoes are the best thing ever</u>
<u n="806" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> roast potatoes and freshly cooked bread with butter on</u>
<u n="807" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> oh amazing <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0041">actually it's strange yeah because they're quite a plain taste aren't they?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0041">so it seems strange that they're the things that you'd be like oh</u>
<u n="811" who="S0084">this is really comforting isn't it? Warming and filling</u>
<u n="812" who="S0041">have you ever had um a jacket potato from town on that uh</u>
<u n="813" who="S0084">yeah train stop thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="815" who="S0084">I love it <pause dur="short"/> I actually love it <pause dur="short"/> the one I like is chicken curry with cheese</u>
<u n="816" who="S0041">oh I haven't had that <pause dur="short"/> see I didn't used to eat jacket potatoes</u>
<u n="817" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="818" who="S0041">um and still now really if I'll make them I'll scoop the potato out in the middle</u>
<u n="819" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="820" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I like the <trunc>ski</trunc> it's like this I like the edges</u>
<u n="821" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0041">but these are small</u>
<u n="823" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0041">so I just maybe scoop just the middle chunk of potato out and then my <unclear/> can go in there</u>
<u n="825" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="826" who="S0041">so I still leave like maybe a centimetre of potato around the edge</u>
<u n="827" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="828" who="S0041">um and when I worked at Top Shop the girls at Top Shop were like oh yeah it's really good you need to go there for your lunch <pause dur="short"/> those girls at Top Shop eat like fuck seriously</u>
<u n="829" who="S0084">do they?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0041">uh huh</u>
<u n="831" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0041">uh hmm <pause dur="short"/> it is cos they're so young</u>
<u n="833" who="S0084">hmm and you've got quite an active job when you work in a shop you're running up and down a shop although you've been quite active now but</u>
<u n="834" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="835" who="S0084">maybe less so when you're working in a shop you're constantly running around aren't you?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I don't  I don't know  how where the hell they put it</u>
<u n="837" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="838" who="S0041">but um yeah cos we'd get them and I'd begin one and not finish it and I'm bigger than all of them</u>
<u n="839" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="840" who="S0041">and they'd clear the lot</u>
<u n="841" who="S0084">I know it is good <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's expensive it's three fifty</u>
<u n="842" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="843" who="S0084">for a pair I think wasn't it?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="845" who="S0084">but it was nice <pause dur="short"/> when I worked at <anon type="place"/> it could get a cold cos I worked there from October to March and uh in the winter it was cold at the shop and we'd have to keep the door open cos the <unclear/> was a fucking bitch <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously she's paying for heating and she's the one that it's it's she doesn't care about it escaping she just wants the customers to come in <pause dur="short"/> um so even though <trunc>whe</trunc> I mean when it snowed she relented finally um <vocal desc="cough"/> she made us put a sign on the door that says you know come in we're still open we're just keeping warm <pause dur="short"/> um which <trunc>s</trunc> she copied from Ted Baker cos that's what they did <pause dur="short"/> they put the same sign on the door <pause dur="short"/> um <vocal desc="cough"/> yeah so I used to go and get it and I think I discovered the chicken curry and cheese thing when I went um when I ordered tuna and cheese and they were like tuna oh well loads of the students get chicken curry and cheese <pause dur="short"/> so the cheese goes in first and I like cheese <pause dur="short"/> the cheese goes in so the butter goes in the cheese goes in so cheese melts and the potatoes really hot and then the chicken curry goes on the top <pause dur="short"/> so you've got a nice chicken like nondescript sort of chicken curry which is quite mild but with a bit of a kick to it</u>
<u n="846" who="S0041">yeah a bit like the curry sauce you get from the chips shop <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="847" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically yeah you know fork handed <pause dur="short"/> you dig your fork in till you get chicken curry and melted cheese butter and potato <pause dur="short"/> oh it was amazing</u>
<u n="848" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="849" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="850" who="S0041">that sounds awesome</u>
<u n="851" who="S0084">it was so good <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> really really good</u>
<u n="852" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> winner</u>
<u n="853" who="S0084">I was quite tempted to get one of the hotdog from the sausage company yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you know the red booths?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="855" who="S0084">the hot dogs there are really nice <pause dur="short"/> but they're not cheap</u>
<u n="856" who="S0041">yeah I know</u>
<u n="857" who="S0084">sausages <pause dur="short"/> they're really nice <pause dur="short"/> they're like really meaty</u>
<u n="858" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0084"><unclear/> they're <trunc>l</trunc> the large sausage with cheese and like sweet chilli sauce or something like that</u>
<u n="860" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="861" who="S0084">they've got lots of relishes that they put on <pause dur="short"/> it's large it's probably they're probably the same actually <pause dur="short"/> cos I think the regular is two seventy-five <pause dur="short"/> so the large must be whatever</u>
<u n="862" who="S0041">this place is expensive to live in</u>
<u n="863" who="S0084">it's ridic isn't it? Cos I mean the cost of living considering</u>
<u n="864" who="S0041">if someone</u>
<u n="865" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that <unclear/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's mad <pause dur="short"/> if someone tried to charge four pound for a hotdog where I lived <vocal desc="laugh"/> they'd be like are you taking the piss?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0084">they don't take that</u>
<u n="868" who="S0041">Cos that what they'll tell you <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's a hotdog company thing in the shopping centre in where I went to uni in <anon type="place"/> and it was one twenty</u>
<u n="869" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> was it nice?</u>
<u n="870" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that's for a small size and one seventy for the big one <pause dur="short"/> they were just they were German</u>
<u n="871" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0041">what do you call them?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0084"><unclear/> or something?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> german sausages</u>
<u n="875" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="876" who="S0041">like proper hotdog sausages</u>
<u n="877" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="878" who="S0041">and they're like the bread bun with like a French stick</u>
<u n="879" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="880" who="S0041">and they'd put this thing in it and it took a hole out in the middle that was the perfect size of the sausage and then pop the sausage in</u>
<u n="881" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> yum</u>
<u n="882" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it <trunc>t</trunc> the small was one twenty and the large was like two Pound something</u>
<u n="883" who="S0084">nice <pause dur="short"/> you know you they do that on the market</u>
<u n="884" who="S0041">do they?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0084">with the sausages <unclear/> with those German sausages if you're having hotdogs like that</u>
<u n="886" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="887" who="S0084">not like you put bread in the thing but they you know the it's a German <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's just hotdogs that are from Germany but during the <unclear/> yeah it's pretty nice</u>
<u n="888" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="889" who="S0084">it's been <unclear/> all day that's just probably <unclear/> and most people who were there like like seven days who've gotten <unclear/> when they're there</u>
<u n="890" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> really?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0084">I suppose it's a bit of afar from the hotel</u>
<u n="892" who="S0041">yeah but then wouldn't you starve? That's the thing I don't  I don't  start going somewhere</u>
<u n="893" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="894" who="S0041">I have to get something for lunch cos then I'd want to <unclear/> time <pause dur="short"/> in fact as it stands now if before <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes out and goes to prep <pause dur="short"/> they have to get me the sandwich remember when you me me and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> the first time I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="896" who="S0041">and I had that sandwich and I got two cos I couldn't decide if I could eat two or not</u>
<u n="897" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="898" who="S0041">well it turns out I don't eat two I eat one</u>
<u n="899" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0041">but that's my favourite sandwich now in the world ever</u>
<u n="901" who="S0084">hmm yum</u>
<u n="902" who="S0041">I should never have tried it and now every time they go</u>
<u n="903" who="S0084">it's a slippery slope</u>
<u n="904" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came back one time from prep and she got the prep bags and I said what did you get? She showed me and I was like that's my sandwich</u>
<u n="905" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="906" who="S0041">then she's like I always get this and I was like yeah me too <pause dur="short"/> so now every time one of us goes can you get me one of our sandwiches please?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Aw <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear/> massive obsessed and I didn't have a little <unclear/> Berlin <pause dur="short"/> she was out she would go and she said as soon as she'd get off the plane that was it <pause dur="short"/> she was at Pret eating everything in sight <pause dur="short"/> she's not fussy she likes everything <pause dur="short"/> I think Pret and M and S I believe this is true have the highest salt levels in their sandwiches which I guess is what makes them so <unclear/></u>
<u n="908" who="S0041">that doesn't surprise me</u>
<u n="909" who="S0084">I <unclear/> that's why people really like them M and S</u>
<u n="910" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0084">I mean they're sole addiction</u>
<u n="912" who="S0041">yup <pause dur="short"/> have you seen I saw on the napkins um it said something like particulars like like please enjoy your sandwich or something <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sm</trunc> please feel free to take a napkin um something rather if our Pret workers or Pret A's or whatever they are whatever it said it was like quite quirky um give you a handful</u>
<u n="913" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0041">um as opposed to just the one that you need please give them the eagle eye evil eye</u>
<u n="915" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="916" who="S0041">um we're trying to save the planet or something like <pause dur="short"/> it was a really cute little thing and I was like no way</u>
<u n="917" who="S0084">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0041">please please give our workers the evil eye so if they basically thrust them at you</u>
<u n="919" who="S0084">fine will do hence take the napkin</u>
<u n="920" who="S0041">sounds a bit normal <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's quite nice</u>
<u n="921" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="922" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0084">oh I thought it was a Milky Way underneath the fridge the freezer I bet it's not that it actually a spanner <pause dur="short"/> it's not a spanner what do you call it?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0041">oh screw</u>
<u n="925" who="S0084">screwdriver</u>
<u n="926" who="S0041">screwdriver</u>
<u n="927" who="S0084">I just saw it winking at me and I thought it was a sign of the Milky Way</u>
<u n="928" who="S0041">oh I would really love some Milky Way right now <pause dur="short"/> in fact if it wasn't raining I think I would walk to the shop for a Milky Way right now</u>
<u n="929" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="930" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/> You ever had their Milky Way yoghurts?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> there's Milky Way yoghurts? It tastes <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0041">uh blimey <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="933" who="S0084">tell me</u>
<u n="934" who="S0041">please don't I'm so sorry they're awful</u>
<u n="935" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I bet they're disgusting</u>
<u n="936" who="S0041">they really are awful they're the worst thing I've ever tried in my life ever</u>
<u n="937" who="S0084">why don't we have any chocolate in the house?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="939" who="S0084">for this reason</u>
<u n="940" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="941" who="S0084">Cos you will eat the chocolate</u>
<u n="942" who="S0041">I'd eat all the chocolate <pause dur="short"/> I'm afraid so</u>
<u n="943" who="S0084">ah did you watch any?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0041">do you think?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0084" trans="overlap">sorry?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0041">I was going to say do you think you could deliver online? Like when we ordered the chicken? Do you think they'd deliver us chocolate?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0084">possibly but we might have to bulk buy in which case you've might have to have crates of Milky Way and we might not ever</u>
<u n="948" who="S0041">ever fit out the door</u>
<u n="949" who="S0084">work tomorrow</u>
<u n="950" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Comatose</u>
<u n="951" who="S0084">passed out</u>
<u n="952" who="S0041">I didn't no I didn't</u>
<u n="953" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="954" who="S0041">watch them</u>
<u n="955" who="S0084">oh you didn't <unclear/> them for a while that's fine</u>
<u n="956" who="S0041">I definitely need to do it with my life</u>
<u n="957" who="S0084">I heard it <unclear/> tonight <vocal desc="yawn"/> what time is it?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0041">quarter to seven</u>
<u n="959" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> ow</u>
<u n="960" who="S0041">ouch</u>
<u n="961" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> oh it's it's heavy</u>
<u n="962" who="S0041">oh they broke  they broke</u>
<u n="963" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="964" who="S0041">well where's the little thing?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0084">you can get them mended it's fine</u>
<u n="966" who="S0041">yeah I'll have to take it somewhere and</u>
<u n="967" who="S0084">aw <pause dur="short"/> yeah you've lost a side haven't you?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah I didn't it was on here <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> it's obviously gone <pause dur="short"/> oh there it is</u>
<u n="969" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah it's just uh</u>
<u n="970" who="S0041">Cos I <trunc>t</trunc> thought about just getting some super glue</u>
<u n="971" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="972" who="S0041">and gluing it back on</u>
<u n="973" who="S0084">it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> it's really heavy</u>
<u n="974" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> pretty</u>
<u n="975" who="S0084">it's really pretty and very nice</u>
<u n="976" who="S0041">very nice <pause dur="short"/> I think I might um</u>
<u n="977" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="978" who="S0041">I want to just snuggle up on into bed but then I know I won't get up and get in the shower and I didn't get in the shower <trunc>yest</trunc> I got in the shower yesterday morning</u>
<u n="979" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="980" who="S0041">so definitely need to wash</u>
<u n="981" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="982" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I'm so tired <pause dur="short"/> I think I've only had five hours sleep Friday night and then Dan woke me up at six this morning and I only</u>
<u n="983" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="984" who="S0084">went back to bed after midnight <pause dur="short"/> I'm knackered</u>
<u n="985" who="S0041">def yeah well I fell asleep this afternoon didn't I? Just watching TV just sleeping on me</u>
<u n="986" who="S0084">uh hmm <pause dur="short"/> aawh</u>
<u n="987" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="988" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="989" who="S0041">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying I don't know <trunc>w</trunc> this came into my head cos he was texting me when I was falling asleep which was I was quite of a hmm hmm hmm thing <pause dur="short"/> um he was saying something like he was texting me when I was drunk the other night and he said so how many like how much would you give your bum I was like yeah I think it's a solid eight</u>
<u n="990" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="991" who="S0041">Cos definitely not I have no bum at all</u>
<u n="992" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="993" who="S0041">um then he was like oh you're pretty confident <pause dur="short"/> yeah of course I am <pause dur="short"/> he said well I'm quite excited to see it cos I would have given  I would have given  your bum a nine before that</u>
<u n="994" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="995" who="S0041">but even before and I was like oh yeah and he said um he was like or maybe an eight maybe an eight and a half definitely I would give your boobs a ten though</u>
<u n="996" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0041">yeah and do you know I get that quite a lot from from guys?</u>
<u n="998" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="999" who="S0041"><trunc>Y</trunc> you know you've got perfect boobs</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0041">which is is a nice thing to hear</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0041">Cos these are boobs</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0041">like really</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0084">there's nothing you can do about them</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0041">so it was quite  it was quite  a bit of a hmm <pause dur="short"/> that he thought I was sexy before I started losing weight</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0041">so that's nice</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0041">that's was like a definitely an ego boost</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0084">yeah a confident boost</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0041">an ego boost</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0041">after uh <trunc>th</trunc> the plummeting of the ego at the weekend</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0041">so that was pretty good</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0041"><trunc>I</trunc> it was a requirement <pause dur="short"/> it was a good kind a requirement</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0041">I think</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> it was yeah it went quite well with the timing</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0084">with all the</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0041">with all the</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> perfect timing</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0084">in other words it's quite nice isn't it? Cos you don't get to talk all the time when you do go and you run into him</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0041">yeah and it means that</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0041">the only thing is the only thing I'm concerned about is I didn't does he I didn't know that he was friends with those lot</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1035" who="S0041">and so</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0084">with them or something?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and so now I'm a bit like oh crap if he tells them what we did we it was quite filthy</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0084">I don't think he will <pause dur="short"/> I mean even if he <trunc>d</trunc> does I mean he's a complete cock and</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0084">you can't ever have sex with him again</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0084">you won't even if you can't have sex with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I think I might send him a message before I got to sleep later and just say</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0041">I'm pre warning you</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0041">make sure you do not tell</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0041">the ones you've slept with</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0084">I mean I don't know if blokes do that though</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0041">Cos they obviously know that I've slept with him</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0084">do blokes do that?</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0041">well they knew because when we were when I was about to leave I got a message saying where you know where did you go? And I was like I'm still in the pub <pause dur="short"/> he was like oh shit I just left um we well you know you've been ignoring me and I said well it's just really awkward</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0084">hmm and it's not like he came over and spoke to you</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0041">well he did try</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0084">did he?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0084">did you just ignore him?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I said hi and like yeah are you alright? And then huh</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why I just felt really uncomfortable because</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0084">that's really embarrassing isn't it? Yeah</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't know <trunc>no</trunc> none of the people I was with knew</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I'd confessed to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she was like why is he saying hi and I was like oh I kind of slept with him <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh about that</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0084">I slept with his cock</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0041">I certainly did that</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0041">um but the guys that he had sat with</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0041">like I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I noticed and he well he doesn't usually smoke and he came out for a cigarette with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1072" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0041">and his mates again twice when he fucking saw that I was out there and I thought like hmm you know what I'm going to do I've going to talk to you <pause dur="short"/> so I feel strange now but when when he said oh I've gone now I passed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and  are having a baby <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother is the footballer that the footballer with him that I don't talk to very often</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0041">so they all kinda know each other</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0084">hmm it's quite tenuous though</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like five lads all sat round</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0041">but I don't really know them very much but they they know me <pause dur="short"/> I could see them in town and say hi how you doing?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0041">if I see them in the pub I say hello and I run then I don't speak to them again unless I'm really fucked because I don't know them <pause dur="short"/> I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a lot</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0041">and he was sat with them which is the link between <trunc>m</trunc> me and him via someone else and I said I passed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother who I don't speak to unless I'm drunk <pause dur="short"/> I was like so I where'd your friend go? And he was like my uh my friend and I was like yeah blondie looked about twelve years old</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0041">and he was like I know exactly who you're asking about and I was like so are you going to answer my question? He was just winding me up and he was like and I know why you're asking and I said do you now? And he was like yeah and he's got a massive smirk on his face and I was like well I don't know what you're talking about</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0041">so and he was like yeah whatever thinking it was funny and I'm thinking why would you do that?</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0041">why would you do that?</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0041">but it's obviously cos I was <unclear/> and I really wasn't expecting to see you <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really think you <trunc>drin</trunc> drink there</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0041">I said well I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't live there</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0041">and I don't live in the village I'll come up every few weeks to catch up with my friends and that's it <pause dur="short"/> I said did you not hear the jib I got when I walked in?</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0041">Cos I'm making a massive deal about you've got a passport to get on <vocal desc="laugh"/> get out of <anon type="place"/> and all that and wherever you being and he was like oh yeah I did  I did  hear that so there you go then</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0041">but I don't want him to go back cos <trunc>t</trunc> they will now know that I went over there</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0041">I just that's fine they cannot know the details <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it would be bad</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0084">no I don't think anyone's going to know I mean unless he's a massive knob like he might enjoy the fact that oh yeah I bedded her because they A they all know you <pause dur="short"/> b you know you're quite a good looking girl and that it's you know it's boys being boys</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0084">and like not brag about it but just be like yeah well you're you</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0041">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0084">but they will probably unless they're a complete knob to not divulging your darkest secrets</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0084">Cos it reflects on them as well</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping that's the case</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0046"></u>
<u n="1112" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> have you been back for your hard drive yet?</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0046">I'm not going to be there on seventh and I'm not going to be</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0084">well why would you be</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0046">just on after seven</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0084">why don't you just give her a text that you'll go round on tomorrow cos the weather's shit?</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0046">no she's busy tomorrow</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0046">and so I said or I'll come round tomorrow when you haven't got your kids</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0046">Cos she said no it's either tonight or Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> so I'd rather get it out of the way <pause dur="short"/> it's quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="1124" who="S0084">it's pretty bad out there though <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know it sounds a lot worse out there than here</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0046">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> I'll be fine <pause dur="short"/> I won't be long</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0084">it's not far is it?</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0084">on a bus</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0046">I can't be late</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0084">I've got more wine in the cupboard</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>Pinot <pause dur="short"/> pinot<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1134" who="S0084">it's the weekend</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>Las Vegas<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1136" who="S0046">it is</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>Pinot<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1138" who="S0046">it is also a <unclear/> out there</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0084">for some people</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0046"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1141" who="S0084">not me</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0046">really?</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0084">um <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> well it depends <pause dur="short"/> do you think that this one has aged well? This is the one that Nicki brought round around about a month ago</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0084">should we just open it up and see</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0041">let's crack it and see</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0084">nice <pause dur="short"/> let it sit for a while <pause dur="short"/> it might just have fermented really nicely</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0041">might be just be like the port now eh?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0046"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1150" who="S0084">port <pause dur="short"/> a bit of fortified wine anyone?</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0041">anybody? Yeah so in fact I <trunc>m</trunc> might do that now so it's not late <pause dur="short"/> so I know he's definitely going to be awake and get the just keep the details to yourself</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0041">message gone <pause dur="short"/> make sure it's a closed message so it doesn't require a reply cos I don't want to invite him into a conversation</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0084">fine <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0046">is this the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> this is</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0084">oh sorry love</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0084">oh I was going to answer on your behalf when you left the room</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0084">then you responded</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0041">um no no this is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number two</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0046">I don't know any <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1165" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number one being the army one</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0046"><unclear/> oh okay</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number two being the blonde that was around here the one that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1168" who="S0046">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0084">blonde child</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0041">the blonde child</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0084">very attractive blonde</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>t</trunc> I think I was trying to think if he's the fittest person that I've bedded but I don't I can't remember</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1174" who="S0041">I mean not that I can't remember the people <vocal desc="laugh"/> that I've slept with <pause dur="short"/> but I'm just trying to sum up you you're not going for a cigarette are ya?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0046">oh no I've got one</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0041">jeez I thought you were going to go out there</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0046">well I've got to go out there in a bit anyway I'll just get my coat</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0041">yeah <trunc>h</trunc> he's up there  he's up there  with the good ones</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number two</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number two certainly is well he's hotter than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number one to look at but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number one is hotter as in</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0084">overruled</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0084">the complete package</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0041">right as a person he's a complete package</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0084">well you had you did get to know Matt number one whereas Matt number two you were refusing to get to know</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0041">well the</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0084">for a good reason</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0041">I know Matt number two <trunc>w</trunc> which I am obviously refusing to get to know for a reason <pause dur="short"/> he uh um just the the way he says things and the way he acts is a little bit childish <pause dur="short"/> like he's twenty-four but he uses the word loser quite a lot which is fine cos I you know I use stupid words</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0041">but you know I was told no go out with him answer it <pause dur="short"/> I cos I wanted to see what he was like</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0041">um he was just it was he reminded me of kind of teenage conversation?</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0046">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0041">do you know what I mean? Like I could never spend a lot of time with him <pause dur="short"/> I mean in the car on the way back <pause dur="short"/> we were in the car for about twenty minutes and I got on with it and it was a laugh but I would never consider him as a love interest</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0046"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1197" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> as hot as he is unless he was a mute a bit like David Beckham</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0041">but not as thick <pause dur="short"/> he's not as thick</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0084">David I mean David he's pretty spesh</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0041">yeah he's pretty spesh</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0084">but he's really hot</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm well the fave list Matt number two pretty hot</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0041">pretty buff</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0084">I mean you could tell that in his little cardigan couldn't you?</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> he's built well</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> it must be a lot of sports</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0041">football</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0041">yeah you'd think</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0084">so he must have hit the gym then <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know some blokes are quite broad generally and don't have to do</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0046">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0084">a lot of work out</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0084"><unclear/> whereas he was really broad and quite muscular in his shoulder but never worked out</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0084">he just had they just it was quite fortunate</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> they are so loaded</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0084">I mean really they just got that built</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> whereas um yeah Matt number one was more all round but <trunc>a</trunc> also you know certainly wouldn't watch question time whatever it is</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0084">the Big Question?</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0041">the Big Question which is a killer really</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0041">Cos you like that don't you?</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0041">you like that bit of a niceness</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0084">it's pretty low I mean it's quite nice there was no sort of uh well pff it's nine AM probably time for you to get your knickers on</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0041">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1231" who="S0084">and get out <pause dur="short"/> um there was none of it not until like the afternoon he said I've got to go do this thing with the <unclear/> boys yeah I've got a  I've got a  do a few things <pause dur="short"/> I was supposed to go to see my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> today and have dinner and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1232" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0084">but she's got a stinking cold so</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0041">nice</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0084">so in my head it's more like right well I've got to leave by lunch time probably and then she text me and said oh no I've I'm too poorly so then I was like well I haven't really got any plans because but you know I've got to get out so right two o'clock afterwards we stayed out of the rain together</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0084">and the day before I was like okay it's a bit weird now maybe we should not be doing the couple thing <pause dur="short"/> um just got my stuff and left <pause dur="short"/> but it is I mean <trunc>i</trunc> it's really hard cos even though in your head you're like no you don't want a boyfriend and you sort of fall into that rhythm naturally <pause dur="short"/> I mean I <trunc>lit</trunc> unless you literally do the hotel shag and leave again</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0084">the more time you spend with someone the more you get to know them the more you care for them like</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0041">yeah even just in a conversation with someone</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0041">even if you just spend more time in a conversation with someone you automatically</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0041">without wanting to <pause dur="short"/> you know more about them</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0084">it's quite an attachment</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0041">and you see which bits who touched who</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's so hard</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0084">it is hard and I think cos even the first time I met him when I was noticing that he was quite skinny and he was saying things that alarmed me <pause dur="short"/> he was saying when he started to train obviously he bulks up and then then he can eat whatever he likes but hmm mostly um he was quite careful with what he eats and he was saying like he lost a bit of weight on his tummy and it was just generally all over cos he's sort of cut back on the food and he really liked how he looked <pause dur="short"/> so he just kept not eating properly and just really cut another food and really enjoyed getting skinner and skinner and I was like you know this is what people with eating disorders say</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0084">you know <trunc>t</trunc> they like the fact that they're disappearing before their very eyes and it motivates them to not eat any food because that's</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0084">what spurs them on and he said yeah I know  I know  it does sound a bit wrong and yeah I am trying you know and I think he really took it to heart which I didn't realise at the time like you say these things and you just think people don't hear your comments</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0084">and it's more because you don't him describing it that way worried me cos I thought it sounds like you might be verging on having a problem and he said well I do know because I'm aware that I'm aware of it you know because it's not like I don't see it <pause dur="short"/> um so yeah when you do start to care for people and</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0084">he was talking about his kids and he was like you know I can't have them here and would it be nice to sort of meet and whatever <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously I'm not ready to meet his kids thank God</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> winner</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0084">um so yeah I do it feels good to know him <pause dur="short"/> I mean we have a really nice time together <pause dur="short"/> but that's all I want to keep it as <pause dur="short"/> but at the same time you're like a part of you does want to be the booty call and part of you doesn't <pause dur="short"/> it's hard isn't it? You know you think well why don't you want to ask me on a date? And then when he does you're like <unclear/> we're not doing that we're not doing the date thing <pause dur="short"/> so I think you know I sort of feel for him <pause dur="short"/> he just can't really win</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0084">but we'll see</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean uh I suppose you won't the more time you spend with him</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0041">then the more secure you'll be in your decision as to whether you want to pursue this as a date situation</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0084">possibly it could be</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0041">or whether you want to keep it as a friends with benefits situation</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0041">but right now I don't think there's any any disadvantage to keeping him at arm's length on it</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0041">until you're sure before you take the <trunc>l</trunc> the leap</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0041">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0084">I mean because really this is what always happens like when I was with <unclear/> for a few months and it wasn't just similar to this you know although we never had the initial conversation that I'm not looking for love it was more let's got a few dates and let's time together and when then I started to realised it wasn't quite what I wanted <pause dur="short"/> whereas in this instance</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0041">should I get my fleece</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0084" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0041">I'm freezing <pause dur="short"/> sorry dear go on <pause dur="short"/> whereas in this instance?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0084">um yeah from the off we both said no we're not looking for anything and so he does really nice things <trunc>c</trunc> he ask me round to dinner he cooks me dinner and I when the night he's not going to kick me out in the morning and you know we we watch movies together <pause dur="short"/> we have nice chats <trunc>w</trunc> none of which I'm reading anything into</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0084">but you inevitably you are spending a lot of time with one person that</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0084">or you know you just  you just  don't wanna I don't wanna really sit in a position where I let myself start thinking oh maybe he is interested and then I tell him and be like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1282" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0084">a girlfriend?</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0084">so um I guess it's just a case of taking it at face value <pause dur="short"/> trying not to be the crazy one</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0041">yup</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0084">it's always a bit of a challenge</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0041">which do you know what I think? In each relationship there's always one crazy one</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0041">do you know what I think? There's always one crazy one</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0084">yeah and invariably it's me <pause dur="short"/> um I think</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0041">well no it's <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0084">I mean I have met a few crazy blokes in my time let's be honest Doctor Phil</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0041">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had been more crazy than you from what you said</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0084">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that was pretty crazy <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0041">I think he probably had more craziness in him</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0041">and I think the crazy person shifts as well</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0041">like initially with with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was the crazy one</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0041">Cos I was like really like him</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0041">which in hindsight was very intense and actually really unlike me but maybe that is because I'd just finished things with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1305" who="S0084">possibly but then he was giving you the signs for you to do that</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0084">like you would have never had done that had he not encouraged it</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> and then he was the crazy one</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0084">he was saying all the stuff that you know I want you to be my girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> I want you to commit to me and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0084">and then he went mental</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Actual mental</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0084">and then you realised that he was the mental one all along</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's the killer and the mental ones  but um</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0084">and you just get on with him so well</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> okay so this message I wrote just said</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0041">say hi hope you had fun the other night um I know lads will be lads but please don't mention details to anyone</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0041">that's enough isn't it?</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0084">that's it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0041">gone</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0084">that's fine</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0041">oh shit <pause dur="short"/> that's sent to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number one</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0084">oh oh</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was like <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1327" who="S0084">that's dangerous</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> it's quite dangerous <pause dur="short"/> living life on the edge</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0084">life on the edge <pause dur="short"/> my sister texted me earlier and she said oh I went to my mum yesterday and <unclear/> was at work <pause dur="short"/> she sent me a message saying hi just a quick question <pause dur="short"/> I got a package in my room yesterday in a <unclear/> and I know that she had a friend stay in last night <pause dur="short"/> I said no it wasn't me it must have been <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her friend <pause dur="short"/> is it something nice? No I'm confused <pause dur="short"/> I got home from work yesterday and found a package on my bed <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was something that I ordered but I checked it today and it's for next door but I didn't put it there and mum says she didn't either</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0084">I know <pause dur="short"/> freaky eh? I'm hoping it's my mum and that she's just forgotten <pause dur="short"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> brought it in with her <unclear/> like she found it at the door and she just brought it in</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0084">completely <unclear/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but it's a bit weird</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0041">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1335" who="S0084">one of them has done it and forgot it or <unclear/></u>
<u n="1336" who="S0041">one of them should own up before you start you know accusing people of breaking and entering</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0084">possibly</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0041">probably</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0041">probably wise <pause dur="short"/> uh does it this nail polish is cracked</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0084">is it?</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0041">I put it on this afternoon it's already</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0041">shit look at that</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0084">pretty shame</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0041">huh <pause dur="short"/> cos I prefer to wear dark nail polish but I get told off for it at work <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0084">oh bastards</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0041">bloody bastards  bloody bastards  has <unclear/> gone? Has he gone to get his thing?</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0084"><unclear/> why would you?</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0041">no idea  no idea</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0084"><unclear/> the same actually isn't it? He doesn't need it?</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0084">but in the short term</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> actually I don't know even why he's even going there cos the plan was going to be that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bag isn't he? Cos he hasn't been around here yet</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0084">he did say he was collecting a bag so yeah I suppose that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0041">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was gonna go for him but he didn't say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> in his hard drive</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0084">so yeah so</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0041">oh are you preparing?</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0046">I haven't been <unclear/></u>
<u n="1360" who="S0084">have you em brushed your teeth?</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0046">not since the <unclear/> cos I don't give a shit</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0046">I don't give a shit what she thinks <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0041">are you taking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bag with you or is he coming to get it?</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0046">I'm not taking it I know I'm going out <unclear/> and after the rain <unclear/> think that he was going to come and get it</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0041">fair enough</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0046">uh yeah <unclear/> so I've gotta go</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> good luck</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0046">I'm going to need it <pause dur="short"/> I might even get my <trunc>a</trunc> ass handed to me or it's just going to be hi bye</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0041">I'd go for hi bye and run if it was me</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0046">I would <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'll see</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0041">Good luck</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0084">see you soon</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0046">bye</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0041">why is he taking the tea towel with him?</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0084">to wipe off his bike I think</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0084">Wise taking the tea towel</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0084">hi <unclear/></u>
<u n="1383" who="S0041">hi <unclear/></u>
<u n="1384" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1385" who="S0041">yes so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to go and knock on the door and say oh and he was going to text her at first but I know</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0046">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1387" who="S0041">bye <pause dur="short"/> just to let her know that he was coming</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to say oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s lent me his hard drive for this evening can I  can I  take it? Which would have been wise really</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely it means he didn't have to see her and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives very close by</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0084">or</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to come here to get his bag anyway so that would be very</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0084" trans="overlap">this is part of the I don't trust <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with my ex scenario</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0041">maybe</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0084">or is it just an <trunc>exc</trunc> or maybe it's</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0041">or maybe it's I love I don't want <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be there cos so I can see some more drama</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0041">which is also ah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to her um he said to her basically whatever <pause dur="short"/> bye <pause dur="short"/> fuck off</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0041">talk to you never <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0084">never yeah</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0041" trans="overlap">unless you're pregnant <pause dur="short"/> yeah so he's like  he's like  oh well just just but just get in touch with me when you've done the pregnancy test yeah uh bit of a concern and then I heard him last night to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I think he said it out out of ear shot to me <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't at all <pause dur="short"/> um but said well if she's pregnant then I've told her that I'll be there no matter what you know <pause dur="short"/> what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1404" who="S0084">but he loves her?</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0041">what <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0084">doesn't he? Yeah cos he loved her but you say it</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0041">this crazy girl</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0084">because it's the right thing to say doesn't he?</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0084">he thinks that that's what is a good person would do and you think</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0084">what's the fucking matter with you?</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0041">so if the crazy girl says yeah I'm in a sprug he's going to go great <pause dur="short"/> let's do this</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0084">let's go tell her but she's the one who says she doesn't want to <pause dur="short"/> he don't he would absolutely have no idea where he really stands because day to day she's telling him different things</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0084">I mean it does uh it does worry me that there are quite as many crazy ladies <pause dur="short"/> I mean we obviously all joke that we're crazy</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0084">to some varying degree but let's say that we're not totally fucking blimey</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0041">no we're not</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0084">in fact <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was telling me today another <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> story I apologise in advance</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0041">nah I'm enjoying</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0084">um <vocal desc="cough"/> obviously he's got a crazy ex</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0084">so they</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0041">it's not the same as <unclear/></u>
<u n="1426" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's always time for <unclear/> as one does <pause dur="short"/> so they were together on and off <pause dur="short"/> she's a bit of a psycho he was <unclear/> with some Samaritans</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0084">because he had a break down <pause dur="short"/> apparently he was on the phone to <unclear/> cos they just has a massive row <pause dur="short"/> he was in the living room and the woman on the end of the phone is saying Dan are you okay? And he's like I I don't know  I don't know  She's saying do you feel trapped? And he said yes and burst into tears <pause dur="short"/> his ex girlfriend is on the stairs laughing at him</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1430" who="S0084">and she's they had a massive row <pause dur="short"/> she's made him <trunc>cr</trunc> pushed him to the floor where he's on the phone I can't take it anymore  I can't take it anymore  I don't know what to do <pause dur="short"/> they've got two kids <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>he</trunc> he's crying</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0041">oh my God</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0084">she's laughing at him because she knows exactly how to push his buttons in</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0041">what a dick</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0084">what a dick <pause dur="short"/> so he leaves um and then <trunc>b</trunc> much like this they're mental and they get back together he <trunc>s</trunc> they shag <pause dur="short"/> she has been telling him that she's on the pill and she has been ever since the previous child was born so who's two at this point I think cos three years between them <pause dur="short"/> he says can you just take the morning after pill just in case <pause dur="short"/> they just got back together and she's like yeah absolutely good I'll definitely do that tomorrow because I definitely don't want any more babies <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> he's made a decision to go back there and then he's like oh and then obviously she called me like three weeks later and turns out that she's pregnant and uh</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she was lying</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0041">oh my God</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0084">the whole time about being on the pill <pause dur="short"/> the whole time <pause dur="short"/> never obviously took that morning after pill she was like yeah of course yeah I know no wants new babies quick cook me a baby</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0041">oh my good gosh</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0084">yes they never got back together <pause dur="short"/> so their this third child came along and they're no longer in a relationship together</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0084">he thinks she's a fucking psycho</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0041">well <trunc>sh</trunc> she's a quite clearly a fucking psycho</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0084">yeah but then he was like uh it's all her fault and I was like well you could have used a Johnny to be fair</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0084">and he was like yeah well I never did you know yeah point taken while we were together for a while we never did <pause dur="short"/> so it just seemed weird like I trusted her</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0084">that she was on the pill</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0041">well yeah</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0084">I suppose you would really <pause dur="short"/> I said well you know <trunc>y</trunc> you'd seen that she was a bit of a psycho but you did go back that was possibly an error before <unclear/> and he'd had a shit time with her parents boo boo boo and I think he really wanted to stay for the kids he was like I just didn't want to leave and I suppose that's probably what a lot of it is with dads you know it's not fair</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0084">if they leave they're it's game over really</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0041">they're the bad person really</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0041">and that's the end of that</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0084">they only see their kids once a month</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0084">um <vocal desc="cough"/> so yeah so the kid's come along <pause dur="short"/> so she is I think they're seven ten and thirteen? Possibly something like that? So they're not  they're not  young young</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0084">but yeah it is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1461" who="S0041">and you were saying he was getting custody of one of them?</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0084">he's getting custody of the son eventually he will get custody of all of them but where he lives now they've been told they can't even have the kids to visit <pause dur="short"/> cos at first I was really I didn't believe him and I was like no no no you can't write that into a tenancy agreement</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0084">and he said when he'd had the kids around before and someone shocked him they called the agency and the agency like a representative came round and said you can't have kids there <pause dur="short"/> so they live in <unclear/> with their psycho mum and so if he gets them he's got to spend the entire day out</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0041">out</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0084">with them</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0084">I never realised it was <unclear/> What are you going to do with them? You've got three kids you've got to entertain</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0041">that's a lot</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0084">so he's moving somewhere else</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0041">that's a lot to take on <pause dur="short"/> three kids</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0041">outside all day <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> all day</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0041">more financially and <trunc>mo</trunc> like physically and mentally exhausting</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0084"><trunc>Y</trunc> exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I think he's gonna take <pause dur="short"/> he's on the house and his friend's and I was a bit like mixed feelings about that but</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0084">you know he's ultimately it's about the kids isn't it?</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0041">yeah that's it why not be?</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0084">if the kids aren't getting a good upbringing</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0084">with the wife?</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0084">then or ex wife whatever she is <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if they were married</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0041">yeah like I'm not saying automatically go to house and <unclear/> but if that's actually</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0084">the short term</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0041">what's going to be best for them</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0041">then</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0084">exactly</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0041">that's what it's there for isn't it really?</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0084">the <trunc>l</trunc> their landlord is selling the house where he's living now so he's been evicted and that he's he said oh I've got to out on the fourth of March and he said I'm really sorry to have to tell you this Dan but that's today and he was like oh right <pause dur="short"/> so his eviction notice is today <pause dur="short"/> he's got to be out of the house by today</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0041">is he packed?</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> he's got no intention of leaving</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh my God</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0084">so at the moment he's squatting in his humble house his skin is giving him some sort of weird allergic reaction</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0041">he's squatting in his own house?</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0084">yeah which again</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0084">normal <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0041">I mean and he has thought about worst case scenario <unclear/> where the hell he's gonna go?</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0084">umm I don't think he's thought that far ahead</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0041">yeah?</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0084">um but <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean part of him is like well I suppose I've got <trunc>b</trunc> but you don't want to</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0084">go down that road</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0084">and uh I mean unless he's literally on the streets</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0041">if he comes to that point yeah of</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0084">I'm not going to see anyone on the street are you? I mean I don't want to sort of go down that road ruse</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0041">you don't want to offer that as an option</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0041">until he gets to the point of he's like shit and then you say okay then</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0084">exactly <pause dur="short"/> but he's been served his eviction notice and so the social have put him on band A and if you think how much drama Emily really he had to go through to get bumped to band A and just <trunc>y</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0084">he's out there you think God yeah she's getting physically abused at home</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0084">I suppose maybe she wasn't telling him the full</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0041">no she wasn't</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0084"><unclear/> was she?</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0041">and fooled the doctor's there as well</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0084">fuck</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0084">I thought it's cos she didn't want to report her mum</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0084">I thought she didn't have a police</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0084">notice to show that is what it was yeah</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0041">she had police reports against him on but she hadn't pressed charges that's the only thing she didn't do</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0084">God</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mental</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0084">really mental <pause dur="short"/> so yes so he's waiting for a house and then the son will come to live with him and then I suppose his in his head the plan is eventually all of them will come and live with him</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0084">because the mum's totally unstable <pause dur="short"/> umm I think he's worried cos his psycho parents he has also weird parents that don't talk to the children <pause dur="short"/> or like try and turn them against him <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously you've got to take it all with a pinch of salt <pause dur="short"/> I don't know this guy so well</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0041">his point of view <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0084">and all I get is his perspective so all of it I was hoping just so I'm not going to question him <pause dur="short"/> I don't know him well enough <pause dur="short"/> I'm not going <unclear/> that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0041">you just kind of uh you agree don't ya?</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0084"><trunc>Y</trunc> yah</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0041">go along with it</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0084">and in your head you're going what the fuck?</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0084">but um it's weird <pause dur="short"/> I thought everything in his life is weird and completely unstable</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0041">oh?</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0084">umm so yeah I think thinking that <unclear/> a good thing like once he's got his son with him he'll have to have a more stable job <pause dur="short"/> you know I was saying to him why don't you do now that you're qualified instructor like why don't you do the um fitness coach? And he was like oh I don't know</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0041">there's shit loads of jobs for it</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0041">load and loads and loads</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0041">every time I used to get emails online like</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0041">twenty percent of all the jobs</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0041">were fitness instructors</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0084">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> especially around here <pause dur="short"/> there's so much money <pause dur="short"/> so many people will pay for a personal instructor</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0084">that actually is and he'll be laughing and he obviously like his job is like Craig's if the weather is shit he can't work cos it's really unstable and he's</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0041">and the extra <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and he's got kids</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0041">fitness instructor without a gym in near near <unclear/> Lane?</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0041">not that I've seen him for about four years <pause dur="short"/> but I went to uni with him when I moved down here and he was like you're in Cambridge?</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>H</trunc> However</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0084">why?</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0041">it's just a silly name from uni cos he used that word a lot</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0084">ha</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0041">but his name's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> ben <trunc>H</trunc> However is also another way that we called him <pause dur="short"/> um but yeah in this <unclear/> down here so he's a bit  he's a bit  of a weirdo <pause dur="short"/> I don't really wanna meet him</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0041">Cos I can't really gauge what he's going to be like now <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0041">he's very friendly <pause dur="short"/> very kind of happy chappy <pause dur="short"/> if it was something this guy wants to do I'm sure he'd  I'm sure he'd  help if he could</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean if it's I mean there's two options I suppose aren't they? You know either try and find a job in gym</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0084">or be a private instructor</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0084">then you have to advertise yourself</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0084">and I think that's for him</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0041">and it's full time</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0084">it's partly the issue</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0041">and it's still going to be a irregular</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0084">exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's just a lot of effort <pause dur="short"/> you might be working weekends you know and I think that's what puts him off <pause dur="short"/> like the <unclear/> the money is so good but it means work and he doesn't want to work weekends</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0084">unless it's an emergency but any kind of job where you're self employed <pause dur="short"/> it's not going to be stable is it?</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0084">or if you've got a kiddie <pause dur="short"/> you've got to think about them</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0041">God <pause dur="short"/> do you know what it sounds like? In the nicest possible way <pause dur="short"/> you know the popcorn that you get that you put in the microwave?</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1594" who="S0041">pop pop pop pop pop there's all this goodness coming out</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0084">I don't know it's quite difficult to tell isn't it?</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0084">Cos he seems like a genuine person which is quite nice but there's no sort of</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0041">and quite rare</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not I was <unclear/> about him that I quite like I'd go just like meeting someone and then seeing everything</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0084">there's nothing hidden with him</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0041">that's so refreshing</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot going on uh there's a lot to him which you wouldn't which you won't get to know in a short period of time like I'm sure there's loads that would take me years to get to know <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0084">he doesn't hide anything which I find quite refreshing</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0084">I suppose where the mind goes</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0041">that's what you need though isn't it?</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0041">like I don't really I think uh I was a bit naive because I've never really entertained any idea of a boy</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0041">at all before <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1613" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0041">apart from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> which you know we both knew I was there for another five six months</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0041">we saw each other for a <trunc>l</trunc> for a month and then we were together for three and a half months three four months something like that</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0041">and lived in each other's pockets <pause dur="short"/> it was very intense <pause dur="short"/> it was very full on and we both knew exactly what we were doing you know I met his family then they came up and I cooked them like apple pie something really English and</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0041">you know he would always invite me to go down and stay <pause dur="short"/> we both knew that as intense as it was it was temporary</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0084">Short term</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0041">we both signed up for that <pause dur="short"/> but before him nah I didn't keep on anyone <pause dur="short"/> it was very much a not a hotel room <trunc>situ</trunc></u>
<u n="1625" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0041">but cos he was <trunc>friend</trunc> with people that I was friends with</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0041">that I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>w</trunc> we did that the whole kind of friends with benefits thing on and off since we were sixteen</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0041">till being twenty-two</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0041">which is quite a long time for a friends with benefits situation</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>f</trunc> for not for both of you not to have entered into a relationship at that time</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0041">well he did but he was cheap</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0041">and I never slept with him while he was with her but they were on and off a bit like this Jeremy Kyle thing <pause dur="short"/> she was a child and I don't know what the hell he was doing with him cos he's not he's lovely</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0041">full of himself</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0041">but in the way that I knew  I knew  him and it wasn't actually true</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0041">and if he tried to pull it I'd just knock him down a pick or two</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0041">cos we've known each other since we were about thirteen <pause dur="short"/> he was actually my first boyfriend that my mum met</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0084">aaw that's quite cute</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> obviously she didn't know that he wasn't my real boyfriend but we didn't care</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0084">not a problem</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0041">not a problem at all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah so now after <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> obviously now he's gone a bit crazy but</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0084">crazy knob</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I did I just really thought that most people</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0084">uh huh</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0041">most boys the majority were pretty standard as the boys that I've known that I've grown up with cos all my friends have always been boys</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0041">apart from a small group of girls like literally now <pause dur="short"/> apart from you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my friends of girls consist of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> literally my entire life seven girls</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0041">um so I'd I kinda just thought that lads are much easier to read than girls <pause dur="short"/> they were very much there's less of a deviation in craziness</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0041">with boys and in girls you get this Jeze gonna have a baby</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0041">craziness</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> love you hate you</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0041">to kind of <trunc>alt</trunc> normalness</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0041">and uh that's quite a massive difference but with boys I always kinda thought it was a a smaller</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0084">A smaller variation</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1669" who="S0084">see I don't know if it's them getting older or what it is but I think you know as soon as someone been <trunc>h</trunc> had their heart broken I think girls you sort of get over it <trunc>a</trunc> you know but keep it with you always cos it shapes who you are</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0084">I think you</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0041">come more to a logical plane</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I think <trunc>y</trunc> inevitably even if you have been really hurt you do go out there looking for it again not to get hurt but</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0084">the possibility of finding somebody and then blokes see it as carte blanche well I can shag whoever I like now because I'm single and I can do it if I like</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0084">I think that's an element of not really giving a fuck and I think that's the problem</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0084">and then they  then they  can say whatever they like</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0041">and do whatever they want</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0084">and so for a moment they will be like yeah of course I really like you then they'll be you know distant again so</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0084">I think I've just had such a long run starting with the Norwegian in Cuba after a very quick breaking up with Will <pause dur="short"/> so I came back from Cuba so that was <trunc>Ju</trunc> May two thousand and eight <pause dur="short"/> this is four years ago and so I've broken up with Will in February <pause dur="short"/> I've gone travelling for three months come back I'm sort of seeing this Norwegian guy all quite casual <pause dur="short"/> he came up to Cambridge like five times <pause dur="short"/> I went to Norway and then when I came back he disappeared off the face of the planet <pause dur="short"/> so that was a start of the where men are crazy</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0084">he was the one who was referring to me as a girlfriend when I was I went up to Norway to break up with him and then realised actually I quite liked him <pause dur="short"/> which is really when he disappeared</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0084">umm</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0041">choice timing</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0084">yes that's when I realised that karma was a bitch like <vocal desc="laugh"/> what the hell? I went off to uni and then met blokes along the way and sort of fell fell for this guy who was married and all that ridiculous behaviour <pause dur="short"/> I mean that was quite intense and then <trunc>m</trunc> back again just sort of odds of sods and nothing really of note <pause dur="short"/> my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was the one who shattered your navy dreams temporarily</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0041">yep but I saw right since then</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0084">exactly</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0041">I've done a lot of digging round of talk and he was actually wrong <pause dur="short"/> so I'm quite</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0084">he is</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0041">in fact</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0084">you've got to remember <trunc>h</trunc> he you know he hasn't been in the army for twenty years and he just talks a lot of bollocks <pause dur="short"/> you've just gotta shout him down <pause dur="short"/> so he and I had a bit of a thing for a while off and on but nothing there's never really been anything of note but all of these blokes who came into my life and I realise that men are just mental like they just don't know</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0084">how to</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0041">have you read <trunc>m</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> Men Are From Mars Women Are From Venus?</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no I just thought it was a bit cheesy</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0041">read it <pause dur="short"/> in fact I might have a copy of it</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0084">is it really cheesy?</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0041">it's quite cheesy but it's really really truthful</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0041">like it's not written as a I thought it would be quite written like a fictional novel would be</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0041">it's not at all it more written like a handbook</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0084">well it's a self help book isn't it essentially?</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0084">that's how they market it <pause dur="short"/> like a bit pops like which is what puts me off really <pause dur="short"/> the idea that women cos it's the sort of at book aimed at women</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0084">you can't get away from that</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0084">though I doubt that many men will read it</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0041">I made Jordan read it</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0084">through choice</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0041">I made him read it cos we were just getting on each other's wicks so much at one point</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0041">I was like do you know what? Fuck this <trunc>re</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> we should read this</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0041">if this is what we actually want to do</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0041">and it helped on a lot <pause dur="short"/> it helped a lot</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0084">well that's good <pause dur="short"/> but I don't imagine there are many men who would sit on a bookcase and think do you know what I should probably read it that it's a bit illuminating</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> even Jordan didn't get on board enough</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0084">no I don't think that they are I think that's probably what annoys me is that these books talk about women things like He's Just Not That Into You <pause dur="short"/> that film came from a book <pause dur="short"/> there's a self help book <pause dur="short"/> it's a pop psych</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0041">oh did it?</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0084">book <pause dur="short"/> it's that sort of idea understanding men</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0084">um and knowing how to read them and I think it's you probably useful in a it's probably interesting to work out how to read what other people think generally</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0084">but this idea that it's targeted women who want to find a husband</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0041">oh no <pause dur="short"/> this this is more like it gave your ideas like if you if you're thinking if you say this that is what he's hearing from it</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0041">so it was quite nice cos I was quite shocked by some of it like <trunc>i</trunc> it says like men are like elastic bands basically they'll stretch and stretch and stretch and you'll think you'll never see them again and then bam they're there</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0041">all the time <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0041">and also like if women have a problem it's annoying the way it's written cos it like on Venus women are like this and you think cut the crap</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0041">you know <pause dur="short"/> what it's saying though is little things like if you  if you  have a shit day and you come home and you run it by your partner you're like do you know what? This happened and this happened and I don't really understand why the fuck why she said this or he said that or blah blah blah and really women come home and say it to get feedback you know the other person's opinion on it</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0041">and to kind of reinforce that yeah that was crazy and but you were right though and do you want a drink and you know and that's it <pause dur="short"/> that's all they want <pause dur="short"/> they want the discussion about the topic</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0041">whereas if you go home you say that to your other half he's going to give you solutions well you should have done this</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0041">and I used to get so angry with Jordan</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0041">well why don't you do this? Well no cos that wouldn't work because this <pause dur="short"/> did you not hear</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0041">that she was emotionally this this this <pause dur="short"/> well okay we'll do this <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>think</trunc> he thinks he's doing the best thing in the world for me</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0041">Cos I'm Mars <pause dur="short"/> if you're presented with a problem it doesn't matter how that problem's delivered you're you think that what's required is a solution bam</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0041">done <pause dur="short"/> here you go <pause dur="short"/> that's what you want this don't ya?</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0041">whereas that's not what the woman wanted at all</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0084">yeah just emotional support</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0041">from that conversation</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0041">yeah and it says that they're like if if a guy has a problem it's not that he won't talk about it because he doesn't want to but a man's brain in order to find the solution won't bounce ideas <pause dur="short"/> they don't want to do that</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0041">their brain is programmed not to bounce ideas and they their their brain is basically made to self consult</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0041">so the guy will be really quiet and go into his cave</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0041">which is what they say <pause dur="short"/> will go into his cave</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0041">and will do you want me move to this table a little bit?</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0084">that's alright I'm just gonna lean against the radiator a little bit <pause dur="short"/> just so that I don't get too cold <pause dur="short"/> are you warm enough in here?</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0041">um yeah basically they self consult until they can find the solution <pause dur="short"/> cos again</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0041">faced with a problem they <trunc>h</trunc> they want the solution really kind of hands on</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0084">it's quite logical isn't it?</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0041">but if you try and talk to her him</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0041">while he's in that that process then he will want you to fuck off</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0041">he will actually want you to fuck off <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't want your help or even if you're not wanting to give help you just say you know how are you feeling or</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0041"><trunc>h</trunc> hate hatred like that will really fire a man up</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0041">because the fact that he the fact that you would ask that implants that</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0084">you don't</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0041">you think he requires help</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0084">he's incapable of it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0041">one <pause dur="short"/> he's not capable <pause dur="short"/> two <pause dur="short"/> you don't trust him</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0041">three <pause dur="short"/> he's failing at life</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0041">Cos he's a man that's what he should be able to do</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0041">so basically he'll just  himself up until he gets to that solution</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0041">which is</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0084">but what did you say I mean like men put it this on a bookcase for example like if you tried to offer any help <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0084">directions? Should we ask for help? No</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0084">I know where I'm going <pause dur="short"/> we <trunc>don</trunc> you clearly don't because this is the third time we've seen that post box <pause dur="short"/> but fine okay</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0084">we'll just go round again shall we?</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0041">like extreme version of it and uh</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> I realised actually a lot of things we were coming to blows to because a lot of the things that we were struggling with were because of the things that were going on with my family</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0041">was we were just reading each other really differently and then it gives you like a list of you say he hears he says you hear idea</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0041">um and a lot  a lot  of our arguments were resolved because instead of thinking that's not what I meant</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0041">we started more along the lines of thinking that's not how I intended you to receive it</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0041">so it was more about it doesn't matter whether you meant it or not or whether you meant it to come across like that <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't matter the way somebody receives that information</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0041">is more valid</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0041">than how you intended to say it</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0041">and so</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0084">but that's quite an interesting point isn't it? It's like when <trunc>bl</trunc> blokes get annoyed with you for being over sensitive about receiving a comment you know like with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today for example but it's happened to me before in the past people be like when blokes have said to me you know <trunc>y</trunc> that's not what I meant or something you're just reading it wrong</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0084">or you're being over sensitive and you think well but that's how I feel like why can't you understand</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0084">that that's how I feel? Like you saying those words makes me feel this big</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0041">there's a whole part there there's a whole chapter in the book</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0041">about don't invalidate her feelings</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0041">Cos men men do this they've had this exact conversation</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0041">except when we hear them say and I didn't mean it like that or don't be daft you know</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0041">I'm thinking I'm not stupid</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0041">because they don't realise that actually what they're making you feel is that you're because you're feeling that way it's not a valid</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0041">it's not valid and it makes you feel like this this big</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0084">yeah and you're in the wrong</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0084">and that's not okay</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> but it's really it was really helpful like</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0084">well that's interesting</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0041">I think everybody should be made to read it</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0084">that is really interesting cos I completely dismissed it out of hand</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0084">always <pause dur="short"/> always have but I mean that's cos I'm quite a book snob when it comes to things like that <pause dur="short"/> I mean I would never read any pop psych but that's not to say that I don't think that it helps people</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0084">I just I never thought that it could help me <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>may</trunc> maybe it does</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0041">and it has even got</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah so I'll do that</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0041">not a relationship wise because they've described <trunc>me</trunc> on the page on the same chapter that men are like elastic bands women are like waves so every woman in a relationship or not the way their emotions are run</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0041">is is like a sea</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0041">so they'll be a calm and instead of a lull before the storm which is not quite accurate this guy was saying and I think that you'll have kind of a really good period in your life</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0041">and then that kind of peak drops so it kind of gets a bit better and then you know you're really have a great time you're feeling really good very confident and then something will some trigger and obviously everybody's triggers are different will happen and it won't even just be oh that's a bit bad <pause dur="short"/> you'll just</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0084">you'll just plummet</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0041">smash like a wave crashing and once you crash like that you have to kind of learn to get your head round the fact you <trunc>w</trunc> that you won't peak again until you've evened out a bit and then it will gradually build up again</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0084">oh God</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0041">which is really it isn't a really strange thing to think of?</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0041">but it's also nice and in the comfort that those days when you're like holy crap</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0041">you know the world's ending</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0041">and you smash to the bottom and what you do is you automatically sort friends and opinions and talk through things</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0084">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0041">that it was quite comforting especially with what I was going through at the time to know actually everybody does that</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0041"><trunc>T</trunc> that is the way women work</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0041">and I think you also compare it to being at the bottom of a  of a  well</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0041">if you're  if you're  in the well <pause dur="short"/> just learn to accept the fact that you're in it</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0041">it's not  it's not  it's inevitable that the wave's going to come back up again</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0041">but women <trunc>don</trunc> just seem to go there and forget that whereas men would never crash and burn</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0041">they're always quite <unclear/> toe whether they're interactive or not is the thing that changes</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> that's interesting isn't it?</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0041" trans="overlap">whereas a woman will always be very interactive</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0041">but whether she's on a real positive or a real negative is quite severe</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0041">how weird is that?</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0084">yeah I mean it doesn't <unclear/> come to think well it's reciprocal you know it's it's gonna happen and if you're going to keep going and so no matter how bad it feels any time it's going to get better <pause dur="short"/> you have to believe that it's going to get better</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0084">and so you know you are going to pick yourself up and you are gonna the situation is going to improve itself</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0084">you know you things are going to get better</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0084">you know it's quite an encouraging thought</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0084">that other women and other people have been in a similar situation and</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0084">it gets better <pause dur="short"/> it gets easier you know whatever it is that you're dealing with</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0041">that's quite</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0084">I guess when you feel quite alone like a lot of the times and sort of reading it</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0084">from another perspective like being able to understand the person that you're with a lot more</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0041">especially like if you're in a relationship and you know that really there's so much that goes on behind closed doors that you can't run by someone else</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0041">even if you wanted to</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's very personal isn't it?</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0041">which I think was quite a which is where Samarra and I came into the if you ever want to get married then I'm going to come and live with you for three months</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0041">because she saw everything one first hand <pause dur="short"/> all their arguments <pause dur="short"/> everything</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0041">which was quite difficult for her at some  at some  point</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0041">cos obviously she lived with us and you can't like get like distance</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0041">if we needed distance but Samarra and I are close enough that if that was the case we'd just go</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0084">you just know</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0041">to your room</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but and she saw some things that I never told her she said I <trunc>c</trunc> I didn't imagine how child like he was with things and how picky and I was like well there you go</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0041">I mean she's very much like she's we're like the same person cos I think when you start to mature</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0041">we we were maturing at the same time in the same surroundings living in each others pockets so inevitably you both kind of get bits of each other <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0041">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the thing was I made Jordan read it and he still  he still  carried on repeating this same type of behaviour that was causing arguments</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1936" who="S0041">and sometimes I'd have to say which makes <trunc>m</trunc> which sounds awful cos you don't want to do this hear this from the person that you love say <pause dur="short"/> did you not read the book? You know the reason why we're arguing is this</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0041">and he's like oh yeah when it it feels a bit not very comfortable that you'd have to bring that up</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0041">when you really I'm thinking you've got a brain how did you not get to that yourself?</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0041">not that this book is like the be all and end all but in some situations they were kind of really stark stark comparisons</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0041">and he <trunc>did</trunc> he didn't get it <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> it was a bit weird but it's definitely worth a punt <pause dur="short"/> I mean I wouldn't take you know everything it's saying it's all</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0041">you know everything's gospel</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0041">but</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0084">maybe I will <pause dur="short"/> it might be quite illuminating</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0084"></u>
<u n="1952" who="S0041">I used to read it and would just go to Samarra cos she was living with us at the time <pause dur="short"/> you're never going to believe this <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1953" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0041">you know if you say this to a boy this happens and this happens you know they're actually thinking this? And Jordan would sit there and go yeah</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1956" who="S0041">it was really strange like he would sit there and we would have this forum sometimes cos some of the stuff that I'd hear I was so shocked by</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0041">I was like what? No way and some of it Jordan got a bit upset by cos it was I think he thought of it as a personal attack</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0041">Cos he did that and I was like no no I'm not trying to say you're wrong for doing it you're obviously not look this is just how you're programmed but this is real news to me</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0041">real news</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> and it does help doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0084">it helps you understand him I think because that's what's important <pause dur="short"/> like if you're saying you know my relationship is important enough to read this book I'd think <pause dur="short"/> actually I want to understand where you're coming from</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was um my copy might be at Jord's but I need to go I need to get my camera from his anyway <event desc="phone rings"/> hello?</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0084">british Gas calling</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Did I just see Bebo there?</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0084">no it's called Badoo</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0041">what's Badoo?</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0084">it's a <trunc>webs</trunc> the dating thing that I'm on</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0041">badoo</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0084">yeah I can show you pictures of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hang on <pause dur="short"/> all these are the boys who are trying to talk to me I'm going to delete them in a minute <pause dur="short"/> you see all these I never just see where all the photos are first</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0041">first some truth ones</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> that is actually what he looks like <pause dur="short"/> see that one he looks a bit like a criminal</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I want to see the criminal one</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0084">he looks a bit like a criminal <pause dur="short"/> and then if you scroll left</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0041">like that?</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> the other way <pause dur="short"/> it's the right then</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0041">I don't really know</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0084">looking for my left and my right</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0084">so he has face fuzz now</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0041">face fuzz</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0084">but he did say that he shaved it off cos the girl his little girls who were seven and ten said dad dad we can't kiss you with your <trunc>fa</trunc> face it's all hairy</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0084">yeah so he shaved it off <pause dur="short"/> so he's <trunc>g</trunc> give him a <trunc>g</trunc> like a kiss and a cuddle</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0041">yeah he's a he's not what I imagined he's cute though isn't he?</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0084">it's he yeah I think he's cute and I think he's funny which obviously helps</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0041">yeah he is cute</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0084">I think he doesn't look like a criminal <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think that's what people think when they see him and I think they probably really judge him</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0041">what's it's? <trunc>Ba</trunc> Badoo? B E D O?</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0084">um B um B A D so he's my <trunc>ph</trunc> my phone</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0041">alright</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0084">my phone is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Bad <pause dur="short"/> cos if whenever you say Badoo <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Bad</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's standard</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0084">pretty standard <pause dur="short"/> so he's <pause dur="short"/> in his list of things that he likes to do cos you can put like interests</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0041">oh right</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0084">his interests writing screen plays photography spelled incorrectly</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0084">writing novels mixed martial arts <pause dur="short"/> so that is what he does <pause dur="short"/> hobbies travelling X Box all the things and then they training so that is the</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0041">yeah that is</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0084">tradesman <pause dur="short"/> he spelled great with three R's like</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0041">Great</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0084">like</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0041">like  <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2007" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's put college and university as his education</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0041">lies</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0084">I don't know if it's lies <pause dur="short"/> he might have college <trunc>educa</trunc> in fact actually he has got um HMDs I think</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> some maybe that's that's half uni so that's like</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0041">the if you do a three year degree HMDs and DO two</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0041">Cos that's what <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> did</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0041">so we did or I did GCSEs A Levels four year degree</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0041">Jordan did GCSEs college incorporating foundation degree H and D one year and topped it up to a degree</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> why did he do that then?</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0041">so usually if you do ah I don't know? Where did he I I I think the idea the split is if you do something that's more vocational or art based</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0041">like illustration or graphic design or health care that instead of doing A Levels people tend to do an MBQ</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0041">which is I think MBQ Three is the same pitch as A Level</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0041">which although I was a snob and didn't believe it currently apparently that's true <pause dur="short"/> whatever <pause dur="short"/> um and then after that you'd go straight to uni there you would do a <trunc>found</trunc> either a foundation year if they needed to top up</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0084">like an MD and then HND</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so whereas if you go to uni and you don't finish your third year</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0041">you walk away with a diploma</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0041">you can actually which I think is like a failure I know it sounds awful but you never  you never  go to uni intending to walk away with a diploma do ya?</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0041">you don't</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0084">well no</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0041">but</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0084">like when you do a post graduate degree like if you do all of the modules without the dissertation you can get a diploma so you can get a post graduate diploma but you don't get a master's qualification</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0041">hmm <pause dur="short"/> is that it?</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0084">social yeah</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0041">I never knew what that was</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0084">it's a PG Dip so you get a post graduate diploma which just means that you've done all the course work and all the classes up until like main or whatever</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0041">that's what my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got but he went for PGC so</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0041">he didn't really want a masters</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0041">and he just got it that's fine</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0084">so yeah if you're teaching that's all you need</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0084">so you wouldn't you don't spend the extra like six months doing it</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0084">unless you've felt like if as a sense of you're doing it for yourself</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0084">rather than it's what the need to have a vocation qualification which I think really my masters was a bit of both <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to be able to prove that even though I got a <unclear/> used to be like I got at Desmond at um undergrad I got a two two um because I basically got every grade across the board</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0041">me too</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0084">so I've got my transcripts cos this is when when I applied for my um MA and there's marks in the eighties and there's fails</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0041">me too yeah</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0084">across the board and my tutor Mister <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> would literally be tearing his hair out <pause dur="short"/> he said what it like he said you are obviously competent you can obviously do it <pause dur="short"/> so why aren't you doing it? And I said like well I've</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0041">aren't interested</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0084">like really struggling <vocal desc="laugh"/> having a difficult time emotionally and he said really? No <pause dur="short"/> I just got really pissed <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>s</trunc> sorry about that <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>l</trunc> I think for them it is frustrating because you're clearly there just to have a good time and learn a bit along the way</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0084">and I think that's why I wouldn't go to university <pause dur="short"/> I had to go now</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0084">because to come up with fifty grand worth of debt just isn't viable for a degree that it's very nice but means nothing to me</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0084">so when I went back I suppose it was a chance for me to prove that I could get a good degree and prove to others even though you don't need to</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0084">just thought you should <pause dur="short"/> so it was partly to go back to prove that I can apply myself because I wanted a vocational qualification to publishing to actually get a job a career at the end of it</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0084">rather than to get a degree for the sake of it <pause dur="short"/> but also to sort of better yourself and to  and to  learn</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0084">to engage your brain again having worked in a shop for three years and it was great and I just I've just really really enjoyed it and been busy all the time and uh I spoke to my mum and I got up doing this and doing that we went to this and you know we're doing that and I'm going to the theatre tonight and you know cos my friend Al worked there so I stayed there all the time and could meet all the people backstage and it sounds very exciting it was a really exciting life and I guess when I moved to Cambridge it all stopped <pause dur="short"/> just like it is whenever you finish uni you just think</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0084">is this it now?</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0041">is this what I was training for all this time?</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0041">is this what I'm given?</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0084">so I've come out with like eight grand worth of debt <pause dur="short"/> so like my career development language the loan I took out to pay for my masters cos I went travelling and it wasn't until I got back in like the June I said maybe I should do something with my life oh my God let's do a masters well I can start in September <pause dur="short"/> brilliant I haven't got any money took out a loan and I took out  took out  eight grand I think took out ten took out enough money five grand for my tuition fees and three grand for living living cost and then I worked so that I could afford to eat</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0084">um but it's a five year repayment plan from a hundred and fifty pounds a month</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0084">so I've only done two and a half years <pause dur="short"/> I still have two and a half to go</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0041">I think it's manageable is it? <trunc>It</trunc> it's manageable but</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0084">it's not a ridiculous amount but when you think you've got rent</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0084">you've got student loan and food and</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0041">I'm paying <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s mum a hundred and twenty-five a month</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0084">for the car?</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0041">yup</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0084">for how much longer?</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0041">I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> I loaned three grand</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0041">I've been paying it back cos I bought the car October November December January February March <pause dur="short"/> so basically a year and a half</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0041">I've been paying about what's that?</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0084">over a hundred and twenty-five pounds a month? You must be nearly there</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0041">for twelve months <pause dur="short"/> say say fifteen months cos I've I don't think we started paying it did I start paying it back till Christmas?</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0084">if you think a hundred pounds a month</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0041">and she let me missed one you know</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0041">back at Christmas I didn't pay her on Christmas and she was like no that's fine <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she doesn't have to pay over Christmas</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0041">she wouldn't let me pay <pause dur="short"/> it must be hard</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0084">if it was a hundred</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0084">pounds a month it would be thirty months wouldn't it? Which is</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0084">twelve twenty-four fourteen so <trunc>j</trunc> like two and a half years <pause dur="short"/> but you're paying over that</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0041">so it's probably going to be two years</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0084">it's going to be two</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0041">and I'll probably pay it back in a year</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0084">two years <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0041">I'll probably be doing this for another year which is fine <pause dur="short"/> I mean to be honest I've if if I'm going to start navy then I'll just bulk pay half</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0041">uh um but also I owe my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about four hundred pounds or five hundred pounds which I thought I had paid off <pause dur="short"/> he's just kept to himself all this time cos basically when I moved down here I had a grand savings</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0041">well that didn't last</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> it wouldn't not with deposit and then first month's rent</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0041">that was it <pause dur="short"/> so he paid my <trunc>dep</trunc> deposit and he got that back and he paid my first two months rent for me and I think he lent me something else <pause dur="short"/> so basically I loaned about a grand off him</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0041"><trunc>Pa</trunc> I thought I'd paid it all back <pause dur="short"/> it turns out I haven't I think he said I still owed him about five hundred quid I <trunc>tru</trunc> I mean I trust him</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0041">um but when I moved jobs remember when my bank account got all that thing with with the stupid lost my card</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0041">shit? And they stopped everything <pause dur="short"/> so they stopped paying him</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0041">and he just that's why I'm really pissed off with him <pause dur="short"/> cos he didn't like say to me then</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0084">the money's not coming into my account</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's just like kinda let it all build up and let it fester and</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0084">uh hmm</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0041">and I mean I didn't start paying it back straight away <pause dur="short"/> I started paying it I loaned it for two years before I started paying it back cos he knew the position I was in</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0041">so until <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and I no a year <pause dur="short"/> until <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and I moved to <anon type="place"/> we didn't started paying it back <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know like he he just hasn't bothered to get in touch on friendship basis more of a you owe me money</u>
<u n="2135" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0041">and which I was resentful for not only because he <trunc>d</trunc> he he hasn't been been a friend but also because he doesn't actually need it <pause dur="short"/> like he's a teacher he earns twenty-four grand twenty-five grand</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0041">he knows I'm taking home half of what he's taking home</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0041">and he's <trunc>see</trunc> he's seemed to be money focused</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0041">which I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't mind <pause dur="short"/> cos I owe him the money like I don't resent him asking for it at all</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0041">like I didn't now I wasn't still paying him</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0041">but it's more like he knows me  he knows me  very well and if I had known that he had a <trunc>st</trunc> standing order I would have done something about it</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0041">I think but why would you not just say it to me?</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0084">yeah and and then just leave it so that he's getting annoyed more and more annoyed</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0084">rather than talking to you about it</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0084">and just finding out what's going on</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0084">so now he's getting riled unnecessarily</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so now because he's riled I'm more resentful to give him</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0041">I mean I will anyway but</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0041">I'm kinda more like well hang on a sec you're pissed off with me because of a hundred pound a month?</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0041">um shouldn't I be pissed off with you over the fact that you're that much of a great friend like</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0084">you never called to find out why you couldn't repay</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> so literally because of how long I've not spoken to him for <pause dur="short"/> I got really annoyed and sent him a message back to his false friend message and I was like yeah my dad and mum are getting divorced <pause dur="short"/> um my dad's still not got his thing through from the court yet so he's basically living in a house with no furniture <pause dur="short"/> trisha's crazy and he's actually dying um I'm joining the navy and yeah <pause dur="short"/> like imagine all those things</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0041">all in one go <pause dur="short"/> and he was like oh sorry I'm sorry you're having a shit time of it <pause dur="short"/> I felt like saying you would know</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0041">exactly <pause dur="short"/> if you were being a good friend</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0041">as opposed to just focusing on a couple of hundred quid</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0041">which you don't actually need seeing as you're you've been on two holidays already this year</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0084">is he where is he living again?</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0041">Reading</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> I thought he was living teaching abroad for some reason</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean they go I mean they go away a lot he they went to Disney <trunc>La</trunc> always going to Disney World like Florida <pause dur="short"/> he's he doesn't need the money</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0041">it's as far as were talking about four hundred pounds</u>
<u n="2179" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0041">perhaps it's my grasp on cash but</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0084">no I mean if he really needed it there's no way he would be going on holidays</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and it's not just the odd holiday <pause dur="short"/> you know the odd trip to Belfast I'm talking</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0041">since I've moved to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so in a year and a half of I know he's been away for about five or six long weekends on booked holidays to Florida</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0084">fuck</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0041">Madrid Berlin uh I think they went to  I think they went to  Paris for valentines</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0084">this is him and his fellow?</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0041">and his boyfriend <pause dur="short"/> yeah quite a few</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0041"><trunc>Qu</trunc> I think went to Disneyland Paris <pause dur="short"/> not just one you know one every couple of you know every six months they have a weekend away I'm talking</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2192" who="S0041">it's he's got he's I saw on his Facebook he's been skiing <pause dur="short"/> do you know how much that one costs?</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0084">A fuck load because it when you get to the resort beer is like eight pounds a pint isn't it?</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0084">eight Euros a pint</u>
<u n="2196" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's a bit like yeah you don't actually need the money at all and if you don't bother speaking to me</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0041">actually on a friendship level you would have probably have said</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0041">forget four hundred quid <pause dur="short"/> just give me twenty quid a month or something like you can and just so so the balance goes down</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0084">Cos yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's the thing <trunc>yo</trunc> it's not like you the only way he can get a hold of you is by phone <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0084">Cos obviously he's been contacting you on Facebook isn't it?</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0084">so</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0041">and then um another thing that really annoyed me was he only let me know that this standing order wasn't going through mid last month</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I was like oh <pause dur="short"/> I was like shit I'm really sorry like I didn't you know of course I didn't know</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0041">he was like well no I expected you didn't but I did send you a few messages and I didn't get a reply <pause dur="short"/> I called your phone number</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0041">and I said I lost my phone <pause dur="short"/> I said you should have sent me a message on here</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> which you would do wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0084">if you're worried about someone if you're worried about a friend you haven't heard from in a few weeks and wasn't responding responding to your messages</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0084">would you not try every avenue?</u>
<u n="2218" who="S0041">and as of as a rule I'm sure he's actually got the phone number perhaps not this one but certainly the one before which I had before <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2219" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="2221" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0041"><trunc>cer</trunc> certainly had that phone number</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0084">or would he have  would he have  <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s number?</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0041">yup <pause dur="short"/> well he hasn't contacted <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> got a nice long email from both him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his fellow asking how he was and was everything okay and obviously</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0041">even even got a message to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he didn't know we'd broken up <pause dur="short"/> he didn't know we'd moved apart <pause dur="short"/> that's how little he's been in contact</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0084">fuck</u>
<u n="2228" who="S0084">so that's a good six months</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0084">we've been here six months haven't we?</u>
<u n="2231" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so really for it <trunc>I</trunc> I'm just more pissed that that is not that's not friendship</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0041">you know I'm really crap at keeping my friendships <pause dur="short"/> I'm really really rubbish</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0084">yeah me too</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0041" trans="overlap">you know I'll not speak to people for months at a time and they think I've disappeared off the face of the earth <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2237" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> got a nice long email from them both hope you're all well lovely lovely lovely lovely</u>
<u n="2238" who="S0084">that's so weird</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0041">I hope <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s alright <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> did <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0084">because it was a you know gathering all this anger against you because the standing order which as you say if you did actually just bothered to get in contact you would understand why</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0084">and really if your other money is not coming through really you start to think okay well there's obviously been a bit of a problem I'm a bit short on cash <pause dur="short"/> but you would call you would give them a text</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0084">so if they didn't respond to a text you might think well a bit weird</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0084"><trunc>m</trunc> might send another one</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0084">might try and call <pause dur="short"/> if he'd called your phone it would be off</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0041">uh hmm</u>
<u n="2250" who="S0084">and he would think that's suspicious</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0084">you know</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0084">no one has their phone off these days</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0084">what's going on?</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0041">so it's all very it's all been very weird</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0084">and that's really hurtful isn't it really?</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0084">that your friend is obsessed just seems to be a bit more concerned about the money</u>
<u n="2261" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="2262" who="S0084">than</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0041">that's the thing</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0084">your feelings</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0041">and I spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's not heard anything from him either full stop</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="2267" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="2268" who="S0084">that's weird though</u>
<u n="2269" who="S0041">I mean we just put it down to the fact that he's just come out as being gay <pause dur="short"/> he's moved in with his fellow</u>
<u n="2270" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2271" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s brother's gay and she said you know when we found first found out that he was gay and he was open about it he kind of went a bit off the wall</u>
<u n="2272" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2273" who="S0041">and was partying up all the time and very much living that type of lifestyle</u>
<u n="2274" who="S0084">but the the fact that he's getting in contact with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="2275" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2276" who="S0084">someone's he's only friends with through you</u>
<u n="2277" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="2278" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> maybe there's a boy thing going on there <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="2279" who="S0041">I don't know</u>
<u n="2280" who="S0084">fYI <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone back</u>
<u n="2281" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="2282" who="S0084">he's definitely gone in</u>
<u n="2283" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> I wanna text him</u>
<u n="2284" who="S0084">just slap and tickle</u>
<u n="2285" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> filth</u>
<u n="2286" who="S0084">I don't think she would shag him though</u>
<u n="2287" who="S0041">he sent a picture I saw a picture of her uh</u>
<u n="2288" who="S0084">oh yeah cos she said hi to me when she came round</u>
<u n="2289" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><trunc>N</trunc> to you?</u>
<u n="2290" who="S0084">well only cos she was in the door when I came out from my room</u>
<u n="2291" who="S0041">damn it</u>
<u n="2292" who="S0084">and she wouldn't come into the house <pause dur="short"/> she was really it was weird actually <pause dur="short"/> I came out of my room and they were going to the shop and she was sort of standing out in the drive and he was sort of getting ready and he was like oh this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she was just like hi you <pause dur="short"/> not like come back to the house to actually have like a proper introduction and then as soon as they got back into the house they disappeared again</u>
<u n="2293" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2294" who="S0084">it felt weird like they were some sort of I don't know anyway</u>
<u n="2295" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no you know this this is new gypsy type designer called <trunc>Po</trunc>? What's it <trunc>call</trunc> stand for?</u>
<u n="2296" who="S0084">Paul's Boutique?</u>
<u n="2297" who="S0041">yeah I Love <anon type="place"/> Boutique is there all their little emblems</u>
<u n="2298" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2299" who="S0041">I have hatred for this</u>
<u n="2300" who="S0084">yeah it's tacky as hell</u>
<u n="2301" who="S0041">tacky as hell and all the school kids have got kind of I Love <anon type="place"/> Boutique hand bags don't they?</u>
<u n="2302" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2303" who="S0041">which are painted and a bit stuck on and</u>
<u n="2304" who="S0084">oh they're disgusting</u>
<u n="2305" who="S0041" trans="overlap">fake gold</u>
<u n="2306" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2307" who="S0041"><trunc>S</trunc> shit</u>
<u n="2308" who="S0084">but then they're like sixty quid? Don't they sell them at Top Shop actually at <anon type="place"/> Boutique I think</u>
<u n="2309" who="S0041">do they?</u>
<u n="2310" who="S0084">I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> the first time I saw them was in Oxford Street</u>
<u n="2311" who="S0041">um maybe in the Oxford Street one</u>
<u n="2312" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2313" who="S0041">uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>cer</trunc> certainly hate hate hate it <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="2314" who="S0084">it's pretty  Yeah</u>
<u n="2315" who="S0041">um and he was saying she's got a new coat <pause dur="short"/> and she said to me well do you like my new coat from <anon type="place"/> Boutique? I was like they do coats?</u>
<u n="2316" who="S0084">I know</u>
<u n="2317" who="S0041">people buy clothing?</u>
<u n="2318" who="S0084">I couldn't buy coats <pause dur="short"/> like pfft</u>
<u n="2319" who="S0041">bags</u>
<u n="2320" who="S0084">bags</u>
<u n="2321" who="S0041">and purses are what I thought</u>
<u n="2322" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2323" who="S0041">while she's got a it wasn't a coat it was a hoodie</u>
<u n="2324" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="2325" who="S0041">so there's a picture of a stud right it's it's sent she'd sent to him in front of the mirror of course <pause dur="short"/> she's got kind of mid blue jeans on <pause dur="short"/> tight skinny jeans like little <trunc>bo</trunc> black booties and a little heel and this hoodie and it's like it's basically like this</u>
<u n="2326" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2327" who="S0041">so it's up to here black and none of this of course um all black and the emblem there right? And she stood taking a photograph like this</u>
<u n="2328" who="S0084">uh <pause dur="short"/> she's a <unclear/> snob</u>
<u n="2329" who="S0041">in a hoodie <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2330" who="S0084">oh dear</u>
<u n="2331" who="S0041">in a hoodie in heels <pause dur="short"/> is</u>
<u n="2332" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2333" who="S0041">with a <anon type="place"/> Boutique thing and he was like oh to be honest you know I think it's uh it's kind of like a traveller brand and that's not you at all</u>
<u n="2334" who="S0084">that's really funny</u>
<u n="2335" who="S0041">she kicked off <pause dur="short"/> I was like well</u>
<u n="2336" who="S0084">I mean really at this stage and he's trying to get  he's trying to get  to do</u>
<u n="2337" who="S0041">was that your phone?</u>
<u n="2338" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's difficult to say <vocal desc="laugh"/> wow that was a message from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on Badoo <pause dur="short"/> he's just sent me a message saying what are you looking at eh? Cos obviously we were on his profile and it tells you when people have been looking at your profile</u>
<u n="2339" who="S0041">oh no <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="2340" who="S0084">so he's like what are you looking at eh?</u>
<u n="2341" who="S0041">nothing</u>
<u n="2342" who="S0084">let's just get out of there <pause dur="short"/> let's get out of dodge <pause dur="short"/> um pretty funny though because really in this is what you were saying isn't it? About him saying stuff that piss her off</u>
<u n="2343" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what else he did as well? On top of that</u>
<u n="2344" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2345" who="S0041">I which he wasn't going to tell me <pause dur="short"/> he I got up and went to go to the loo and he was in there and I said oh I need a wee <pause dur="short"/> is somebody in the bathroom? You know like you're asleep you don't know what's going on</u>
<u n="2346" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2347" who="S0041">uh he was like yeah you found the <unclear/> pancakes? I was like yeah tell me if I was <unclear/> pancakes <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="2348" who="S0084">sorry that's this morning?</u>
<u n="2349" who="S0041">this morning</u>
<u n="2350" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2351" who="S0041">and then after we'd had pancakes and eaten the said pancakes about two hours later I went upstairs to get a DVD from him</u>
<u n="2352" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2353" who="S0041">and he got his Facebook left up and I saw his status said making pancakes for breakfast on on a or pancakes for breakfast for my lover winky <trunc>f</trunc> winky smile</u>
<u n="2354" who="S0084">no he didn't</u>
<u n="2355" who="S0041">I kid you not <pause dur="short"/> I kid you not <pause dur="short"/> it either said pancakes making pancakes for breakfast with my lover or pancakes for breakfast for my lover winky face <pause dur="short"/> so he's doing it on purpose to wind her up <pause dur="short"/> he's purposely winding her up and I mean after I mean apparently they've been to and fro in arguing on messages since last night so I can see</u>
<u n="2356" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="2357" who="S0041">why he he thought to do it but</u>
<u n="2358" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> it's just so damaging</u>
<u n="2359" who="S0041" trans="overlap">isn't it?</u>
<u n="2360" who="S0084">the whole thing is so damaging like I just <trunc>won</trunc> I just wonder why he thinks that that's okay?</u>
<u n="2361" who="S0041">God knows</u>
<u n="2362" who="S0084">like he like the way he acts <pause dur="short"/> like the way oh well you know the kids for the wedding and boo boo boo and you just think what planet are you actually living on? Like how</u>
<u n="2363" who="S0041">no idea</u>
<u n="2364" who="S0084" trans="overlap">this is not acceptable <pause dur="short"/> this is not okay <pause dur="short"/> it's never going to be okay</u>
<u n="2365" who="S0041">not a clue</u>
<u n="2366" who="S0084">fucking weirdo</u>
<u n="2367" who="S0041">not a clue <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if he's getting it on? Need a</u>
<u n="2368" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="2369" who="S0041">he's not uh</u>
<u n="2370" who="S0084">he's not come back</u>
<u n="2371" who="S0041">absolutely</u>
<u n="2372" who="S0084">yeah<pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2373" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2374" who="S0041">fresh mug?</u>
<u n="2375" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2376" who="S0041">it's not through the <unclear/></u>
<u n="2377" who="S0084">well yeah I mean they would have told you wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="2378" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2379" who="S0084">they probably <unclear/> Okay</u>
<u n="2380" who="S0041">yeah I know it's really low</u>
<u n="2381" who="S0084">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="2382" who="S0041">so it's fine now? <trunc>Sh</trunc> I say I feel dizzy often and sometimes I feel like I wanna shit sometimes I just think well I feel like the ground's as if you're on a ferry do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="2383" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="2384" who="S0041">yeah only that it doesn't last very long <pause dur="short"/> it usually makes me laugh a lot cos it feels like being really drunk <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2385" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="2386" who="S0041">it lasts like ten seconds twenty seconds</u>
<u n="2387" who="S0084">does it?</u>
<u n="2388" who="S0041">yeah not for very long I know and it just goes again <pause dur="short"/> just okay fine well if it's really low we'll probably give you medication for it but if that's what you're getting from it you don't <trunc>h</trunc> have you ever fainted? No never they're like yeah you'll be fine</u>
<u n="2389" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> good stuff</u>
<u n="2390" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2391" who="S0084">well I mean if they were worried they would certainly let you know <pause dur="short"/> would you like a hot chocolate?</u>
<u n="2392" who="S0041">oh I love hot chocolate total goodness <unclear/></u>
<u n="2393" who="S0084">yeah you really fill all the goodness  all the goodness</u>
<u n="2394" who="S0041">all the vitamins you'll ever need</u>
<u n="2395" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2396" who="S0041">I think I'm going to be quite lazy and get a a nice bath</u>
<u n="2397" who="S0084">hmm sounds grand I'm just going to get into bed <pause dur="short"/> snuggle under and write all the birthday cards <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be a week of cakes that's going to be quite difficult to resist cos my college <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s cos it's if it's your birthday you have to bring in cake for the whole department</u>
<u n="2398" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2399" who="S0084">which actually is quite dangerous cos of the</u>
<u n="2400" who="S0041">being in cake land</u>
<u n="2401" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos it's there's quite a lot of birthdays generally <pause dur="short"/> so there's always cakes <trunc>al</trunc> we also have a biscuit tin as well and whoever eats the last biscuit gets to replace the biscuit tin</u>
<u n="2402" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2403" who="S0084">so that's also quite dangerous <pause dur="short"/> so it's Jo my <trunc>coll</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday was yesterday so I'm sure she'll have made cake but she's the biscuit goddess <pause dur="short"/> that's fine thanks love <pause dur="short"/> um so she'll probably bring a cake tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday on Sunday but she's obviously flying to New York like my boss uh flying this weekend <pause dur="short"/> so she's and it's we have um every three months we have an away day for the team and we go go to like the building in town and the <unclear/> building and <unclear/> We go there and discuss the latest issues <pause dur="short"/> a good chance to sort of sit talk down and talk about what's going on in the team and we're having one on Friday which means being out of the office all day <pause dur="short"/> so she's going to bring in cake on Thursday <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/> she could go on and it's just so hard <pause dur="short"/> I suppose if I do go to the gym</u>
<u n="2404" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2405" who="S0084">three times this week and don't eat</u>
<u n="2406" who="S0041">yeah you could</u>
<u n="2407" who="S0084">anything naughty apart from that</u>
<u n="2408" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2409" who="S0084">of course it would be okay isn't it?</u>
<u n="2410" who="S0041">it's definitely doable</u>
<u n="2411" who="S0084">I can do Wednesday Friday <pause dur="short"/> I've got other plans for Friday but</u>
<u n="2412" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2413" who="S0084">but thanks for washing up love</u>
<u n="2414" who="S0041"><unclear/> Um I'm gonna do gym tomorrow</u>
<u n="2415" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2416" who="S0041">gym Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> I think for</u>
<u n="2417" who="S0084">gym <pause dur="short"/> gym</u>
<u n="2418" who="S0041" trans="overlap">take up to see Kate on Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember she sent me an email on Friday about coming to Adam Brooks for something?</u>
<u n="2419" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="2420" who="S0041">yeah something to do with the thyroid</u>
<u n="2421" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2422" who="S0041">um but that yes so she you know  you know  we should meet up</u>
<u n="2423" who="S0084">oh that would be nice</u>
<u n="2424" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2425" who="S0084"><unclear/> having laundry tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> dirty shirt <pause dur="short"/> yeah  Dirty shirt</u>
<u n="2426" who="S0041">I need to <unclear/> to the gym so all that I do quite enjoy the gym and turning laundry <pause dur="short"/> I think that's</u>
<u n="2427" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2428" who="S0041">I think that's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> I think Sunday's should be made for gym time and laundry</u>
<u n="2429" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>t</trunc> that's basically their their routine everyday isn't it?</u>
<u n="2430" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2431" who="S0084">their daily routine <pause dur="short"/> I mean they've got it pretty sweet haven't they?</u>
<u n="2432" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2433" who="S0084">like no real major issues to speak of <pause dur="short"/> all they've got to do is sell t-shirts in a shore store</u>
<u n="2434" who="S0041">which one? I find they're normally quite boring</u>
<u n="2435" who="S0084">have you seen the one where they go to Italy yet?</u>
<u n="2436" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="2437" who="S0084">yeah you have to watch that one</u>
<u n="2438" who="S0041">the thing is I keep thinking to watch it but then like oh Larry uh</u>
<u n="2439" who="S0084">at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2440" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2441" who="S0084">that's foolish yeah</u>
<u n="2442" who="S0041">I was thinking about getting a notebook you know?</u>
<u n="2443" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2444" who="S0041">like a really baby laptop</u>
<u n="2445" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2446" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="2447" who="S0084">they're good you can't watch but you can't play dics on them</u>
<u n="2448" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2449" who="S0084">or anything cos they're that small</u>
<u n="2450" who="S0041">yeah cos and then I thought cos I'm going to get a new laptop or something like that</u>
<u n="2451" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2452" who="S0041">I should probably get one with a disk drive on it <pause dur="short"/> so I won't have to</u>
<u n="2453" who="S0084">you never know when it might come in handy</u>
<u n="2454" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I thought about getting um quite an old Mac</u>
<u n="2455" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2456" who="S0041">just like the basic one</u>
<u n="2457" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2458" who="S0041">um for a couple hundred quid</u>
<u n="2459" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2460" who="S0041">Cos I don't use it for I don't need it for anything particular anymore like uh when I was at uni I needed a disc one for the work and stuff like that</u>
<u n="2461" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2462" who="S0041">but now</u>
<u n="2463" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2464" who="S0041">literally Word internet</u>
<u n="2465" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2466" who="S0041">DVD done</u>
<u n="2467" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2468" who="S0041">so I do I'll have to get one before I go away anyway</u>
<u n="2469" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> maybe they'll do you a special deal <pause dur="short"/> probably cos actually they in fact I know they do because like my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her brother's just joined the navy navy officially had his passing out in December and he gets a specialty with Volvo specialty with Hewitt Packard <pause dur="short"/> what else does he get a special deal with? Lots of big manufacturers do deals with the navy <pause dur="short"/> uh well armed forces in general</u>
<u n="2470" who="S0041">you probably need to ask him how difficult that training was?</u>
<u n="2471" who="S0084">very difficult <pause dur="short"/> but he left it <pause dur="short"/> did he get he didn't get gangrene <pause dur="short"/> he got something really bad like foot wart like really really bad when he was doing his training <pause dur="short"/> he got some sort of leg injury and he's a bit of a psycho <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>l</trunc> kept pushing himself and they were like no your leg might fall off you probably shouldn't do the thing now <pause dur="short"/> I think he</u>
<u n="2472" who="S0041">oh God</u>
<u n="2473" who="S0084">cos he went in but not in as an <trunc>of</trunc> in as an officer and he loves it and it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s now dating his one of his mates from the navy <pause dur="short"/> but Will her brother didn't know for ages like it's quite funny</u>
<u n="2474" who="S0041">oh yeah they were only saying about this now</u>
<u n="2475" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2476" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I probably need to find I he probably needs to tell you on a scale of one to ten</u>
<u n="2477" who="S0084">how bad it was</u>
<u n="2478" who="S0041" trans="overlap">how much <unclear/> cos I mean if we're anything above an eight I'm really quite scared</u>
<u n="2479" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's good to go into these things with your eyes open I suppose? I don't know whether they <unclear/> the <anon type="place"/> assessment <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who I love <pause dur="short"/> he's just also just joined the navy but the year before so his passing out was the Christmas before so he's been in the navy for a <trunc>y</trunc> just over a year but he went to university to train to be a pilot <pause dur="short"/> so he's got a pilot's degree</u>
<u n="2480" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="2481" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that cost sixty grand</u>
<u n="2482" who="S0041">shit</u>
<u n="2483" who="S0084">because he was doing that when we worked at <anon type="place"/> assessment <pause dur="short"/> he had one more year to go and I just thought that's a fuck load of money and he's like it's okay because when you graduate that first year out of uh uni you'll be earning a hundred grand and I thought okay so what do they like guarantee you work? And he was like there's always work <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there were no there were no jobs</u>
<u n="2484" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> when he came out</u>
<u n="2485" who="S0084">none whatsoever <pause dur="short"/> so basically his parents have footed the bill sixty grand worth of education and he joined the navy anyway <pause dur="short"/> but at least he's gone in that's it he can fly planes</u>
<u n="2486" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2487" who="S0084">and sort of got one ahead of everybody else</u>
<u n="2488" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a guy that I was he was doing his recruiter when I was doing mine</u>
<u n="2489" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2490" who="S0041">umm was saying how easy he found the mechanical engineering bit and I was like</u>
<u n="2491" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2492" who="S0041">and how difficult he found the English bit and I was like no I found that bit the easiest it was the mechanical engineering bit that I found hard</u>
<u n="2493" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2494" who="S0041">and he was like oh yeah I have got an engineering degree though <pause dur="short"/> so I was like uh a bit of a head start there mate</u>
<u n="2495" who="S0084">well that will give you a heads up won't it? What an idiot</u>
<u n="2496" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2497" who="S0084">that sort of thing shouldn't be allowed really should it?</u>
<u n="2498" who="S0041">it's unfair <pause dur="short"/> it's an unfair advantage</u>
<u n="2499" who="S0084">it's a massive <trunc>ad</trunc> disadvantage for you</u>
<u n="2500" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I thought actually the other day when I was at the pub I need to think of the answer to the question why do you want to join the navy? Cos I have no answer</u>
<u n="2501" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="2502" who="S0041">I have no answer</u>
<u n="2503" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="2504" who="S0041">and everybody that I've spoken to has said so why are you joining the navy? And I'm like well you know shits and giggles that's not gonna wash <pause dur="short"/> that is not gonna wash</u>
<u n="2505" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="2506" who="S0041">so what we need to do is anybody who over here is joining the navy anybody <pause dur="short"/> so you ask through these people you say</u>
<u n="2507" who="S0084">all these people that I actually know weirdly <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2508" who="S0041">say why did you join the navy? And we're going to steal one of their perfect answers <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean they've already been indoctrinated with this now are they?</u>
<u n="2509" who="S0084">they've already done this <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2510" who="S0041">exactly</u>
<u n="2511" who="S0084">they're totally clued up</u>
<u n="2512" who="S0041">if I just take their fake answer</u>
<u n="2513" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2514" who="S0041">I think that's fine</u>
<u n="2515" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> well that sounds fine</u>
<u n="2516" who="S0041">Cos there's no real reason <pause dur="short"/> it's just going to be hard <pause dur="short"/> it's just sounds like an adventure and it's hard and the money's great and</u>
<u n="2517" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2518" who="S0041">it's a big team unit which I love</u>
<u n="2519" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2520" who="S0041">Cos everywhere I've worked before the ethos between the people is so stretched that I feel like <trunc>smash</trunc> people face against the wall</u>
<u n="2521" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2522" who="S0041">but um</u>
<u n="2523" who="S0084">probably not going to say that</u>
<u n="2524" who="S0041">probably not  probably not  going to wash when it comes to it</u>
<u n="2525" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> well I mean it's the usual bollocks when I whenever you go for a job interview and they say well why do you want to work for us? And you just say well I've done well normally you tell like I've done lots of research into the company and I was really interested by this and I was really you know interested by your um your scheme that supports the your employees to volunteer or whatever bollocks that you just made up or that you happened to have stumbled across on their website</u>
<u n="2526" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2527" who="S0084">you know you just make it up on the day don't you?</u>
<u n="2528" who="S0041">yeah but when you've got two days</u>
<u n="2529" who="S0084">that's</u>
<u n="2530" who="S0041">and not an hour</u>
<u n="2531" who="S0084">it's pretty intense</u>
<u n="2532" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's going to be pretty bad <pause dur="short"/> oh so you're still <unclear/>? So why aren't you then joining our communication branch?</u>
<u n="2533" who="S0084">yeah <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="2534" who="S0041">um cos the pay is shit?</u>
<u n="2535" who="S0084">you don't say that <pause dur="short"/> umm not enough of a challenge not <trunc>interest</trunc> not varied enough</u>
<u n="2536" who="S0041">yes not varied enough and also it's computer I mean computers</u>
<u n="2537" who="S0084">say you're more of a people person</u>
<u n="2538" who="S0041">I'm more of a <trunc>st</trunc> I'm a strategy builder</u>
<u n="2539" who="S0084">hmm <pause dur="short"/> uh hmm that's sounds better <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2540" who="S0041">which is true <pause dur="short"/> remember the day when we had the moving of the  the moving of the  uh drier? And you remember the day after I said to you when Stu came and you were moving the drier</u>
<u n="2541" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2542" who="S0041">and so the day after I said I don't know why but I get really impatient cos I really get there</u>
<u n="2543" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2544" who="S0041">quite quickly</u>
<u n="2545" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2546" who="S0041">really that's true <pause dur="short"/> that's not a lie I'm giving</u>
<u n="2547" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="2548" who="S0041">and it's not  it's not  really a whole truth because</u>
<u n="2549" who="S0084">oh <trunc>w</trunc> well yeah I mean sometimes things seem much <trunc>m</trunc> more clear than others don't they? You know like</u>
<u n="2550" who="S0041">hmm</u>
<u n="2551" who="S0084">it's easy to see it sometimes but not always so</u>
<u n="2552" who="S0041">but you know the more people we speak to I know Jake was in the navy the guy that uh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knows quite that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works behind the pub in Cottingham that he lives next door to <pause dur="short"/> looks a bit like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2553" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="2554" who="S0041">yup</u>
<u n="2555" who="S0084">on the page</u>
<u n="2556" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2557" who="S0084">and who was the cute one?</u>
<u n="2558" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2559" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> lovely <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2560" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Lovely <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he wasn't working this weekend</u>
<u n="2561" who="S0084">for the best I think <vocal desc="laugh"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> probably for the best</u>
<u n="2562" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2563" who="S0084">so he wouldn't get interfered with by fake flowers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2564" who="S0041">yeah so I probably just need to just suck fake answers from everyone</u>
<u n="2565" who="S0084">okay well that's fine</u>
<u n="2566" who="S0041">so that's the plan</u>
<u n="2567" who="S0084">I can sniff a brief</u>
<u n="2568" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="2569" who="S0084">fine</u>
<u n="2570" who="S0041">that's a brief</u>
<u n="2571" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll get on it</u>
<u n="2572" who="S0041">just ask them all why did you join navy?</u>
<u n="2573" who="S0084">uh hmm <pause dur="short"/> that's fine I'll send them all a message tomorrow</u>
<u n="2574" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> we shall collate the answers choose the best <pause dur="short"/> mash them all together and I'll remember it parrot style</u>
<u n="2575" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="2576" who="S0041">I'll do that <pause dur="short"/> winner</u>
<u n="2577" who="S0084">bud</u>
</body>
</text>
