<text id="S7SZ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:26:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0262 S0300</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At ANON's home in Harston, Cambridgeshire. </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Hospital appointments and medical procedures, death in family, funeral arrangements, dealing with death and grief, family members expressing emotions in the nuclear family, family relationships, family members’ and friends’ body weight and image; diets; nutrition. </topics>
		<activity>Two acquaintances having a cup of coffee. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0300">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur></hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>cleaner</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> exactly ah so how did it go with the appointment then?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0300">that was okay actually</u>
<u n="3" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> I took my tablety stuff things on the Wednesday</u>
<u n="5" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0300">and I was fine till five o'clock</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0300">so I was like really annoyed cos I thought I couldn't have gone out and done things</u>
<u n="9" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0300">cos it didn't have any <trunc>eff</trunc> till I took the second sachet of whatever it was I took</u>
<u n="11" who="S0262">right okay</u>
<u n="12" who="S0300">then it worked</u>
<u n="13" who="S0262">okay yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0300">prior to that it didn't</u>
<u n="15" who="S0262">ah right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0300" trans="overlap">so erm yeah so I was at home until five dying to eat food</u>
<u n="17" who="S0262">ah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> just moping about really</u>
<u n="19" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0300">erm but then yeah once that kicked in then that was it you're sort of up and down every five minutes</u>
<u n="21" who="S0262">god</u>
<u n="22" who="S0300">so that was probably the worst part because then <pause dur="short"/> got up on the Thursday went in was seeing all like was the second one in erm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0262">oh good so you didn't have to wait about too much then? that's good</u>
<u n="24" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no but I don't remember anything</u>
<u n="25" who="S0262">you don't remember?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0300">no I remember going in and laying on this bed in like this theatre room</u>
<u n="27" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0300">and erm and I can remember him giving me my injection and that's it then I just remember being at home</u>
<u n="29" who="S0262">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> god you were really knocked out then</u>
<u n="30" who="S0300">yeah I don't remember</u>
<u n="31" who="S0262">you don't remember coming round or getting home or?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0300">no <pause dur="short"/> no I just remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sitting on the sofa well sort of half lying on the sofa and I was well how did I get here?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0262">and how how did you get there?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and I actually walked I walked out out of the car</u>
<u n="35" who="S0262">and then your <trunc>y</trunc>your partner picked you up?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0300">my daughter was with me the whole time</u>
<u n="37" who="S0262" trans="overlap">your daughter yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0300">so</u>
<u n="39" who="S0262">so you don't remember talking to her or <trunc>ge</trunc>getting in the car?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no not not until we got home no</u>
<u n="41" who="S0262">you would have been well out of it then</u>
<u n="42" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah so I think they might have given me a little bit too much to be honest</u>
<u n="43" who="S0262">could well be</u>
<u n="44" who="S0300">so</u>
<u n="45" who="S0262">could well be yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0300">but I didn't feel ill or or groggy</u>
<u n="47" who="S0262">you just felt like knocked out</u>
<u n="48" who="S0300">just a bit yeah just sort of like</u>
<u n="49" who="S0262">drugged up</u>
<u n="50" who="S0300">yeah like a really really bad hangover</u>
<u n="51" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0300">type thing really</u>
<u n="53" who="S0262">yeah okay yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0300">so no so that actually went really well</u>
<u n="55" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0300">a bit of pain for a couple of days <pause dur="short"/> back to normal</u>
<u n="57" who="S0262">oh good</u>
<u n="58" who="S0300">so yeah so that was that I'll phone up for my results on Thursday</u>
<u n="59" who="S0262">and right</u>
<u n="60" who="S0300" trans="overlap">to see if they found anything</u>
<u n="61" who="S0262">did they say anything at all to you? like or anything?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0300">they said to my daughter that they erm they could see quite a lot of inflammation</u>
<u n="63" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="64" who="S0300">but that was about all she remembers</u>
<u n="65" who="S0262">yeah okay</u>
<u n="66" who="S0300" trans="overlap">you know what they're like they don't really listen</u>
<u n="67" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no she's probably more concerned about trying to get you home than really understand what yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so er no</u>
<u n="69" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but still quite a lot of inflammation</u>
<u n="70" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0300">so that's a bad thing anyway because it shouldn't because it's the inflammation that causes all the problems</u>
<u n="73" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0300">like it causes my arthritis in my elbows and my knees to flare up and and stuff so yeah inflammation isn't good</u>
<u n="75" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0300">but they didn't say if they I mean they took biopsies but they didn't say if they saw anything untoward so I'll find out Thursday</u>
<u n="77" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> so you'll ring up Thursday</u>
<u n="78" who="S0300">yeah yeah I just have to call the sister that I see on the in the clinic and then she'll call me back and let me know</u>
<u n="79" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I suppose it's a good thing that you can ring up but then also it's a bit kind of weird as well don't you think?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0300">it's alright if you're getting good news</u>
<u n="81" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0300">if you're getting sort of not so good news then you kind of think mm not really what you wanted discussed over the phone</u>
<u n="83" who="S0262">no I suppose it's most convenient</u>
<u n="84" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0262">thing to do</u>
<u n="86" who="S0300">yeah cos trying to fit you in for an appointment is is a nightmare</u>
<u n="87" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0300">cos as far as I know <anon type="place"/> are just mental at the moment on the appointment side</u>
<u n="89" who="S0262">are they?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0300">because I should have gone to the hospital last Tuesday for my throat check-up</u>
<u n="91" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="92" who="S0300">well not my throat my neck check-up and I had to cancel that because of the funeral</u>
<u n="93" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0300">when I went to rebook it I've got to wait two months so instead of going last week I'm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0262" trans="overlap">two months?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0300">on the seventh of October I now go on the sixth of December</u>
<u n="97" who="S0262">it's just it's just unfathomable</u>
<u n="98" who="S0300">and my dad had to do the same he's got an eye problem</u>
<u n="99" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0300">so he has to go to the eye clinic he had an appointment last Monday</u>
<u n="101" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0300">but again he had to cancel cos we were travelling on the Monday</u>
<u n="103" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0300">erm he rang up and his is exactly the same as mine he's now got to wait till the fourth of December the day before my appointment so he's on the same waiting list</u>
<u n="105" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so it's two months</u>
<u n="106" who="S0300">waiting time</u>
<u n="107" who="S0262" trans="overlap">waiting two months that's a long time</u>
<u n="108" who="S0300">it's a long time</u>
<u n="109" who="S0262">particularly when you've already had an appointment booked in</u>
<u n="110" who="S0300">yeah cos I said well can't you get any earlier appointments I said I've got a funeral to go to I said obviously</u>
<u n="111" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0300">I have to go to this funeral erm and I said and I've also been waiting nine months for this appointment because they mucked me mucked it all up at the hospital to start with and she said no <pause dur="short"/> she said it will be the whatever of December</u>
<u n="113" who="S0262">pff</u>
<u n="114" who="S0300">so so yeah so I've got to wait two months for that appointment now</u>
<u n="115" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0300">so but no so all in all <pause dur="short"/> and then last Monday if as we were getting ready to go to go leave to go to Plymouth went to feed my little animals cos we've got a guinea pig a rabbit and a dog</u>
<u n="117" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="118" who="S0300">and the guinea pig had died</u>
<u n="119" who="S0262">oh no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0300">I opened his hutch and he just lay there I was like mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0262">oh no</u>
<u n="122" who="S0300">and it was it was just so so upsetting cos we had two</u>
<u n="123" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0300">and one was mine and one was my eldest daughter's and then the rabbit was the younger daughter's</u>
<u n="125" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="126" who="S0300">so we all kind of had our own little pet</u>
<u n="127" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0300">and I used to have hamsters as well I love little hamsters</u>
<u n="129" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0300">but erm and then when my daughter left home she kind of like passed her guinea pig over to the youngest daughter</u>
<u n="131" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="132" who="S0300">so she had the <trunc>t</trunc> although I'm the one that feeds them every day and</u>
<u n="133" who="S0262">takes care of them really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0300">yeah but she clean yeah but she cleans them out that's what I I won't I won't clean them out because the rabbit won't let me actually get him out the hutch cos he hates me</u>
<u n="135" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="136" who="S0300">erm even when I go to feed him he he tries to bite my fingers</u>
<u n="137" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0300">so she does all that but erm but yeah I was mortified and the of course didn't have time to bury him</u>
<u n="139" who="S0262">oh no you just had to leave him there</u>
<u n="140" who="S0300">and then I then I forgot to bury him</u>
<u n="141" who="S0262">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="142" who="S0300">cos wrapped him up and put him in a little cat box and put him in the garage cos I thought oh it'll be quite cool</u>
<u n="143" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0300">in there and then I thought oh I I'll mention to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I speak to him Monday night to <trunc>be</trunc> dig a hole and put the guinea pig in it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0300">erm forgot so and of course I don't even told him it had died</u>
<u n="147" who="S0262">oh no</u>
<u n="148" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and then erm came back late Tuesday night so didn't do it then and then completely forgot to it Wednesday and it was Thursday afternoon I actually buried him</u>
<u n="149" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="150" who="S0300">and the <trunc>fe</trunc> weirdest thing was as I was digging the hole I hit something so I dug out some more dirt and there was this blanket and I thought</u>
<u n="151" who="S0262">oh no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0300">I'm sure I put your brother in a box</u>
<u n="153" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0300">and it and I and I kind of scooped it out I didn't look at it I scooped it out with the erm with the <trunc>sh</trunc> the shovel erm and laid it on the on the ground and then I saw bits of the box cos obviously the box is disintegrated</u>
<u n="155" who="S0262">yeah sure yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0300">so I knew it was his brother so it was quite sweet in a way</u>
<u n="157" who="S0262">yeah you'd gone back</u>
<u n="158" who="S0300">so I put them both exactly the same spot</u>
<u n="159" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0300">put them on top of each other</u>
<u n="161" who="S0262" trans="overlap">which was pretty cool in a way</u>
<u n="162" who="S0300">no I just thought how uncanny was that</u>
<u n="163" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0300">cos I don't mark where I've put them I mean we've got dogs we've well I know where the dogs are <pause dur="short"/> erm there they have got like proper little grave things</u>
<u n="165" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0300">but the little animals that like the hamsters and the guinea pigs</u>
<u n="167" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0300">they're they're sort of like along this hedgerow</u>
<u n="169" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0300">but where you wouldn't know</u>
<u n="171" who="S0262">yeah but you obviously do</u>
<u n="172" who="S0300">and the fact that I dug this hole as the hole I dug before</u>
<u n="173" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0300">was just amazing</u>
<u n="175" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0300">so</u>
<u n="177" who="S0262">how long <trunc>wa</trunc> ago was that?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0300">he died about April time</u>
<u n="179" who="S0262">right okay</u>
<u n="180" who="S0300">no February he died on Valentine's Day</u>
<u n="181" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="182" who="S0300">yeah that <trunc>he</trunc> it was Valentine's day so yeah February</u>
<u n="183" who="S0262">oh gosh these little little things have a habit of passing on</u>
<u n="184" who="S0300" trans="overlap">passing at the wrong time</u>
<u n="185" who="S0262" trans="overlap">at the wrong time exactly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0300">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I the thing is I I have a lot of feeling for little animals</u>
<u n="187" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0300">you know like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like ah they're just animals you know I mean like one of the guys that rents one of our sheds said well why don't you just put it in the recycle bin?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0262">oh no you can't do that</u>
<u n="190" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and I'm like why why would you do that?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0262">it's been your pet</u>
<u n="192" who="S0300">I said would you put your dog in the recycle bin when it dies?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="194" who="S0300">he went no I said well there you go</u>
<u n="195" who="S0262" trans="overlap">course not yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0300">so I said no</u>
<u n="197" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's a little creature</u>
<u n="198" who="S0300">I said I'm gonna dig a hole so I did</u>
<u n="199" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0300">but yeah so mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so how was the funeral then?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0300">it was <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0262">still coughing</u>
<u n="204" who="S0300">it was actually quite weird in a way because</u>
<u n="205" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0300">as I say I've only ever been to one funeral</u>
<u n="207" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0300">and that was my nan's and that was sort of like <pause dur="short"/> it was a it was a sad it was a sad time erm and it was a proper burial because this was a cremation I've never been to a cremation before so I didn't know what to expect</u>
<u n="209" who="S0262">yes <pause dur="short"/> different atmosphere</u>
<u n="210" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and it was all yeah it was completely different I mean while we were waiting outside the crem for the like for the hearse to turn up everybody was just they was just all out there smoking laughing fooling around</u>
<u n="211" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0300">then you follow the coffin in</u>
<u n="213" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0300">and it's like <vocal desc="misc"/> everybody started to cry</u>
<u n="215" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0300">erm and then obviously why they're the back back back oh I don't know what he was called he wasn't a vicar <pause dur="short"/> minister no I don't know I can't remember what he was called</u>
<u n="217" who="S0262">was he the <trunc>c</trunc> person who took the service?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0300">so we he he was then like talking so of course as he's saying things you get really quite kind of upset so the whole time you were in there it was really really tense and and my brother actually did lose it completely</u>
<u n="221" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> er and then when you sort of come out it was back to everybody lighting up fags and <pause dur="short"/> sitting there laughing and I was like is this really what happened?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0262">it's weird surreal yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0300">you know and I just thought I hope people are a little bit more upset when I've</u>
<u n="225" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0300">you know when when you lay me to rest</u>
<u n="227" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0300">er then we went to a pub which just seemed to seemed weird because she died through alcohol</u>
<u n="229" who="S0262">alcohol yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0300">so it just seemed bizarre that you would have like this little wake in a pub</u>
<u n="231" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0300">so basically once you all got there and everybody started to have a drink it was just like a family get together</u>
<u n="233" who="S0262" trans="overlap">people just down the pub</u>
<u n="234" who="S0300">down the pub</u>
<u n="235" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0300">and that was it no more there was no more tears me you know like my mum said said said you would have thought that someone would have spoke I mean like when we got our drinks like cos like we sat at a table and I just went <pause dur="short"/> er to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and my <trunc>mu</trunc> and then everyone else did the same but nobody toasted her</u>
<u n="237" who="S0262">no no</u>
<u n="238" who="S0300">or or spoke about her everybody sort of sat in their own little groups</u>
<u n="239" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0300">and I just thought <pause dur="short"/> no this is weird</u>
<u n="241" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that is what's slightly the problem with the crem services is that that was very what you described is quite similar to erm some of the services I've been to</u>
<u n="242" who="S0300">right</u>
<u n="243" who="S0262">erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> I think it's because the the service itself is so short</u>
<u n="244" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0262">so it's it's so short but it's so intense</u>
<u n="246" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0262">which means that people need to laugh around the intensity because you can't actually just maintain that level of intensity for the whole sort of</u>
<u n="248" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah no no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0262">whereas I think with a more of a funeral service it breaks it up quite a bit</u>
<u n="250" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0262">because you've got the church well you've got meeting people being shown where to sit sit down the service that goes on for some time</u>
<u n="252" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0262">and then you know you go and walk out to or you might even have to take a car to where the</u>
<u n="254" who="S0300" trans="overlap">to where the yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0262">you know the cemetery is and so it's quite a lot but but the good thing is then is that it's is you're all still together in the sort of the <trunc>pa</trunc> the patchwork of what's going on</u>
<u n="256" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0262">but you can actually have a bit of headspace</u>
<u n="258" who="S0300">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0262">time out whereas I think the crem services are just so intense</u>
<u n="260" who="S0300">oh it yeah it was just weird it was</u>
<u n="261" who="S0262">and the way the actual buildings are <pause dur="short"/> you are outside</u>
<u n="262" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0262">then you're sort of standing round going well what do? I'll wait for the family to turn up</u>
<u n="264" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0262">but they can't talk to everyone</u>
<u n="266" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="267" who="S0262">erm and of course they're emotionally overladen anyway and then you get in there and the something happens that takes you know not really twenty minutes</u>
<u n="268" who="S0300">that's it</u>
<u n="269" who="S0262">and then you wave bye bye to the coffin which is all a bit</u>
<u n="270" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0262">that's quite full on I mean I know that the <trunc>fu</trunc> the grave in the er sorry the erm the coffin into the <trunc>gra</trunc> is pretty full on but at least you've still got the words going</u>
<u n="272" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0262">whereas when the coffin goes in to the <pause dur="short"/> behind the curtain</u>
<u n="274" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0262">some people have it and some people don't</u>
<u n="276" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0262">there's just music</u>
<u n="278" who="S0300">that's it that's all it was</u>
<u n="279" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and the music tends to be really emotional as well</u>
<u n="280" who="S0300">the music that was played was erm a ferry <pause dur="short"/> ferry Across the Mersey</u>
<u n="281" who="S0262">oh crikey that's enough to <unclear>anybody</unclear> it's a bit of a tear jerker that one</u>
<u n="282" who="S0300" trans="overlap">well yeah and that was and what what he said was he said this is for you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was her brother and they both supported Liverpool</u>
<u n="283" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="284" who="S0300">so of course he just totally went to bits</u>
<u n="285" who="S0262">yeah you see this is the thing</u>
<u n="286" who="S0300">er I didn't know that until after but I saw him crumble erm and couldn't understand <trunc>ho</trunc> why</u>
<u n="287" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="288" who="S0300">erm cos I didn't even know that was her brother at the time I I you <trunc>st</trunc> you're standing there and you're kind of putting two and two together and everything's coming</u>
<u n="289" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0300">together and I was like oh my god that must be her brother and stuff like that so and that played twice</u>
<u n="291" who="S0262">oh god</u>
<u n="292" who="S0300">cos I don't think the coffin had gone quick enough</u>
<u n="293" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0300">cos you had this guy standing there with his baton thing</u>
<u n="295" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0300">and and ten like he walked up to the curtain and he bowed and then he stood there while the music played and then as the music was about to stop he like turned round bowed to us and then started to walk towards the door</u>
<u n="297" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="298" who="S0300">then the music instantly <pause dur="short"/> played again same song</u>
<u n="299" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0300">so of course he then walked back in <pause dur="short"/> went back towards where the curtains were bowed stood there while the music played so you had to listen to this song twice</u>
<u n="301" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh so all all over again yeah that was not good</u>
<u n="302" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and it and no one could move you couldn't get up and walk out</u>
<u n="303" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no no no that that sounds a bit rubbish really</u>
<u n="304" who="S0300">and it was it was a just horrific I just thought you know surely they know how long it takes for a a</u>
<u n="305" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they should know yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0300">a coffin to to go</u>
<u n="307" who="S0262">yeah they got that one wrong somebody hadn't pressed the button to move the coffin along</u>
<u n="308" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah they got that wrong big big big time yeah and then <unclear>sat</unclear> and then once you'd sort of left there and you stood outside and everybody gathered in their own little groups again cos there wasn't that many people there</u>
<u n="309" who="S0262">no it's like my mum's service yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0300" trans="overlap">cos we're all they're all from <anon type="place"/> and they moved to <anon type="place"/> so there was only a few of us that actually was able to get to <anon type="place"/> for the funeral apparently there was or there is going to be a service here for the people that didn't make it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh okay that's nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0300">erm so of course there wasn't many people there there was probably only about fifteen people including</u>
<u n="313" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0300">erm and then on top of that like my brother and his his daughter so there really wasn't many people</u>
<u n="315" who="S0262">no and and in a way that's probably not such a bad thing because</u>
<u n="316" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="317" who="S0262">what I was so worried about with with mum's service I can't remember so much with gran's service though you know it was up in erm <pause dur="short"/> off the A14 the crematorium up there</u>
<u n="318" who="S0300">oh yes</u>
<u n="319" who="S0262">erm I've forgotten the name of it now and erm but anyway what I was worried about for my mum was <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> the erm the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who are the funeral directors told me that erm it's quite likely that there is going to be another service <pause dur="short"/> on the dot</u>
<u n="320" who="S0300">straight after</u>
<u n="321" who="S0262">these things go like on the dot if it's two thirty it starts and if you're not out by two two two twenty-two they're gonna hurry you along</u>
<u n="322" who="S0300">right</u>
<u n="323" who="S0262">so it was like oh great this is now feeling like pressure you know to even finish on time</u>
<u n="324" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0262">so it's a lot of pressure for <trunc>da</trunc> erm <trunc>da</trunc> a lot of pressure for my brother and myself cos we both spoke to make sure that we actually kept the timing that we were given or that we had kind of given ourselves erm mine was alright cos I read a sort of read a children's story poem that my mum always used to read to me</u>
<u n="326" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="327" who="S0262">so that I knew how long that would take but my brother on the other hand he did a erm sort of like erm a eulogy sort of thing to my mum and he was freewheeling it and when people get nervous you could just go on forever and not realise that you're actually taking quite a long time but thankfully he's got a really good idea for what the time's like cos he does lots of presentations</u>
<u n="328" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> right right</u>
<u n="329" who="S0262">so it was actually alright</u>
<u n="330" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0262">we all finished on time you know and it was good but it was a pressure but yeah when we came out there were already like a whole forty or fifty people lining up lining up outside ready to go in for the for their</u>
<u n="332" who="S0300" trans="overlap">for theirs <pause dur="short"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="333" who="S0262" trans="overlap">service and it was weird because we all sort of came out probably about fifteen to eighteen of us I think I don't know <pause dur="short"/> maybe twenty I'm not even sure but not a lot</u>
<u n="334" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0262">and and then we were sort of like crowded out by this other lot who like you were saying like they're laughing smoking whatever</u>
<u n="336" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0262">and some of them were obviously looking really quite kind of shocked but most of them were kind of like trying to sort of ease things up a bit but then our lot just went like oh and then we all zipped off into our cars</u>
<u n="338" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0262">but thankfully we knew where we were going cos we were gonna go and have afternoon tea at the <anon type="place"/> erm in <anon type="place"/> which was actually a good location for everyone to get to</u>
<u n="340" who="S0300" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0262">it's a good car park in there <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah it's it I think there's something there's a lot to be said about being cremated I'm sure</u>
<u n="342" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0262">but for the people who attend the service it's it's not quite the same</u>
<u n="344" who="S0300">no you see my mum and dad both want to be cremated <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0262">but then you don't care if that's your wishes you're not gonna</u>
<u n="346" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="347" who="S0262">you're not gonna know about are you so?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I'm kind of thinking <pause dur="short"/> yeah do I really want them cremated? you know but that's their wish so you've got to go along with what they <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="349" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's their wish</u>
<u n="350" who="S0300">and my mother-in-law turned round and said yes erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I want to be we we're gonna have a humane <trunc>crem</trunc>cremation I said well what the hell is that? and she said no service <pause dur="short"/> nothing <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="351" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="352" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0262">well</u>
<u n="354" who="S0300">and I was like whoa</u>
<u n="355" who="S0262">the thing about those places is you know you know they're a crematorium they're not a place of worship and I'm not religious so I don't</u>
<u n="356" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no see we're not</u>
<u n="357" who="S0262">but I know that when I walk into a church whether I believe or not I know that there are people who do believe and it calms me down</u>
<u n="358" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0262">because that kind of level of spirituality whether you're kind of into it or not there is something about a church that you can just go</u>
<u n="360" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0262"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0300">yeah you can just let it all go</u>
<u n="363" who="S0262">yeah cos cos you know that's kind of what you're meant to do in a church</u>
<u n="364" who="S0300" trans="overlap">erm and feel relaxed yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0262">is sort of try to unwind a bit</u>
<u n="366" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but in a crem you're not relaxed</u>
<u n="367" who="S0262">not at all</u>
<u n="368" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="369" who="S0262">and they it's so artificial it's it is it's everything is so</u>
<u n="370" who="S0300" trans="overlap">it did it felt fake</u>
<u n="371" who="S0262">oh fake very fake</u>
<u n="372" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0262">and I mean you know you try to jolly it up a bit with the flowers and everything but what what was weird up in that one I've never liked it up there is because the flowers for because the services are so tight the flowers don't get moved away in time for the new lot coming in so they actually had they were obviously a family who believed in big wreathes</u>
<u n="374" who="S0300">right</u>
<u n="375" who="S0262">you know with the person's name</u>
<u n="376" who="S0300">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0262">you know really shy kind of stuff which I <trunc>fi</trunc>fine it's fine you know that we went for <trunc>so</trunc> you know smaller things and just things that my mum liked really but erm but yeah theirs were and so they were all coming along and and and I'm I'm like oh <unclear/> your little flowers for my mum I'll just kind of move them here and you know but the funeral director was like no no no don't worry we'll take care of that that's their job to do that but it felt a bit weird</u>
<u n="378" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0262">you know I felt like oh I really should move our stuff now</u>
<u n="380" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0262">my dad was oblivious to that cos I said that to him I said oh you know what didn't you feel a bit like? he's like god I didn't even think about the flowers you know I mean he was absolutely out of it</u>
<u n="382" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0262">you know for most of the day I don't know how he kept it together but I suppose family being close by you know you can sort of manage to just sort of talk</u>
<u n="384" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0262">but it's it's so weird</u>
<u n="386" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0262">I mean your brain is doing something weird because your whole emotions are just</u>
<u n="388" who="S0300">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right up in the air but you're still having to have a conversation with people</u>
<u n="390" who="S0300">exactly it was very bizarre it was just I don't know it's just something I don't really feel</u>
<u n="391" who="S0262">yeah I've not given it much thought I mean the the downside I suppose with the with the erm being you know erm buried is that you actually have to wait around for a slot</u>
<u n="392" who="S0300">yes</u>
<u n="393" who="S0262">that can be hard going for the family erm yeah it just depends on where your local kind of burial you know ground or your local cemetery would be but it's it's a bit yeah that can be problematic</u>
<u n="394" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0262">I mean friend of mine actually his mum died last week <pause dur="short"/> yeah she I think it was alcoholism as well</u>
<u n="396" who="S0300">oh really?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0262">well yeah she'd led an expat lifestyle where it was so easy to drink</u>
<u n="398" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0262">I mean it's kind of almost expected you know it just started as it does I don't think anybody meant to really kind of turn out that way but both her and her husband quite liked a tipple erm quite a lot and then I suppose boredom sets in and she just got used to drinking during the day</u>
<u n="400" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="long"/> right</u>
<u n="401" who="S0262">now I never saw her drinking during the day but my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is a really good friend well we all used to go to school together it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum who died but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I know and she went out there to spend some time on a family holiday and erm she yeah she did make a few comments and was like right G and T sort of at about eleven in the morning kind of thing</u>
<u n="402" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0262">but quite outwardly about it not like an alcohol you know like <trunc>he</trunc> someone who's trying to hide it which is what I would more associate</u>
<u n="404" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0262">but I know there's different types of but the ones who are kind of</u>
<u n="406" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> sneaking</u>
<u n="407" who="S0262">hiding it</u>
<u n="408" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0262">to me feels like they know they've got a problem</u>
<u n="410" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0262">but true people who who keep drinking sociably do have a problem but they're just not thinking that they have got one</u>
<u n="412" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="413" who="S0262">so I don't know which is worse <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="415" who="S0262">but anyway so and then erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad died the same year as my mum but she her dad died in May and so yeah so May two thousand and twelve and then I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just really was pining for him</u>
<u n="416" who="S0300">yeah they just give up</u>
<u n="417" who="S0262">and she just really didn't know what her life was all about without him cos he was such a core for her life you know I think he kind of did manage her you know drinking a bit and you know of course then you know if there's no one there to really manage your drinking or even to think about your life I mean you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a wonderful daughter but she's taking full care of her mum and everything you know but of all accounts <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't really understand that and she just kept drinking drinking drinking drinking and so much so where she was beginning to turn a little bit on the nasty side with it</u>
<u n="418" who="S0300" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0262">like I don't know I was never there but I heard that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was taking a lot of shit from her mum</u>
<u n="420" who="S0300">mm mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0262">but then so she kept drinking but and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her husband went to Cuba on holiday and her mum passed on while they were in Cuba so poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had to get on a flight and I know what that must be like <pause dur="short"/> knowing full well she's coming back to the fact that her mum had died and erm nobody knows what really happened to her because she was on her in her house on her own <pause dur="short"/> sunday she spoke to her other daughter she sounded weak and then the cleaner was due in on a on a morning I don't know I suppose cleaner couldn't get in</u>
<u n="422" who="S0300" trans="overlap">found her oh couldn't get in</u>
<u n="423" who="S0262">was worried and then called the police the police went we're coming round get round to have a look and there</u>
<u n="424" who="S0300">there she was</u>
<u n="425" who="S0262">just died on her own there so</u>
<u n="426" who="S0300">oh how awful</u>
<u n="427" who="S0262">yeah so and then I she's gonna be cremated <pause dur="short"/> yeah she's gonna be cremated I think that's right yeah so the funeral will actually be next Friday twenty-fourth</u>
<u n="428" who="S0300">mm mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0262">cos we were all like oh because she's Catholic we're thinking <pause dur="short"/> that could be a burial like in a cemetery and it was kind of like oh that's going to be one of those really long services and then you go have to go to the you know and we were kind of like you know not that we were saying oh we don't want to do it</u>
<u n="430" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="431" who="S0262">it's just like you're mentally preparing yourself you're going like right okay it's gonna be like that</u>
<u n="432" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it's going to be like this de de de de</u>
<u n="433" who="S0262">and then when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said no my her mum wanted to be cremated then we were like okay right but then again I know what it's gonna be like</u>
<u n="434" who="S0300">yeah it's gonna be yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0262">it's gonna be like what we were describing it's just like ch ch ch ch ch</u>
<u n="436" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's just so</u>
<u n="437" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and then to a pub</u>
<u n="438" who="S0300">yeah it's just so quick</u>
<u n="439" who="S0262">you know</u>
<u n="440" who="S0300">I just don't believe how quick it was</u>
<u n="441" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0300">you've got all that build up to it</u>
<u n="443" who="S0262">and you know it costs a fair bit of money</u>
<u n="444" who="S0300">mm I mean the one that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had cost three thousand pound</u>
<u n="445" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0300">it was very and that was the minimum the basic that was a classed as the basic</u>
<u n="447" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0300">erm and she's getting a grant to pay for that cos she's only seventeen</u>
<u n="449" who="S0262">yeah okay</u>
<u n="450" who="S0300">so she she kind of took over</u>
<u n="451" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh that's good yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0300">and didn't and obviously my brother wouldn't have been able to afford er it anyway</u>
<u n="453" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0300">erm because obviously none of them had any money they didn't have any savings</u>
<u n="455" who="S0262">right yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0300">so you know so I think because it went</u>
<u n="457" who="S0262">well thank god for that then isn't it?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0300">yeah I think because it went through <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and as I say she's only seventeen they've allowed her this this grant</u>
<u n="459" who="S0262" trans="overlap">she gets help yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0300">so it hasn't cost anybody anything I think all they had to pay for was the few sandwiches that were made</u>
<u n="461" who="S0262">for the pub</u>
<u n="462" who="S0300">at the pub</u>
<u n="463" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0300">erm but other than that they haven't had to pay out for anything</u>
<u n="465" who="S0262">well I mean thank god for that</u>
<u n="466" who="S0300">but that's a <trunc>mi</trunc> that's that's the minimum three thousand pounds</u>
<u n="467" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no I know I know three thousand</u>
<u n="468" who="S0300">I'm like that's a lot of money for someone to have to find to have the most basic cremation <pause dur="short"/> you know and I just thought it I know you've got</u>
<u n="469" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> then when you think about it what how why is it three thousand pounds? if it's a thousand I'd understand but why is it three thousand?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah cos I mean it's the hire of the hearse</u>
<u n="471" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0300">and obviously the coffin and what the funeral directors had done and then you've got your pall bearers whatever they're called</u>
<u n="473" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> and then your <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>pre</trunc> vicar he'd whatever they're called</u>
<u n="475" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0300">and and that and the hire of the the crem for twenty minutes so</u>
<u n="477" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then and then I suppose they've got to do the bit where they take the coffin and put it in a <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but then obviously they take the coffin and obviously that goes wherever it goes so</u>
<u n="479" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0300">so yeah so but that's still we just sort of sat there and said that really doesn't warrant three thousand pounds <pause dur="short"/> it just doesn't</u>
<u n="481" who="S0262">not in my head it doesn't</u>
<u n="482" who="S0300">well not in mine either</u>
<u n="483" who="S0262">but then you know <pause dur="short"/> I know like when we were talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who had they're local we used them with granny erm granny's er funeral erm I mean they are pretty good because they come to the house</u>
<u n="484" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0262">that has got to be pretty hard work</u>
<u n="486" who="S0300">oh yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0262">and well you know with granny and mum it was all actually right because basically they'd sort of you know they were contained what I would say</u>
<u n="488" who="S0300">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0262">whereas I know from stories not from <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> they wouldn't dream of telling stories but from other people in Australia who are funeral directors or or assistants you can find all sorts you know in people's houses</u>
<u n="490" who="S0300">oh gosh</u>
<u n="491" who="S0262">and they they they're in you know there they have to clean it up I mean they have to make it erm for the families so the family haven't got any idea what's actually happened</u>
<u n="492" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="493" who="S0262">because you can't be having that sort of thing so I can see why they get paid quite a bit of money</u>
<u n="494" who="S0300" trans="overlap">well no <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0262">for</u>
<u n="496" who="S0300">for all of that yeah yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0262" trans="overlap">the headspace you must take up when you have to do things like that</u>
<u n="498" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0262">but really like the other stuff I don't know I mean I suppose you know <trunc>pu</trunc> er a pall bearer erm what would you pay them? I don't know I mean like</u>
<u n="500" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="501" who="S0262">fifteen pounds an hour or because when you think about their work I suppose they do have to be there on time</u>
<u n="502" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0262">ready to do their bit because if they're not there wow there's going to be all hell to pay because you know you know you can't even get the coffin you can't even ask the family to carry it unless they particularly wanted to you know but not really</u>
<u n="504" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think there's many people that do it now do they?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's not really what it's about <pause dur="short"/> I mean we had a lovely vicar from erm who lives just over there in <anon type="place"/> and we'd never met her before but she's quite <pause dur="short"/> she's quite erm I suppose she's quite well known round the area cos she's like a minister or something and then she decided she didn't want to do that any more she just really wanted a bit of a peaceful life and just sort of lived down there and just do her sort of pastor thing</u>
<u n="506" who="S0300" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0262">her parish erm her parish <anon type="place"/> parish and erm but yeah she was really good because she'd never met my mum but she spoke about my mum as if she had</u>
<u n="508" who="S0300">as if she knew her yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0262">which that's quite an art in itself and she course you've got to pay them money too</u>
<u n="510" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="511" who="S0262">but that is quite a skill and you have to keep everyone on track you know and especially people are losing it you've got to try and <unclear/> them all up with it</u>
<u n="512" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0262">which is a skill so I can see why she was or what she cost but yeah like I still think three thousand cos ours was about that if not a bit more I thought</u>
<u n="514" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0262"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0300">I don't know</u>
<u n="517" who="S0262">thank god mum had some money to pay for that you know</u>
<u n="518" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and when she turned <pause dur="short"/> yeah and when she turned round and said that was the minimum</u>
<u n="519" who="S0262">yeah yeah that's right yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I went wow you know you're seventeen you haven't got a a a pot to pee in you know if you hadn't been able to get a grant how the hell could you have done it?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0262" trans="overlap">wouldn't have been able to</u>
<u n="522" who="S0300">well no</u>
<u n="523" who="S0262">unless the family <trunc>co</trunc> would have had some</u>
<u n="524" who="S0300">it would have had well it would have had to have been</u>
<u n="525" who="S0262">a family loan</u>
<u n="526" who="S0300" trans="overlap">all the family chipping in</u>
<u n="527" who="S0262">or a bank loan</u>
<u n="528" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0262">some people have to get bank loans</u>
<u n="530" who="S0300">but you know I just kind of think whoa <pause dur="short"/> you know I mean <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't I I've not told either of my girls how I would like to cos I don't know</u>
<u n="531" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="532" who="S0300">I mean it's not something I think about at the moment</u>
<u n="533" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well no it doesn't</u>
<u n="534" who="S0300">I know you should</u>
<u n="535" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0300">erm cos as you say you never know what's round the corner but <pause dur="short"/> you know like my mum and dad have always said they want to be cremated they've got two trees they've got a tree each in their garden</u>
<u n="537" who="S0262">oh okay</u>
<u n="538" who="S0300">erm so they specifically said that we want to be cremated and our ashes are to be scattered</u>
<u n="539" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh well that's nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0300">at our tree</u>
<u n="541" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0300">so we know exactly when if anything happens to my mum and dad or if it happened at the same time we we would know what to do</u>
<u n="543" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah which is good because you don't want to worry about that</u>
<u n="544" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you see nobody would know I mean I wouldn't know how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted cos if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would turn round and say well I don't care cos I don't I won't know nothing about it</u>
<u n="545" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0300">so he'd kind of leave it up to you you know it'd be up to us what we wanted to do with him</u>
<u n="547" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0300">but I do think that you should be able to say to somebody maybe you know</u>
<u n="549" who="S0262">give it some thought <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah when I give them an idea you know</u>
<u n="551" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah exactly or don't or tell me what you don't want</u>
<u n="552" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah and then we know what their</u>
<u n="553" who="S0262">and then we know where we're gonna you know <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah if you don't want to be cremated then say I don't want to be cremated</u>
<u n="555" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0300">I mean I know there is only cremation or burial there's only two</u>
<u n="557" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0300">choices but</u>
<u n="559" who="S0262">but you see I'm I'm a donor for all of my organs like I wouldn't you know if they wanted something they can have it as far as I'm concerned I don't think I crossed anything that I didn't erm not taken</u>
<u n="560" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="561" who="S0262">erm and then in my mind I'm thinking well if there really have got a big chunk of you for what bit of the other that they felt that they needed in the bigger scheme of things you know really what's the point of going and having a service really when there might only be half of you there? and I know that sounds just ghastly</u>
<u n="562" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it's true</u>
<u n="563" who="S0262">but <vocal desc="laugh"/> but in a way it's like</u>
<u n="564" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah it's true</u>
<u n="565" who="S0262">what is what is the point really? when</u>
<u n="566" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0262">you see the thing I couldn't get my head round with my mum and my gran I think more for my mum cos I felt it more keenly but I knew that she was over with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s erm in a erm in a erm cooler box I</u>
<u n="568" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't remember what you call them was trying to think about what it is can't remember</u>
<u n="570" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0262">anyway and er so she would've been there until she was ready to to you know for the funeral service</u>
<u n="572" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0262">and er he <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s had said to me if you'd like to drop over and er just pop over and drop some of her personal artefacts off that you think she would like</u>
<u n="574" who="S0300">mm mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0262">er in her coffin with her and I was like <pause dur="short"/> right so I did as I was told because I couldn't think of anything else to do I was just like right okay do what he asks me to do so I I brought some things over and I was waiting there and <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> actually this is quite funny because he I've never seen him stressed out but he was stressed that morning the reason why was because he had another funeral service that very morning and the person who said that they would organise the flowers hadn't so this was a family member who had just obviously forgotten to organise the flowers so he was having to do it now</u>
<u n="576" who="S0300" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0262">so he was all in a panic and then anyway he came out and he was having his little cigar and he was chilling out a bit and you know we were talking about death and you know how some of the funny <trunc>mu</trunc> more amusing sides of it</u>
<u n="578" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0262">which there are you know and he must have seen a lot</u>
<u n="580" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0262">and I said I guess in the bigger scheme of things this isn't the worst thing that can happen he goes oh no I could tell you a few things</u>
<u n="582" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0262">and anyway so I said but you know do people really come back to have a look at the body at like? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he's like oh he said oh yes they do and and we have to you know present the body he used very sort of grave words but you know the body needs to be presentable at all hours for any family member far or wide who'd flown in from New Zealand or whatever and had only five minutes to go and say goodbye whatever you know and I was like oh</u>
<u n="584" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0262">so they have to get the body ready and erm and that obviously takes a fair bit and then <pause dur="short"/> I said oh I said I see what you mean and is that the reason why I should bring some things for mum? you know cos I couldn't really figure out who was going to go and have a look so I certainly wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't dad wasn't couldn't think of anybody else that was going to he said well yeah but also you know you sort of think about in the afterlife you know some people believe in that some people think you know this is such a an important part of that person's life that you think that they want that with them you know I'm like <pause dur="short"/> okay she's dead but alright I can sort of buy it that maybe it's more for the family to think that it's quite comforting</u>
<u n="586" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="587" who="S0262">and er so I said oh right well I I and I pulled pulled out cos I didn't know what to bring so I just had a bag full of stuff and er and he went oh that's quite suitable that's nice he goes but no that won't be and I said oh that's my mum's college scarf and he said well yeah but that's something that you could wear you see that's something that you could wear still and have</u>
<u n="588" who="S0300" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0262">as part of her and I went <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I'd never thought about it like that before</u>
<u n="590" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="591" who="S0262">but then there're <trunc>cer</trunc>certain other little things he thought was great like I bought in little cigarillos that she used to like you know and er you know er what else did I bring? just just a dress that I knew she liked and you know I don't know I some smaller things like that you know maybe a little or yeah a little hat cap that she used to really like wearing</u>
<u n="592" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0262">and er interestingly enough he said have the take back the college scarf but we'll keep the hat <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was laughing I could have seen I was trying to understand his logic but</u>
<u n="594" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah if he's took that why didn't he take the scarf?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0262">right I know and I and I just</u>
<u n="596" who="S0300">and he's took her dress but not her scarf</u>
<u n="597" who="S0262">I know</u>
<u n="598" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0262">and the dress was so big because</u>
<u n="600" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0262">when she died she was really like nothing you know</u>
<u n="602" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0262">the all of her all of her you know unfortunately all of her body mass really had kind of wasted away but erm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0262">but erm this dress was just I I'd forgotten that she was so small and that you know she had been quite you know a sizeable lady I mean like as in a size fourteen fifteen like sixteen I don't know</u>
<u n="606" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0262">and erm so I presented this dress and it was massive and I was like oh crikey I've really buggered that one up</u>
<u n="608" who="S0300" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0262">maybe I should've given one of my dresses or you know something with a little bit more</u>
<u n="610" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0262">and he said no no no that's fine if she would have worn it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't even worry about that don't even think about that that if she would have worn in and you can see her wearing it then we'll put it on her and you will I'll tell you that all these things I I promise you will be all nicely arranged in the coffin so when you're looking at the coffin try not to look at the coffin but looking at what you're</u>
<u n="612" who="S0300" trans="overlap">visualise</u>
<u n="613" who="S0262">thinking about inside okay and he goes if you ever want to ask me what you you know in the service just ask me and I'll you know I didn't cos I was like whatever but you know I could have asked him I could've said oh you know and he would have just calmed me down and said something so I guess a lot of their job is quite behind the scenes stuff and we don't really see</u>
<u n="614" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="615" who="S0262">everything we just see them kind of organising us</u>
<u n="616" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0262">but really they have to put quite a lot of effort into it</u>
<u n="618" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0262">cos there's families that must just fall apart</u>
<u n="620" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0262">and they have to keep it all together they've got to keep the show on the road</u>
<u n="622" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0262">cos they've got to get those families out of the crematorium</u>
<u n="624" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0262">they can't have them all</u>
<u n="626" who="S0300">no <pause dur="short"/> sobbing <pause dur="short"/> in there</u>
<u n="627" who="S0262">that's just</u>
<u n="628" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="629" who="S0262">not good for anyone</u>
<u n="630" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="631" who="S0262">so they have to keep everyone together but</u>
<u n="632" who="S0300">no I mean I went to see my nan erm in in at the funeral place</u>
<u n="633" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="634" who="S0300">and I wished I hadn't</u>
<u n="635" who="S0262">oh yeah I see I</u>
<u n="636" who="S0300">she looked normal</u>
<u n="637" who="S0262">thought it would be a bit weird</u>
<u n="638" who="S0300">yeah I mean my mum wanted to go but she didn't wanna go on her own</u>
<u n="639" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0300">nobody else would go with her so I kind of said I'd go with her but not meaning I'd go</u>
<u n="641" who="S0262" trans="overlap">in with her</u>
<u n="642" who="S0300">with her with her</u>
<u n="643" who="S0262">yes</u>
<u n="644" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0262">you'd wait outside <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no she took me in there and you know yes she can only see sort of from there upwards and it did look like my nan</u>
<u n="647" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0300">erm but no <pause dur="short"/> it was just</u>
<u n="649" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0300">well it just looked like a waxwork</u>
<u n="651" who="S0262">well this is it and</u>
<u n="652" who="S0300" trans="overlap">that's what she looked like she looked like a Madame Tussauds' waxwork you know</u>
<u n="653" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="654" who="S0300">and I don't I mean I think it was about a week after she'd died cos I think after a certain time cos my niece and brother weren't allowed to go and see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a week before she was cremated</u>
<u n="655" who="S0262">weren't allowed?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="657" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="658" who="S0300">no cos the body had started to</u>
<u n="659" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh yes well it would yeah that's right yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0300">er</u>
<u n="661" who="S0262">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0300">so er yeah so they kind of stop you after about a week or so anyway</u>
<u n="663" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0300">so it must have been within a week that we went to see my nan but I do I kind of I I won't do it again</u>
<u n="665" who="S0262">no I I might do depending on the circumstances</u>
<u n="666" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0262">like with my mum I did get to see her before she died but the thing is is that I saw her after she'd died so I actually did see her</u>
<u n="668" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0262">and you know got to say goodbye and you know some people have this idea that the you know sort of just just after someone's died you know there is this sense of soul in the room</u>
<u n="670" who="S0300">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0262">you know some religions are in to that Buddhism is quite into it</u>
<u n="672" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0262">and that you can sit in the room and wait for the soul to pass on</u>
<u n="674" who="S0300">that's it</u>
<u n="675" who="S0262">and it can be something like forty-eight hours</u>
<u n="676" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="677" who="S0262">and that's why some religions are really people sit and mourn and don't talk because they really believe that so</u>
<u n="678" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no but yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0262">so I was kind of into that idea but I thought oh no you know well whatever</u>
<u n="680" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0262">and but when it came to mum I just thought there's no point going back and having a look because really she wasn't herself when she died she didn't look anything like the mum I remember</u>
<u n="682" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="683" who="S0262">not at all</u>
<u n="684" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="685" who="S0262">this is this is something completely different as in you know <pause dur="short"/> yeah why would you wanna have that lasting memory? you really don't want to have that lasting memory you're probably better off just looking at photos of when she was well well and</u>
<u n="686" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0262">happy and</u>
<u n="688" who="S0300">and happy you've got so many photos</u>
<u n="689" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah like those photos yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0300">so</u>
<u n="691" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="692" who="S0300">you know and there's loads in there and</u>
<u n="693" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0300">your dad's got them in his room and you know so yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's better to have that</u>
<u n="696" who="S0300">I think so</u>
<u n="697" who="S0262">but I can see why it might be useful if <pause dur="short"/> particularly if you really hadn't seen the person for a long time</u>
<u n="698" who="S0300">yeah see I yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0262">and they're someone very close to you</u>
<u n="700" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0262">I could see why there's that sense of closure</u>
<u n="702" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0262">I don't know what it is about actually seeing someone but some people believe that you need to really go to start the grief process you <trunc>ha</trunc> it's like a trigger you need to see the person's passed on</u>
<u n="704" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I think my niece went to see her her mum three times</u>
<u n="705" who="S0262">yeah to really believe it</u>
<u n="706" who="S0300">to really yeah for it really to sink in</u>
<u n="707" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah to start the grief</u>
<u n="708" who="S0300">to her head that her mum wasn't here</u>
<u n="709" who="S0262" trans="overlap">otherwise you're in limbo</u>
<u n="710" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0262">and you can't start grieving yet <unclear/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0300" trans="overlap">cos although you know they've gone</u>
<u n="713" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0300">and they're not coming back</u>
<u n="715" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="716" who="S0300">but as you say there's something in your head that's telling you <pause dur="short"/> well I can still go and see my mum</u>
<u n="717" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0300">and I can go and talk to my mum</u>
<u n="719" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0300">you know so I just think until they're gone gone</u>
<u n="721" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0300">so like after last <trunc>so</trunc>sort of say once they they took that coffin away to everybody then it was over</u>
<u n="723" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0300">cos you know no one was ever gonna see the coffin</u>
<u n="725" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="726" who="S0300">or or her again</u>
<u n="727" who="S0262">no that's right</u>
<u n="728" who="S0300">so in in your head you can kind of like think this is it she has gone and this is the end</u>
<u n="729" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's final yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0300">and then you get you know I know you don't just get on with things but you you do start to start thinking a little bit more normally</u>
<u n="731" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="732" who="S0300">and think you know well I've got to do this now and I've got to that that but</u>
<u n="733" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah well it you've got to get on with life</u>
<u n="734" who="S0300">you have I know it sounds harsh but as you say life goes on you've got to get on with it</u>
<u n="735" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0300">you know you can't dwell on someone passing for the rest of your life</u>
<u n="737" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0300">as I say you're always gonna think about it and and stuff but you know so no so in my eyes as soon as that coffin had gone last week life went on for everybody and everybody just started to laugh and as I say get all them I call them cancer sticks cos I I I'm one of those erm I I smoked and gave up</u>
<u n="739" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm that's right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0300">so I'm one of the really negative people</u>
<u n="741" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0300">I always said I wouldn't do it my dad he gave up and he is the most anti-smoker going</u>
<u n="743" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah right</u>
<u n="744" who="S0300">and now I am and sadly my <trunc>you</trunc> eldest daughter does smoke</u>
<u n="745" who="S0262">oh dear</u>
<u n="746" who="S0300">I can't stop her</u>
<u n="747" who="S0262">yeah does she smoke much?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0300">not really no she's more of a social smoker</u>
<u n="749" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0300">or she might have a crave you know like er where was we? <pause dur="short"/> we was out on Saturday we went in erm to to <anon type="place"/> Tesco's and er as we're walking back to the car she's like ah just walk slow cos I need to have a fag she said and you won't let me smoke it in your car I said oh lord <vocal desc="laugh"/> because it's just disgusting</u>
<u n="751" who="S0262">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0300">you know and I mean I was hypnotised</u>
<u n="753" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0300">as well so to give up smoking so</u>
<u n="755" who="S0262">so it really is bad for you</u>
<u n="756" who="S0300">it really is</u>
<u n="757" who="S0262">if you smell it it's like er</u>
<u n="758" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah you you sort of your subconscious has got this particular smell or taste</u>
<u n="759" who="S0262">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0300">for a fag</u>
<u n="761" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="762" who="S0300">so if I was to light up a fag and draw on it that that's the taste I would get or subconsciously I would get I mean whether it would work after ten years I don't know but</u>
<u n="763" who="S0262">yeah yeah well probably</u>
<u n="764" who="S0300">but the smell is horrific</u>
<u n="765" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0300">d'you know? I mean I hated the smell of <trunc>fa</trunc>fags when I did smoke</u>
<u n="767" who="S0262">anyway yeah but now it's extra bad yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0300">but er you know and and she like if she walks in the house and she's had one in her car and</u>
<u n="769" who="S0262">you can smell it yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0300" trans="overlap">or it just it does it makes me want to vomit</u>
<u n="771" who="S0262">oh dear</u>
<u n="772" who="S0300">so er but yeah she does smoke and erm but yeah they were all she <trunc>w</trunc> she was one of them and they all smoke roll-ups as well and I just find roll-ups are so common</u>
<u n="773" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0300">I'm not a snob but d'you know what it's not not the <trunc>commo</trunc> not common I think it's the sitting there watching them roll it</u>
<u n="775" who="S0262">rolling up yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0300">if you're gonna have a rolly then roll it before you go out</u>
<u n="777" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="778" who="S0300">you know and just</u>
<u n="779" who="S0262">yeah it's the whole rolling-up thing yeah</u>
<u n="780" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but they <trunc>ac</trunc> they was all sitting along this wall</u>
<u n="781" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's like a little production line <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0300">in the graveyard you know all on the wall and they were all sitting there going <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0300">and putting their <trunc>d</trunc> ah I was just like what? you know I thought no if you you know say if if you're a rolly smoker then roll some up beforehand</u>
<u n="785" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah especially at an event like that you'd probably want to just have a quick one yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but that's all you saw all day was just people rolling fags</u>
<u n="787" who="S0262">gosh and how was your niece?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0300">d'you know what she <trunc>di</trunc> I don't think I saw her cry once</u>
<u n="789" who="S0262">yeah I think that's true <pause dur="short"/> you're so numb</u>
<u n="790" who="S0300">she did kind of hold it together</u>
<u n="791" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0300">she did like a speech thing</u>
<u n="793" who="S0262">oh good for her</u>
<u n="794" who="S0300">erm she did start to crumble a little bit when she did that but she didn't completely go</u>
<u n="795" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0300">erm but no I don't think apart from that I didn't see her cry or look sad at <trunc>a</trunc> even when the coffin was sitting there in front of you outside in the car still hearse still you know there's me going ah you know and then she's just standing there just but then I think</u>
<u n="797" who="S0262">you're so numb</u>
<u n="798" who="S0300">yeah I think sort of say when everybody had gone home cos everybody that was there from this end of the country erm we were all leaving on the Tuesday</u>
<u n="799" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0300">so there would only have been her grandad her dad and her in the house</u>
<u n="801" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0300">whereas prior to that she'd had friends staying and you know plenty of people there so I think it probably would have hit them all</u>
<u n="803" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0300">quite hard on Tuesday evening by that time though I think they all might have been quite drunk</u>
<u n="805" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes yes that's</u>
<u n="806" who="S0300">so it would've maybe hit them maybe Wednesday Thursday</u>
<u n="807" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0300">erm and then apparently today as far as I know my niece is coming back to <anon type="place"/> with her grandad</u>
<u n="809" who="S0262">oh good cos you were wondering if she was gonna</u>
<u n="810" who="S0300" trans="overlap">er <trunc>fo</trunc>for two weeks</u>
<u n="811" who="S0262">oh good</u>
<u n="812" who="S0300">and then my brother stayed in Plymouth</u>
<u n="813" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="814" who="S0300">erm cos they've got two dogs as well two little dogs so and he's got his job there as well so he's there on his own</u>
<u n="815" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0300">which he's quite happy he's like me he's quite happy to be on his own</u>
<u n="817" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0300">erm we are both of us</u>
<u n="819" who="S0262">for some people it's quite good</u>
<u n="820" who="S0300">we are <trunc>lo</trunc> not loners but we like our own company</u>
<u n="821" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0300">erm</u>
<u n="823" who="S0262">you need space</u>
<u n="824" who="S0300">we like peace and quiet</u>
<u n="825" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0300">er I don't like to be around too many</u>
<u n="827" who="S0262">too much clatter yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0300" trans="overlap">people no</u>
<u n="829" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="830" who="S0300">erm I think my mum's like that too I think it's just the fact that our heads can't take</u>
<u n="831" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0300">too much it's like if I go into a pub or some or into a shop and you can just hear all these voices</u>
<u n="833" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0300">and music playing</u>
<u n="835" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0300">and my head just feels like it's gonna <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="837" who="S0262">yeah explode yeah</u>
<u n="838" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah so I just like to sit in my own silence and erm</u>
<u n="839" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's very good it's sort of like meditating in a way isn't it?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0300" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> but it's I do I love it it's my way of</u>
<u n="841" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0300">you know when I suffered with <trunc>dep</trunc> well I still do but not as badly but I do suffer with depression</u>
<u n="843" who="S0262">oh okay</u>
<u n="844" who="S0300">erm which I had a really bad bout at the beginning of this year</u>
<u n="845" who="S0262">oh right</u>
<u n="846" who="S0300">and it only sort of finished about two months ago where it sort of pretty calm at the moment</u>
<u n="847" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="848" who="S0300">so I find sitting on my own somewhere at home</u>
<u n="849" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0300">is how I I deal with it if I'm having a bad day then I just say I'm having a bad day and I just go off and I sit on my own for hours</u>
<u n="851" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0300">and people just know to leave me alone</u>
<u n="853" who="S0262">oh that's good yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0300">otherwise I will just start going rah rah rah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0300">to them</u>
<u n="857" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0300">erm and my brother's like that he's got depression too so it I think it must run in our generation cos no one other than my my brothers and my generation <trunc>da</trunc> and then it's downwards from there that people seem to be suffering with depression in our family</u>
<u n="859" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise it was hereditary</u>
<u n="860" who="S0300">I don't think I don't know if it is or not it might just be but we seem to have</u>
<u n="861" who="S0262" trans="overlap">something that people have in common in your family</u>
<u n="862" who="S0300">yeah but then saying that doctors diagnose depression for everything nowadays</u>
<u n="863" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="864" who="S0300">and that annoys me because there's depression and there's being unhappy</u>
<u n="865" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="866" who="S0300">and the I find they're two completely different things</u>
<u n="867" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="868" who="S0300">cos depression makes you do things that you wouldn't</u>
<u n="869" who="S0262">normally do</u>
<u n="870" who="S0300">normally do</u>
<u n="871" who="S0262">no that's true yeah very out of character</u>
<u n="872" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I've experienced one really out of character thing</u>
<u n="873" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="874" who="S0300">but yeah erm but being unhappy and and miserable</u>
<u n="875" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0300">is completely different because you're choosing to be unhappy and miserable if you've got depression you're not actually choosing to have it</u>
<u n="877" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you haven't got a choice</u>
<u n="878" who="S0300">it's there</u>
<u n="879" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0300">and apparently when I saw a psychiatrist I've <trunc>i</trunc> I've had it here since I was about fifteen</u>
<u n="881" who="S0262">yeah I was gonna ask if you'd had it for</u>
<u n="882" who="S0300">yeah it goes back</u>
<u n="883" who="S0262">can go back for quite</u>
<u n="884" who="S0300" trans="overlap">to when I was a teenager</u>
<u n="885" who="S0262">a long time yeah</u>
<u n="886" who="S0300">and the same with my brother</u>
<u n="887" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0300">erm looking back now we can we can work it back to when he was a kid</u>
<u n="889" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0300">so erm</u>
<u n="891" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I I'm a big believer that it probably happens in the formative years</u>
<u n="892" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean it might the onset of it might come on</u>
<u n="893" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0300">I mean my I've only been diagnosed with it for three years</u>
<u n="895" who="S0262">oh okay</u>
<u n="896" who="S0300">so it's not very long at all</u>
<u n="897" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0300">but</u>
<u n="899" who="S0262">did you have any postnatal depression?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="901" who="S0262">no it wasn't that</u>
<u n="902" who="S0300">no no which is what the psychiatrist asked cos he he wanted to see how far back he thought it went</u>
<u n="903" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0300">but I did have problems as a teenager at home and stuff and did some stupid things</u>
<u n="905" who="S0262">like we all do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="906" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="907" who="S0262">don't we? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="908" who="S0300">yeah erm so yeah so he's kind of took it back to the to like when I was about fourteen erm</u>
<u n="909" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> and do you get pills like you know for it? to manage it?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0300" trans="overlap">they do give you anti-depressants</u>
<u n="911" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0300">which I did take but they they make your head go even more doolally sometimes so <pause dur="short"/> when I sort of like had a a bad flare up of it flare up's the wrong word but erm in the beginning of this year erm I went to see a counsellor</u>
<u n="913" who="S0262">oh okay</u>
<u n="914" who="S0300">rather than take drugs</u>
<u n="915" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0300">and it was just a lady she was <trunc>sk</trunc> like it was like talking to my mum but she doesn't know anything about me</u>
<u n="917" who="S0262">mm and she's not judging you <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0300" trans="overlap">erm and I would just <pause dur="short"/> no and I would just meet her once a week for an hour and that just seemed to what she taught</u>
<u n="919" who="S0262" trans="overlap">wow just once a week for an hour?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0262">that's impressive</u>
<u n="922" who="S0300">and what she taught me to do was she taught me to self-medicate</u>
<u n="923" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="924" who="S0300">so she taught me how to get out of a situation</u>
<u n="925" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="926" who="S0300">without needing to see her or take drugs and analyse things</u>
<u n="927" who="S0262">yeah so like coping mechanisms right</u>
<u n="928" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah and then <pause dur="short"/> deal with it yourself</u>
<u n="929" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="930" who="S0300">basically and touch wood</u>
<u n="931" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's pretty impressive isn't it?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0300">yeah I haven't seen her for about six months</u>
<u n="933" who="S0262">yeah and there's quite a lot you could have been kind of brought on depressions particularly around now</u>
<u n="934" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> since then</u>
<u n="935" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0300">I mean I have had bad days and I do I sit there and I think do I call her? cos I've got her number so if ever I have a bad really really bad day I can always call her and talk to her over the phone but I haven't I I've just sort of as I say taken myself off to a quiet area of the house</u>
<u n="937" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0300">and then you just sort of like your brain goes into overdrive and you start thinking this that and this that and this that</u>
<u n="939" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0300">but you can you can self <trunc>sor</trunc> you know you can sort it out</u>
<u n="941" who="S0262">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's good</u>
<u n="942" who="S0300">if you put your mind to it see a lot of people are worse that what I am</u>
<u n="943" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0300">I mean I'm a moderate depressed have moderate depression</u>
<u n="945" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0300">I don't have severe depression</u>
<u n="947" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="948" who="S0300">if you've got severe depression then obviously yes you are on drugs you are seeing a counsellor and you are seeing a psychiatrist</u>
<u n="949" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0300">because I'm sort of like in the middle</u>
<u n="951" who="S0262">yeah you can actually do that</u>
<u n="952" who="S0300" trans="overlap">erm I can actually</u>
<u n="953" who="S0262">yeah do it yourself yeah</u>
<u n="954" who="S0300" trans="overlap">do it myself if I put my mind to it</u>
<u n="955" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0300">and you you know you just sort of sit there and you think do you wanna go on drugs?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="958" who="S0300">I take too many already for other reasons</u>
<u n="959" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's true</u>
<u n="960" who="S0300">erm you know the fact I have to inhale an inhaler is getting on my nerves cos it's just another thing that you've got to to think of doing every day</u>
<u n="961" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="962" who="S0300">erm but yeah so I do manage to cope</u>
<u n="963" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="964" who="S0300">erm but I do have to make it known to everybody in my family</u>
<u n="965" who="S0262">yes they understand</u>
<u n="966" who="S0300" trans="overlap">that yeah you know</u>
<u n="967" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0300">or or they'll turn around and say are you feeling a bit low this week? you know cos they've picked up on on certain clues like my my mum mum and dad would</u>
<u n="969" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> your mood <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="970" who="S0300"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gives you the silent treatment</u>
<u n="971" who="S0262">oh dear</u>
<u n="972" who="S0300">so he can't deal with illness</u>
<u n="973" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="974" who="S0300">or or anything so like when I had cancer when I was in hospital for my bowel disease when I have to go in to hospital like last Thursday you know he he just cuts you off</u>
<u n="975" who="S0262" trans="overlap">shuts it out <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's too much</u>
<u n="976" who="S0300">cos he he won't talk about it</u>
<u n="977" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="978" who="S0300">and he can't talk about it cos he can't deal with illness</u>
<u n="979" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="980" who="S0300">so</u>
<u n="981" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="982" who="S0300">that's that's quite hurtful in a way because you feel like you need his support</u>
<u n="983" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0300">but you know you're not gonna get it</u>
<u n="985" who="S0262">oh gosh</u>
<u n="986" who="S0300">and when I was going through the cancer he would talk to everybody about how upset he was and you know how he was worried and this that and the other but never once said it to me</u>
<u n="987" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but never to you</u>
<u n="988" who="S0300">so you had to hear it from other people so although I know deep down he's thinking of you</u>
<u n="989" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="990" who="S0300">but he won't show you it because he's an emotionless person</u>
<u n="991" who="S0262">okay right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0300" trans="overlap">so you know he's he doesn't know how to show emotion he wasn't brought up to be emotional or to show feelings</u>
<u n="993" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="994" who="S0300">so whereas we're completely different in that way you see I I mean I cry at the telly you know</u>
<u n="995" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so do I <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0300">I cry reading a book</u>
<u n="997" who="S0262">overly emotional sometimes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah I am I mean I'll be reading a a magazine you know and it'll just be a a a two page story and I'll be like</u>
<u n="999" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> welling up yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0300">you know and I'm like whoa what are you doing you know? you know</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0300">erm so yeah I am highly emotional and one of my daughters is but the other one is emotionless like her dad</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yeah interesting so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0300">but they've both been brought up to have emotion</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0300">and and show it you know</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0262">I suppose one well the other one might just think it's easier not to show emotion</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0300">yeah see like <pause dur="short"/> with my asthma attack on Friday it was quite quite a bad attack you know and I I did I thought I was gonna die I was like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1009" who="S0262">oh god</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0300">like that I couldn't breathe and I was on my own</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> you know and I did go into panic mode</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0262">yeah I can imagine</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I mean when I contacted the eldest daughter and told her what had happened she was like oh my god mum are you okay rah rah rah? the youngest one she was like oh right well you look okay now then and that that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you see if they can't physically see anything wrong with you then</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0300">there's nothing wrong with you</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0262">there's no reaction there's no response yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no I mean if I've got like erm I don't know a battered body or whatever you know you can see a bruise on my face or something it would make them think oh yeah she's you know</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0300">she's had a bit of a donk today</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but if they can't see it</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but because they <trunc>ca</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah and because my <trunc>whee</trunc> when I was wheezing yeah they they could hear it so they were like oh you know she did sort of sometimes say oh do you need your inhaler? or whatever but other than that there's nothing there so you know with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you just have to to</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just let it be</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0300">yeah just get on with it</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0262" trans="overlap">let it <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean yeah I I find that really hard cos I'm not like that at all as a person</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no see I'm not I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a cold</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0300">you know man flu</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0300">and even this morning I said oh I said how're you feeling? oh I said do you want me to get you some more Lemsip? no you know and I'm kinda he all he's got is a cold and I'm still sort of like saying how you know how are you this morning? sort of thing</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0300">but you know Saturday morning I've woke up and I go <vocal desc="misc"/> like this and there's just nothing there</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0300">you know and I'm like I'm I'm dying here</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's so funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0300">you know I'm going</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0300">I'm dying here can you hear me? you know and it's like hurry up then you know but <pause dur="short"/> there's just nothing</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0262">no I know it's some people are yeah</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0300" trans="overlap">you know deep down inside there is but he just can't show it</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah can't show it it's just too hard</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0300">and he say he wasn't brought up with it so you know it is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and I think it is more difficult for men because I know not necessarily but it depends on the generation they're brought into but I think like you know for my dad when I think about it he you know er the tradition is is that men don't cry</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0262">men don't get overly emotional</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0262">you know? they're the ones to calm the womenfolk down you know</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0262">and all this sort of thing</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and especially someone like your dad really cos he was in army wasn't he?</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0262" trans="overlap">the army yeah yeah so you're trained</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0300" trans="overlap">so yeah he's quite <trunc>regi</trunc>regimental</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah you're trained not to be emotional</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah to have emotion</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0262">you're meant to be</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0262">unemotional</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0300">yeah but then I have seen your dad cry</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0262" trans="overlap">er <unclear>for your job</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah and so have I</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0300">when when yeah when little <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> passed away</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0262">yeah when mum yeah you know</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and then obviously yeah and the year before that was your mum so but I remember coming in on the Tuesday he'd already emailed me and said that he'd he'd have to have him put to sleep and then I came in on the Tuesday and the first thing your dad did was just stand there and burst into tears</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> just blub yeah</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0300">and put his arms round me</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0300">you know and then we both blubbed together</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0300">you know cos I I obviously I quite liked loved little <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> he was just so sweet</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0262">he was wasn't he? yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0300">er you know I'm you know we <trunc>n</trunc> we don't barely know each other</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0262">yeah that's right but</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0300">we were both standing in the middle of the room blubbering you know in each other's arms</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but we both knew how each other felt which is the</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0262">important thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0300">so erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so even even men that have had it drummed into them</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0262">oh they can be I mean my dad I think underneath the surface is highly emotional</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0262">it's just that he's not a shower you know</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0300">no see when you look at your dad and you hear hear your dad speak you'd think <trunc>i</trunc> he was quite a stern <pause dur="short"/> not cold but a cool man</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0300">erm but he's not</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0262">no no</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0300" trans="overlap">so you can never judge a book by its cover</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no he's</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0300" trans="overlap">cos like when I first met your dad I thought</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he's Scorpio if you believe in any of all that stuff that Scorpio stuff he's highly emotional</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0262">it's just that he's learnt how to</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0300">control it</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0262">control it yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1093" who="S0262">whereas I I don't see the point like I'm like oh let it go I'm in and out it's kind of like the tide you know</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0262">to me I can be up one down whatever but that's to me that's actually healthy</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0262">cos it's like your temperature</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0262">you're hot you're cold but somehow your body's gonna regulate it</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0262">if it's alright it's working okay and that's how I know if I'm actually alright cos if I can regulate my emotions</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0262">then I'm thinking okay I'm not losing the plot but if I can't</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0262">then I'm like oh that's what's so scary</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0300" trans="overlap">well you're not normal are you?</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0262">about when mum died</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0262">I was like this isn't me normally I'd be all over the place crying and like running around but I was numb and that was the first time in my life where I thought I don't feel anything</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> feel right yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0262">anything anything</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0300">yeah no</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0262">I didn't feel anything</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0262">I <trunc>ke</trunc>kept waiting to feel something</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0262">and I was like it's gonna set in soon isn't it this grief?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0262">this whole thing is gonna happen soon isn't it? then it was like oh but you can't force that either</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0300">no no</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0262">you just have to let that numbness kind of you know</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no control over it like yeah</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and that's obviously the shock</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0300">which I think is what my niece is going through now</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0262">such a shock to the system yeah</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0300" trans="overlap">she's gonna come down here for two weeks and have a ball and she's going to be getting so much attention and she's gonna be seeing so many people she's not going to have time to really grieve</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0300">so until she gets back home</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0262">that's when it hits you</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and then realises it's just her and her dad</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0300">then by that time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would have been in his grieving process</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <trunc>may</trunc>maybe maybe not</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0300">maybe not though cos again he's</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he might wait until she gets back</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0262">cos everyone's a bit funny like that</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0262">you know I've noticed now that since <pause dur="short"/> I've got back to <anon type="place"/> because I think living in Australia meant that I didn't actually know I know that my mum died but I didn't feel it as keenly because I wasn't living in the house or seeing dad or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or whatever so now being back for three months I'm quite aware of the fact that I've been grieving like what I would say quite in depth grief</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> you wasn't here no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0262">which isn't dealing with the superficial bits which you deal with you know when someone initially dies is you actually go through the whole emotional almost your whole life of emotion in a way</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0262">and I'm sure dad's going through the same because he's called me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a couple of times</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> has he? ah</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0262">and he's acknowledged that but I can also see that in some respects me being here is kind of triggering bits of grief for him</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0300" trans="overlap">grief off yeah course it is</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0262">which he may have kept on tap until he could get someone who is emotional enough like me to kind of get that erm grief going around the system</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0262">cos some people will just hold on to it</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0300">just hold on yeah</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0262">because they actually have no idea what to do with it otherwise</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0262">they don't know how to channel it</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0262">so I feel like I'm the catalyst and it's quite painful because it's painful for him it's painful for me and it's you know painful for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and you know he really loved my mum too</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0262">and he misses her and you know you you also all of those things bring back other things</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0262">that have been painful in your life whether it's been someone's death or not but it can also trigger I can see how it can actually be in a way I'm trying to say <pause dur="short"/> sometimes it's like that saying isn't it to be cruel to be kind but it's not really what I meant</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0262"><trunc>some</trunc>sometimes you have to go through those really hard patches <pause dur="short"/> to kind of everyone move on</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0300">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0262">I don't mean move on from my mum's death but just kind of get through some of the crappy stuff so you can clear that and make way for some better stuff</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0262">that's meant to be coming your way</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0262">cos I noticed that with my mum that she held on to erm really quite negative emotions I think about her dad which I <trunc>bri</trunc> talk about going to see my mum's half sister</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0262">who's lovely Welsh woman</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0300">ah</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0262">she is absolutely adorable her name is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I'm I really like her a lot she great she's really great</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0300" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0262">and we spent hours talking like a couple of hours erm at her home but I told her that cos they shared the same dad</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0262">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> unfortunately was at the time was illegitimate you know not that anybody really minds now any more cos there's no such thing really in a way is there? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1176" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no no no</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0262">illegitimacy doesn't really</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0262">in our modern day doesn't really exist <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1180" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0262">so but in her day back in the nineteen forties it certainly did</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0262">and erm so they shared the same father and erm and it must have been that erm her mum <pause dur="short"/> put it this way my granny probably got divorced because her mum came on the scene</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0300">right</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0262">and that's probably what triggered that divorce</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0262">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then her you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's who's my grandad and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0262">he went on to have a second child with erm with her mum</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0262">so it wasn't just like a flash in the pan thing</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0300">no it wasn't just a <pause dur="short"/> a bit of yeah</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but they actually had a boy as well as he has she has a brother so mum would've had a half-brother half-sister but half-brother quite sure I don't think he's all that interested but definitely <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is and and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said well you know the thing about it is is that my mum really harboured major like hatred <pause dur="short"/> it was hatred</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0262">because she loved him really <pause dur="short"/> but what she hated him for was that he rejected her and he didn't love her back and as a kid you can completely understand that you know this was from an early age</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0262">she was like under ten she's got the picture dad's not interested in me doesn't love me moving on to somebody else</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0262">so she kept that for way too long like you know way too long we would talk about it and I'd go mum really this one you've got to put to bed it's no good for you it's no good for you for your your health it's no good for your mental space it's no good for anyone's relationships you've got to put it to bed I kept trying to convince her <pause dur="short"/> nothing and you know I really do think that yeah she she <pause dur="short"/> it's really weird I don't know if I told you the story but I was telling my I had a massage before I got on the plane to come back to here when I knew my mum was dying cos I thought I've got to chill right out because it's gonna be like twenty-eight hour flight I'm not quite sure touch and go with mum</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0262">and er so anyway so I told her that my you know my mum was dying and erm she the masseur said <pause dur="short"/> erm oh did she have erm oh did she worry a lot? and I said yeah my mum worried like crazy about everyone everything and er she said oh did she have like spleen or did she have cancer in the spleen or something like this? I went <pause dur="short"/> it well not spleen but pancreas very nearby and she said mm and I went why? and this wasn't even before she started massaging me cos I think I was very emotional and er and I said why is that? and she goes well that's the thing about anger <pause dur="short"/> if you store it you think about the spleen is that when we think about anger</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0262">you can see where parts and this is the Chinese they're all into this they think the whole thing and the body and and and my way of saying to myself that it's okay to let my anger show sometimes not too much but sometimes it's healthy because when I think about how my mum kept this</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> bottled up</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0262">negative emotion it must have got into her system somewhere and stored somewhere it stored in the pancreas</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0262">now I know that's a leap of faith from cancer to whatever but all I know is it's taught me a lesson</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0262">in my mind which is deal with it because there's no point holding on to it</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0262">whatever grudges are I I don't think it really causes cancer all I'm saying is that in my mind grudges aren't gonna help you</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0262">I think that's the thing you know?</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0262">you know</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0262">that's what I've learnt</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0262">I think from my mum</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0262">and and she really did begrudge her dad and I just thought it's such a shame because having now spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she never had a particularly erm strong relationship with her father though he gave her away at her wedding</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0300">right</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0262">em but she doesn't really have any emotions to him one way or the other she's actually quite indifferent</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0262">and I thought that was quite interesting</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0262">and er but you know she said that's the thing I don't hate him but then again I don't love him</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0262">he's my father and I recognise that and he recognised me as his daughter but that's it and I thought in a way that's actually alright isn't it? cos you're neither one</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0300">or the other</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0262">or the other <pause dur="short"/> you're not gonna be disappointed</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0262">but then you're not gonna be you know erm thinking that he's somebody that he that he's not</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0300">yeah that he's not no no</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0262" trans="overlap">or wants he's dead now so in a way that's quite a</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0262">good way of dealing with stuff and I thought mm</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wonder if I could take this new kind of indifferenceness to things you know rather than going hot and cold hot and cold hot and cold</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah gosh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> just stay the same all the time</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0262">just kind of oh well that's life just</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0262">it's all going to pass</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I've always always said to my girls I said you don't have to it's like with family I said you don't have to like them</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0300">but you should always love them</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> which we do get quite a lot of in our <trunc>fam</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I mean I've freely said to him I said I don't like you</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0300">very much I said but I do love you with all my heart</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0300">you know and you don't have to like a person it's like your <trunc>sibli</trunc> I mean my girls don't like</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0300">they they make out</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0262" trans="overlap">they're not close yeah</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0300">but yeah they are close that's the <trunc>thin</trunc> well they are and they aren't</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0300">they they make out that they can't get on</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0300">but they can</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0262">they can it's the choice they make</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0300" trans="overlap">you know and they just choose to be bitchy to each other every time the <trunc>oth</trunc> you know like</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0262">it's easier to be a bitch that not to be <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah and also if you're being a bitch you're being listened to</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0262">yeah you're getting attention</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0300">if yeah if you're just sitting there having a <trunc>conve</trunc> like say for example today if I was to walk in and both the girls were there if they were sitting there having a proper conversation</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0300">then I would ignore them</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0300">but if I was to walk in and they're going like this they're both going to get attention</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah you'd stop them yeah that's right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0300" trans="overlap">cos I'm gonna shout at both of them to shut up</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so they're still vying for mummy's attention really</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah and it is it's all an attention thing</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0300">er and you know and they'll say of well I hate her and it's like <trunc>sh</trunc> I hate her and I say like it's fine to hate</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0300">although hate is a harsh word</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0300">dislike is really the better word</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0300">but it's alright to hate somebody but if they're your family you <trunc>wha</trunc>whatever you should still love them</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0300">you know so this but I don't know I don't know how you can</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0262">yeah yeah I don't think you can I think</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I don't think you</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0262">the way that <pause dur="short"/> people</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I don't think you can you <trunc>lik</trunc> not like someone and not love them but still</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0262">yeah I think a lot of it's to do with respect</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0262">I think that tends to help</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I think that's a major thing is is respect</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah I think if you can at least respect someone</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0300">somebody</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0262">and they can respect you then love might come follow from that</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> might come with it yeah</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0262">but if you haven't got respect but you're still demanding love and I think that happens with a lot of parents actually they demand love from their kids</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0262">but the kids don't respect them</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0262">it's like</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0262">what <trunc>ha</trunc> what happened there? you know</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0262">and I think that's an awful shame</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0262">I don't know why the kids don't respect their parents</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0300">no cos mine my mine do and don't I mean I <trunc>ha</trunc> my mum flipped at me the other weekend in front of the girls I don't know what caused her to have this mental breakdown</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0300">we were talking about something and she was convinced she was right and I knew that I was right</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0300">so I was trying to explain how I knew I was right</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0300">and as I'm trying to explain she's talking over me and in the end she just went will you shut the <pause dur="short"/> up</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0300">now my mum has never swore at me</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0300">and I've never swore at my mum</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so she must be stressed yeah</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0300">and she said it twice</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0262">oh dear</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0300">not just once <pause dur="short"/> I said don't speak to me like that and she said just shut the and she said it again and er I sat there like with my mouth open cos I was like</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0300">and then it all kicked off and I said and I just turned around and said well obviously you don't have any respect for me then</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0262">mm that's true <pause dur="short"/> that's a good point</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I said to swear at me like that in front of my kids</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's not that doesn't show respect yeah</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I said I would never ever ever swear at my parents I mean I know I'm not the parent I'm the daughter but I wouldn't swear at my kids like that</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0300">not <pause dur="short"/> I I do swear</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but the point is is that you're she's still your mum she can't let the side down</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah so I didn't swear back</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0300">how I don't know cos I do swear</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0300">and if someone really pees me off I will just keep going and going and going but I didn't swear once and and it after it had all calmed down I mean my mum did apologise and said I was totally out of order I don't know what happened there de de de de de</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0300">erm my <trunc>yo</trunc> eldest sat there and said my god I said what? and she said I really <trunc>di</trunc> I really don't respect you do I? <pause dur="short"/> and I went well no <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh she'd seen something where she recognised yeah okay</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah cos I because I said I would never speak to my mum</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0300">the way my mum had spoke to me erm because I respected my mum too much</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0300"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> then realised that she maybe doesn't speak to me the way she should speak to me</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0300">and doesn't show me the respect that she should not that it's made any difference</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah<pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0300">but <trunc>psycholo</trunc> she she kind of sat there and registered my god I don't respect my mum</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0300">and maybe as she gets older she will now learn to you know cos everybody in this everybody seems to swear at everybody swear is swearing is the norm but it's what context it's took in now I I can be having a conversation it my my mum and a and an F word will slip into sentence but it's not aimed at my mum you see</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0300">it's in the conversation</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0300">erm what my mum did was she aimed the F word bang at me erm</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0262" trans="overlap">at you yeah it was it was aggressive style and</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0300">yeah and obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has aimed swear words at me in anger</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0300">erm and maybe she thought you know well my mum moans about her mum all the time but she's never swore at her and she's never said anything horrible to her face mean I moan about my mum all the time to people</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0300">because she does my head in</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0262">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1362" who="S0300">I wouldn't sit there you know she does she</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like most mums do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1364" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah she's serious I mean I moan about everybody because <trunc>pe</trunc> and people moan about me you know but they don't moan to me to my face</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> and like I wouldn't say to my mum to her face what I'm saying behind her back which doesn't make me two faced</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0300">it just means I've got more respect for my mum</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0300">to speak to her</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0300">the way I'm thinking about her</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0300">you know I can sit here and say my god you're really pissing me off and blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0300">you know and be really horrible</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0300">but I wouldn't be able to do that to her face</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0262">no no</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0300">erm I wouldn't do it to my dad you know I wouldn't do it to anybody</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no you're right you're right and I think that these are learned responses that probably happens from when when you were really small and then also your daughters as well erm and I think that it's really hard once you've got into a kind of habit to break out of that habit</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0262">particularly because you are so close in the family and it's almost like you don't have any <pause dur="short"/> way out</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah and</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0300">also with my girls it's more like a friendship rather than a mum daughter thing</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0300">because like if my mum and perhaps you with your mum it was a proper mother daughter thing</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0300">you know we I mean yeah I've gone shopping with my mum and done things with my mum</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0300">but what I do with my girls is so much more than what my mum did or wanted to do with me</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0300">so with me it was <trunc>j</trunc> it was just a mother daughter relationship and we we fought like cat and dog</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0300">with the girls it's not like that you see there's too much friendship there rather than mother daughter ship</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0300">so it's it's hard cos</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0300">and I think that's why the <trunc>rece</trunc></u>
<u n="1401" who="S0262">yeah cos they may not see the boundaries</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0300">yeah and I think that's why the respect and that isn't there is because they're looking at me how they would look at a friend</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0300">and treating me cos that's what I say to them I say I'm not one of your friends from down the road I'm your mum</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but even then they should have respect for your their their friends so even if they classified you as a friend they should still have respect</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah but then they don't because all they do is moan about everybody</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1408" who="S0300">so and that's what I do I stand there and I go well I dread to think what you say about me to people</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1410" who="S0300">if that's how you talk about your friends</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0300">d'you know? and they say oh we never bad mouth you well you know they do</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0262">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0300" trans="overlap">we've all we've all gone off to our mates and said oh I hate my mum she's this she's that rah rah rah</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0262">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1416" who="S0300">you know we've all done it erm</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0262">of course we have yeah</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0300">and I know my kids are no different I mean you know they they must text it to people rather than say it you know</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0300">erm but yeah I mean I know if I have an if I have a to-do with one of my kids the first thing they do is de de de de on their phone and I'm thinking I wonder who they're putting me down to now</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0300">d'you know what it's just</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0262">and that's the thing about mobile technology</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0300">you can't hear them</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0262" trans="overlap">is that <pause dur="short"/> well and and but then you see they can vent whereas before like you know if I was with my mum and we'd had a row or something you know I'd go up to my room and I'd sulk and then I'd go okay well this is quite boring so I'd come back down and start talking to her normally and then we'll have a kiss and make up and say sorry</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah that's what my two do do yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0262">you know a but they're <trunc>the</trunc> you know I hardly ever bad mouthed my mum to to anybody</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0262">first of all I didn't have the chance and I don't think anybody of my friends really wanted to hear it</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0300">no no you see as a kid as a kid I didn't</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0300">I mean I I probably</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0262">they weren't actually that interested</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no I probably moan</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0262" trans="overlap">they're more interested in me than my mum if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> more about my mum now than I would have done as a kid</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0300">so yeah I don't think as a <trunc>ki</trunc> but nowadays as you say they've got these phones and</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0262">they can yeah they blah blah blah blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and they're constantly ch ch <pause dur="short"/> you know they're on Ipads or</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and and if you think about all the time if that is actually something that's going on in your life year after year after year after year after year that then becomes a habit and that then becomes something that you you realise is a crutch cos you get immediate responses back oh really you've had a falling out with your mum ah</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0262">so you're not dealing with anything you're just kind of responding</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0262">and you're just kind of either blocking or allowing things in I find that I think about you know young people and I think oh god I really don't envy them at all</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0300">mm mm</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0262">when I think about how hard it is for them today to grow up with all that stuff</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0262">body image</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0262">cos it's all over the place it's not like just adverts like we used to you and I used to see on television we'd go oh she's pretty or whatever la la la</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0262">or in a few magazines</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0262">if you can just go oh well I'll just close that down <unclear>lop it off</unclear></u>
<u n="1456" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0262">but now it's actually it's the internet it's all the social kind of media it's everything that they do</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0262">it's all about body image</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0262">and it does have a major effect on girls</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0300" trans="overlap">it does yeah</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0262">particularly girls</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but then both my girls are quite big girls</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0300">which is weird</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but they but they don't seem to have that kind of issue then well thank god for that then because some do</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no no they I think at school they did as <trunc>a</trunc> as I mean they're not adult I don't class them as adult adults but they're sort of like not in the the teenage thing but no they</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0262">good</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0300">they no they're they've never</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I'm glad to hear that</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0300">I mean I I don't remember ever thinking I wanna be skinny like that model in that magazine when I was a kid</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0300">and we've always <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s kind of like <pause dur="short"/> he does have this thing about bigger people</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0300">erm and he's always said to me if you get if you got you know we'll be watching the telly and he'll joke and say mm you look you're getting a bit like that now</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0262">oh god</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0300">and I say cheeky git and you know it's only a joke</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1480" who="S0300">but I kind of say to him well what would you do if I was like a size eighteen to twenty then? you'd be out the door</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1482" who="S0300">so you know image is a thing for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1483" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh god <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0300">so and I am the smallest one and I'm not small but I'm the smallest one in my house</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0300">because both my girls are but they're they're funny shapes</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0300">now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like up here the youngest one she's like her dad but she's and she's quite butch</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0300">erm <pause dur="short"/> she's not fat at all she's not at all she's got a jelly belly that's it the rest of her body is all in the proportion with her height so she's but she's big framed girl</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0300">erm and if she didn't have long hair from behind you'd think she was a bloke</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1494" who="S0300">she walks just like her dad as well now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't quite know where she's come from <pause dur="short"/> but she's my height</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0300">but she's quite a bit wider than me and she's got a very big jelly belly but she's got thighs like that</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0300">they're <trunc>humoung</trunc> I've never seen thighs I mean I did say to her at one point you need to go to the doctor's cos that must be some medical problem</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> some medical condition</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but then I watched but then I watched telly and a lot of these young girls for some unknown reason have these I mean they they they</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0262" trans="overlap">big thighs</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0300">bump yeah they bump out</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0262">wow</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0300">they have a bump and actual bump they're not just <trunc>fa</trunc> and they're solid they're not fat</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0300">they're they're</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0262">wow rock solid yeah</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0300">they're what you'd call a tree trunk you know they are</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah wow <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0300" trans="overlap">you know I mean yeah I mean I'd love to have solid legs</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0262">if you're an athlete or something that'd be kind of handy</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0300">but they're just massive you know and erm</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort of like a bloke like a rugby player or something yeah</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> and she's quite petite sort of from her chest upwards I mean she's got you know she's not but she she she say she's <trunc>qui</trunc> she's round</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1516" who="S0300">she's just I can't explain it</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0262" trans="overlap">lots of gesticulating wow</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah but it's just <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0262">and solid</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0300">she's just the weirdest shape I've ever seen</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1522" who="S0300">but she doesn't care</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0262">oh that's good yeah</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0300">you know and I do say to her though well perhaps you should care enough to lose some weight cos they also both weigh quite a lot more than me and again <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s height</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0262" trans="overlap">the only problem with that is the diseases that come later with it yeah</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well see now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s complaining she's always got sore ankles I said well that's because of all the weight you're carrying on top</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0262" trans="overlap">probably yeah</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0300">you know? I mean I said okay it's okay if you're happy to have you're your big legs and</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0300">and you know she's always out of breath she's always complaining that her joints are hurting and I said it's purely because</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> its probably lack of exercise is it? yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and she doesn't move</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0300">you know she starts work different times every day yesterday morning she had to start at half past seven she said oh my god I've got to get up at six o'clock in the morning and I'm like but that's the norm for most people you know</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0300">erm and then I've gotta work <trunc>un</trunc> er work until half past three and was like oh my god</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0262">you have no idea <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0300" trans="overlap">you know so then she's going home cos she lives with her boyfriend and his parents and apparently she's not allowed to do <trunc>an</trunc> you know his mum does all the housework and does everything how she wants it done so all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has to do basically is just make sure the bedroom's kept clean and tidy and er yeah so the she goes home and just sits there couch potato <pause dur="short"/> and her job isn't physical she works</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0262" trans="overlap">how old is she?</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0300">she's twenty-two this month</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0262">oh god no she needs to be putting some good</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0300">and then yeah and she works in H and M in in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1543" who="S0262" trans="overlap">habits in place</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0300">so it's not a physical job <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on the other hand is eighteen <pause dur="short"/> and built like a bloke erm <pause dur="short"/> and does weigh more than both myself and my youngest daughter but she's very active in what she does erm</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah well she's got a bit of a more of a chance then</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0300">and every job that's she's had has been to do with animals so it's either been to do with horses okay it might only be mucking out stables all day long</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> but that's hard work <pause dur="short"/> god</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0300" trans="overlap">but that's hard work you know it's very physical work and sweeping yards and all that lot</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that's hard work</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0300">at the moment she's working at a er dog kennels stroke</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0300">erm grooming place erm so again she's walking the dogs</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah she's active yeah</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0300">she's physical when she's cleaning the the runs out she does the grooming side</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0300">they've also got a hydrotherapy pool thing</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0262">oh right</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0300">so she actually does get in there with the dogs and and swims with the dogs sort of thing</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> oh wow amazing</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0300">so everything she does she's do she's moving</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's active yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0300">all her body</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0262">yeah yeah that's great</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0300"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just either standing at a till so she's only really using her hands <pause dur="short"/> you know and her mouth erm</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1566" who="S0300">well that's probably the smallest part of her body is her is her little mouth which I don't think she's got any any fat around that</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1568" who="S0300">erm or she's on the shop floor or or no she's in delivery standing there going bending down and putting putting taking clothes out of a box putting them on a coat hanger and putting them on a rail</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0300">nothing she I mean and if you think prior to that she did care work but again some care work can be very physical</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0262">can be yeah</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0300">if you're doing all the hoist I mean I I went to a new job yesterday in <anon type="place"/> in this little cul-de-sac and it's an old people's place</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0300">so it's all houses full of old people erm and they have carers but this one guy the guy that I clean for he has two live-in carers</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0300">and he does have to be hoisted and lifted and he can't do anything for his</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0300">I mean I think he can just about feed himself erm</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> how old is he do you think?</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0300">oh he looked about seventy odd so</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0262">god</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0300">yeah he didn't he's not old old old cos I kind of look at your dad although I didn't realise how old your dad was until one of his birthday cards I thought your dad was only in his sixties</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah he does look pretty well and he and he <unclear/></u>
<u n="1584" who="S0300" trans="overlap">cos he does look pretty pretty pretty young and cos he's quite active</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and dad's active yeah and he always was you know he was like a runner and stuff and <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah so but no you know</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0262">not a smoker</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0262">bit of a drinker but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1590" who="S0300">we've all got to have something don't us?</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0262">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0300">you know you've got to</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0262">it never stops him from getting out of bed in the morning to go do a job</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0300" trans="overlap">I mean I don't drink also</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0262">you know</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0300">yeah and I don't drink coffee or or anything and I don't do I don't do anything erm but</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> bad for you yeah</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0300">yeah no erm apart from eating maybe the wrong foods now and again but I mean that's the only privilege I've got in life is to eat something wrong</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0300">you know like go and get a Big Mac from Macdonald's or something</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1602" who="S0300">and I'm like oh yes you know this is my sin of the year</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sin of the year</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0300">so sad <pause dur="short"/> but you know so</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0262">well that's hardly a sin really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1606" who="S0300">it's only a beefburger</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0262">that's right</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0300">but erm but no you know and I just kind of thought watching these people with this guy yesterday their work is very not always physical I mean a lot of the time they're just sitting there watching TV with him</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it can be <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0300">because once they've got him in his chair and done whatever</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but still you know in the mornings and the night time it is</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0300">exactly</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0262">to get him undressed and dressed</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0300" trans="overlap">where whereas what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did I mean she would describe it as just going round there making sure they took their meds making them a cup of tea and maybe a sandwich erm</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0300">and then sitting there with them for half an hour and then off you go to the next one so they'd just be in her car driving you know the actual thought of having to walk somewhere I mean she she works in the <anon type="place"/> but doesn't park in the <anon type="place"/> she parks round one of the back roads and then she has</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> oh right where it's free?</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0300">and then she has to walk ten minutes</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0300">oh my god</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1624" who="S0300">the first time she did it she rung me up she was going <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1625" who="S0262">oh no</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0300">I was like whatever's wrong with you? she said I've just had to walk ten minutes to get to my car</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's actually a bit of a worry</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0300">and I said to her I said I think you ought to go and have a medical</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0262">is she the one who's a smoker?</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0262">ah no</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0300">and both my girls were asthmatic as children anyway</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0262">oh god</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0300">as well so I do feel like she needs go and be checked out</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0300">but obviously she won't cos she says and there's nothing wrong you know and she'll say oh I know it's to do with my weight or it's to do with this to do with but she doesn't do anything about it you know she'll say oh I hate being size cos like when they went on holiday and you know she probably you know I'm I'm not being horrible but she probably didn't look that flattering in her bikini erm <pause dur="short"/> but then there's bigger girls than her there</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0300">but she'd sit there and say you know or like she saw pictures of me on holiday in my bikini she'll say oh I wished I looked like you and and erm what is it what's it feel like being the skinniest one in the house? and what's you know? and I just think if you're asking me these questions then obviously</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> something's bothering you</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0300">you're wishing that you was the skinniest one</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0300">and you were the one that looked better in a bikini so why aren't you doing something about it?</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0300">but with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's all moan moan moan moan moan</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0300">but she's got no motivation</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0300">you know like the other day she said oh we had such and such and such and such for dinner and then we went out and got a Macdonald's and then we did this and then we did</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh crikey she's just loading on the calories yeah</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0300" trans="overlap">you know and I just and I just say to her you know and then you're going home to bed</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0300">and then you're going to sleep and then you're not burning any of it off</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0262">what might happen is what happened to my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was all throughout her twenties pretty much erm really quite well <trunc>she</trunc> doctors would call her obese I mean not like some of the people on television you see nothing like that</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0262">but yeah definitely what they would say obese</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0262">erm <pause dur="short"/> and she went in for something I think it was just a just something quite regular and the doctor said hang on have you er had a erm you know a weight check recently or anything like that blood you know blood pressure whatnot? and she's like oh and then he said no no I want to see what you're all about and erm and he said to her listen and he gave her a right stern talking to and he said you are looking at diabetes</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0262">which is not fun</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0300">yeah which is what they told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0262" trans="overlap">blah blah heart disease <unclear/> and woman you know strokes woo woo do do and listed a whole big thing and he said d'you want to live? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1662" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0262">I don't think he actually did say that but I think the message was</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0300" trans="overlap">he may have done</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0262">if you like your life you're going about it all the wrong way erm as in staying about for a little while longer</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0300" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0262">and erm and then he and then he just said listen you need to really lose some weight and she went on this Cambridge Diet <pause dur="short"/> where it's one that before you go and have the she's not going to have her stomach erm <trunc>cl</trunc> erm clamped whatever it's called</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0300" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0262">she's not actually gonna have it but it's the one that they give the people who do need to</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0300">right</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0262">furiously lose weight</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0300" trans="overlap">to lose <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0262">so she's lost it all lost lost lost lost haven't seen her in a couple of months erm and then what they do cos she goes once a month er once a week to get erm like I think more like counselling</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0262">he's actually there to sort of talk about the weight but it's a bit more like pep you up</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0300">mm</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0262">you know keep going keep going</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0262">and she's doing really really well erm and then they're going to reform her eating habits so that she's actually eating all the right things so then they can allow her to keep er slowly put the calories back on but it's calories with exercise</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0300" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0262">so that she can maintain some sort of decent weight for the rest of her life you know until you get a bit old and you can't do stuff but that sounds to me like okay quite radical you've you've got to lose it</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0262">you know and she has</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0262"><vocal desc="misc"/> but then that just goes to show how much she didn't need to be eating</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0300">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0262">calorie wise</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0300" trans="overlap">and then now she can control her calories</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0262">and then she can eat normally</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0262">you know she has had to have all those protein drinks and whatnot because you do have to have that if you need to lose weight quickly there's just no way around it</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0262">otherwise you're not eating anything</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0262">but the things is is that she said the good thing is that I will then be able to have you know calorie controlled normal food</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0300">yeah</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0262">and have that for the rest of my life but just not eating crap</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0300">no</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0262">and I thought yeah if we all took that idea of not eating crap</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah cos I mean yeah I mean we all eat crap I mean you know as as healthy as you think it might be a lot of the time it's not</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh it's isn't yeah and you kind of like now you're we're all could could watch the telly and we all know sort of bits and bobs and we're all like ah really oh no really pot noodles aren't good for you? oh what a shame</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh wow</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0262">you know that's my little vice at the moment</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0300" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I mean I love a pot noodle <pause dur="short"/> don't get me wrong</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but I'm like oh well you know I only have it once in a while and I think this is what my granny said too was oh god look at the time erm I think we're finished but granny said that as well she said you know everything in moderation <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1706" who="S0300" trans="overlap">gosh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
