<text id="S7VD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:39:45</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0509 S0510</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON &amp; ANON's home, Hastings</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Education, group work</topics>
		<activity>Mother and Daughter talk about college and university</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0509">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hastings</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0510">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Receptionist</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0509">yeah so I've still got lots of homework to do</u>
<u n="2" who="S0510">oh dear</u>
<u n="3" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0510">and not many days before you go back</u>
<u n="5" who="S0509">no well I say homework it's just revision</u>
<u n="6" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0509">erm but yeah and it but today even I've got to do some more Ted Hughes</u>
<u n="8" who="S0510">oh okay what are you <trunc>do</trunc>? what revision do you need to do on Ted Hughes?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0509">I need to analyse more of the animal poems cos I need to have read and know a bit about all of those and I need to find links between them so I can talk about the collection <pause dur="short"/> in a wider context in in my mock</u>
<u n="10" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="long"/> well that might make him a bit more interesting for you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0509">oh my god I was analysing animal poems the other day and oh it is just interminably dull</u>
<u n="12" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0509">ah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0509">I can't I can't stand it it's just he's just oh the pike did this it's like oh <trunc>go</trunc>good for the pike</u>
<u n="16" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0509">I don't care the only good animal poem I read was called the bee god and that was because it was about Sylvia <trunc>Pla</trunc>Plath because it was from Birthday Letters</u>
<u n="18" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right okay</u>
<u n="19" who="S0510">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh this is interesting oh it's from Birthday Letters that'll be why then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so are you telling me that your other poems like pike or whatever don't have any hidden meanings or messages <unclear>of a sort</unclear>?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh I'm sure they do</u>
<u n="22" who="S0510">but you just haven't</u>
<u n="23" who="S0509">they are not very interesting ones</u>
<u n="24" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0509">because he's all about like erm <pause dur="short"/> being connected to nature and stuff</u>
<u n="26" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0509">and er it's it's about you know glorifying how great these animals are and how great their connections to the real world are whereas we're all like da da da <unclear/> and things</u>
<u n="28" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear>really</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="29" who="S0509">like the Jaguar is quite</u>
<u n="30" who="S0510" trans="overlap">like do you find it disconnected?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0509">the Jaguar is quite good because that's about that's got all like this prison imagery and then it's all really good but</u>
<u n="34" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="35" who="S0509">some of it some of it's a bit <vocal desc="sigh"/> a bit dense it just feels a bit a bit much for this animal</u>
<u n="36" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right right a bit over the top <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah it's like okay I get it <pause dur="short"/> but you're giving me too much stuff to wade through here to get at what you're the like the deeper meaning of it you know</u>
<u n="38" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right right <pause dur="short"/> whereas if you were for instance an American Indian and you read that poem it might come to life quicker and</u>
<u n="39" who="S0509" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="40" who="S0510">and be more revealing</u>
<u n="41" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0510">because of their connection with animals and the importance of animals</u>
<u n="43" who="S0509">mm yeah perhaps</u>
<u n="44" who="S0510"><vocal desc="cough"/> whereas we we</u>
<u n="45" who="S0509" trans="overlap">also if they you know liked poetry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is it? as a poet is he a rhythmic poet? or what what kind of?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0509">yeah kind of sometimes</u>
<u n="48" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="49" who="S0509">he just plays around with stuff he he tends to have like quite a strict form though</u>
<u n="50" who="S0510">does he? yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah although the the crow poems are more like experimental and out there but</u>
<u n="52" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="53" who="S0509">and they were interesting but this is not</u>
<u n="54" who="S0510" trans="overlap">no what's his set form tend to be then?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0509">oh he has like different forms for different poems</u>
<u n="56" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="57" who="S0509">but they tend to like er like a lot of poets will like break form for effect</u>
<u n="58" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="59" who="S0509">whereas he is a more traditional poet</u>
<u n="60" who="S0510">right right yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so yeah yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0509"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0510">have you studied any Sylvia Plath yet?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0509">no I think we do next year though</u>
<u n="66" who="S0510">oh that'll be interesting</u>
<u n="67" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah I've got an anthology that I think belonged to Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0510">oh really?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and I've <trunc>ma</trunc> I've somehow got it upstairs because I think she lent it to me once and er it's got all her annotations in it and things like that</u>
<u n="70" who="S0510">oh interesting</u>
<u n="71" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0509">so that will be fun</u>
<u n="74" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0509">oh I've just clicked my hip</u>
<u n="76" who="S0510">oh was that what that that was?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's what that was</u>
<u n="78" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh my goodness girl you are breaking down</u>
<u n="79" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said oh it didn't hurt at all</u>
<u n="80" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was like oh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah it is</u>
<u n="83" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh that's strange</u>
<u n="84" who="S0510">there was an unexpected sound coming from my body that must hurt <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>y</trunc>yeah basically</u>
<u n="86" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="88" who="S0510">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh woah so revision</u>
<u n="89" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0510">it's it's crazy really if you think about it that you know you went through what the last two years and it just seemed to be nonstop <trunc>revis</trunc>revision and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> and now I've got another five years</u>
<u n="92" who="S0510">yes and then you thought you know okay finish school finish revising for all those exams and you literally have just finished your second term</u>
<u n="93" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0510">and you you're already going into a another exam</u>
<u n="95" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's the middle of year it's the middle of the year in terms of exams</u>
<u n="96" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but it's literally <pause dur="short"/> well it's three months in</u>
<u n="97" who="S0509">yeah but then yeah so</u>
<u n="98" who="S0510">less than three months in</u>
<u n="99" who="S0509" trans="overlap">well it's September October November December no it's four months by the time I go back</u>
<u n="100" who="S0510">well that's true yeah it is yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and then you've got January February March April and then May I start having exams</u>
<u n="102" who="S0510">god it's mad isn't it it's just round after round you'd've thought it's like give some leverage here</u>
<u n="103" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh and do feel like important because they are going to affect university offers</u>
<u n="104" who="S0510">yeah no I know</u>
<u n="105" who="S0509"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0510" trans="overlap">but you know your your other exams were important as well</u>
<u n="107" who="S0509">yeah but do <trunc>y</trunc> oh it's so annoying how many people after all that will be like I've heard so many times people going but GCSEs don't matter that much and like older <pause dur="short"/> older people</u>
<u n="108" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0509">who've who are in <trunc>u</trunc>uni or whatever I mean they don't</u>
<u n="110" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well they don't if you haven't if you haven't done very well in them and you've managed to scrape through in your A levels yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0509">no but even yeah other people oh oh there's like it's weird because there was a big sort of competition between when you are at you're at school people going you've got to get these GCSEs because</u>
<u n="112" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0509">they stay with you for the rest of your <trunc>l</trunc>life</u>
<u n="114" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0509">they are super important and then once like once you are out people will be like GCSEs don't matter that much A Levels are more important</u>
<u n="116" who="S0510">yeah but they matter in in the greater scheme of things don't they?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but like it's weird that kind of contrast between</u>
<u n="118" who="S0510">how quickly yeah as well yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah it kind of switches to people being like that</u>
<u n="120" who="S0510">it's almost like oh they have to say how important they are otherwise you would never get through school you know you'd never <vocal desc="laugh"/> you'd never bother kind of thing but I mean they are important in terms of the grounding that they give you for <unclear>everything</unclear></u>
<u n="121" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh yeah no I think they are important but it's just a bit like</u>
<u n="122" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0509">oh well just all that work and then you get <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0510">yeah but you're you're the one that's going to have on your CV or whatever you know ten A star A</u>
<u n="125" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0510">er GCSEs</u>
<u n="127" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0510">which count for a lot actually which say a lot you know it's er yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0510">so when you come to do your exam entries and you get your UCAS points your <trunc>UC</trunc> you know you get your</u>
<u n="131" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0510">points are equated from your exam</u>
<u n="133" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0510">results they are just on your A levels?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0509">I don't actually know</u>
<u n="136" who="S0510">you see that would be interesting to know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0509">yeah I did wonder because I looked it up once</u>
<u n="138" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0509">I don't know because you do like if you look at erm the sheet you get I'm sure it tells you how many UCAS points all your <trunc>grade</trunc>grades are worth for GCSE</u>
<u n="140" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0509">but I don't know if they count them when they are</u>
<u n="142" who="S0510">yeah well</u>
<u n="143" who="S0509">doing stuff like if you go to a university league table it will often tell you the erm the average amount of UCAS points an entrant there has</u>
<u n="144" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="145" who="S0509">and I don't know whether that includes their GCSE points it must do because some of them are so high like</u>
<u n="146" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it must do <pause dur="short"/> yeah well there you go yeah yeah so therefore you know you break that down</u>
<u n="147" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0510">they do count <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0509">yeah yeah but</u>
<u n="150" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I know you do <trunc>any</trunc> you know that anyway</u>
<u n="151" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0510">and you believe that anyway</u>
<u n="153" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0510">but you know for all those doubters out there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0509">yeah but erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> but like but universities when they are asking for entries they don't go by UCAS points</u>
<u n="156" who="S0510">no no no they say a minimum of whatever at A level don't they?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0509">and sometimes like <pause dur="short"/> at least grade B in English or whatever you are studying</u>
<u n="160" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu</u>
<u n="161" who="S0509">but erm yeah what was I gonna say? <pause dur="short"/> oh personal statements as well</u>
<u n="162" who="S0510">oh they are very important aren't they?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they are like</u>
<u n="164" who="S0510">for your applications</u>
<u n="165" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0510">so are they going through that at college?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0509">not yet I think they will do</u>
<u n="168" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I think they will be yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0509">yeah and <anon type="place"/> will be on it cos like</u>
<u n="170" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0509"><trunc>a</trunc>and I'll have to do it <trunc>o</trunc> like I'll have to start on it over the summer</u>
<u n="172" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="173" who="S0509">and then get feedback from teachers and stuff when I go back</u>
<u n="174" who="S0510">that's good that's good</u>
<u n="175" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0510">and erm the fact that you've got extra input from <anon type="place"/> as well is going to be really helpful yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah it's good <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0510">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah you see when when I went for my uni place <pause dur="short"/> I did it last minute <pause dur="short"/> I was absolutely last minute because I wasn't going to</u>
<u n="179" who="S0509" trans="overlap">hadn't the term like already started or something?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yes it had it had so er I I know I must have done a personal statement but I can't for the life <vocal desc="laugh"/> of me think what it you know</u>
<u n="181" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I am brilliant <vocal desc="laugh"/> take me</u>
<u n="182" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so I was yeah I was I kind of missed out on a lot of that stuff I reckon you know the the stress of all of that</u>
<u n="183" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because you were just like well let's just try it</u>
<u n="184" who="S0510">let's just chuck it in and see what happens erm and it really was very late well it must have been September that I did it <pause dur="short"/> so I was <trunc>luc</trunc> really lucky to get a place</u>
<u n="185" who="S0509">yeah like how?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but I did have a recommendation from my</u>
<u n="187" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0510">my tutor who was good friends with the head of school</u>
<u n="189" who="S0509">who was your tutor? where were they from?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0510">it was er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> erm and actually he went on to teach at the uni as well</u>
<u n="191" who="S0509">yeah but how did you know him?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0510">he was my er tutor for my HND my multimedia HND because I did a two year</u>
<u n="193" who="S0509">oh I thought you were talking about getting into your HND</u>
<u n="194" who="S0510">oh no no no no I was talking about my university place at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0509" trans="overlap">what was your university place for?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0510">multimedia</u>
<u n="197" who="S0509">what was your HND? where where did you where did you do your HND?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh I did it at <anon type="place"/> college</u>
<u n="199" who="S0509">I don't even remember that</u>
<u n="200" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you know in <anon type="place"/> road you used to go to nursery there</u>
<u n="201" who="S0509">that's probably why I don't remember it there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah so I'd</u>
<u n="203" who="S0509">oh it was all just one thing for me</u>
<u n="204" who="S0510">yeah no <trunc>u</trunc> they were completely different institutions and erm well the thing was I <trunc>wa</trunc> you're right though I was quite late in applying for my college course as well I because we were living here in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0510">and erm I'd already started a college course in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="208" who="S0510">it was the first year that they ever did it it because it was you know multimedia it was all new and exciting</u>
<u n="209" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0510">erm this was er <vocal desc="cough"/> it must have been ninety-eight nineteen ninety-eight <pause dur="short"/> and erm I think we'd just had we just had no it was before you then oh maybe it was ninety-seven because you were born ninety-nine</u>
<u n="211" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0510">yeah I don't know it was before you were born anyway I started erm a HNC in multimedia and it was the first year that <anon type="place"/> college had ever done this course and they were linked to the university of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0509">uhu</u>
<u n="214" who="S0510">and <anon type="place"/> I think had only just run it the year before erm and it was so new anyway I was a few months in and daddy got very ill with his eyes and it all it was just really bad timing</u>
<u n="215" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0510">and er <pause dur="short"/> no it must be ninety-nine oh I don't know anyway it was very bad timing so I pulled out and actually the course itself it was alright but it wasn't that brilliant so that was so I pulled out in the December and then we had erm <pause dur="short"/> you were already born so it was already ninety-nine er we had a holiday in <anon type="place"/> didn't we?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0510">when you were a baby you were a few months old er and we decided it would be really nice to move to <anon type="place"/> and then we got this opportunity because daddy had a pension that came up <pause dur="short"/> er there was a company he used to work for in London that he paid into a pension for a short amount of time and we found out that he could actually cash in this pension because he was disabled early so it meant that suddenly within a year less than a year of us sort of talking about it because we had gone in the summer</u>
<u n="219" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0510">that you were born <pause dur="short"/> and it was like we could actually do this we could move to <anon type="place"/> and then we got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> looking out for us <pause dur="short"/> and then in the June <pause dur="short"/> we moved and I was emailing this guy at <anon type="place"/> college because I <trunc>cou</trunc> I saw you know before we moved there</u>
<u n="221" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0510">that they had a multimedia course and he turned out to be my course tutor</u>
<u n="223" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0510">erm and he was really you know passionate about the course it was</u>
<u n="225" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0510">the first year they were running it as well <pause dur="short"/> and er we had a really nice bit of correspondence and he was like well just when you get to <anon type="place"/> come and see me even if it's the summer because I will still be in college yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0509" trans="overlap">around yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0510">so I just popped down to see him one day after we'd moved in the summer</u>
<u n="229" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0510">it was really informal and <trunc>ob</trunc>obviously I had to do all the you know the obligatory bits the form filling and all the rest of it but it was kind of so casual <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0509">yeah hop on board</u>
<u n="232" who="S0510" trans="overlap">er and and like you know his interview of me was really more a tour of the facilities and you know just showing me things and just chatting really really erm really nice and er I got he was so passionate about it all so <trunc>enthusias</trunc>enthusiastic and it was so different to the way they taught it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="234" who="S0510">and the biggest thing was that they had the equipment</u>
<u n="235" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0510">they had a full Mac studio they had all the software software that you know <pause dur="short"/> we only barely touched on in <anon type="place"/> and they didn't have all the macromedia suites and and it was just woah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0510" trans="overlap">what a surprise <anon type="place"/> the fun fair</u>
<u n="238" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah it was like woah this is like really proper this is going to be kicking it you know and so then I started in the September but I had to go through all the <pause dur="short"/> the grant process and all the rest of it so there was a lot of that summer when we first arrived there was a lot of stuff I had to sort out for starting in the September but erm and getting your nursery place sorted and all the rest of it you know</u>
<u n="239" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0509">so erm so that was great so one of the tutors that was then on that course erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> he oh he he was a smart guy anyway when I decided last minute after I'd already finished my I started a HNC which was a part time it was only like I don't know fifteen hours a week or something and it was a lower qualification than a HND but sort of two thirds of the way through that first year I was enjoying it so much and time you know</u>
<u n="241" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0510">everything was working out in terms of looking after you and kind of all</u>
<u n="243" who="S0509" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="244" who="S0510">and it was all really fitted into place <pause dur="short"/> I thought oh blimey and my my tutor as well was like you know you could do the HND you should just kind of go for it really</u>
<u n="245" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0510">and erm so I asked if I could transfer then and I transferred to the HND so I literally had loads of catching up to do at the end of that first year to get up to the standard of the</u>
<u n="247" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0510">first year HND and I <trunc>d</trunc> I think I did a project as well over the summer just to to kind of get it all in</u>
<u n="249" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah to get into it yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0510">yeah erm and then when <pause dur="short"/> so I'd already transferred two thirds of the way through to the HND</u>
<u n="251" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0510">and then the second year did that and then at the end of that <pause dur="short"/> my erm I I didn't know what I wanted to do actually I was a bit I was at a <pause dur="short"/> sort of crossroads</u>
<u n="253" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0510">really for various reasons things that were happening <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> and then in the summer I just thought oh god I'll just <trunc>g</trunc>go for it <trunc>be</trunc> I <trunc>d</trunc> because I never really was that keen on doing a degree <vocal desc="laugh"/> it wasn't until I thought oh I will just just get out there and get working and</u>
<u n="255" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0510">you know <pause dur="short"/> and then I can't remember the exact thought process but there was a lot of stuff going on and so it meant that it would <pause dur="short"/> probably be worth my while <vocal desc="cough"/> carrying on with study <pause dur="short"/> and seeing how far I could get</u>
<u n="257" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0510">so it literally was yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he'd put a word in for me to the head of the department and try and get me <trunc>i</trunc>in to see him for an interview so I did and I had to take my portfolio in and and just sort of you know present it and everything <pause dur="short"/> and er <pause dur="short"/> did I start there and then that day? I don't know I can't remember oh well actually I I got enrolled that day</u>
<u n="259" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0510">I literally <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got one of his <pause dur="short"/> er heads of department to take me through everything like a fast track I went through erm oh what do they call it? admissions and</u>
<u n="261" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0510">you know all the rest of it and er <pause dur="short"/> it was all done in a kind of day I mean I'd had to before I had the interview with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'd had to put various statements and I'd had to fill out</u>
<u n="263" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0510">various you know form</u>
<u n="265" who="S0509" trans="overlap">forms</u>
<u n="266" who="S0510">bits but yeah I was certainly fast tracked through <vocal desc="laugh"/> at the end of that day I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0509" trans="overlap">you must have been good</u>
<u n="268" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> well thanks yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah crazy really</u>
<u n="269" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0510">absolutely crazy but yeah but it all worked out</u>
<u n="271" who="S0509">good</u>
<u n="272" who="S0510">in fact I think I actually I did I actually started my college day that day as well because the first lesson that I had was in a group project <pause dur="short"/> they were doing erm I can't remember which lesson it was but basically they were making each group had to make a game or a <trunc>g</trunc> a game intro</u>
<u n="273" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0510">and so you had we were working with other teams so we were working with people who were on the sound engineering degree people who were on the graphic design degrees so they'd mixed you know the students</u>
<u n="275" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="276" who="S0510">up to produce a team multiples to do a game so I literally walked into this lesson they'd already had a group formed but suddenly there I was I think it was the second lesson if you like</u>
<u n="277" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0510">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I was just put on this group</u>
<u n="279" who="S0509">thrown in the deep end</u>
<u n="280" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and it was like oh er you know and it was a bit awkward for the group because they'd already figured out what they were doing</u>
<u n="281" who="S0509" trans="overlap">what they were doing</u>
<u n="282" who="S0510">but it turned out to be really good and it was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know</u>
<u n="283" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0510">Irish <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm and in the end we there were four people in the group me included one was er <pause dur="short"/> no actually five one of them pretty much dropped out as soon as it started I never got to meet them that was the sound guy erm there was a 3D games guy <pause dur="short"/> that was just so flaky incredibly flaky erm and then there was one other I think he was the graphics guy and again he the graphics guy actually I think dropped out of the course <pause dur="short"/> was it was it? no maybe it was the sound guy he dropped out of the course graphics guy I think we might have met him once and he never did anything and then you know he just <pause dur="short"/> in the end it was just three of us in the group</u>
<u n="285" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0510">so two multimedia students and a 3D guy whereas other teams you know</u>
<u n="287" who="S0509" trans="overlap">had graphics and sound</u>
<u n="288" who="S0510">yeah so we were trying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were trying to you know cover for the sound and the graphics and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="289" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0510">which was fine because we ended up doing loads of sound in the studio at home we were able to record lots daddy helped out</u>
<u n="291" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0510">you know with setting it up for us</u>
<u n="293" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0510">so that we could just produce our sound samples and effects and everything</u>
<u n="295" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0510">erm it worked out really well <pause dur="short"/> erm the 3D graphics guy <pause dur="short"/> was as I say very flaky and he let us down at the eleventh hour so he'd been going on and on that he had all these er animated 3D graphics sorted for us at all these different intro points and he kept saying you know it's alright it's okay and we were like are you sure you don't want any help? are you sure? you know</u>
<u n="297" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0510">and he was like no no it's alright you know I'll <trunc>g</trunc> I'll have it done for when we need it so this is so many months in <pause dur="short"/> and we saw he <trunc>ke</trunc> he kept throwing this little erm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0509">bits</u>
<u n="300" who="S0510" trans="overlap">carrots if you like of just er static images frames taken from his 3D renders because 3D renders take forever to render you know and er so it was like oh yeah you know so I I think he just kept feeding us with those but all along he was a million miles away from finishing <pause dur="short"/> and then it got to literally the night we were pulling it altogether the next day we were presenting it <pause dur="short"/> he didn't turn up with the goods he he bailed out on us <vocal desc="laugh"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I really we had started which you know a while before plan B started a plan B in case he just doesn't deliver er so we had something up our sleeve that we could kind of pull out in case but of course it was right at the end he was still</u>
<u n="301" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah right at the</u>
<u n="302" who="S0510">saying right until that night no don't worry I've got them it's fine <pause dur="short"/> so we worked through the night just putting stitching together some extra stuff that we kind of had in in the bag that we then</u>
<u n="303" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0510">jazzed up a bit animated stuff that needed to be that we'd done from 2D graphics rather than 3D graphics</u>
<u n="305" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0510">and erm <pause dur="short"/> I think I went home she lived up in <anon type="place"/> and I think I went home about five o'clock in the morning er and then we had a couple of hours sleep and we were due to meet back I think ours was one of the first presentations that had to be done <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you would have thought they'd give you a bit of leeway</u>
<u n="308" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well they didn't know did they? at that point but <pause dur="short"/> erm so literally we'd written the disc that we were presenting it on at her house I mean we'd tested it and all the rest of it and it was fine</u>
<u n="309" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I was gonna say did you test it?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0510">however we then had to put it on the uni <trunc>compu</trunc> Macs and play it and there was something that we hadn't noticed because we were so tired probably er to do with a couple of the links through the game <pause dur="short"/> that weren't working and I'm not kidding you I was literally working until seconds before we were presenting fixing them</u>
<u n="311" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="312" who="S0510">we literally we had fifteen a fifteen-minute window where we realised oh</u>
<u n="313" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh no yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not working and like I just went into er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what mode I went into</u>
<u n="315" who="S0509" trans="overlap">you just bypass like worrying and stuff and just</u>
<u n="316" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0509">just into that mechanic just do it mode</u>
<u n="318" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it was exactly that you've got it spot on and er and so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was sort of sat there and I just began right okay so now we need to do this and I was just talking it through and doing it and like can you get me this? and can you <trunc>down</trunc>? can you put that on you know <pause dur="short"/> seconds to spare we'd done it <pause dur="short"/> however there was one little glitch in there that I hadn't been able to mend but I'd said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right okay hopefully we'll be alright I'll just talk my way through this one I'll manually do this bit myself as I'm talking so they won't try it out and I know <trunc>wh</trunc> how to connect it up there was some pathway that wasn't quite right <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it and it worked <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="320" who="S0510">it was just mad erm and the fact that we'd had to just present it ourselves and we had no other help we got a like equivalent of a first for it for our group project</u>
<u n="321" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah cos you'd just had so many trials group project more like duo project</u>
<u n="322" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0509">oh my god well like well like the the people who like ran the the course what were their reactions</u>
<u n="324" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="325" who="S0509">to the fact that all these people had left?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0510"><vocal desc="cough"/> well they couldn't believe it because they had no idea that it had been that</u>
<u n="327" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0510">bad although you know they knew that the the earlier sound people had dropped out</u>
<u n="329" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0510">because we'd we'd continued on and</u>
<u n="331" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0510">er you had different points where you checked in with them on the project anyway so you know</u>
<u n="333" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0510">they knew we were doing the sounds on our own and you know</u>
<u n="335" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0510">kind of gave a little bit of advice as well on that the sound guy although he was <pause dur="short"/> he wasn't particularly helpful you know erm and actually when it came to it in the conversation after we'd presented the game it was him that was he was quite tricksy actually because they would just they discussed it in front of you what they think and</u>
<u n="337" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0510">you know erm give you feedback and I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was one of them saying well I mean considering</u>
<u n="339" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0510">they had put all of this together pretty much of you know and the quality of what they've done when they're not</u>
<u n="341" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0510">even either 3D graphics sound or whatever</u>
<u n="343" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0510">you know er I mean they have a marking scheme that they have to compare</u>
<u n="345" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0510">to but the sound guy was oh I don't know he was really negative so we were like <pause dur="short"/> woah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0510">you know this isn't going very well sort of thing but actually we did we got a first</u>
<u n="349" who="S0509">he got a bit overruled then</u>
<u n="350" who="S0510">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0509">they were like come on now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0510">but yeah I'll never forget that oh gosh I'm trying to remember the name of the game though <trunc>z</trunc><trunc>z</trunc>zeron or something zeron I think it was zeron</u>
<u n="353" who="S0509">what what was the game?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0510">it was erm <pause dur="short"/> it was kind of like these different fighter spaceships the ones that we never got in the end you know erm <trunc>i</trunc> going into this in it was a bit Star Wars going into this intergalactic world the opening sequence it was really cool actually it was like going into this galaxy</u>
<u n="355" who="S0509" trans="overlap">far far away</u>
<u n="356" who="S0510">and then zooming in into this spaceship so we had the visual from his 3Ds of the spaceship that we'd like flattened and then er did a it was like a hatch door erm that you heard the <vocal desc="misc"/> as it kind of opened and then opened up into the game and then there was all the screens and you had to choose your fighter you know you choose your spaceship choose your erm captain or whatever different manpower the manpower stuff you know the the kind of weaponry <unclear/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0510">the weaponry <pause dur="short"/> I mean me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we we really that really wasn't our speciality so the guy that was supposed to be doing the 3D graphics he did kind of help a lot in terms of you know what terminology to use because we didn't <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but that was about it though he threw you some words</u>
<u n="360" who="S0510">he threw us some words that's it</u>
<u n="361" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what happened to him then did he drop out?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0510">yeah he did yeah he he did drop out</u>
<u n="363" who="S0509" trans="overlap">why did he spend all that time just lying?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="365" who="S0509">did you ever see him again?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0510">I think we did actually I think we saw him once</u>
<u n="367" who="S0509">I bet that was fun</u>
<u n="368" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> now I'm just trying to remember whether I think it was the other way round <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ye</trunc> this he was repeating his second year <pause dur="short"/> rather than he then went on to to repeat his second year I think he was a repeater already</u>
<u n="369" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="370" who="S0510">so <pause dur="short"/> that should have told us something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0510">but yeah he did he <trunc>dro</trunc> he dropped out he dropped that was it that was the moment that he crashed and burned <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> can't really get away with that though you can't expect to get away with that</u>
<u n="374" who="S0510" trans="overlap">no no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0509">blimey</u>
<u n="376" who="S0510">anyway</u>
<u n="377" who="S0509" trans="overlap">woah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0510">so took you on a <pause dur="short"/> on a journey didn't I? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0509" trans="overlap">on a journey <pause dur="short"/> oh god <pause dur="short"/> some people hey</u>
<u n="380" who="S0510">I know</u>
<u n="381" who="S0509">I've done a <trunc>o</trunc>over the years I've done a lot of er working with people who who aren't pulling their weight but</u>
<u n="382" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0509">I've just had to go right we are doing this you are saying this</u>
<u n="384" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0509">I'm just going to write it all and you are going to say this and you are going to do this</u>
<u n="386" who="S0510">what because they are not offering up? they are not doing what they should be doing? yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm and sometimes I have ended up you know pulling other people's weight a bit bit too much but you know</u>
<u n="388" who="S0510" trans="overlap">too much <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> mm that's you know that's not an easy job to have either because you can and it is a real balancing act isn't it?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm just the one that people look to for like</u>
<u n="390" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0509">somebody to like with presentations they are like so who is going to speak? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0509">like even at college erm we had to do something in form and we had to like present our ideas to some other forms and erm <pause dur="short"/> our our tutor just went <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can do it I was like <pause dur="short"/> right <vocal desc="laugh"/> fine then it's always me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0509">and it's quite funny I don't mind that much though but I I kind of like <pause dur="short"/> I like some of it but it's just</u>
<u n="396" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just the way they it's naturally assumed that it's always going to be you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0509">yeah I take it on because I'm like</u>
<u n="398" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0509"><trunc>no</trunc>nobody else wants to do it they'll just be stressing and like quiet and stuff</u>
<u n="400" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0509">I might as well do it because I know I can sort of do it alright so</u>
<u n="402" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah well it's certainly helped with your your skills upping your skills isn't it</u>
<u n="403" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0510">you've had so much experience of it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0509">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the only time I've ever had it the other way round where somebody else has just like dominating</u>
<u n="406" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0509">is er with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0510">oh yes</u>
<u n="409" who="S0509">he's just you just can't</u>
<u n="410" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0509">his way or the highway like to an extreme</u>
<u n="412" who="S0510">right yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0509">but erm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0509">yeah I might see a bit more of that if I'm going to a competitive uni</u>
<u n="416" who="S0510">yes yeah that's true yes</u>
<u n="417" who="S0509">which could be nice because people might be more willing to <pause dur="short"/> to be leaders and want to</u>
<u n="418" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0509">you know <pause dur="short"/> help out</u>
<u n="420" who="S0510">and that will help you I mean it would be good if if that did happen because that will then give you more skills in in you know how to handle that competitive</u>
<u n="421" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0510">kind of nature because if you know if you've naturally always at school by default been the person leading</u>
<u n="423" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0510">you know there are other skills that you need to also learn in order to be able to get by in that competitive environment</u>
<u n="425" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the annoying thing is like <trunc>I</trunc> like I'm quite happy to be like</u>
<u n="426" who="S0510">in the side lines</u>
<u n="427" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0510">back room</u>
<u n="429" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but it always ends up you know when when I'm not immediately looked as the leader we get a really terrible leader who then just doesn't do anything and so then I end up sort of <pause dur="short"/> chivvying people along beneath them</u>
<u n="430" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0509">like I remember on <anon type="place"/> there was this one guy and I really tried to make him be a leader and be like well you've got to make this decision what do you want us to do? and he just wasn't</u>
<u n="432" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="433" who="S0509">and it was like come on and he didn't</u>
<u n="434" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0509">so he <trunc>j</trunc> but like there were there was like six of us in the group the leader and his sort of sub leader they were just not doing it they literally did nothing</u>
<u n="436" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="437" who="S0509">and so the rest of us were just like oh well <unclear> I cried a bit</unclear> because everyone was kind of like wanting to do stuff but</u>
<u n="438" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0509">what do we do? so I said well if I do this bit you do this bit you do that bit and you do that that bit and we'll get on with it and so we did and then sort of</u>
<u n="440" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right yeah <pause dur="short"/> pulled it through</u>
<u n="441" who="S0509">I think I've told probably told you about this but we did a presentation and the leader guy was just coming up with all this stuff that he'd never <trunc>to</trunc></u>
<u n="442" who="S0510" trans="overlap">what random stuff?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0509">yeah that he'd never mentioned he hadn't done anything for the whole time</u>
<u n="444" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0509">and he never mentioned any of this and then he was just saying things that were obviously just not going to work</u>
<u n="446" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0509">and so I remember just sort of covering him and being like well obviously that would be the ideal situation <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0509">but it was so bad cos we were presenting so it was like</u>
<u n="450" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0509">you can't have an argument whilst presenting but that's ridiculous <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0509">but I think everyone else in my team was kind of on my side and just what are you doing? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0509">but somebody made a really great model cos we had to we had to make a games console that's it</u>
<u n="456" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="457" who="S0509">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> one guy he was obviously like a really sciency sort of engineeringy type guy</u>
<u n="458" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0509">and he just made this amazing model it was the best model out of any of them</u>
<u n="460" who="S0510" trans="overlap">woah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0509">out of this cardboard and stuff and it was just great</u>
<u n="462" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0509">so that was like yeah we've got a great model we might have a terrible pitch but look how pretty it looks <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Blue Peter at a whole another level</u>
<u n="465" who="S0509">yeah that's what it was like <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm trying to think what the <trunc>ne</trunc> oh <anon type="place"/> will be going away on a residential in January</u>
<u n="466" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is it February? oh January when in January is it?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0509" trans="overlap">January <pause dur="short"/> sort of like mid like the nineteenth or something? I'm not sure</u>
<u n="468" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh is it? and are you <trunc>t</trunc> are you going for a week or a weekend?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0509">er three days</u>
<u n="470" who="S0510">three days</u>
<u n="471" who="S0509">so it will be like I don't know if it's Monday to Wednesday or Wednesday to Friday</u>
<u n="472" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="473" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0510">oh yeah it would be a bit tricky if it was over the weekend wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0509">er yeah yeah it's not over the weekend</u>
<u n="476" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mind you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> owes you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0510">you've got one in the bag there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0509">yeah <pause dur="short"/> quite</u>
<u n="480" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's difficult though isn't it you know that whole leadership thing that you are talking about and sort of being forced into a position <pause dur="short"/> of leading a team erm sometimes it's more helpful for the rest of the people within that team</u>
<u n="481" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0510">if those people that take on that leadership team fail <pause dur="short"/> because all the while somebody is like you know back room</u>
<u n="483" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0510">helping get through it they don't necessarily get the full impact of where they went wrong <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know which is easier said than done because when you are in a group situation you want the group to be able to you know to pull through erm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah oh right yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes oh right I I couldn't quite get what you mean but I get it now yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="487" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0510">so erm like those two guys who completely you know didn't do anything</u>
<u n="489" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0510">and then just fronted it out at the end to a really ridiculous degree er the yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0509">I remember the assessor being like afterwards when we were talking about it she was like well done for taking on the leadership role there</u>
<u n="492" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0509">like you were really doing well from behind the scenes so I was very obvious but like yeah I was like oh thank you but they <trunc>were</trunc> they they weren't great</u>
<u n="494" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="495" who="S0509">I hadn't a I <trunc>di</trunc> one of them I don't remember seeing on <anon type="place"/> recently so one of the fuchsias dropped out yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> dropped away yeah yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0509"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> got kicked out</u>
<u n="498" who="S0510">he he got what?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0509">he got kicked out</u>
<u n="500" who="S0510">he got kicked out? oh</u>
<u n="501" who="S0509">yeah because he was he he just wasn't <pause dur="short"/> because he got suspended</u>
<u n="502" who="S0510" trans="overlap">did he? <pause dur="short"/> oh from school</u>
<u n="503" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0509">and then I think I don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> left or got kicked out but she's not there any more</u>
<u n="506" who="S0510">right so natural wastage there then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0510">so it kind of came round in the end anyway by the sounds of it</u>
<u n="509" who="S0509">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah funny <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <trunc>co</trunc>college is a bit better</u>
<u n="510" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="511" who="S0509">for people in some things</u>
<u n="512" who="S0510">people more willing to sort of speak up and</u>
<u n="513" who="S0509">yeah there's normally like at least a couple in like and because obviously you are in different classes</u>
<u n="514" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0509">you don't get so much of a reputation for being that one who who gives the answers</u>
<u n="516" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah yeah yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0509">but I I guess you do to <trunc>a</trunc>an extent but like <pause dur="short"/> if I go through all my classes</u>
<u n="518" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0509">I can think of at least like one or two other people who always give answers</u>
<u n="520" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0509">as well</u>
<u n="522" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0509">English literature not so much</u>
<u n="524" who="S0510">oh right mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0509">but a bit <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0510">I mean it's different dynamics as well isn't it you know</u>
<u n="527" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0510">sort of when you are moving from class to class and so you know when you're going through in one class the majority of your lessons like you were in secondary school there are set patterns that everybody falls into isn't there you know</u>
<u n="529" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0510">and relationships and you know</u>
<u n="531" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0510">erm alliances or or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so it's easier for those to because of the nature of how long you are <trunc>spen</trunc>spending with each other for those patterns to become very firm very quickly</u>
<u n="533" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0510">whereas if you're mixing it up a lot</u>
<u n="535" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0510">that helps</u>
<u n="537" who="S0509">no in some of my classes like in English language</u>
<u n="538" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0509">like if she asks a question and then there's a long silence like I I will often have the answer but I will wait a little while to see if anyone else</u>
<u n="540" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0509">will say it</u>
<u n="542" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and then I'll just go well obviously not <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know it's a it's a funny old thing</u>
<u n="544" who="S0510">yeah <vocal desc="yawn"/> so what would you say out of all your classes is your your kind of favourite?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0509">I don't know because it changes</u>
<u n="546" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="547" who="S0509">but it's either drama or English lit</u>
<u n="548" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0509">it depends what we are doing in drama as well</u>
<u n="550" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0509">where yeah and it would depends what book we are doing in English lit like A Room with a View is like woah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah happy days</u>
<u n="553" who="S0509">but erm Ted Hughes less so we've still got to do Streetcar Named Desire</u>
<u n="554" who="S0510">mm when are you supposed to be doing that then? when you go back or?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0509">yeah it must be because we are doing it after A Room with a View and we are like we've got like one chapter left of A Room with a View</u>
<u n="556" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0509">so we'll be doing that then but it's quite short A Streetcar Named Desire I need to read it <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="yawn"/> they will probably get you seeing clips of the film as well won't they?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0509">oh bound to <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0510">Marlon was it Marlon? was Marlon Brando in A Streetcar Named Desire?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I don't know I saw we saw some clips of it on a taster day</u>
<u n="562" who="S0510">or am I getting it muddled up?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0509">don't know</u>
<u n="564" who="S0510">Tennessee Williams did he do?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0509" trans="overlap">Tennessee Williams wrote it yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0510">yeah did he do Cat on a Hot Tin Roof as well?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0509">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="568" who="S0510">right so it's kind of deep south sort of</u>
<u n="569" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0509">yeah from the little I know of it yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0510">Cat on a Hot a Hot Tin Roof is really good it's got so much tension in it</u>
<u n="573" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="574" who="S0510">yeah mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0509">it's a funny old title</u>
<u n="576" who="S0510">yes</u>
<u n="577" who="S0509">you are like say titles so many times they just lose their meaning</u>
<u n="578" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0509">it's quite <pause dur="short"/> a weird old <unclear>long one</unclear></u>
<u n="580" who="S0510">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
