<text id="S7ZG">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:50:36</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>House-sitting in Australia</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Setting personal goals, career professional development, discussing joining up with friends, and family planning. </topics>
		<activity>A couple talking about making life arrangements. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0262">okay erm you know fine yeah give that a go</u>
<u n="2" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0262">and see <unclear>cos</unclear></u>
<u n="4" who="S0261">and and and that might not be directly connected to what we're trying to do but but the mechanism of the things you learn in doing that are certainly of value</u>
<u n="5" who="S0262">alright</u>
<u n="6" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">erm okay now you you really really really can't get upset when I say what I'm about to say to you okay? <trunc>y</trunc>you've just you've gotta understand I'm saying it for the benefit of both of us I think in the marketplace you're worth a lot of money as what you used to do as er as a <trunc>c</trunc> as a what did they call it? a contractor yeah? <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> jesus a hundred and twenty fucking thousand dollars <vocal desc="laugh"/> a year and that was as a paid member of staff I don't fucking know how much you cost as a freelance contractor engineer type person right? shitloads of money <unclear>just</unclear> shitloads of money <pause dur="short"/> you'd get your capital <unclear>in next to no time it's a sacrifice yeah is that you go</unclear> do something that you go fuck it it's a means to an end and then you go thank you I've got fucking what I want for my money fuck off I'm just gonna go off and <trunc>p</trunc> spend my capital</u>
<u n="8" who="S0261">er <trunc>y</trunc>yeah yeah erm <trunc>tha</trunc>that's that that's an interesting point of view and of course that's quite obvious <unclear>you know</unclear>? but erm <pause dur="long"/> I will take that on board and think about it <pause dur="short"/> and I'll leave it at that <pause dur="long"/> in context of where we're at right now yeah? you've <trunc>tha</trunc>that's <trunc>tha</trunc>that's fine to say that but I'm not doing anything about it today until after I get back yeah?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0262">no I know you're not and I never asked you to</u>
<u n="10" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0262">but I think we have to set quite a strong objective now</u>
<u n="12" who="S0261">yeah and and I mean timewise this is what my driver is is that timewise erm when when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said well what's your what's your time frame? yeah? for certain things and I said six months six months I want to have a foundation for something that I can then work towards carrying on with <unclear>mm</unclear>? so he's kind of oh well you wanna <trunc>m</trunc>you wanna move quick <unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah yeah and and also the other thing is is that it's it's <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>if you if you talk about money yeah? you need you need money to to live but you also need money to seed as capital erm and you know you need to know in a way that's reversing back because you need to go if I wanna do those things that you've just told me I need to know how much that's <trunc>g</trunc> theoretically how much capital I'm gonna need</u>
<u n="14" who="S0261">yes of course</u>
<u n="15" who="S0262">okay?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0262">and how long that capital's gonna last am I gonna burn through it?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0262">or am I gonna be able to chip away at the capital</u>
<u n="20" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0262">and just use it right at the right time?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0261">that's right</u>
<u n="23" who="S0262">so until you've got that answer <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you could just be earning money while you're thinking that bit through</u>
<u n="24" who="S0261">working those things out yes yes of course yeah yeah yeah yeah exactly yeah and erm <pause dur="short"/> and yes er and and of course you do you need to be earning money to carry on so that's <trunc>wha</trunc>what we're talking about but erm and put those that that research and those plans in place until you get this kind of coherent this is what we're doing how much it's gonna cost and where we're gonna start with objective for six months one year <trunc>f</trunc> and and then beyond yeah?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0262">see the way I'd do it is like if I didn't have this job and I was trying to set up like you I'd go right how do I earn money real fast? okay I would erm go and do summer schools cos they pay you gross er you don't have to be there forever you just do an intensive month and because it's just on <trunc>te</trunc> intensive months they'd pay you er top salary okay? and I'd do a number of those throughout the summer so I'd block off my summer in the UK and I'd go right objective is basically if I can put three or four of those back-to-back I'd earn about twenty thousand pounds</u>
<u n="26" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0262">okay? that will be my seed money</u>
<u n="28" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0262">and then I go off and do what I wanna do</u>
<u n="30" who="S0261">yeah mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0262">I'd go that's all I'm willing to commit to doing that's those summer schools it's not about me knowing that I need twenty thousand pounds I'm just guessing that if I have twenty thousand pounds that that's gonna take me some way yeah?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0262">erm and er and and that's all I'm prepared to give of my time anyway to to earning money on on er in that particular job</u>
<u n="34" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="35" who="S0262">because it I don't like it so I'm only going to do enough of it to get me to where I need to be</u>
<u n="36" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0262">financially</u>
<u n="38" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0262">to seed my capital</u>
<u n="40" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0262">that's how I'd do it</u>
<u n="42" who="S0261">yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0262">and I think most people do</u>
<u n="44" who="S0261">erm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and I just think most people who haven't got access to investment <trunc>c</trunc> er you know er capitalists and</u>
<u n="46" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="47" who="S0262">bank managers</u>
<u n="48" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0262">and stuff like that most of them will go <unclear>yeah I fucking</unclear> hate that fucking job but I stomach it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0262">because it's actually the thing that actually got me a lot of fucking money</u>
<u n="52" who="S0261" trans="overlap">means to an end means to an end</u>
<u n="53" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0261">yeah mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0262">cos when you leave normally you leave at the time when you're actually earning quite a good peak of money cos what I've seen what people were doing was that they were leaving not because er the money was good <unclear>because I fucking ain't working with fuckwits</unclear></u>
<u n="56" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but still the money was the same it was good</u>
<u n="58" who="S0261">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="59" who="S0262">look at what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did he fucking turned Microsoft down and what did he do? he went away and became a backpacker for a while and went back and worked for them <unclear>and</unclear> still working for them so you know I'm not saying that you'll go back and work for for whoever but you can see that a hundred and twenty thousand dollars a year is a good wicket in Sydney</u>
<u n="60" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and when you break that down into a contract of you know whatever that is doing something or other that <unclear/> be a fucking fast way of earning some capital <pause dur="short"/> much faster than <unclear>this other bit</unclear></u>
<u n="62" who="S0261">you've made your point erm <vocal desc="misc"/> so <pause dur="short"/> so we talked about er <trunc>w</trunc> outsourcing in terms of going away and making something out of the time that I'm away the actions that I can undertake are <pause dur="short"/> that I need to talk to a bunch of people before I go I need to make connections with people who are there so we've got erm <pause dur="long"/> we've got erm contacts and <unclear/> got Singapore <pause dur="short"/> I'll put down question mark do you think it's worth <unclear>not</unclear> going to Vietnam?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0262">I don't know I mean I think you need to sleep on all of that stuff yeah I think we've kind of gone through that bit quite a bit let's just sleep it let's sleep on that stuff and come back to it fresh tomorrow</u>
<u n="64" who="S0261" trans="overlap">righty-ho</u>
<u n="65" who="S0262">don't think I can make any decisions now on those things but what I think we do need to do today erm <vocal desc="misc"/> is be very honest with each other in terms of the actual reality of the time frame</u>
<u n="66" who="S0261">the time frame for what?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0262">for for erm what's going on and er what's going on what's er what I've I've marked out some some pointers I'll actually get my little book so I can show you what I've been thinking of</u>
<u n="68" who="S0261"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0262">do we need a gin and tonic?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0261">erm if you've got some tonic</u>
<u n="71" who="S0262"><unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0261">no okay</u>
<u n="73" who="S0262">huh? <pause dur="long"/> do you wanna beer?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0261">erm well you're not gonna make er something else?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0262">well <pause dur="short"/> what normally goes with ginger ale?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0261">have a look at what's there <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="77" who="S0262"><unclear>but</unclear> it would be kind of interesting to look at it from a erm sort of seems arbitrary but I guess it's about the <trunc>vi</trunc></u>
<u n="78" who="S0261" trans="overlap">monthly basis</u>
<u n="79" who="S0262">well it's the visa thing so I worked backwards from</u>
<u n="80" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0262">twenty-first of July</u>
<u n="82" who="S0261">that's this year</u>
<u n="83" who="S0262">er sorry next year</u>
<u n="84" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0262">so</u>
<u n="86" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0262">two thousand and fourteen <unclear>er whatever</unclear> so when I looked at it I thought oh actually you know what? that's fourteen months</u>
<u n="88" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="89" who="S0262">not very long <vocal desc="misc"/> and er it had occurred to me as I explained to you that erm I am more than likely quite keen to if it fits in with</u>
<u n="90" who="S0261">the big picture</u>
<u n="91" who="S0262">where is it? fits in with</u>
<u n="92" who="S0261">what?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0262">that</u>
<u n="94" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="95" who="S0262">I would like to do a doctor's degree in that</u>
<u n="96" who="S0261">if the if if if there is something research out of it that comes together</u>
<u n="97" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0261">right so if you did that you could frame that information in the context of business at the same time couldn't you?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0262">get seed money</u>
<u n="100" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0262">cos it's research</u>
<u n="102" who="S0261">yes mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0262">UK very forward-thinking</u>
<u n="104" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="105" who="S0262">uhu</u>
<u n="106" who="S0261">okay so you're interested in that in context of the thing in <anon type="place"/> you were talking about</u>
<u n="107" who="S0262">with the Singapore thing</u>
<u n="108" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="109" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0261">okay right</u>
<u n="111" who="S0262">so it gives us travel to Singapore and Asia and Australia</u>
<u n="112" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0262"><unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="114" who="S0261">yeah okay erm <pause dur="short"/> right and that that is</u>
<u n="115" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that would start in October two thousand and fourteen</u>
<u n="116" who="S0261">right okay so that's er what? a semester-based thing? start of a year?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0262" trans="overlap">erm yeah it's just said it just says it starts in October</u>
<u n="118" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="119" who="S0262"><unclear/> normal academic year</u>
<u n="120" who="S0261">okay so <pause dur="short"/> so in that context <pause dur="short"/> what would one build before that? in terms of business?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0262">well I have to go about I I I'll have to go about erm being the researcher cos I'd have to put a thesis <trunc>partic</trunc> a thesis proposal together which is by the way a professional stroke research erm degree it's actually a sort of hotchpotch</u>
<u n="122" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0262">so you can you er er it's one of these weird ones that's some sort of hybrid where you're still getting a doctorate degree but you are actually a professional working like a work</u>
<u n="124" who="S0261" trans="overlap">for an outfit</u>
<u n="125" who="S0262"><unclear>er well</unclear> I <trunc>c</trunc>I could do I could do freelance work I could do work for a company I could work for an NGO I could work for a I'm a worker an employer but also attached to my research a bit like what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did she's quite clever</u>
<u n="126" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0262"><unclear>cos she was working she's doing her research</unclear></u>
<u n="130" who="S0261">yeah okay so you get a doctorate out of having done work with certain people and doing the research and presumably the company you work for get the benefit of your research?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0262">no the research'll be mine</u>
<u n="132" who="S0261">no? right</u>
<u n="133" who="S0262">erm dunno how that all works out that's why I have to</u>
<u n="134" who="S0261" trans="overlap">oh so that you have time off like it's erm you know day off for uni kind of thing</u>
<u n="135" who="S0262">yeah <trunc>p</trunc>possibly possibly possibly I <trunc>d</trunc>I don't know like if you can get individual grants so that you can get seed money to develop your research ideas I er look to be honest with you I actually don't know enough about it that's why I'm siding up to people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> down at the university of <anon type="place"/> and go how do you <unclear/> she gets to travel round the world</u>
<u n="136" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0262">how do you do that? how? you know</u>
<u n="138" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0261">of course</u>
<u n="141" who="S0262" trans="overlap">someone passes on that information and</u>
<u n="142" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0262">you basically try and put what you can together but essentially I would want to be earning money</u>
<u n="144" who="S0261">mm yes yeah while you're trying to do that</u>
<u n="145" who="S0262" trans="overlap">cos it's er professional development</u>
<u n="146" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0262">so I need to be in a profession but I <trunc>r</trunc>really want the doctorate degree out of it cos as everybody says you go up amazingly higher as soon as you've got doctorate you know</u>
<u n="148" who="S0261">if you want to work in a university</u>
<u n="149" who="S0262">no no no even if you wanna prove that you fucking know what you're talking about with this shit cos you get credibility</u>
<u n="150" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes that's right</u>
<u n="151" who="S0262">you know you go into industry and you're like I'm I'm a professional</u>
<u n="152" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0262">with a doctorate degree like oh</u>
<u n="154" who="S0261">so I'm curious about the perception by some people that if you've got a doctorate degree the options that you have when you've got that are limited because you are so specialised</u>
<u n="155" who="S0262">no no because there's different types of doctorate degrees</u>
<u n="156" who="S0261">I know it's a very generic</u>
<u n="157" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no it's alright</u>
<u n="158" who="S0261"><unclear/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0262">PHD <trunc>ph</trunc> er philosophy er <trunc>d</trunc> er doctorate of philosophy</u>
<u n="160" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="161" who="S0262">mine's not a PHD it would be an EDD doctorate of education education is a profession</u>
<u n="162" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="163" who="S0262">so if I work within the industry of education</u>
<u n="164" who="S0261" trans="overlap">oh er er okay oh I haven't seen that before</u>
<u n="165" who="S0262">mm PHD's academia</u>
<u n="166" who="S0261">right yes so it was the academic side</u>
<u n="167" who="S0262"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="168" who="S0261">of it I was thinking well you'd just end up down a a deeper tunnel</u>
<u n="169" who="S0262">no fuck that I'm not doing that</u>
<u n="170" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="171" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0261">and that's I'm glad you said that</u>
<u n="173" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0261">alright so</u>
<u n="175" who="S0262">I'm not interested in doing a PHD</u>
<u n="176" who="S0261">right okay so that that that's fine erm <pause dur="short"/> that in itself that sounds interesting and if the professional basis of your work involves well you'd expect it'd involve being in <anon type="place"/> or er would it involve being somewhere?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0262"><trunc>w</trunc>well you could you <trunc>c</trunc> you you've gotta be <unclear/> a bit of an architect you've gotta create something really quite interesting and you've gotta get people on board and</u>
<u n="178" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0262">you've gotta do travel and you've gotta get funding and</u>
<u n="180" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0262">you know you've got to pitch and pitch and pitch away at it for probably about three to four years</u>
<u n="182" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="short"/> so can your business stuff be your research and you're getting paid for it? so you're <trunc>s</trunc> you're you're consulting or you're providing people services that are wrapped around your <trunc>re</trunc>your research is wrapped around it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0262">I think you can I think if you look at more like a community capability development or er er you know like a <trunc>s</trunc> er if you can explain at the moment this is the trend it might change <unclear>all</unclear> soon but everybody talks about building skills capability in others</u>
<u n="184" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0262">it's this idea at the <trunc>m</trunc>at the moment that's all about sharing that kind of you know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0261">sharing knowledge and teaching people <unclear/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah it's a big trend I guess in the world going on about that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and <unclear>online</unclear> and so everybody's <unclear>growing up</unclear></u>
<u n="189" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0262">so I think if you can prove that</u>
<u n="192" who="S0261"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0262">I think if you can prove you can do that yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0261">so er imagine if er for instance this thing we talked about in Vietnam that that you get a connection with some outfit</u>
<u n="195" who="S0262" trans="overlap">British Council</u>
<u n="196" who="S0261">that is doing that yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0262">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0261">and erm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0262"><unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0261">and that you're doing the work</u>
<u n="201" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0261">you're getting paid to do the work and a part of your your your personal remit is to carry out research related to what you're doing</u>
<u n="203" who="S0262">yep</u>
<u n="204" who="S0261">so the output is yours</u>
<u n="205" who="S0262">mm it has to be it's your original work</u>
<u n="206" who="S0261">yeah but that has to be independent of your work because typically your employer will carry copyright for anything that you do</u>
<u n="207" who="S0262">no not not no it doesn't work like that mm mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0261"><unclear>oh well er what er in what I do</unclear></u>
<u n="209" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="210" who="S0261">what I have been doing it is like that</u>
<u n="211" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0261">any work you do is the copyright of the business</u>
<u n="213" who="S0262">yeah no I can work I can do work for my employer</u>
<u n="214" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="215" who="S0262">I'm just not doing the research for my employer</u>
<u n="216" who="S0261">right yes exactly okay</u>
<u n="217" who="S0262">I'm doing research on my doctorate degree</u>
<u n="218" who="S0261" trans="overlap">but what if er and then what if there's crossover though?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0262">well you come to some sort of arrangement most of the time</u>
<u n="220" who="S0261"><unclear>well</unclear></u>
<u n="221" who="S0262">people understand you're doing a doctorate degree understand that you've got to produce original work it's got to be of your name</u>
<u n="222" who="S0261">right okay so if we look at that</u>
<u n="223" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0261">in in context erm <pause dur="long"/> right <pause dur="long"/> so do you see there are things that would be done before that that you would do to benefit</u>
<u n="225" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>well I was gonna</unclear></u>
<u n="226" who="S0261">business-wise er and certainly the research side of it?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well yeah I mean you know <trunc>y</trunc> it <trunc>d</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc> it doesn't just happen overnight</u>
<u n="228" who="S0261" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="229" who="S0262">you've gotta you've gotta</u>
<u n="230" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0262">you've gotta go to the UK you've gotta go to the <anon type="place"/> you've gotta</u>
<u n="232" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you've gotta start somewhere</u>
<u n="233" who="S0262">go and talk to them and find out exactly what the degree entails then you have to find a supervisor that won't happen in August you've gotta have a thesis proposal</u>
<u n="234" who="S0261">to present to somebody for them to consider to er mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0262" trans="overlap">to present for them to even think about whether they want it</u>
<u n="236" who="S0261">mm yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0262">the lead time is probably is about a year if you're really looking for a quality supervisor</u>
<u n="238" who="S0261">yeah okay</u>
<u n="239" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0261">and if you give yourself that amount of time then you'll get that</u>
<u n="241" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0261">and that's fine <pause dur="short"/> that's cool <pause dur="long"/> that doesn't fit together with Asia well it doesn't have to have to it doesn't have to</u>
<u n="243" who="S0262">well if we're taking this we're moving round the world kind of thing</u>
<u n="244" who="S0261">yeah it doesn't have to this is the whole point</u>
<u n="245" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah it <trunc>does</trunc>doesn't really matter</u>
<u n="246" who="S0261">mm yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0262">it's just like what you just go where who what</u>
<u n="248" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0262">whatever suits you</u>
<u n="250" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0262">you know? pick out fly to wherever it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="252" who="S0261" trans="overlap">exactly mm yeah erm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0262">you do need a base to put your shit</u>
<u n="254" who="S0261">yes physically</u>
<u n="255" who="S0262"><unclear>and I'll</unclear> just put it either well it's <trunc>g</trunc> it makes sense to put it in Europe put it in the UK</u>
<u n="256" who="S0261">well and then you really wanna cut down on the cost of that</u>
<u n="257" who="S0262" trans="overlap">cos both of us can fly in and out of well I know but I mean look people are doing it and <trunc>Re</trunc><trunc>Reb</trunc><trunc>Reb</trunc> Location Rebel they're flying to places they live in places <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0261">yeah yeah and most of their stuff just probably ends up at their parents' house</u>
<u n="259" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0262">but I mean if we're following that dream</u>
<u n="262" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah of course</u>
<u n="263" who="S0262">we have to fucking start thinking about it right doing it right now</u>
<u n="264" who="S0261">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0262">cos otherwise it's never gonna happen you're never gonna internalise that process if <unclear/> actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0261" trans="overlap">no you have to operate like that <unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="269" who="S0262">yeah so that's why I'm I've already accepted it as an assumption</u>
<u n="270" who="S0261">and you have to accept that that's er it's a potential cost</u>
<u n="271" who="S0262">yes of course it is</u>
<u n="272" who="S0261">mm yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0262">mm that's why you have to find a way to fund it</u>
<u n="274" who="S0261">mm yeah erm and there are mechanisms that you can use that are quite <trunc>ch</trunc> a lot cheaper than renting a gaff from somebody or something</u>
<u n="275" who="S0262">well yeah I mean clearly like when you get to England</u>
<u n="276" who="S0261">that's just all detail anyway let's not worry about that</u>
<u n="277" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I mean you know the er the</u>
<u n="278" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah that's all just er who cares?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0262">yeah you keep doing detail stuff</u>
<u n="280" who="S0261" trans="overlap">erm yeah I don't no er erm erm don't step back so <pause dur="short"/> that that's fine</u>
<u n="281" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0262">cool</u>
<u n="284" who="S0261">erm and and that kind of stuff is good in a way because erm it is good because erm it provides you a timeline through which certain things have to happen</u>
<u n="285" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0261">and you try to synthesise things together</u>
<u n="287" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0261">such that you get the maximum benefit at each stage out of it</u>
<u n="289" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0261">erm so you you really think hard and strategically about how do we make this work for ourselves</u>
<u n="293" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0261">in the best possible fashion</u>
<u n="295" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0261">and if you look at look it doesn't matter where you are in the world but if you look at relative cost et cetera it is obviously cheaper to live in Asia or something like that</u>
<u n="297" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0261">so if you er started such a thing in Singapore as an example erm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0262">yeah I don't know the details of how it works out</u>
<u n="300" who="S0261" trans="overlap">who who know who know who knows but it's</u>
<u n="301" who="S0262">but but yeah we certainly would be leaving Sydney and we're going to the UK so I can start in the UK in October</u>
<u n="302" who="S0261">that kind of <unclear>idea</unclear></u>
<u n="303" who="S0262">yeah because until somebody tells me it's any different that's the assumption that I'm making</u>
<u n="304" who="S0261">mm that's fine</u>
<u n="305" who="S0262">okay but yeah Singapore does feature</u>
<u n="306" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm yes but what that means is</u>
<u n="307" who="S0262">just don't exactly know when where and how</u>
<u n="308" who="S0261">er yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah just don't know</u>
<u n="310" who="S0261">as er as another thing</u>
<u n="311" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0261">so you would be hoping in August to draw something out of your time there in relation to this</u>
<u n="313" who="S0262">yeah I'd wanna satisfy that I'm picking the right course and I've got the right kind of idea about it and how much it's really gonna cost me and how can I really get funding you know I'm gonna be asking some really</u>
<u n="314" who="S0261" trans="overlap">some of those detailed <trunc>questio</trunc> so</u>
<u n="315" who="S0262">really detailed questions in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so is it er is it possible to ask that without you know have a lot done in advance</u>
<u n="317" who="S0262">no I'm I make an appointment er and I'll I'll you know okay there might be a way so there's a lot I might have to do my email anyway</u>
<u n="318" who="S0261">you can do it online wherever</u>
<u n="319" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but no when I'm in <anon type="place"/> I will go and check out the whole fucking place</u>
<u n="320" who="S0261">oh yeah for sure</u>
<u n="321" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I'm not signing up for something that I don't fucking</u>
<u n="322" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm that's not real mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0262">talk to students</u>
<u n="324" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0262">talk to other people I'm just so you know once bitten twice shy with some of these things <unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="326" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes yeah you need to know that for real you've gotta yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0262">you've gotta have a on-the-ground feeling about it</u>
<u n="328" who="S0261">yeah yep</u>
<u n="329" who="S0262">you really do</u>
<u n="330" who="S0261">exactly and you want to understand that with your background that it's feasible that you're going to be accepted to this stuff et cetera et cetera</u>
<u n="331" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah and I might even go to another university just to sort of compare and contrast</u>
<u n="332" who="S0261">find the other side of the fence</u>
<u n="333" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0261">yes and that's not a bad idea either</u>
<u n="335" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0261">erm er</u>
<u n="337" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> dad's <unclear/> university and ask them a few questions I'm like dad and he's like well why not?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0261">mm mm well of course</u>
<u n="339" who="S0262">I'm like yeah I suppose yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0261">my uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did that he he went straight into <anon type="place"/> as an adult learner</u>
<u n="341" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear> so</u>
<u n="343" who="S0262">he said you know why why not?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0262">why why would you not place yourself you know somewhere</u>
<u n="346" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear>right at the height</unclear></u>
<u n="347" who="S0262">all they're gonna tell you is</u>
<u n="348" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0262">you know</u>
<u n="350" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0262">and I was like and he said you know you've got a first-class degree so you're already in there from their perspective</u>
<u n="352" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0262">your first degree if you can get the equivalent of a first-class degree on your masters of education then</u>
<u n="354" who="S0261" trans="overlap">on your masters yeah why not?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0262">why can't you?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0261">yeah uhu</u>
<u n="357" who="S0262">so I went alright</u>
<u n="358" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0262">I'll see how it goes</u>
<u n="360" who="S0261">mm oh well it's worthwhile just having a chat with people there</u>
<u n="361" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0261">because it's an easy thing to do</u>
<u n="363" who="S0262">mm dead easy and I made I didn't <trunc>m</trunc> I made that mistake when I was doing that whole you know bloody going around England</u>
<u n="364" who="S0261">yeah why didn't you just go and <unclear>two</unclear> er on your doorstep</u>
<u n="365" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I er could've just bowled up to <anon type="place"/> and there were people already doing the work that I was interested in doing <unclear/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0261" trans="overlap">oh er of course yeah yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0262">I could've just done the whole fucking week with them</u>
<u n="368" who="S0261">exactly</u>
<u n="369" who="S0262">rather than wasting all this time</u>
<u n="370" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and you would've saved the effort and the time and the money and all of that flapping around</u>
<u n="371" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so yeah <trunc>d</trunc>dad's got a point</u>
<u n="372" who="S0261">yes yeah have a look at what's on your in your own backyard first</u>
<u n="373" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="375" who="S0262">especially if it's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0261">yes well <trunc>e</trunc>exactly of course</u>
<u n="377" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0261">erm but that that's cool <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0262">so the penny's dropped then?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0261">well there's no dropping pennies</u>
<u n="381" who="S0262">but</u>
<u n="382" who="S0261">I'm thinking with an open mind</u>
<u n="383" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0261">which is that you know the context is you know you could do that and one could live in France</u>
<u n="385" who="S0262">yeah I love that idea</u>
<u n="386" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you know?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0262">go and live in dad's place</u>
<u n="388" who="S0261">but <trunc>th</trunc>that's what I mean is that when you've got the right tools at your fingertips you can think like that you don't have to think oh well work's over there therefore I've got to be there and I've got to turn up at eight AM every morning</u>
<u n="389" who="S0262">yeah er</u>
<u n="390" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0262"><trunc>a</trunc><trunc>a</trunc><trunc>an</trunc>and by the way when you're er like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she doesn't she's doing she is doing her PHD at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you're er your own architect</u>
<u n="393" who="S0262">but look she's in Brisbane</u>
<u n="394" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="395" who="S0262">and she's you know been remote for some time and she's still she's</u>
<u n="396" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and she's travelling to Spain to do it</u>
<u n="397" who="S0262">as long as you can get to your supervisor when you need to</u>
<u n="398" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0262">and by the way sometimes supervisors can fly into where you are</u>
<u n="400" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="401" who="S0262">if it's an attractive place to be like Paris for example</u>
<u n="402" who="S0261">absolutely of course</u>
<u n="403" who="S0262">and er the other thing is is that erm <vocal desc="misc"/> <trunc>y</trunc>yeah you know they do want you to turn up in blocks sometimes</u>
<u n="404" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0262">like the other thing <unclear>we</unclear> did where you have to go for two weeks and you have to be there and but that's your education that's your fees</u>
<u n="406" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that's fine that's fine</u>
<u n="407" who="S0262">that's what you're paying fees for</u>
<u n="408" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes of course</u>
<u n="409" who="S0262">to get some sort of educational training thing</u>
<u n="410" who="S0261">but you get the context that you</u>
<u n="411" who="S0262">yeah and you should have a relationship with some of the people in your university because <unclear>it seems</unclear> a bit weird otherwise</u>
<u n="412" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc>you can have whatever yes of course so erm that is all part of the bigger picture of the way that I <trunc>th</trunc> I'm thinking</u>
<u n="413" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0261">which is you can be anywhere to do whatever you want for whatever reason</u>
<u n="415" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0261">whether it's need or a want all of that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="417" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0261">yeah? and that you can er act and react on your toes as you need to</u>
<u n="419" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0261">yeah? so that would be the best context that you can go overnight erm we're gonna go and do this next week and then you put plans in place and you go and do that</u>
<u n="421" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0262">and if we've got a wee nipper in tow well so be it</u>
<u n="424" who="S0261">yes exactly now</u>
<u n="425" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did it</u>
<u n="426" who="S0261">yeah and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s saying well don't forget you're older and all this kind of stuff</u>
<u n="427" who="S0262">well</u>
<u n="428" who="S0261">well you just put other <trunc>th</trunc>other things in place to make it easier for you</u>
<u n="429" who="S0262">the the truth of the matter is is that er <unclear/> when if you if you give er if you give birth you are probably a little bit fucked for about six months</u>
<u n="430" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="431" who="S0262">erm and you probably aren't right for the you know until really a year</u>
<u n="432" who="S0261">for the bigger journey yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0262">but that's why you need somebody you can rely on to take some of the pressure off the two of <trunc>t</trunc> the couple</u>
<u n="434" who="S0261">exactly and when that's somebody that</u>
<u n="435" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and dad's perfect for that</u>
<u n="436" who="S0261">yes exactly and er and whether it's somebody that's as close as family or somebody else that you build into your life to allow that</u>
<u n="437" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well think about all that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and blah de blah and</u>
<u n="438" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes of <trunc>cour</trunc> and they're all examples of exactly the same thing</u>
<u n="439" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0261">you know you just share the wealth</u>
<u n="441" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0261">and and you can make it possible feasible</u>
<u n="443" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0261">so that's just open-minded thinking as far as <unclear>I I see it</unclear></u>
<u n="445" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah and I I I'd be quite happy to have the baby born in Britain</u>
<u n="446" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0262">cos fair dos then it's really obvious what happens is they get a British passport</u>
<u n="448" who="S0261">yes which in theory has its er</u>
<u n="449" who="S0262">which is a European passport</u>
<u n="450" who="S0261">yes of course</u>
<u n="451" who="S0262">which is already access to how many countries?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0261">yes er of course yes</u>
<u n="453" who="S0262">it's a win-win for that child</u>
<u n="454" who="S0261">mm mm and through connection erm simply they themselves <trunc>p</trunc>presumably would have rights to to Kiwis</u>
<u n="455" who="S0262" trans="overlap">New Zealand yeah for sure look at what happened with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's <trunc>w</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I mean he got you know New Zealand passport</u>
<u n="456" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah mm and that's how it exists at the moment but <unclear>erm in time</unclear> hopefully it will still be the same</u>
<u n="457" who="S0262">well you just apply straight away for one apparently that's what you can do</u>
<u n="458" who="S0261">yes that's right on behalf of your child</u>
<u n="459" who="S0262">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was born in England</u>
<u n="460" who="S0261">yeah mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0262">he got a <trunc>p</trunc> Kiwi passport pretty</u>
<u n="462" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah no that's that's the way that you do it that's the way you do it mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he got a Kiwi passport in three weeks when they found out <vocal desc="laugh"/> they had to come here</u>
<u n="464" who="S0261">of course</u>
<u n="465" who="S0262"><unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="466" who="S0261">so one would imagine it er works either way but aside that again is detail but</u>
<u n="467" who="S0262">it's pretty important detail though</u>
<u n="468" who="S0261"><trunc>y</trunc>yes the big picture fits and the glove fits the big picture and all of that stuff so that's that's straightforward in my head yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0261">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="471" who="S0262">and also I don't think British er immigration would have too much of a problem if I bowl up looking quite pregnant and they're going like oh right so are you here to have a baby? I'm like</u>
<u n="472" who="S0261">no but you're a British resident it's got nothing to do with them</u>
<u n="473" who="S0262">yeah exactly that's why I don't er think I'll have a problem with it</u>
<u n="474" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0262">it would be a bit different if I bowled up to New Zealand</u>
<u n="476" who="S0261">yes you would have to be in the door beforehand</u>
<u n="477" who="S0262">don't think they'd like that very much</u>
<u n="478" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="479" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="480" who="S0261">you have to be in the door beforehand</u>
<u n="481" who="S0262">and here was just a fucked idea there's no point having a baby here</u>
<u n="482" who="S0261">no yeah that's right mm exactly erm <pause dur="short"/> that in itself is fine and that fits the context of all of those discussions as well that <unclear>the</unclear> that fourteen-month picture that kind of thing so that's cool</u>
<u n="483" who="S0262">can I also mention something else to you? this is round about the time we can start</u>
<u n="484" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="485" who="S0262">even if it got to December until I actually got pregnant</u>
<u n="486" who="S0261">yes and then you've got nine after that carry on er overlaps that October no? it's right on the nail of it</u>
<u n="487" who="S0262" trans="overlap">two three four five six seven eight nine</u>
<u n="488" who="S0261">oh no it'd be on the same day <vocal desc="laugh"/> no way <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0262">I can take six and a half months maternity leave from <anon type="place"/> university</u>
<u n="490" who="S0261">yeah that that's pre and post though isn't it?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0261">yes so the you've got three pre and three post let's say</u>
<u n="493" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="495" who="S0262"><unclear>does that mean</unclear>?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0261" trans="overlap">or does that is that how it work? I dunno it could be shorter before and more after</u>
<u n="497" who="S0262">it's it's look it's it's <trunc>y</trunc> it's up to complications and stuff</u>
<u n="498" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0262">it's always you have to <unclear/> discuss it with your unit</u>
<u n="500" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="501" who="S0262">but quite clearly <vocal desc="laugh"/> it wouldn't be that difficult for me to stop working around about then</u>
<u n="502" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0262"><unclear>I dunno</unclear> I'll just fucking <unclear>take</unclear> the money</u>
<u n="504" who="S0261" trans="overlap">tootle off tootle off</u>
<u n="505" who="S0262">yeah just do what we wanna do together</u>
<u n="506" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="507" who="S0262">enjoy that time together working out what you know what's going on with you and stuff and business and proposals and</u>
<u n="508" who="S0261">well that that in itself would be quite er quite advantageous wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0262">and that's only that's only if er you know if it had got a bit earlier so <unclear/> bit luckier</u>
<u n="510" who="S0261">then bigger picture better off yes <pause dur="short"/> like your thinking</u>
<u n="511" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0261">mm not to be said to anybody</u>
<u n="513" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0261">but that's quite cool <pause dur="long"/> I might <vocal desc="laugh"/> was it three minutes of footage went missing</u>
<u n="515" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0262">well it'd be funny wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0261">well er it would be it would be no I I do and er I <trunc>li</trunc>I like your thinking I can see some common sense there erm what? you think we digest some of that and come back to it tomorrow?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0261">or something? but really what I'm trying to drive at is I want some key actions that we can both buy into having value <pause dur="short"/> that either feeds into some of the elements of that big picture which is education</u>
<u n="520" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0261">or or otherwise it is simply related to <unclear>process the mechanism of operations</unclear></u>
<u n="522" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0262">well I I would also say that you know the the the the <pause dur="long"/> I'll find out more about it on Friday but erm it probably is just as well if you do as much of your travelling which you are gonna be doing erm you know</u>
<u n="525" who="S0261" trans="overlap">in June</u>
<u n="526" who="S0262">er er in these in er you know the time when the time when you can be away without things being too problematic and anyway we're gonna be away together in England</u>
<u n="527" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0262">but after that you are gonna have to be around because otherwise I'm not gonna get pregnant</u>
<u n="529" who="S0261">no that's absolutely right of course</u>
<u n="530" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah I need you there</u>
<u n="531" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0262">but</u>
<u n="533" who="S0261">no don't worry about that</u>
<u n="534" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so you know</u>
<u n="535" who="S0261">look this is related to my birthday that's related to your birthday</u>
<u n="536" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0261">they are the reasons why that's there really yeah? and the fact that I'm trying to put this stuff together now is to make the most of what's been a bad situation</u>
<u n="538" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0261">the intention initially hadn't really crossed my mind more that it being erm <pause dur="short"/> gaining more experience about travelling in those areas and just trying to operate something</u>
<u n="540" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0261">you know erm and that's kind of the big picture</u>
<u n="542" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0261">erm when you start to refine it and say well I want to get something out of this who can I meet? who <trunc>h</trunc>how can I get the the most out of this?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0261">erm and <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was right in the context of see whether you can find key people to meet with</u>
<u n="546" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0261">which you can simply do some standard market research with you know</u>
<u n="548" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="549" who="S0261"><unclear>talk to them</unclear> right there you know you're the ears and you want them to talk as much as much as they want</u>
<u n="550" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0261">about whatever they do and learn about what they need what they want</u>
<u n="552" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0261">where they think they're going what their future looks like that kind of stuff and there is definitely value in any of those conversations</u>
<u n="554" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0261">with whoever and like you say you meet with somebody and if they show you something else I'm sure there's something you learn out of seeing that</u>
<u n="556" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0262">absolutely</u>
<u n="559" who="S0261">erm so</u>
<u n="560" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="561" who="S0261">if I say there's three two weeks</u>
<u n="562" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0261">two weeks let's say four occasions</u>
<u n="564" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0261">that are of a let's try and get the most value out of those four occasions and the rest of it becomes other things that may or may not happen but can provide some other benefits as well</u>
<u n="566" who="S0262">yeah I think I understand what you're saying</u>
<u n="567" who="S0261">now there's no reason why I can't meet four different people</u>
<u n="568" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0261">in in four different countries</u>
<u n="570" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0261">really erm if if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is around it could be somebody who's in Malaysia she works for a university in Singapore erm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0262">write this down and I'll make another drink</u>
<u n="573" who="S0261">okay</u>
<u n="574" who="S0262">it's not bad actually is it?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0261">yeah it's cos the ginger's a little flat</u>
<u n="576" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0261">okay</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="578" who="S0261">okay so I'm back on recording now I just paused it for a moment so what I've got in terms of people is in Malaysia <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> worked for a university and presumably she has connections to some people</u>
<u n="579" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0261">it's just up the road from Singapore so easy to get to</u>
<u n="581" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0261">erm there's a guy from Location Rebel who has who I mentioned who lives in Singapore he's Singaporean</u>
<u n="583" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0261">so he's a native you've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who may know people if you ask the right questions</u>
<u n="585" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0261">er but I don't rely on that specifically</u>
<u n="587" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="588" who="S0261">Location Rebel wise <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> mentioned that there's a particular guy who lives in Singapore that I could meet up with</u>
<u n="589" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="590" who="S0261">he's likely to be American</u>
<u n="591" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="592" who="S0261">but <unclear>who'll have an outlook</unclear></u>
<u n="593" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0261">erm you've got and then you've got Indonesia you've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his understand of things</u>
<u n="595" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0261">so trawl the brain for that</u>
<u n="597" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0261">erm and also in Indo there's potentially people that are <unclear/> people that erm live in in Bali as well right? and there are certainly others that erm like there's a a guy who's gone back to America but he lived in Indonesia in a different part of Bali and he's married to an Indonesian woman so he himself has a different cultural outlook he's got children as well</u>
<u n="599" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0261">he's a little older than us</u>
<u n="601" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0261">so mature</u>
<u n="603" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0261">but erm very receptive and I <trunc>h</trunc> I've had quite a few conversations with him</u>
<u n="605" who="S0262"><unclear>yeah erm</unclear> sounds good</u>
<u n="606" who="S0261">so erm er I've just forget his name off the top of my head but erm he's very approachable yeah erm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0262">you got erm you got erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s husband <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0261">yes we have erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0262">erm who else do we know in Sydney? <vocal desc="misc"/> let's think this through</u>
<u n="610" who="S0261">people who have Asian business connections</u>
<u n="611" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="612" who="S0261">that could be erm <unclear>wise</unclear> for us</u>
<u n="613" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0261">well rather than halting there we'll come back to that</u>
<u n="615" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0261">erm what I know is we talked about this Vietnam thing you know the guys who I listen to on the radio</u>
<u n="617" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0261">they live in Ho Chi Minh city</u>
<u n="619" who="S0262">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0261">at the moment</u>
<u n="621" who="S0262">well that's <trunc>ha</trunc>that's handy</u>
<u n="622" who="S0261">right? so you've got erm er his name's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when he first came out of work moved to Bali and worked for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="624" who="S0261">right? so that connection's very strong and they're very good friends</u>
<u n="625" who="S0262">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="626" who="S0261">right? so and that guy I think if he presents him well himself truly has an open mind to talk to anybody about anything</u>
<u n="627" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="628" who="S0261">and he's got a philosophy background as well so he he he's a thinker</u>
<u n="629" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0261">you know? he likes his business stuff but he is a thinker</u>
<u n="631" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0261">which is quite good</u>
<u n="633" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0261">and he's very much he's lived and worked in different parts of Asia so he's been in Bali he's been in the Philippines he's now in Ho Chi Minh he's probably travelled to everywhere</u>
<u n="635" who="S0262">so how long would it take to travel from Singapore to Ho Chi Minh?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0261">well I'd say it's probably an hour and bit on a plane</u>
<u n="637" who="S0262">oh right</u>
<u n="638" who="S0261">yeah not far</u>
<u n="639" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="640" who="S0261">because it's that's just</u>
<u n="641" who="S0262">south isn't it?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0261">it it's quite a way south</u>
<u n="643" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0261">relatively and er</u>
<u n="645" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0261">and and it's erm probably way over the east coast</u>
<u n="647" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>well then</unclear> talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you never know she might still have people in Ho Chi Minh <unclear/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0261">well I did ask her</u>
<u n="649" who="S0262">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0261">I did ask I said have you still got friends there <unclear>you're connected with</unclear>? you know and it might be you know and she's kind of said yeah so that's erm</u>
<u n="651" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay we'll put that down too</u>
<u n="652" who="S0261">so that's er that's erm <trunc>Vi</trunc>Vietnam and that's erm Ho Chi Minh HCM erm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah erm now of course she's rather negative person but that doesn't matter in terms of she doesn't really know what we're trying to achieve erm I just wanna talk to people about <unclear/> the way they see the culture</u>
<u n="653" who="S0262">yep</u>
<u n="654" who="S0261">and and how they operate in those places and out of this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> fella there are a myriad of people who work all over Southeast Asia that could be of worthy connection and they're they're all crawling all over the place</u>
<u n="655" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0261">you know you can go to Chiang Mai it's the head of where all the backpackers hang out and do business</u>
<u n="657" who="S0262">backpackers do business? fucking hell</u>
<u n="658" who="S0261">well they're not they're not just back they're not just backpackers</u>
<u n="659" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>thought they just er</unclear> fucking sit around drink piss and smoke pot <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0261">you know they're people who are actually trying to run a business but they like to be based in Asia cos it's cheap</u>
<u n="661" who="S0262">fair enough</u>
<u n="662" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear>you know it's</unclear> that's fair enough you know er hedging your bets and making the most out of the <unclear>bloody</unclear> cash that they've got</u>
<u n="663" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0261">but provides them a good benefit erm <vocal desc="misc"/> we talked about Taiwan and that was in the context of</u>
<u n="665" who="S0262">well yeah erm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0262">certainly <trunc>cert</trunc> well yes erm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0261">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I wouldn't mind asking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I I dunno maybe I'd ask <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but <unclear>mm</unclear> but certainly I'd ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0261">yes?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0262">definitely ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she's good <unclear/> and</u>
<u n="672" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0262">she'd be delighted</u>
<u n="674" who="S0261">right okay</u>
<u n="675" who="S0262">delighted to have got something</u>
<u n="676" who="S0261" trans="overlap">to earn more yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0262">oh yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0261">well to tell the story yeah so we could Skype</u>
<u n="679" who="S0262">yeah?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0261">yeah this is er a lot of this I'm thinking and and generically I was gonna say my message out to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0262">didn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and and what's his name? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> live in Taiwan? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> Chinese <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0261">Hong Kong?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0262">think it was Taiwan</u>
<u n="684" who="S0261">you could ask her</u>
<u n="685" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="686" who="S0261">cos I could have a chat to him get <trunc>h</trunc> get a get a a Western person's point of view</u>
<u n="687" who="S0262">actually no don't talk to him cos he</u>
<u n="688" who="S0261">he's a bit wired</u>
<u n="689" who="S0262">yeah he he'd probably put put he'd probably put you off</u>
<u n="690" who="S0261" trans="overlap">he can maybe yeah well he'd put you in the wrong direction too</u>
<u n="691" who="S0262">yeah maybe and I think you've got enough people on your plate now so</u>
<u n="692" who="S0261" trans="overlap">negative yeah yeah yeah erm general er general questions so erm really my point is it's best to <trunc>l</trunc> meet up with some natives which <trunc>y</trunc>you er you could get a connection through Western</u>
<u n="693" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0261">er Western people so</u>
<u n="695" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0261">that creates that kind of feeling of there's a business connection potential</u>
<u n="697" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah it's very</u>
<u n="700" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and that they're kind of the go-between</u>
<u n="701" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0261">to start with <unclear/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0262" trans="overlap">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gonna be in Indonesia when <unclear>we're there</unclear>?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0261">well he's talking about moving kind of soonish isn't he? so erm he mentioned <unclear/> <unclear>he was going</unclear> so it's feasible</u>
<u n="705" who="S0262">really keep in contact with him don't rely on me to</u>
<u n="706" who="S0261">no I did I sent him a message the other day</u>
<u n="707" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh good</u>
<u n="708" who="S0261">and I said gimme erm gimme the details of your mate who's a graphic designer</u>
<u n="709" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0261">I wanna know that</u>
<u n="711" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="712" who="S0261">I wanna look at what he does</u>
<u n="713" who="S0262">mm <unclear>then</unclear> back</u>
<u n="714" who="S0261">no he <trunc>di</trunc> he <trunc>s</trunc> he <trunc>c</trunc> he <trunc>g</trunc>got back to me and said I'll send you some details over the email but he hasn't done it yet</u>
<u n="715" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="716" who="S0261">yeah cos you know if I ask him again I'm sure you know</u>
<u n="717" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0261">but he's easy to get in contact with and he's reliable to get back to you</u>
<u n="719" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="720" who="S0261">I just put it on Twitter and he gets back to me straight away</u>
<u n="721" who="S0262"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="722" who="S0261">yeah erm so those kind of connections are what we're looking for so is there anybody else that we <trunc>c</trunc> that we've missed off the thing that that could be I know we've got a longish list</u>
<u n="723" who="S0262">I'd say for now we'll probably do alright with just keeping that for now for Saturday evening when we're having a few drinks</u>
<u n="724" who="S0261">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="725" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0261">and we might erm streamline that but I can bung out a bunch of messages quite easy</u>
<u n="727" who="S0262">and some people will just go no but I know somebody who has</u>
<u n="728" who="S0261">yes and that's fine and that's what I'm looking for</u>
<u n="729" who="S0262">what about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? do they know anybody that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0261" trans="overlap">oh yes of of of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I wanted to get their erm I wanted to get their collective mind on <unclear>certainly</unclear> operating you know relationships connections what's <foreign lang="chi"/> mean again?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0262">er connections <unclear>could mean</unclear> connected</u>
<u n="732" who="S0261"><unclear>to er as in</unclear>? to to</u>
<u n="733" who="S0262">to be connected to be well-connected</u>
<u n="734" who="S0261">right as networking</u>
<u n="735" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0261">context of networking</u>
<u n="737" who="S0262">to yeah yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0261">it's not it's not gifts?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0262">er</u>
<u n="740" who="S0261">cos cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me you know what <foreign lang="chi"/> means and then I thought it meant to be connected but then <unclear/> it made me think it's not like kind of like you give somebody an offering when you meet them?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0262"><unclear/> <foreign lang="chi"/> could probably have a number of definitions</u>
<u n="742" who="S0261">right I remember when I was trying to get in contact with erm that university that Adelaide lot I'd gotten in contact on Linkedin with a lady who is a consultant who briefs people about how to do business operation in China and she had a video online which talks about that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="743" who="S0262">yeah <trunc>y</trunc> whenever those opportunities arise you should just really try and clarify what that person's talking about</u>
<u n="744" who="S0261">yeah I know I just kind of it was in er it was just er kind of we were in a flow in the flow so it was just kind of like</u>
<u n="745" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh right okay</unclear></u>
<u n="746" who="S0261">oh yeah okay</u>
<u n="747" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="748" who="S0261">and I thought I'll just go back to that</u>
<u n="749" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="750" who="S0261"><unclear>but</unclear> I <trunc>sh</trunc>I should've asked</u>
<u n="751" who="S0262">mm you should</u>
<u n="752" who="S0261" trans="overlap">certainly his point of view</u>
<u n="753" who="S0262">always ask your questions that's what you're practising</u>
<u n="754" who="S0261">yes that's right erm</u>
<u n="755" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay so that's good now can I have a turn about what I want to talk about?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0261">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="757" who="S0262">okay good erm so</u>
<u n="758" who="S0261" trans="overlap">is this for the record?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="761" who="S0262">cos it's bigger picture stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0261">fine</u>
<u n="763" who="S0262">erm <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> we are hopefully having <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in December</u>
<u n="764" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="765" who="S0262">so I think we've agreed we're not going back to <anon type="place"/> for Christmas</u>
<u n="766" who="S0261">no that's right</u>
<u n="767" who="S0262">we'll stay here</u>
<u n="768" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="769" who="S0262">and it will be you know our last Christmas here for some time</u>
<u n="770" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="771" who="S0262">so it's gonna be good</u>
<u n="772" who="S0261">timing</u>
<u n="773" who="S0262">er we're gonna I'm gonna try and store up as much annual leave between August's annual leave which was three weeks but I won't take off any annual leave between September October November try and store it all up for December if I can</u>
<u n="774" who="S0261"><unclear>uhu</unclear></u>
<u n="775" who="S0262">erm and then erm</u>
<u n="776" who="S0261">maybe you'll wanna <trunc>s</trunc> mention to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that your plans aren't longer term to stay here</u>
<u n="777" who="S0262">look if he wants to come out here just</u>
<u n="778" who="S0261">just as long as he knows <pause dur="short"/> it would be disappointing for him to find out he was hoping to be in some place to get to <trunc>b</trunc></u>
<u n="779" who="S0262" trans="overlap">needed a swap <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0261">get to know his sister better</u>
<u n="781" who="S0262">we went to <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0261">mm mm I know</u>
<u n="783" who="S0262">but that's alright because we could come out and visit him</u>
<u n="784" who="S0261">yeah but you know what I mean</u>
<u n="785" who="S0262">erm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0261">yes that's right</u>
<u n="787" who="S0262">but what it what it does mean is I would like to work on my father erm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0261">beg your pardon?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0262">to well work on my father I mean I wanna wanna find out when he's thinking of coming out to see us again in Australia and when suits us for him to come</u>
<u n="790" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="791" who="S0262">which clearly wouldn't be er Christmas because we well unless <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes and stays with her sister which I don't think's a good idea erm er you know we'd want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> here kind of thing</u>
<u n="792" who="S0261">that's right</u>
<u n="793" who="S0262">so which is slightly problematic because I'm not entirely sure when I'd get a good dose of annual leave unless it was about you know taking annual leave while I'm pregnant I mean annual leave meaning maternity leave when I'm at the later stage of things yeah? in terms of pregnancy erm and that would might be helpful</u>
<u n="794" who="S0261">sorry I haven't understood that</u>
<u n="795" who="S0262">oh okay so annual leave is only three weeks a year <unclear/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0261">is it nor four?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0262">three or four it's not very long</u>
<u n="798" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="801" who="S0262">if I'm trying to store it all up for December when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes</u>
<u n="802" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="803" who="S0262">and my father can't come out at that time</u>
<u n="804" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="805" who="S0262">but my father should come and see us again</u>
<u n="806" who="S0261">yes in between yes</u>
<u n="807" who="S0262">so I need to find a time to accommodate him because I don't want to be going to work every single day ignoring him</u>
<u n="808" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that that that's right so if you're working from September October November December that's four months so that's a quarter of your annual leave entitlement</u>
<u n="809" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0261">for the year that you've earned</u>
<u n="811" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="812" who="S0261">so so that is about a week</u>
<u n="813" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="814" who="S0261">right? and through that Christmas period typically a week is about how much you need to to get you through that whole period</u>
<u n="815" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0261">yeah? erm and then <pause dur="short"/> and then let's say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> comes out four months after that post-summer pre-winter April</u>
<u n="817" who="S0262">cos it's a bit cooler</u>
<u n="818" who="S0261">when it's a wee bit cooler</u>
<u n="819" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="820" who="S0261">he would probably like that</u>
<u n="821" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="822" who="S0261">and it's a lot more calmer less windy rainy and all of that erm then er then</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
