<text id="S87R">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:21:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-09</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0432 S0503</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home (Potton, Bedfordshire)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Babies, feeding babies, other family members</topics>
		<activity>Sisters talking about babies</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0432">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>White British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands/ East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Gamlingay, Cambridgeshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Chinese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0503">
				<exactage>22</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands/ East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Potton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Maternity Leave</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- GCSE</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0503">yeah she came around and she was like erm I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like saw her in Tesco's or something and he said about going around to see me cos I'm on my own all day but she didn't like text before oh dear</u>
<u n="2" who="S0432" trans="overlap">is this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0503">yeah erm but she didn't text before so she just like knocked on the door and sort of turned up</u>
<u n="4" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0503">erm but then she was saying like erm she said oh I've not seen him in two weeks blah de blah and I was thinking well you could bloody come around and see him then</u>
<u n="6" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0503">you don't have to like I'm not always gonna go to you erm and then erm <pause dur="short"/> what was she saying? erm <pause dur="short"/> she was making things about cos she was apparently everyone was saying he's like really big and she was like I don't think he's very big erm in fact he's not big at all is he really? and I was like well he is really heavy like and he weighs a lot for</u>
<u n="8" who="S0432">he's big for his age isn't he?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0503">yeah on that erm box of Cow and Gate stuff he erm <pause dur="short"/> I think he's weighing about the same as a four-month-old if not more but he was at eight weeks he was weighing the same as a four-month-old</u>
<u n="10" who="S0432">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0503">right so now he's obviously more than that</u>
<u n="12" who="S0432">bless you</u>
<u n="13" who="S0503">and then she said that erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying that him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't fit in their like prams anymore and she was saying oh it's ridiculous all we need to do is like put like a cushion like in it so they can like sit up a little bit like there's plenty of room in there there's like</u>
<u n="14" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">won't be long</u>
<u n="15" who="S0503">see you later</u>
<u n="16" who="S0432">bye</u>
<u n="17" who="S0503">erm <pause dur="short"/> she's like there's plenty of room and I said and I said no he doesn't fit I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like put him in it <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> he said he looked like he was in a coffin cos like he's so wide and he said there's a tiny bit of green</u>
<u n="18" who="S0432" trans="overlap">this is the flat one?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0503">plus he don't really like it in there anyway like he much prefers it in that one and that one's suitable from birth anyway cos it reclines so he could have been in that from when he was born</u>
<u n="22" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0503">but we just got the carrycot cos I dunno why erm and then she was like oh okay then and then she was like well maybe he's only like bigger because whereas like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets to lie on the floor and like kick his arms and legs about and use all his energy up he can't here can he cos of the dogs? and I was thinking so what are you basically saying he's like fat and lazy then just cos of dogs?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="25" who="S0503">and I was thinking erm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0432" trans="overlap">he no I don't think can you even over feed a child that much?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0503">no I said he has what he has and he uses more energy by like trying to sit up like than like we'll like stand like holding him and sort of</u>
<u n="28" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0503">standing him up and that like so he's gonna</u>
<u n="30" who="S0432" trans="overlap">he uses energy</u>
<u n="31" who="S0503">have like yeah I know and I was thinking oh do you know she's just making it sound like <pause dur="short"/> oh I was just thinking oh shut up</u>
<u n="32" who="S0432" trans="overlap">just ignore her</u>
<u n="33" who="S0503">I can't remember what else she said as well before and I was just thinking oh just please shut up like and then he kept crying and erm he was due a feed in about forty minutes so I said right I'll go and get his bottle ready then erm I was in the kitchen and I could hear her going you're not hungry you're not hungry and I was like you haven't been here how the hell do you know when he's due a feed? he is hungry I know he's hungry because I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0432" trans="overlap">even if she had been here she I don't think there's any</u>
<u n="35" who="S0503" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0432">there's she's got no place to say I know she's I know I said the other day she's a <pause dur="short"/> a grandma and a mother but really?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0503">no I was thinking he is hungry he's not far off a feed <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0432" trans="overlap"><unclear>is he allowed</unclear> a cuddle?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0503">yeah he needs burping actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0432">burping</u>
<u n="41" who="S0503">and then she was saying <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0432"><unclear/> baby <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="43" who="S0503">yeah and he was like crying and stuff and she kept like holding him in ways that he doesn't like you holding him like well apart from when he's like</u>
<u n="44" who="S0432" trans="overlap">not like a baby</u>
<u n="45" who="S0503">when he's like really tired and he needs to go to sleep</u>
<u n="46" who="S0432" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what are you doing?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0503">like he likes being held like that</u>
<u n="48" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0503">but not all the time and then erm I was like he wants to go in his bouncer and play cos he'd been like groggy all day but like because he'd actually woken up and I don't think he was tired because he'd been asleep <unclear/> wants to play now <unclear/> so I put him in his bouncer with the toys on and he like shut up <unclear/> sort of like that</u>
<u n="50" who="S0432">yeah you do know what you're doing</u>
<u n="51" who="S0503">and then that was like the first time she's ever seen him in his bouncer apparently <unclear/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0432">is it? <pause dur="short"/> how old is he?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0503">eleven weeks ago</u>
<u n="54" who="S0432">eleven <trunc>wee</trunc> it was today isn't it? oh</u>
<u n="55" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0432">I keep forgetting it's Friday</u>
<u n="57" who="S0503">so it just really annoyed me and I was just <unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0432" trans="overlap">eleven weeks <pause dur="short"/> just I know it's hard like and there's always gonna be family members that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0503">my mum says <unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0503">like when she was saying oh I haven't seen him for <unclear/> and then she <unclear/> time and I was thinking well bloody come around more often</u>
<u n="62" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0503">this is the first time you've come around for like a month</u>
<u n="64" who="S0432" trans="overlap">does she what did she say that you shouldn't leave it so <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0503">yeah and I was just thinking <unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0432" trans="overlap">well it's not your fault that they've not come enough <pause dur="short"/> burp <pause dur="short"/> is auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not doing it very well?</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="67" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0432">what are these noises?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0503">just keep rubbing</u>
<u n="70" who="S0432">chunky monkey</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0432">oh I'm sorry I love you really <pause dur="short"/> oh oh</u>
<u n="73" who="S0503">we've been watching the Walking Dead today</u>
<u n="74" who="S0432"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh have you?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0503" trans="overlap">and I was like I hope you don't turn <unclear>her</unclear> into like a psycho</u>
<u n="76" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0503"><unclear/> buttercups</u>
<u n="79" who="S0432">yeah and puppy paws whatever that programme?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0503">Paw Patrol <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0432">Paw Patrol <vocal desc="laugh"/> Puppy Paw <pause dur="short"/> it was close</u>
<u n="82" who="S0503">he was watching Noddy this morning <shift new="singing"/> Noddy <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0432">oh I can't believe is that still on or is it like a?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0503">it's a different version and I don't think I don't ever remember it though to be honest</u>
<u n="85" who="S0432">is it with erm what's his name Noel Edmonds <pause dur="short"/> edmonds?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0503">I dunno</u>
<u n="87" who="S0432">Noel <unclear/></u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="88" who="S0432">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0503">that was like it's like shocked you as well his face just went oh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that was so loud</u>
<u n="91" who="S0503">he did a burp in my face and it was like it absolutely stank I thought I was gonna be sick and I was like er</u>
<u n="92" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0503">disgusting <pause dur="short"/> and then he did a massive one in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s face this morning but he said it didn't smell and I was like good job it didn't cos it was like the loudest burp ever</u>
<u n="94" who="S0432" trans="overlap">definitely a lad</u>
<u n="95" who="S0503">yep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0432">he's starting early is that all of them? or are you just holding them all in?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0503"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're so warm do I need to carry on? <pause dur="short"/> are you moving yourself? you're moving yourself <pause dur="short"/> I love his pyjamas or his top</u>
<u n="99" who="S0503"><unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0432">oh it's like a</u>
<u n="101" who="S0503">erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0432">oh no wait that's a <vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought it was like</u>
<u n="103" who="S0503"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's his erm vest thing</u>
<u n="104" who="S0432" trans="overlap">bless him <pause dur="short"/> that's so</u>
<u n="105" who="S0503" trans="overlap">he started singing Bare Necessities and I was like no no no that's Lion King and I was thinking no it isn't Lion King's Hakuna Matata</u>
<u n="106" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0503">but then I can only remember <shift new="singing"/> look for the bare necessities the <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0432"><shift new="singing"/> the simple bare necessities forget about your worries and your strife <shift new="normal"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <shift new="singing"/> the bare necessities the simple bare necessities forget about your worries and your strife <shift new="normal"/> that's all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0503">I know I <unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0432">that's all I know</u>
<u n="111" who="S0503">daddy knows more doesn't he?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0503">he's better at singing <pause dur="short"/> daddy's better at singing</u>
<u n="114" who="S0432">what other Disney songs are there? do you know? <vocal desc="laugh"/> so smiley I swear you've grown in like three days though are you still getting bigger? are you?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0503">well they're all pre-six clothes and they're not exactly big on him are they?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0432">no <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> has auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> been stealing cuddles from you?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0503">yeah she has missed him <unclear/> didn't she?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0432">have you had cuddles from auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I'm your best</u>
<u n="119" who="S0503"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> she was like we must must must make more time like to do stuff with the boys <unclear/> disappeared and I thought oh</u>
<u n="120" who="S0432" trans="overlap">whoops</u>
<u n="121" who="S0503"><unclear/> I'm up to that point <unclear/> going round</u>
<u n="122" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah I suppose <unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0503">I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm not <unclear/> obviously <unclear>be out</unclear> tonight so but <unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0503"><unclear/> erm but I thought at least she's noticed sort of thing</u>
<u n="126" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's true <pause dur="short"/> at least it might mean that she might make an effort</u>
<u n="127" who="S0503">yeah she was like there's a baby group in <anon type="place"/> on Tuesday and she was like it's two pound like <unclear/> she said apparently it's quite a good one and then she was like the baby sensory ones are going so you get to meet them before you start the baby sensory with him <unclear/> there</u>
<u n="128" who="S0432">what is all that stuff like play like feel?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0503">baby sensory?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0503">yeah I think so I think she creates sort of like</u>
<u n="132" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0503">environments and stuff that like stimulates <unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0432">have you got to be up early? yeah?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0503" trans="overlap">well he can stay in bed until I can get ready and then he can get up</u>
<u n="136" who="S0432">yeah yeah do that</u>
<u n="137" who="S0503">and I'll have to get myself out of bed and it's hard to get him up when <unclear>he's not</unclear> if he's asleep honestly</u>
<u n="138" who="S0432">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0503"><unclear>got</unclear> to be earlier than him</u>
<u n="140" who="S0432">you've got to let mummy sleep through the night</u>
<u n="141" who="S0503">I'm scared he won't sleep through tonight cos he's only he's gonna have to have a feed cos he's had this at half four unless he has another one at like half six and half eight so he has sort of then that's only two hours between feeds</u>
<u n="142" who="S0432">so when does he usually have them like throughout the day?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0503">he has one say he has one at like five</u>
<u n="144" who="S0432">in the morning?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0503">yeah then like nine twelve three six and then like eight say on average</u>
<u n="146" who="S0432">like nine and twelve three six and eight</u>
<u n="147" who="S0503">but when he was waking up at about say two three o'clock he'd still have sometimes he'd have seven bottles other times he'd have a longer stretch between so he wouldn't have like three-hour gaps so</u>
<u n="148" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0503">he was still getting sort of six to seven bottles</u>
<u n="150" who="S0432">yeah so before he was having one between like eight and five <pause dur="short"/> at night?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0503" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no so he has his last one like originally his times were like for sleeping through on the night say he goes to bed at say eight he'd wake up at like sort of two-ish and then it started going to three and then this past week he's started going until five</u>
<u n="152" who="S0432">oh okay so he</u>
<u n="153" who="S0503" trans="overlap">but then last night he slept through until seven so he's not had that night feed so he's not had as many feeds today</u>
<u n="154" who="S0432">oh yeah I see yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0503">like but sometimes when he's slept like if he woke up say at about three so he had one at three in the morning <pause dur="short"/> five <pause dur="short"/> then like sort of nine twelve <pause dur="short"/> four <pause dur="short"/> maybe <trunc>s</trunc> well yeah he'd usually have sort of like oh I can't work it out cos I'm too tired</u>
<u n="156" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I can't even <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm sorry did I scare did you see him?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0503">no</u>
<u n="158" who="S0432">he just went</u>
<u n="159" who="S0503">oh he was startled</u>
<u n="160" who="S0432">sorry was that too loud?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0503">yeah but he'd usually have sort of seven to six bottles but recently it's been six because he's going that little bit longer at night without one</u>
<u n="162" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0503">because he went from seven last night today it's been seven ten and one sort of four so maybe like seven seven and that's only five bottles and that's an earlier bottle as well so unless I can try and squeeze another one in between now and sort of eight so he has sort of two-hour gaps between them</u>
<u n="164" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0503">rather than three</u>
<u n="166" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0503">cos otherwise I'm not I don't know if he'll sleep through because he's had like there's seven ounces less than usual</u>
<u n="168" who="S0432" trans="overlap">so he's had four so far today?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0432">but by this time he would have had five or six?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0503" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0432">no five</u>
<u n="173" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0503">so I'm not</u>
<u n="176" who="S0432" trans="overlap">so he's only got one more to fit in?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0432">technically</u>
<u n="179" who="S0503">really but then say he starts getting hungry about like half six cos he hasn't seemed to have been lasting three hours today for some reason erm <pause dur="short"/> so he might still want the same amount of he might think I've slept through but I still want the same amount that I would have had</u>
<u n="180" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0503">so the gaps are getting shorter sort of thing cos I gave him eight ounces this morning which he like drank all of but then the ten o'clock one I did another eight but he only had six</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="182" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0503">so then it averages out at seven ounces anyway so then I've just made</u>
<u n="184" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="185" who="S0503">seven-ounce ones at one and four</u>
<u n="186" who="S0432">but he had six is that what you're saying?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0503">no he usually has seven</u>
<u n="188" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I'm slightly lost oh okay</u>
<u n="189" who="S0503">he has seven all day apart from eight before bed but like because he'd gone so long last night I gave him eight this morning <unclear/> but then the next morning he only had six so it still averages out at seven</u>
<u n="190" who="S0432">oh okay I see yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0503">so it's not because I was gonna try and give him an extra ounce in every feed so that he's not technically missing a bottle and gave him</u>
<u n="192" who="S0432" trans="overlap">but he just wasn't drinking?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0503">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0432">you know what she's doing</u>
<u n="195" who="S0503" trans="overlap">so I may try and fit another feed in</u>
<u n="196" who="S0432" trans="overlap">you're just gonna wake him up at two in the morning? <pause dur="short"/> mm?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0503">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that is the thing like if he wakes in the night now I'm not gonna know whether like I said whether it's cos we've been at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <pause dur="short"/> like he's not gonna have like a bottle feed like I don't know <trunc>whe</trunc>where he's gonna sleep</u>
<u n="198" who="S0432">yeah you don't know if it's like disruption of</u>
<u n="199" who="S0503" trans="overlap">and like he's gonna be in the lounge as well</u>
<u n="200" who="S0432">routine</u>
<u n="201" who="S0503" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0432">going to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or the fact that he slept so well last night and missed a bottle</u>
<u n="203" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0432">what do you think? <pause dur="short"/> what do you think?</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="205" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0503">because like as I said I don't know what's happened with like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <unclear/> this morning they slept through and she said she was like I'm so jealous she was like erm she was like I'm starting to think am I doing something wrong? I said to be honest I don't think we've done anything differently like he has a lot of milk and they do say that when they get to certain weights they like drop a feed so it might be that he's dropping the night feed</u>
<u n="207" who="S0432">yeah so he might be alright anyway</u>
<u n="208" who="S0503">yeah but then also I said it could just be a phase like I don't expect I still expect him to get up at like two o'clock so anything later is a bonus really</u>
<u n="209" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0503">because otherwise I'd be really like gutted if he started waking up at like three again</u>
<u n="211" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0503">erm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0432">he's just got the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> gene and likes sleeping all the time don't you?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0503" trans="overlap">but erm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0432">just like your aunties and your grandparents</u>
<u n="216" who="S0503">yeah then she was saying like oh I've got him into such a routine and she was like I don't know if it's just routine for him waking up and I'm like it's probably the problem</u>
<u n="217" who="S0432">what? does she wake him up?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0503">no but like <pause dur="short"/> because like his routine in the day is like is the same every single day with nap times and food times every single day is exactly the same</u>
<u n="219" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh is it?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0503">times and stuff so it's like well then his it probably is a routine for him whereas his nap times in the day if he's awake and happy I'll leave him awake when I know he starts getting tired I'll try and get him to sleep if he's hungry like less than three hours I don't like to give him too much but if he's really screaming I'd be like well sod it you're gonna have to have it then</u>
<u n="221" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0503" trans="overlap">or if he goes a little bit longer between a feed I'll let him go a bit longer</u>
<u n="223" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0503">so it's not like</u>
<u n="225" who="S0432">yeah like he's like dictating it to you</u>
<u n="226" who="S0503">yeah like I think with</u>
<u n="227" who="S0432" trans="overlap">which is not a bad thing I don't think</u>
<u n="228" who="S0503" trans="overlap">no I mean I know eventually we'll have we'll have to start trying again into some sort of routine but</u>
<u n="229" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah but right now I think</u>
<u n="230" who="S0503" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0432">you seem to be doing it well</u>
<u n="232" who="S0503">I'm just sort of listening to him at the minute and</u>
<u n="233" who="S0432" trans="overlap">he's happy</u>
<u n="234" who="S0503">he's like been like like like I said I don't think we've done anything differently for him to sleep through he's just started going a little bit longer cos every morning we'll wake up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be like what time have you fed him? and I'll be like I haven't yet</u>
<u n="235" who="S0432">really?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0503">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is like really? and I'm like yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0432" trans="overlap">what cos he thinks you would have got up in the night?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0432">would he not wake up for that though?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0503">for what his night?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0503">who <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0432">would he not even notice that you've woken up to feed him?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0503">he doesn't sometimes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0432">oh God <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0503">most of the time he does but <trunc>becau</trunc> he used to when I used to make it all like fresh and stuff but I've stopped doing that now</u>
<u n="247" who="S0432">what do you do?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0503">refill the bottle up and so we go to bed at like eleven I fill the</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="249" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0503">I fill that up with boiling water <vocal desc="laugh"/> have you been shouting?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0432">are you trying to explain too?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0503">what are you saying? eh? oh oh</u>
<u n="253" who="S0432">do you reckon he's a bit like I wanna sit up?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0503">he's trying now</u>
<u n="255" who="S0432">are you trying? <unclear/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0503" trans="overlap">yeah I fill that up with erm <pause dur="short"/> cos I do eight ounces before bed but night feeds I just do seven ounces</u>
<u n="257" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0503">erm I fill it up with seven ounces of boiling water put it in his thermal bag thing and</u>
<u n="259" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="260" who="S0503">take a formula pot out and then when it gets to his night feed I just like take out the thermal bag and put the formula in it's obviously with him sleeping through it's cold</u>
<u n="261" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0503">so I will come down and tip a bit out and top it up with a bit of boiling water and then put it in</u>
<u n="263" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0503">so it's the right sort of temperature I mean I know I shouldn't do that but <unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0432">well he seems to be fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0503">and like if it's like say he sleeps till three and it is cold but it's not been cold <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0503">like but if he's not had a feed and like I think I'll give him a warmer breakfast <pause dur="short"/> but yeah he is fine so</u>
<u n="269" who="S0432">yeah well like our <trunc>par</trunc> like our generation of parents does that make sense? <vocal desc="laugh"/> they did it like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mum said that she'd put stuff in the fridge and then</u>
<u n="270" who="S0503" trans="overlap">oh I was gonna ask how is she getting on?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0432">yeah I think she's alright</u>
<u n="272" who="S0503">is she starting to speak better now or not?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0432">I don't know I'm going I was gonna go around there yesterday but she was going out at six and she was like oh there's not gonna be enough time for us to catch up <pause dur="short"/> as in there's not gonna be enough time for her to tell me everything</u>
<u n="274" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="275" who="S0503">oh yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0432">oh yeah erm so I'm going over on Tuesday after work and I'll find out she hasn't said anything else apart from she just sent me a few photos of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in some dresses</u>
<u n="277" who="S0503">let me see</u>
<u n="278" who="S0432">there's a better photo of her but it's in black and white and I felt really bad cos I was like well maybe it looks good cos it's</u>
<u n="279" who="S0503">edit</u>
<u n="280" who="S0432">edited yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0503">filter</u>
<u n="282" who="S0432">filter <pause dur="short"/> so it looks like her bruises <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> on her eyes have gone but I don't know if that was the <trunc>pho</trunc> erm because it was black and white</u>
<u n="283" who="S0503">mm</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="284" who="S0503">uh-oh</u>
<u n="285" who="S0432">are you joining in? <pause dur="short"/> you've got cold hands <pause dur="short"/> baby <pause dur="short"/> what is going on with my phone?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0503"><unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0432">this is one this is a black and white one <pause dur="short"/> her hair looks a bit bald</u>
<u n="288" who="S0503">oh yeah it looks like it's not</u>
<u n="289" who="S0432">it's a bit straggly</u>
<u n="290" who="S0503">fallen out at the front but it's like it's sort of comes from the back to like cover it yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah like a comb forward instead of a comb over</u>
<u n="292" who="S0503">and I think you're cute I think you are</u>
<u n="293" who="S0432">he looks I think he <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looks more like a baby</u>
<u n="294" who="S0503" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0432">I know that sounds stupid <pause dur="short"/> but that's</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="296" who="S0503"><unclear/> tiny</u>
<u n="297" who="S0432">yeah she is</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="298" who="S0503">what is up with you?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0432" trans="overlap">these are the recent ones <pause dur="short"/> do you need to sleep?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0503">she doesn't have a baby nose does she?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0432">no maybe that's it</u>
<u n="302" who="S0503">like babies always have a flat sort of button nose whereas hers looks like a normal person's</u>
<u n="303" who="S0432">yeah I think it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s nose that she's got but and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s face</u>
<u n="304" who="S0503">his mum says they don't usually have like the bridge of their nose and stuff like yet</u>
<u n="305" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0503">but I think that she <unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0432" trans="overlap">she does you can tell in that photo I don't know if it's the light</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="308" who="S0432">what's the matter? do you need sleep?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0503"><unclear/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0432" trans="overlap">was that a yes? did you just say yes?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0503">oh</u>
<u n="312" who="S0432">let's bounce you oh</u>
<u n="313" who="S0503">bottles and pyjamas I have to do</u>
<u n="314" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="315" who="S0503">you see I don't know if I should try him in his grobag but then I'm like if he doesn't sleep I don't know whether it's cos he won't be tucked in and he doesn't like a grobag?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0432">what is yeah maybe not tonight maybe tomorrow is that like a sleeping bag?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0503">yeah it like zips up and it's like over there and then just</u>
<u n="318" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0503">it zips up like that</u>
<u n="320" who="S0432" trans="overlap">they're cute aren't they?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0503">yeah cos he did kick all his blankets off but I think I tucked him in a bit better last night cos usually I put I did a blanket and then a sheet but the sheet's quite small cos it always just he'd pull it out but I put the blanket underneath and then the blanket is really long and I tucked that under so I think that'll hold the sheet in a bit more so he was still tucked in this morning</u>
<u n="322" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="323" who="S0503">unless he just wasn't as wriggly cos that one night Wednesday night when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to pool and when he got back he had to retuck him in cos he'd shoved up the bed a bit</u>
<u n="324" who="S0432">is that because he gets really hot and he doesn't wanna be in the</u>
<u n="325" who="S0503" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="326" who="S0432">in the <trunc>qu</trunc> in the blanket?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0503"><unclear/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0432">if he's anything like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0503">yeah I know</u>
<u n="330" who="S0432">for the cold</u>
<u n="331" who="S0503" trans="overlap">then I always think he has a few blankets on and like a little vest and sleepsuit yet we're in like pyjamas with a massive quilt on us</u>
<u n="332" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0503">and I sometimes get into bed and think oh it's chilly</u>
<u n="334" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh <unclear>who's <trunc>wrig</trunc></unclear> you're so wriggly <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0503">like he's started being sick as well a bit recently and I don't know whether he's having too much milk for his belly but like he obviously is still hungry and he has it all</u>
<u n="336" who="S0432" trans="overlap">is it anything to do with the fast teat? oh that would have hurt</u>
<u n="337" who="S0503" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="338" who="S0432">he just put his head into my earring</u>
<u n="339" who="S0503">oh he always head-butts me</u>
<u n="340" who="S0432">is it do you reckon he's getting like too much too ah <pause dur="short"/> too much too quick?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0503" trans="overlap">it might be it might just be that it's too much milk for his belly cos he was falling asleep in the other one so I made it that's two <unclear/> I should probably get very <unclear/> teats but they're well expensive so <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah I can imagine what is that based on like how they suck it?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0503">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0432">you just wanted to see me? did you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> did you? and what's happened to your top again? I pulled that down <pause dur="short"/> mr wriggly bum <pause dur="short"/> tickle tickle tickle <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
