<text id="S8CB">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:15:35</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-12-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0592 S0593 S0594</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON/ANON/ANON's house, Surrey</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Internet game, mood, psychology, Christmas, travel, work, university, science</topics>
		<activity>Family having a general conversation</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, requesting, apologising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0592">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Frimley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Camberley (home) Lancaster (uni)</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years / 3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0593">
				<exactage>53</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English - mix of south eastern and north west</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Camberley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>27 years 6  months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0594">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Frimley, Surrey</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Camberley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 roughly</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0592">right so basically er he he was the <foreign lang="ita">consigliore</foreign> which</u>
<u n="2" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0592">I I know it's it's Italian cos like he was in the mafia basically</u>
<u n="4" who="S0593">oh okay</u>
<u n="5" who="S0592">and and what the what the <foreign lang="ita">consigliore</foreign> does it's really cool erm because there's two <trunc>si</trunc> no there's more than two sides in this game but for simplicity we'll say there's two sides</u>
<u n="6" who="S0593">what's the game called?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0592">Town of Salem</u>
<u n="8" who="S0593">oh yeah you've been playing that for years haven't you?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0592">no not years for a while like</u>
<u n="10" who="S0593" trans="overlap">but that's that's the one isn't it? where you <pause dur="short"/> you have to like hunt out who is doing the murders or yeah? I know</u>
<u n="11" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah and it's fun cos each time you play the game you get a random role <pause dur="short"/> so you you know what your role is but no one else does and no one else knows each other's each other's roles except members of the mafia and vampires</u>
<u n="12" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="13" who="S0592">erm but basically what a <foreign lang="ita">consigliore</foreign> does is it's like it's like the mafia's <trunc>i</trunc> version of the investigator because the investigator is a town role</u>
<u n="14" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0592">and the investigator what they can do is they check a target each night and they can find two or three possible roles that that target is so for example if a target was a serial killer see there's loads of roles but if the target was a serial killer the investigator would get your targets covered in blood they're either a doctor a vampire or a serial killer</u>
<u n="16" who="S0593">oh charming</u>
<u n="17" who="S0592">so you you have to guess which one they are based on like other people getting information erm but the <foreign lang="ita">consigliore</foreign> what they can do is they can get the exact role</u>
<u n="18" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0592">so they they're more powerful than the investigator but they're also on the bad side so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0593">ah not so good</u>
<u n="21" who="S0592">but they can <trunc>so</trunc></u>
<u n="22" who="S0593" trans="overlap">didn't you always used to get killed off in this though really early?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0592">not not all the time I I had bad luck yesterday though I I had some weird games I had one game where <pause dur="short"/> they're I think they were using bots or something?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0593">using what?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0592">bots</u>
<u n="26" who="S0593">bots</u>
<u n="27" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0593">as in robots?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0592">yeah so someone was using a bot or something and they were doing something weird like I dunno if they were hacking or whatever but they were doing something weird with the game</u>
<u n="30" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0592">and basically there's this role called the mayor which might be obvious cos it's a town but erm <pause dur="short"/> what the mayor can do because when the investigator investigates the mayor it comes up as mayor godfather or vampire hunter and <pause dur="short"/> if you know <trunc>p</trunc>people generally they want the major to reveal themselves cos otherwise they're likely to be the godfather and the godfather's a member of the mafia</u>
<u n="32" who="S0593">it just seems like <pause dur="short"/> one role has so many different roles within it</u>
<u n="33" who="S0592">no not really what what's confusing you?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0593">everything</u>
<u n="35" who="S0592"><trunc>o</trunc>okay</u>
<u n="36" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0592">well I I don't I don't I don't see how <pause dur="short"/> you think one role has loads of different roles what</u>
<u n="38" who="S0593">well you've just said that something comes up and it can be the three different things</u>
<u n="39" who="S0592">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm that that's the <trunc>invest</trunc> the investigator the investigator investigates the mayor</u>
<u n="40" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0592">the mayor will appear to the investigator as either the mayor the godfather or the vampire hunter because the mayor doesn't get the exact role</u>
<u n="42" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="43" who="S0592">which is why the major has to <trunc>tr</trunc> reveal themselves to prove that they're actually good and not the godfather</u>
<u n="44" who="S0593">okay so what's actually what's the best role to have?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0592">oh it <trunc>de</trunc> it <trunc>de</trunc> it depends on what you like to do <pause dur="short"/> erm personally I like to be the spy the spy is quite fun</u>
<u n="46" who="S0593">is it?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0592">what the spy can do is they can read mafia chat but they can't actually see who the members of the mafia are cos that would just be overpowered</u>
<u n="48" who="S0593">is that like helpful at all?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0592">it is it is helpful erm because you can <pause dur="short"/> if you're if you're quite good I think I'm quite good as being the spy but you can kind of see how people type and then compare it to people typing during the day</u>
<u n="50" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0592">so if you if you think someone's typing a certain way you think oh I've been reading mafia chat this person types exactly like someone in the mafia I think they're a member of the mafia</u>
<u n="52" who="S0593">yeah okay</u>
<u n="53" who="S0592">that has worked</u>
<u n="54" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0592">also some people are a bit silly probably cos they're new and sometimes they end up saying their names not realising that there's a spy in the game <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have you ever done that?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0592">I've I've done I haven't done that I have done something stupid though erm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0593" trans="overlap"><unclear>what?</unclear></u>
<u n="59" who="S0592">erm basically one time the godfather got jailed the first night and I went oh no the godfather's jailed and there was a spy and they said whoever you jailed first night was the godfather I'm like <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="60" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0592">I was like I I <trunc>ca</trunc> I shouldn't do that again I should just have a poker face and not say anything</u>
<u n="62" who="S0593">I think what you were saying about erm watching how people type <pause dur="short"/> I think people do type and text in in their own style it's almost like erm <pause dur="short"/> their voice</u>
<u n="63" who="S0592">yeah I <trunc>mea</trunc></u>
<u n="64" who="S0593" trans="overlap">they're voice but in</u>
<u n="65" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0593">text</u>
<u n="67" who="S0592">yesterday yesterday was funny because erm I was actually an executioner and the executioner is</u>
<u n="68" who="S0593">boo hiss</u>
<u n="69" who="S0592">the executioner is a neutral role but the a neutral evil role so</u>
<u n="70" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how can you be a neutral and evil at the same time?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0592">because because <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>r</trunc> I'm trying to think the <trunc>ex</trunc> the executioner can win with anyone as long as they get their target lynched but the target is always a member of the town that's why they're evil</u>
<u n="72" who="S0593">okay it just seems a bit screwy to me but go on I'll I'll</u>
<u n="73" who="S0592" trans="overlap">they they they're neutral because they don't really have allegiances with anyone in particular just they just have a vendetta against that one person that they want to get lynched</u>
<u n="74" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="75" who="S0592">erm that's why they're neutral and that's why they're evil at the same time because they're trying to get a member of the town lynched <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah but I I was an executioner and I noticed that someone had spelt their name wrong in the game <pause dur="short"/> and then I looked cos when when people kill they can leave a death note</u>
<u n="76" who="S0593">oh right</u>
<u n="77" who="S0592">that appears</u>
<u n="78" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0592">erm and I noticed that in the death note they had spelt something incorrectly they spelt only as onely basically</u>
<u n="80" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0592">I don't know I don't know I don't know if their first language is English <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="82" who="S0593">well maybe not</u>
<u n="83" who="S0592">maybe not but</u>
<u n="84" who="S0593">maybe they're more dyslexic than I am</u>
<u n="85" who="S0592">maybe but I I was half joking but half not joking and I basically said I basically said oh you know they misspelt this in their death note and this person can't spell their name coincidence? I think not erm and and and <trunc>so</trunc>some people were kind of with me and then someone said that that's a stupid you know stupid what what's the <trunc>phra</trunc> blueugh phrase I'm looking for?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0593">theory</u>
<u n="87" who="S0592">no it's a stupid line of reason that's what I was looking for</u>
<u n="88" who="S0593">oh okay</u>
<u n="89" who="S0592">and I didn't think it was erm but then that person <pause dur="short"/> the person I was accusing got killed by a veteran erm and then it turns out they they're with the mafioso so I was completely correct even though I was completely bullshitting</u>
<u n="90" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0594">oh yeah er by the way er</u>
<u n="92" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0594">just just just a warning just in case my mood is shit for the next <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how long while the side effects of the antidepressants kick in</u>
<u n="94" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="95" who="S0594">so yeah er sorry if I'm a bit moody</u>
<u n="96" who="S0593">is that what she warned you might happen it might get worse before it gets better?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0594">yeah I mean that that's what happened the first time I took them</u>
<u n="98" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0594">er the subsequent times I took them it wasn't so bad but this is the biggest gap that I've had between <pause dur="short"/> being <pause dur="short"/> off them and on them again so</u>
<u n="100" who="S0593">okay so what what warnings did she give you about it?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0594">she said that er</u>
<u n="102" who="S0593" trans="overlap">cos it sounds like quite a new med</u>
<u n="103" who="S0594">it it's exactly the same type of med that I was on before</u>
<u n="104" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0594">erm so it I I don't think it works any differently</u>
<u n="106" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0594">erm yeah she just said that I might feel a bit nauseous in the first few days which didn't ever actually happen to me before and that erm er my levels of you know agitation and anxiety will will probably go up er I think</u>
<u n="108" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah so it's gonna get worse before it gets better</u>
<u n="109" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0593">okay well</u>
<u n="111" who="S0592">but that should only last a couple of weeks if if that</u>
<u n="112" who="S0593">just just be aware that you know if you're being a complete and utter <pause dur="short"/> pillock that you will need to be told to calm down</u>
<u n="113" who="S0594">oh yeah I know</u>
<u n="114" who="S0593">and you know to go up to your room not sent up to your room like a naughty little boy but somewhere where you can calm down so hopefully you'll be on top of it by Christmas</u>
<u n="115" who="S0594">hopefully it's only</u>
<u n="116" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah it's gonna be</u>
<u n="117" who="S0594">it's only nine days</u>
<u n="118" who="S0593">yeah it's gonna be erm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0594">need to get some wrapping paper actually</u>
<u n="120" who="S0593">oh yeah but I can't see any that I like</u>
<u n="121" who="S0594">mm <pause dur="short"/> dunno <pause dur="short"/> where have you looked?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0593">Sainsbury's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0594">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0593"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got some didn't you?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0592">wrapping paper?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0592">well I picked it I didn't buy it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0593">no I know you didn't buy it I think erm <pause dur="short"/> possibly BHS normally has nice wrapping <trunc>pa</trunc> or it did last year anyway <pause dur="short"/> had nice wrapping paper</u>
<u n="129" who="S0594" trans="overlap">have to have to have to ask dad to fund that cos I've got no money I'll have some <pause dur="short"/> next week hopefully</u>
<u n="130" who="S0593">well that'll be plenty of time won't it?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0594">when the <unclear/> comes back in</u>
<u n="132" who="S0593">yeah that that'll be in time he's gonna send me some money for a taxi tomorrow</u>
<u n="133" who="S0594">that's good</u>
<u n="134" who="S0593">well it is it would have been <pause dur="short"/> better if he'd have <pause dur="short"/> just <pause dur="short"/> been able to drive in the morning <pause dur="short"/> but he's out for his Christmas do with his friends so</u>
<u n="135" who="S0592">yeah but that doesn't mean that at least he's given you a way to get there instead of just <unclear/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0593" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah no no that's fine <pause dur="short"/> he's going to pay for a taxi for me so you know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0592">that's yeah that's fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0593">yeah that's that's fine</u>
<u n="139" who="S0594">yeah yeah that's fine yeah yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="140" who="S0593" trans="overlap">but it doesn't look that difficult to get to on the bus actually</u>
<u n="141" who="S0594">what to <anon type="place"/>? <pause dur="short"/> you'd probably have to change buses wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah but I mean all told the journey takes about forty minutes <pause dur="short"/> if the buses and that turn up on time</u>
<u n="143" who="S0592">I would just take a taxi personally</u>
<u n="144" who="S0594" trans="overlap">what do you do? do you get do you get the bus into?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0593">oh no I'll take a taxi tomorrow I I won't take the chance then</u>
<u n="146" who="S0594" trans="overlap">what what what do you do do do you get the bus into <anon type="place"/> and then change there or get on the number four</u>
<u n="147" who="S0593" trans="overlap">no erm opposite way bus into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0594">oh</u>
<u n="149" who="S0593">and then get the bus erm I think it said the bus heading towards <anon type="place"/> of all places</u>
<u n="150" who="S0594">oh okay</u>
<u n="151" who="S0593">erm the bus bus went into erm oops <pause dur="short"/> into <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so but yeah no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I will definitely get a taxi tomorrow I'm not taking chances of being late or what have you or <pause dur="short"/> like a drowned rat when I get there</u>
<u n="152" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0593">but I was speaking to you your dad about you know <pause dur="short"/> when I go back to work having help to get there and back because it is no fun <pause dur="short"/> standing at bus stops at minus eight degrees in the morning</u>
<u n="154" who="S0592">ah no no no</u>
<u n="155" who="S0593">no I <trunc>hav</trunc> I <trunc>ha</trunc> you know <trunc>we</trunc> it's dark and its cold and there's snow on the ground and <pause dur="short"/> I used to go I used to have to get the bus from out here about ten past seven no before that I used to leave here at five to seven get the bus at seven and then I'd get down to <anon type="place"/> and I'd have wait half an hour in minus eight degrees with erm snow on the ground for the next bus to turn up then when I got off at the other end I would have to walk ten to fifteen minutes up the hill <pause dur="short"/> to get into work that is</u>
<u n="156" who="S0592" trans="overlap">that that is</u>
<u n="157" who="S0593">but it's</u>
<u n="158" who="S0592">sounds like it sucks</u>
<u n="159" who="S0593">it did suck it was hard work and then on the way back because the buses stop running in the village at seven o'clock and I didn't finish work until eight <pause dur="short"/> I'd have to walk about two or three miles I think it's three miles from erm the care home <pause dur="short"/> into <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> wait at the bus stop for twenty minutes at the erm bus er bus stop in <anon type="place"/> hope it turns up on time and then get get back here so it would take me about an hour to get back to get home in the evening</u>
<u n="160" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0593">so it actually is about forty minutes all told on the bus including all bus journeys you know completely</u>
<u n="162" who="S0592">what this one now or?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0593">the the one now</u>
<u n="164" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="165" who="S0593">yeah so it should actually be quicker</u>
<u n="166" who="S0592">yeah isn't even though it's further away isn't it?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0593" trans="overlap">erm no it's just <pause dur="short"/> it's slightly further away but even so it would be nice if erm if your dad could <pause dur="short"/> manage to just get out of bed a little bit earlier cos even though it means he's getting out of bed a bit earlier it also means that I can stay in bed half an hour later and when you've been doing twelve hour shifts on <trunc>yo</trunc> on your feet all day that extra half an hour makes a big difference <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0592" trans="overlap">mm I mean I know I haven't been doing twelve hour shifts or anything but that's one thing I'm gonna miss about living on campus second year is the fact that I can have extra sleep and it only takes me fifteen minutes to get to to my lessons at most but when I'm gonna be living off campus I'm gonna have to get up early actually walk to the bus stop wait for the bus get a bus there and then I'm not going to just be able to go back in between lessons to have a nap</u>
<u n="169" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> or or just grab your lunch or something no that that is a nice thing cos I remember work working <pause dur="short"/> living in the nurses home when I was working at <anon type="place"/> and it was nice to be able to just go back and get what you needed you know have your lunch or have a half an hour's kip between</u>
<u n="170" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0593">you know your shift and what have you if you had time to have that because it was often so busy on the ward you often didn't actually get a break</u>
<u n="172" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0593">you know I mean legally you we're supposed to have a break but you often didn't have a break there's erm an in house joke about nurses having bladders like bin liners <pause dur="short"/> because they wait so long to go for a pee cos they never get time to go</u>
<u n="174" who="S0592">no</u>
<u n="175" who="S0593">you know so you you go hours and hours and hours I know that I have gone <pause dur="short"/> on duty and I've been there at half past six in the morning because of the way the buses have been running down the road I've been there at half past six no at seven to start at half seven I think it was and <pause dur="short"/> it's been some some days it's been like two two o'clock in the afternoon before I've even got near a toilet</u>
<u n="176" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0593">you know I've been busting to go but you just get kind of used to it I suppose</u>
<u n="178" who="S0592">yeah probably</u>
<u n="179" who="S0593">but then sometimes you end up with pains in your tummy you know those horrible pains you get in your tummy when you you need to go</u>
<u n="180" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0593">when you're busting for a wee</u>
<u n="182" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0593"><unclear/> it and then other days other days you're like no I can't wait any longer and you've just got to go</u>
<u n="184" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0593">but yeah so hopefully anyway getting backtracking to what we were saying hopefully your dad'll help me out getting there and back</u>
<u n="186" who="S0592">hopefully</u>
<u n="187" who="S0593">because when when you know like on bank holidays and what have you when the buses weren't running that early in the morning <pause dur="short"/> I used to have to pay about fifteen quid to get <pause dur="short"/> to get to work</u>
<u n="188" who="S0592">that's a lot</u>
<u n="189" who="S0593">it's a lot of money to get to work that's like three hours' pay</u>
<u n="190" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0593">you know so I might as well I said to them I said I might as well just not come in until ten o'clock</u>
<u n="192" who="S0592">weren't they alright with that though? didn't didn't they say that was okay</u>
<u n="193" who="S0593">no no no no you can't you can't do that they were alright for me to get in <pause dur="short"/> erm and a a Sunday erm the buses <pause dur="short"/> were they started late <pause dur="short"/> but I was only <pause dur="short"/> oh actually how late was I? <pause dur="short"/> no I I I ended up about half an hour late</u>
<u n="194" who="S0592">oh okay</u>
<u n="195" who="S0593">erm on on a Sunday and they were okay with that <pause dur="short"/> but a lot of the time somebody would see me standing at the bus stop that was driving there and they they would pick me up</u>
<u n="196" who="S0592" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="197" who="S0593">erm and get in the car but sometimes I wouldn't get a lift it was sometimes I wouldn't actually get in the car because there was a lot of erm <pause dur="short"/> there'd be too many people in the car already and most of them weren't strapped in or you know even if there was room in the car <pause dur="short"/> a lot of the they didn't strap in and I won't get in a car where people are not wearing seat belts</u>
<u n="198" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0593">you know it it's dangerous <pause dur="short"/> very very dangerous so I won't but yeah hopefully we'll see</u>
<u n="200" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0593">we'll see what happens I haven't got the job yet</u>
<u n="202" who="S0592">no but it's good to think ahead maybe try and think more optimistically <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0593">I have been so optimistic <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean I've been for interviews and one one man said to me <pause dur="short"/> he said you've handled <trunc>yo</trunc> he said thank you for being very open and honest about what's gone on he <pause dur="short"/> said and you have handled yourself with complete grace and dignity which I thought was a really nice thing to say</u>
<u n="204" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0593">guy I spoke to on the phone didn't get that job erm but I think I didn't get that job because I have too many skills</u>
<u n="206" who="S0592">what so they think you're overqualified?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0593">I'm definitely overqualified <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> even for this one I'm overqualified</u>
<u n="208" who="S0592">yeah it kinda sucks though because I I appreciate that employers don't want people who are overqualified cos maybe they feel that they won't be challenged enough or something like that</u>
<u n="209" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0592">but er obviously they're looking for a job they're desperate for a job if they're looking for positions where they're overqualified so I I don't know it it feels <trunc>e</trunc> <trunc>k</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I I understand but also feels <pause dur="short"/> not that fair either</u>
<u n="211" who="S0593">yeah because you also know that they can do the job</u>
<u n="212" who="S0592">yeah and instead you're gonna</u>
<u n="213" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah and they would be good at it</u>
<u n="214" who="S0592" trans="overlap">instead you're gonna be hiring someone who isn't as qualified but you think maybe won't get as bored I don't know if that's their thinking?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0593" trans="overlap">actually you know that's that's a very good point because the guy that I was just telling you about <pause dur="short"/> he said to me when he employs somebody there's got to be a two-way street he said you you have got to have something that you can offer us he said and I'm not going to even going to insult you ask you what skills you have he said because your skills are obviously in abundance he said your skills are coming out of your ears <pause dur="short"/> he said you have more than enough skills to do this job he said but the other side of the coins I have to have something to offer the erm offer you</u>
<u n="216" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0593">other other than a job</u>
<u n="218" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0593">and he said and I don't know what I've got to offer you</u>
<u n="220" who="S0592">I know I mean I don't know I I I thought it was too late to apply for any temporary job here anyway so I haven't bothered erm but you you you know how people say oh no one's too good to work in Mcdonald's or something like that</u>
<u n="221" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0592">I mean I mean there's an obvious reason why I wouldn't but</u>
<u n="223" who="S0593" trans="overlap">I've never heard that but carry on</u>
<u n="224" who="S0592">I I've heard it a lot of times I mean there's there's one obvious reason why I wouldn't work in Mcdonald's now erm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0593">you're not spotty enough <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0592">erm that's not what I was thinking but</u>
<u n="227" who="S0593">slap my wrist</u>
<u n="228" who="S0592">yeah but but but okay yeah okay</u>
<u n="229" who="S0593" trans="overlap">I I was only joking I was only yeah I didn't mean it</u>
<u n="230" who="S0592">but I would I would feel I would get so bored</u>
<u n="231" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0592">if I was to work in Mcdonald's <pause dur="short"/> I I don't I don't know it's not that I think I'm too good er er that might be a bit of a lie but erm cos obviously a job's a job and if you work in Mcdonald's you know you're earning money</u>
<u n="233" who="S0593">see now that's the way to look at it and that's the way I have to look at it with doing these care home jobs <pause dur="short"/> you know a a a job's a job and if it brings you in a bit more money and a bit more freedom you you've just got to deal with it haven't you? until something better comes along</u>
<u n="234" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah but I <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't think I would work in Mcdonald's though I wouldn't apply to work at Mcdonald's</u>
<u n="235" who="S0593">sometimes you have to start right at the bottom and work your way up</u>
<u n="236" who="S0592">I know I'm just saying I I would apply sooner to go and work in a grocery store rather than at Mcdonald's</u>
<u n="237" who="S0593">I would be actually quite happy to work in a grocery store</u>
<u n="238" who="S0592">why don't you apply for jobs at grocery stores?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0593">cos I did one of their stupid online assessment things that said to me no</u>
<u n="240" who="S0592">oh oh I hate I hate</u>
<u n="241" who="S0593" trans="overlap">actually I should get you to do the Tesco's one with me</u>
<u n="242" who="S0592">you that's not well you're not meant to you're meant to do it on your own <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0593">yeah I know that but</u>
<u n="244" who="S0592" trans="overlap">no no but the thing is right I did it one time did it fine you know I got the interview at <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0593" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0592">I was thinking I was thinking <anon type="place"/> that's Sainsbury's erm <pause dur="short"/> I got I got the interview at the one at <anon type="place"/> obviously I didn't get the job erm I don't know why I don't know <pause dur="short"/> if I did something wrong or cos he was saying that he didn't want me getting too caught up trying to work and also study so maybe he was considering that as well</u>
<u n="247" who="S0593">I I actually would agree with you on that one I think he was because he did sound to me like he was erm looking at what was best for you as well</u>
<u n="248" who="S0592">yeah it was a bit disappointing but I'm over it but anyway I <pause dur="short"/> then later on I applied for one erm like a little express store <pause dur="short"/> and I applied for one the answers from the questionnaire had been saved from my time before so I just put those in</u>
<u n="249" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0592">and then they said oh you haven't reached the interview stage cos your questions weren't good enough my</u>
<u n="251" who="S0593">yeah I I've read online about erm <pause dur="short"/> about their interview things but</u>
<u n="252" who="S0592">it it <trunc>stu</trunc></u>
<u n="253" who="S0593">one one girl said that she sent in <pause dur="short"/> those answers so many times and she changed her answers so many times and you know so they were completely different and <pause dur="short"/> she still didn't get get in yet her friend who put the same answers got in</u>
<u n="254" who="S0592">it it's stupid they must do it randomly and that that that that's unfair though because oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> I I don't know it's <trunc>ju</trunc> it's just frustrating because I know they need some sort of filter system so they don't have so many people coming for interviews and things but just because I might have failed this questionnaire doesn't mean that I'm gonna be a bad worker</u>
<u n="255" who="S0593">exactly</u>
<u n="256" who="S0592">but all I don't know how they would combat that but besides the fact that I got an interview with a set of questions then entered the exact same set of questions and then failed is a bit fishy</u>
<u n="257" who="S0593" trans="overlap">it's ridiculous yeah it's ridiculous isn't it?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0592">I I don't know what they expect people to do if they get an interview with one set of answers and then get rejected with the same set of answers well what do you want what do you want from me?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0593" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="260" who="S0592">I think I'm just gonna try and get do some volunteering or try and get an internship</u>
<u n="261" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0592">you know psychology-related try and get experience with that rather than looking for particular for a paid job because I'm gonna need experience erm <pause dur="short"/> and a lot of experience if I want to try and apply for a postgraduate</u>
<u n="263" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0592">so I</u>
<u n="265" who="S0593" trans="overlap">I think actually I think that's a very sensible idea</u>
<u n="266" who="S0592">I I I need to focus on that first</u>
<u n="267" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0592">erm I mean I did see a few that were quite <pause dur="short"/> cool did I tell you about that one about the brain erm? the it's a shame because it looks really interesting but I don't think I'm experienced enough for it</u>
<u n="269" who="S0593">I think you mentioned it yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0592">one about erm <pause dur="short"/> someone I I don't remember the exact thing they were doing neuroimaging</u>
<u n="271" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0592">and F M FMRI I'm not sure what FMRI is <pause dur="short"/> erm but it's a way it's a way of I guess imaging the brain or viewing the brain</u>
<u n="273" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0592">but they said one of the requirements is that you needed good knowledge of the anatomy of the brain and I don't</u>
<u n="275" who="S0593" trans="overlap">well you have haven't you?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0592">no <pause dur="short"/>n I'd love to learn it and I could look in my biopsychology books and try and remember things cos I remember when I was doing one of my web-based assessments erm I looked at the biopsychology book I was looking at the pages and I thought wow this is really really interesting</u>
<u n="277" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0592">like I got you you know?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0592">the developmental one was okay but developmental psychology really isn't what interests me <pause dur="short"/> I just found it really interesting when they were talking about the areas of the brain and like how different things are connected</u>
<u n="281" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that's why you wanna do neuro yeah?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0592">yeah that's why it's interesting me</u>
<u n="283" who="S0593" trans="overlap">do you think do you think you'd be more interested now than rather than <pause dur="short"/> cos when you went into this you were all for the <pause dur="short"/> sort of counselling side of it</u>
<u n="284" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0593">in helping particularly people with anxiety depression stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> do you think now you because you're more interested in the neuropsychology that you would be more interested in the research?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0592">I think so</u>
<u n="287" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0592">because <trunc>e</trunc> yeah <trunc>e</trunc>even now I wouldn't be <pause dur="short"/> well I I I could be working directly with people actually because I would need participants for the research but you know research can do a hell of a lot of good in helping you know erm one of the lecturers <pause dur="short"/> I think yeah one of the lecturers <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he he does a lot of research into Alzheimer's and <pause dur="short"/> you know he was he was telling us about his research and I thought that's interesting you know and it's quite valuable the research they're doing into Alzheimer's because they've they've kind of figured out the mechanisms of why people get Alzheimer's so they're obviously they're still working on a way to prevent it and they're developing drugs but the fact that they know why people develop the symptoms is good</u>
<u n="289" who="S0593">oh yeah? and what why is that then?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0592">er I'm trying to remember exactly what it was <pause dur="short"/> I know that <pause dur="short"/> there's these things called beta-amyloid plaques</u>
<u n="291" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="292" who="S0592">basically er there's a protein I can't remember the name of it though it it I think the the abbreviation I think is APP <pause dur="short"/> let me look it up <pause dur="short"/> aPP amyloid precursor protein that's it <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="294" who="S0592">and</u>
<u n="295" who="S0593">I have no clue what that means but</u>
<u n="296" who="S0592">it's <trunc>ju</trunc> it's just it's just a protein basically <pause dur="short"/> erm what happens is that <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember I can't remember the different enzymes and I should because I learnt these but I can't remember them at the minute basically <trunc>nor</trunc>normal people without Alzheimer's erm an enzyme er chops up APP and then the fragments get transported out or like like they're they're not stuck in the brain but with people with <trunc>Altz</trunc>Alzheimer's a different enzyme <pause dur="short"/> chops the APP protein and that causes different shaped fragments that can't be broke down properly and so the</u>
<u n="297" who="S0593">so where does this different component come from to <trunc>wh</trunc>what makes that change?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0592">oh I don't know I'm sorry</u>
<u n="299" who="S0593">okay well no I just wondered if if this had already been found in the research you were saying your tutor whatever he is is doing</u>
<u n="300" who="S0592">I I don't I don't know exactly where the other protein come not other protein other enzyme comes from <trunc>basic</trunc> so that's what happens</u>
<u n="301" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0592">the fragments can't be broken down and so they kind of aggregate together and form a pack and that prevents signals</u>
<u n="303" who="S0593">from getting through</u>
<u n="304" who="S0592">getting through effectively so that's one thing</u>
<u n="305" who="S0593">so why I wonder then I'm not asking if you know the answer to this I'm just wondering now I wonder then how that affects <pause dur="short"/> people being stuck in the past you know when when they get like dementia</u>
<u n="306" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0593">how you know a thing is because they it's like their short-term memory</u>
<u n="308" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0593">is non-existent but their long-term memory's fantastic</u>
<u n="310" who="S0592">yeah I I I think that's what it is I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why but basically their short term memory's severely affected but they're they're still very very good at remember long-term events so that's probably why they think or they act like as if they're in the past because they can't remember what happened recently but they can remember what happened years and years ago</u>
<u n="311" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> some of them can't remember what happened five minutes ago</u>
<u n="312" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="313" who="S0593">you know they they have no no idea and it also I don't know how true this is but when I was erm <pause dur="short"/> when I was nursing I got told or we we got taught that one of the really sad things about it is it can completely change a person's personality</u>
<u n="314" who="S0592">yeah it can</u>
<u n="315" who="S0593">so <pause dur="short"/> like if you get somebody who <pause dur="short"/> would normally be very sweet and very kind and very gentle can actually become quite violent and it's just not like them and that obviously must be</u>
<u n="316" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0593">very very distressing and uncomfortable and <pause dur="short"/> it it must be heartbreaking for families to live through this</u>
<u n="318" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0593">because they're <pause dur="long"/> memories because they get stuck sometimes way way back they don't always remember even recent people in their lives like their children or their husband or what have you I worked with erm looked after a man and his poor wife was like a saint</u>
<u n="320" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0593">and <pause dur="short"/> he knew she was his wife but he thought she was his first wife</u>
<u n="322" who="S0592">oh okay</u>
<u n="323" who="S0593">and that must have been really hard for her</u>
<u n="324" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0593">but he used to tell me all these stories Scotsman he was and he had this really broad Scots accent and he used to be a shepherd up in the hills <pause dur="short"/> and he used to play the bagpipes and he said the sheep loved the bagpipes and he said that they used to follow him round like the pied piper</u>
<u n="326" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0593">and he's go home and he'd take the sheep back to the house with him and all the sheep would be like coming in and in the lounge and things like that and his mum'd be going mad saying all tho <trunc>s</trunc> er all these sheep are shitting all over my <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0593">all over my floor get these bloody sheep out of here <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> you know it he used to tell some very funny stories but yeah <trunc>o</trunc>occasionally he he recognised his wife for who she was but a lot of the time <pause dur="short"/> he thought she was his first wife</u>
<u n="330" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0593">you know? which was <pause dur="short"/> I I found very sad</u>
<u n="332" who="S0592">yeah it is sad it <trunc>ma</trunc> it makes sense that <pause dur="short"/> people's personalities will change or might change obviously they don't always have to but considering the fact that signals are being blocked they can't go through properly it makes sense that there's going to be changes to her personality there's also another thing within the neuron in the brain <trunc>ne</trunc> you know what a neuron is yeah?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know what a neuron is</u>
<u n="334" who="S0592">well I'm just I'm just</u>
<u n="335" who="S0593">yeah no that's fine</u>
<u n="336" who="S0592">I'm I'm not trying to patronise you or anything</u>
<u n="337" who="S0593">no just carry on</u>
<u n="338" who="S0592">but I I just want to make sure we're on the same page <vocal desc="laugh"/> before I start explaining things</u>
<u n="339" who="S0593">no you on sixteen and I'm on thirty-four</u>
<u n="340" who="S0592">that's that's you're implying that I'm stupid</u>
<u n="341" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah go on carry on</u>
<u n="342" who="S0592">right erm within the neurons there's erm <pause dur="short"/> microfibrils I think I pronounced it correctly microfibrils <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> which I don't know how to explain what they are but basically they help transport erm materials throughout the neuron</u>
<u n="343" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="344" who="S0592">erm like they transport help transport signals and different the different what's the word? ions I'd say that <pause dur="short"/> generate action potentials throughout</u>
<u n="345" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0592">throughout the neuron erm these micro <trunc>fibril</trunc>fibrils they get the</u>
<u n="347" who="S0593" trans="overlap">easy for you to say</u>
<u n="348" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0592">it's one it's one of those weird words erm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0593">one of those ones you can say quite clearly in your head but you just cannot get out passed the tip of your tongue</u>
<u n="352" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0592">but these I I'll try and say it again micro <pause dur="short"/> fibrils</u>
<u n="355" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0592" trans="overlap">no I've messed up the end oh well erm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0593" trans="overlap">never mind <trunc>tho</trunc>those things</u>
<u n="358" who="S0592">those things</u>
<u n="359" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0592">they get tangled <pause dur="short"/> and so things can't be transported properly</u>
<u n="361" who="S0593">well with a name like that it's quite understandable isn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0592">ah they they get tangled and so</u>
<u n="363" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0592">materials <pause dur="short"/> ions and proteins they can't be transported properly <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>prop</trunc> I I feel like I can't speak English today erm they can't be transported <trunc>prop</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> sake</u>
<u n="365" who="S0593">properly?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0592">properly ha they can't be transported throughout the neuron</u>
<u n="367" who="S0593">uhu</u>
<u n="368" who="S0592">and so the neuron ends up dying</u>
<u n="369" who="S0593">oh</u>
<u n="370" who="S0592">so there's billions and billions of neurons in our brain but you know if they start dying</u>
<u n="371" who="S0593">well it depends at you know you might well think oh there's billions and billions <pause dur="short"/> and it's gonna take an awful long time for you to get through billions and billions but it depends like how many die at once doesn't it?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0592">yeah and also</u>
<u n="373" who="S0593" trans="overlap">if if if you say they start dying and they start dying like <pause dur="short"/> one one at at a time one an hour</u>
<u n="374" who="S0592">oh I I don't know the rate</u>
<u n="375" who="S0593" trans="overlap">it it it might be like they're dying by their thousands</u>
<u n="376" who="S0592">I I don't know the rate at which they die I I mean <pause dur="short"/> I assume I don't know because Alzheimer's and dementia is is slow slow onset</u>
<u n="377" who="S0593">yeah it's insidious yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0592" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> so I don't think they must die thousands and thousands at a time <pause dur="short"/> but they must die at quite a quick rate for you know there such to be such a deterioration over the years erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so</u>
<u n="379" who="S0593">and there are stages to it as well</u>
<u n="380" who="S0592">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> we did erm we were looking at Alzheimer's in a seminar as well and we watched some videos on it that's <pause dur="short"/> that's how I remember about the different like the beta-amyloid plaques and the <pause dur="short"/> er I think <trunc>neurofibu</trunc> I can't say the word I know it in my head but I can't say it properly neurofibrillary tangles</u>
<u n="381" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="382" who="S0592">I I don't know what it is about that word that I just can't say <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you just get words sometimes don't you? that you just can't say properly</u>
<u n="383" who="S0593" trans="overlap">you do you do and then you know in a day or two's time it might just trip off your tongue</u>
<u n="384" who="S0592">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0593">no but it what I could never understand is <pause dur="short"/> why Alzheimer's and dementia are different</u>
<u n="386" who="S0592">because</u>
<u n="387" who="S0593" trans="overlap">I mean the effects are the same</u>
<u n="388" who="S0592">yeah but I think it's cos <pause dur="short"/> you can get dementia or Alzheimer's <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm trying to think Alzheimer's is like a cause of dementia but you can get dementia from other things as well as Alzheimer's</u>
<u n="389" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0592">so I I I guess <pause dur="short"/> I guess that's the difference because just cos someone has dementia doesn't mean they have Alzheimer's <pause dur="short"/> you can the</u>
<u n="391" who="S0593" trans="overlap">so so many erm contributing factors <trunc>me</trunc> and different types of dementia as well</u>
<u n="392" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah I mean the the main difference with some types of dementia and Alzheimer's in that Alzheimer's is irreversible but you can get some types of dementia where if there's a particular physical symptom that you can identify you can reverse it</u>
<u n="393" who="S0593">can you? I didn't know that</u>
<u n="394" who="S0592">yeah no there are some types of dementia where that is the case I I I found that interesting actually erm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0593" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> I I did not know that</u>
<u n="396" who="S0592">erm but not with Alzheimer's cos Alzheimer's is specifically what was I talking about with the amyloid plaques and things</u>
<u n="397" who="S0593">coconut oil <pause dur="short"/> is meant to be erm and see the thing with coconut oil is <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people speak very very highly of it and what it does for your body and your mind and blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but there aren't there hasn't been actually any proper in depth studies done on it</u>
<u n="398" who="S0592">yeah just</u>
<u n="399" who="S0593" trans="overlap">but however it is actually meant to some people have said erm <pause dur="short"/> to have a great effect on reversing the effects of dementia</u>
<u n="400" who="S0592">I'm not <trunc>ba</trunc> so I'm I'm reading up I'm reading up on it now this is a website called Alzheimer's dot org dot UK so I trust it because it's got org in it so that's</u>
<u n="401" who="S0593" trans="overlap">dot UK yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0592">yeah er that that's what we were taught in primary school if it's got org in it it's a trustworthy website erm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0593">right</u>
<u n="404" who="S0592">so I I think so basically it says that there have been some claims that coconut oil could be used as a treatment or even a cure I doubt it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0593">no I'm not saying a cure</u>
<u n="406" who="S0592">but this is just what the website is saying</u>
<u n="407" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0592">erm for Alzheimer's disease however there is currently not enough experimental evidence to back up these claims</u>
<u n="409" who="S0593">which is exactly what I've just said isn't it?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0592">I know I'm just reaffirming what you are saying</u>
<u n="411" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0592">erm it it is saying the claim is based on the theory that the neurons erm in the brains of people with Alzheimer's disease are unable to use glucose to produce energy properly and therefore starve and the theory is that coconut oil might act as an alternative energy source but there is not enough scientific evidence to know for sure whether this is the case erm and there is a clinical trial being conducted in the US</u>
<u n="413" who="S0593">oh</u>
<u n="414" who="S0592">it says the results of this clinical trial are due to be announced in mid two thousand seventeen</u>
<u n="415" who="S0593">oh oh</u>
<u n="416" who="S0594">is is is the dog not getting any tea today?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0593">er I suppose we did say we would take the dog out so you really need to get dressed and you need to take her O U T down the road</u>
<u n="418" who="S0592">did did dad leave my wellies here?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0593">yes</u>
<u n="420" who="S0594">yeah the both both pairs are in the kitchen</u>
<u n="421" who="S0593" trans="overlap">they're both yeah they're both in the kitchen</u>
<u n="422" who="S0592">oh okay</u>
<u n="423" who="S0593">so we get her down the road and better take a torch with us this time</u>
<u n="424" who="S0594">I mean I would have done it myself but you know like</u>
<u n="425" who="S0593">yeah <pause dur="short"/> your dad your dad is probably er <pause dur="short"/> finished early and er <pause dur="short"/> well actually he's working from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s today</u>
<u n="426" who="S0594" trans="overlap">yeah he's got he's got an all-day meeting he's probably still in it</u>
<u n="427" who="S0593">yeah probably <pause dur="short"/> but never mind at least he hasn't got far to go to to the party afterwards</u>
<u n="428" who="S0594">no what is like next door? or</u>
<u n="429" who="S0593">no he's actually working from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house</u>
<u n="430" who="S0594">yeah but is this the party at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0594">they're having a they're having a work Christmas party at someone's</u>
<u n="433" who="S0593" trans="overlap">oh it's <trunc>o</trunc> no it's only it's it's only his small group of friends</u>
<u n="434" who="S0594">oh</u>
<u n="435" who="S0593">so it it they'll go to the pub</u>
<u n="436" who="S0594" trans="overlap">yeah but they they're they'll still probably</u>
<u n="437" who="S0593" trans="overlap">also yeah they'll go to the pub</u>
<u n="438" who="S0594">yeah they'll still probably go out somewhere</u>
<u n="439" who="S0593">yeah they they'll go to the pub which I think is within walking distance <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0594">probably probably going to</u>
<u n="441" who="S0593" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> usually cook a nice meal for for everybody</u>
<u n="442" who="S0594">oh that's good</u>
<u n="443" who="S0592">it's confusing hearing all these <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0593">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> mm look at this photograph of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's lovely</u>
<u n="445" who="S0594">is it of our <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this this mystery <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0593" trans="overlap">no our <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no no no our our our <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0592"><trunc>mu</trunc>mum just thought she'd show you a random picture of this woman called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just for the hell of it</u>
<u n="448" who="S0594"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> Rachel Stevens from S Club Seven</u>
<u n="449" who="S0592">it was taken a few months ago I don't know why she took so long to put them up it was at her birthday party her being <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0594">god who are all these people?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0592">oh god there's so many people so many names we need to remember</u>
<u n="452" who="S0593">what what is that? oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0592">what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> done?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0593">share this and in five minutes you will find this in your yard <pause dur="short"/> it's a hundred hundred dollar bill</u>
<u n="455" who="S0594" trans="overlap">ten dollars?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0592">well that's going to be useless here isn't it?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0593">yeah it's no use to me is it?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0594">er you know we have these things called er</u>
<u n="459" who="S0593" trans="overlap">if he goes into the garden soon we'll know why</u>
<u n="460" who="S0594">yeah we have we have these things called erm you know bureau de change yeah you you you can get your money changed <pause dur="short"/> it's how it's how people go abroad</u>
<u n="461" who="S0592">okay smarty pants</u>
<u n="462" who="S0593">just by changing their money?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0592" trans="overlap">well the</u>
<u n="464" who="S0594">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0593">so if I go to the bureau de change or whatever it's called</u>
<u n="466" who="S0592">great pronunciation</u>
<u n="467" who="S0593">yeah shush</u>
<u n="468" who="S0594" trans="overlap">yeah yeah sorry we didn't take French cos we're not traitors</u>
<u n="469" who="S0592">what do you mean traitors?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0594"><trunc>any</trunc> anyone who learns a foreign language is a traitor</u>
<u n="471" who="S0593">you learnt <trunc>Fre</trunc> er Spanish</u>
<u n="472" who="S0592" trans="overlap">alright fair enough</u>
<u n="473" who="S0594">only cos I was made to</u>
<u n="474" who="S0592" trans="overlap">what do you mean you were made to</u>
<u n="475" who="S0593" trans="overlap">anyway anyway if I went there and changed some money I could automatically just be in a different country when I turn around</u>
<u n="476" who="S0594">yeah yeah pretty much</u>
<u n="477" who="S0593">oh right okay I like that right let let me find this picture of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0594">oh rats there's no hundred dollars</u>
<u n="479" who="S0592">oh no it's like</u>
<u n="480" who="S0593">they lied they lied</u>
<u n="481" who="S0592" trans="overlap">was that was that mean to <vocal desc="laugh"/> what <pause dur="short"/> was that was that meant to be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0594">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0592">how how come he's suddenly speaking in an American accent?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0594">cos that's what he do sometimes</u>
<u n="485" who="S0593">there</u>
<u n="486" who="S0592" trans="overlap">it's annoying</u>
<u n="487" who="S0593">there it is</u>
<u n="488" who="S0594">I know but oh I I don't know who</u>
<u n="489" who="S0593">that one there's your sister</u>
<u n="490" who="S0594">yeah I know</u>
<u n="491" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0594">christ there's like everyone <trunc>er</trunc> in your flat like six foot ten</u>
<u n="493" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0592">there's <trunc>o</trunc> there's only one hold on let me take it I swear</u>
<u n="495" who="S0593" trans="overlap">there's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0592">there's only one really tall guy and that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's I think he's about six foot four actually</u>
<u n="497" who="S0594"><trunc>ev</trunc><trunc>ev</trunc>everyone in that photo apart from the person right next to you everyone in that photo looks like a giant compared to you</u>
<u n="498" who="S0592">well actually I think she's slightly shorter than me she's just further in the front so she looks taller</u>
<u n="499" who="S0593">oh it's just because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is so much taller than her</u>
<u n="500" who="S0592">I mean I I look tiny don't I?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0594">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0592">but mind you they're all they're most of them are guys so they're gonna be taller than me</u>
<u n="503" who="S0594">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0593">not necessarily</u>
<u n="505" who="S0592">well I mean there is</u>
<u n="506" who="S0593">he doesn't look that tall</u>
<u n="507" who="S0592">no he is quite short to be honest</u>
<u n="508" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/> to be honest it's the first time I've seen his face in that photograph cos he's so short bless him</u>
<u n="509" who="S0592">no that's</u>
<u n="510" who="S0594">this looks like he's been photoshopped in as well</u>
<u n="511" who="S0592">no he hasn't he's erm he's he's a fourth year who was I think he was our block rep so he was the rep for all of house one</u>
<u n="512" who="S0594">oh okay</u>
<u n="513" who="S0592">erm yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0593">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> erm what time when can we take the D O G O U T?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0592">erm <pause dur="short"/> er half an hour</u>
<u n="516" who="S0593">it will be dark</u>
<u n="517" who="S0592">I know that's okay</u>
<u n="518" who="S0593">okey-dokey</u>
<u n="519" who="S0592">I can handle the dark oh I keep losing my earphone things it keeps coming off it's annoying</u>
<u n="520" who="S0593" trans="overlap">I might might just walk her round the roads actually rather than just take her to erm the P A R K</u>
<u n="521" who="S0592">yeah <pause dur="short"/> might be that might be better</u>
<u n="522" who="S0593">then you won't have to worry about losing the ball</u>
<u n="523" who="S0592">and then I won't have to wear wellies <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0593">and I won't have to wear wellies either</u>
<u n="525" who="S0592">I do like those wellies though they're good</u>
<u n="526" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0592">they're quite nice they're yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's nice not having to worry about getting my jeans dirty</u>
<u n="528" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0592">oh <pause dur="short"/> shall we shall we go back to talking about the game? cos</u>
<u n="530" who="S0593">if you wish</u>
<u n="531" who="S0592">erm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0593">yeah no that's fine</u>
<u n="533" who="S0592">erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying to remember what point we got to though before</u>
<u n="534" who="S0593">I can't remember because as always as in any conversation <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we ended up digressing</u>
<u n="535" who="S0592">yeah well that's fine erm <pause dur="short"/> oh what did we talk about? I maybe I'll I'll talk <trunc>ab</trunc> er oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think we talked about how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a good role <pause dur="short"/> that he his thing</u>
<u n="536" who="S0593" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0592">glitched and that was really annoying because it was a <trunc>re</trunc> it's a really fun role the <foreign lang="ita">consigliore</foreign></u>
<u n="538" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/> say it say it again</u>
<u n="539" who="S0592" trans="overlap"><trunc>pe</trunc><trunc>pe</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="ita">consigliore</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> I think I think that's how it's pronounced</u>
<u n="540" who="S0593">I have no idea it just sounds very cute</u>
<u n="541" who="S0592">yeah erm most people they abbreviate it to <foreign lang="ita">consign</foreign> which is easier to remember</u>
<u n="542" who="S0593" trans="overlap">understandably</u>
<u n="543" who="S0592">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> which was a shame but then the next game he got he was a jester and the jester's a bit weird cos the jester what they're trying to do</u>
<u n="544" who="S0593">be right up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s street then</u>
<u n="545" who="S0592">I was I was giving <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tips on how to play it but he said no no I can't do that no cos I think he was bit self-conscious erm basically what the jester wants to do is they're the ones who want to get lynched <pause dur="short"/> so basically what they what they want to do</u>
<u n="546" who="S0593" trans="overlap">why why would somebody want to be lynched? are they depressed or something?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0592">no they're crazy erm <pause dur="short"/> basically what what the jester is meant to do is they're meant to trick the town into thinking that they're a bad person so they get lynched and then what the jester does is once they've been lynched they can haunt someone and kill them</u>
<u n="548" who="S0593"><vocal desc="gasp"/> no no no that's not good</u>
<u n="549" who="S0592">it's a fun it's a fun role to play it's so great when people actually think your bad and then you get lynched and then ha ha screw you guys and then you just kill someone</u>
<u n="550" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/> can you can you only kill one person?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0592">yeah and they have to <trunc>vo</trunc> they had to</u>
<u n="552" who="S0593" trans="overlap">so do you <trunc>al</trunc> do you always want to kill the one that's getting on your nerves the most</u>
<u n="553" who="S0592">there was there was this one person that I'm trying to remember exactly what happened erm <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm trying to remember what my name was in this game because it's quite pertinent to the story <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I think I think my name might have been lamp I might have called myself lamp in this game</u>
<u n="554" who="S0593">do you change your name every time?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0592">yeah you can if you want erm for some reason I like to call myself pieces of furniture like I've been chair I've been lamp I've been table</u>
<u n="556" who="S0593" trans="overlap">weird <pause dur="short"/> weird girl</u>
<u n="557" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah some people have weird names weirder than mine</u>
<u n="558" who="S0593">I have a weird daughter</u>
<u n="559" who="S0592">it's fine erm <pause dur="short"/> but I think my name was lamp and I got very lucky actually I got very lucky with the circumstances cos what had happened was I think people were suspicious of me anyway I don't know why I can't remember why but they were suspicious of me anyway but they didn't really have much evidence so what happened was the werewolf attacked me but I got healed by a doctor so I didn't die but what what happened was cos I need to explain what the werewolf does what the werewolf does is they attack someone and then anyone who visits the person they attacked also gets killed so for example because the werewolf attacked me the doctor visit me visited me to heal me and so the doctor died because they visited me does that make sense?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0593">okay so you're a bit like a virus?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0592">kind of <trunc>ba</trunc>basically they just attack anyone who visits their target as well erm <pause dur="short"/> and but also what the werewolf can do is stay at home and then anyone who visits them gets attacked</u>
<u n="562" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="563" who="S0592">and so basically what happened was I got attacked by a werewolf but I got healed by the doctor so I didn't die but the doctor died instead and I think a sheriff or someone else also died because they visited me to check me and what it looked like it looked like I was a werewolf who stared at stayed at home and then killed the people who visited me</u>
<u n="564" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah I was gonna stay</u>
<u n="565" who="S0592">and so people <trunc>pe</trunc>people were like oh you're obviously the werewolf and I told them the truth I said oh maybe I got healed by the doctor and the werewolf attacked me I was actually telling the truth but I was telling it in a way that made it sound like I was maybe lying or trying to bullshit them</u>
<u n="566" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0592">but I was telling the truth though but erm what happened was <pause dur="short"/> erm I said you know guys you know doctor healed me it's not my fault <pause dur="short"/> the werewolf attacked me I'm not the werewolf erm and this one person said lamps are trash they did they they just yelled out lamps are trash and I said oh lamps are trash are they? well let's see how you like this and then I ended up killing them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0593" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="569" who="S0592">cos they lynched me</u>
<u n="570" who="S0593">no no no I think I think you're a secret psychopath</u>
<u n="571" who="S0592">it's fun it's fun being the jester I do like it it's always annoying though because sometimes you can get killed at night and you're not meant to get killed at night as jester cos you don't win that way you have to get lynched erm you can get killed at night by the mafia or a serial killer or even a werewolf like one of them tried to do erm <pause dur="short"/> but I think the werewolf might have ended up winning that game actually which is good erm cos they helped me out unintentionally but they helped me out</u>
<u n="572" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0592">erm <pause dur="short"/> oh what was I just</u>
<u n="574" who="S0593" trans="overlap">just turn the light on can't see you</u>
<u n="575" who="S0592" trans="overlap">what was I just saying? <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="576" who="S0593">erm you were saying</u>
<u n="577" who="S0592" trans="overlap">oh no I was talking about getting killed at night wasn't I?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0592">it's annoying as jester sometimes because you can get killed at night without actually having a chance to get yourself lynched and that's just annoying that's just bad luck it happens</u>
<u n="580" who="S0593">seems to me like all <pause dur="short"/> characters have got their good and their not so good points to them</u>
<u n="581" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah oh I had such bad luck yesterday cos I got the werewolf <pause dur="short"/> like three times I think</u>
<u n="582" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0592">erm and werewolf I find werewolf a fun role and one time what I'd managed to do was lay low the entire game because I had just stayed at home and no one had visited me on full moons so I didn't attack anyone so no one knew that there was a werewolf in the game so I just</u>
<u n="584" who="S0593" trans="overlap">so do they not have the same characters in each each game?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0592">no erm cos there's this game mode call all any and basically the role is just there's any so there can be any combination of roles</u>
<u n="586" who="S0593">oh okay</u>
<u n="587" who="S0592">so erm that's my favourite one because you can get so many different combinations it's quite fun</u>
<u n="588" who="S0593">yeah it makes it a bit more challenging wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0592">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> but basically no one knew that there was a werewolf in the game because I had hidden so well <pause dur="short"/> and I just acted like a survivor and a survivor can win with anyone so there's no reason to kill me if <trunc>y</trunc> there's <trunc>n</trunc> there's no reason to kill a survivor even though a lot of the time they get killed anyway which is a shame <trunc>pe</trunc> some people hate survivors because they think oh the survivor's done a vote with the bad team so therefore we need to get rid of them <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm and then also if there's other roles in the game claiming survivor can be quite dangerous even if you are one <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0592">you know which sucks but <pause dur="short"/> basically they thought I was a survivor at the end it was me left I think with a member of the mafia and a serial killer</u>
<u n="592" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0592">and it didn't really matter which one I got rid of erm because I would have won anyway</u>
<u n="594" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="595" who="S0592">so I could have got rid of the mafia first <pause dur="short"/> or the serial killer I think I ended up going for the serial killer because I felt like if I accused this other person that they would just get me back</u>
<u n="596" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0592">and there was more evidence against the serial killer so I just you know I said I'm a survivor trust me you know this person's a serial killer they were the <trunc>se</trunc></u>
<u n="598" who="S0593"><shift new="singing"/> I'm a survivor de de <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0592">yeah they they were the serial killer we lynched them and then it came up with the werewolf wins and everyone was like what we had a werewolf this game? and I was like yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0593">yay go me</u>
<u n="601" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I was try I was trying to do the same thing just stay at my house and hope no one visits me <pause dur="short"/> but what happened was these stupid vampires these these</u>
<u n="602" who="S0593">damn those vampires</u>
<u n="603" who="S0592">no because this this happened twice I believe actually no it didn't it it happened once but I was thinking of something else erm <pause dur="short"/> what happened was like vampires I don't know it's quite obvious they bite people to try and turn other people into vampires</u>
<u n="604" who="S0593">uhu</u>
<u n="605" who="S0592">but certain roles are immune to being bitten so they <trunc>ca</trunc> so the vampire will know that if you try to bite someone and they're immune they'll get told oh your target was immune to your attack <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> roles that are mutual not mutual roles that are immune</u>
<u n="606" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0592">to erm <pause dur="short"/> vampire bites are members of the mafia <pause dur="short"/> werewolves <pause dur="short"/> serial killers <pause dur="short"/> executioners <pause dur="short"/> and arsonists I believe</u>
<u n="608" who="S0593">seems like quite a few</u>
<u n="609" who="S0592">yeah I mean yeah there is quite a few that are immune but basically what the vampire'd done is they tried to bite me night one and I didn't know they tried to bite me cos they didn't actually say that I got attacked or anything</u>
<u n="610" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="611" who="S0592">erm <pause dur="short"/> they tried to bite me night one <pause dur="short"/> but they failed obviously cos I was a werewolf and I couldn't be turned <pause dur="short"/> it would be funny a werewolf turned into a vampire <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I I couldn't be turned</u>
<u n="612" who="S0593">a vam wolf</u>
<u n="613" who="S0592">and the vampire had written in their will cos when you die you present a will erm someone had written in the will oh this person was immune to me biting them and everyone was like oh what what are you why why are you immune to the vampire biting you? I said I I'm a survivor I used my vest that's why I was immune because survivors can use vests to protect themselves</u>
<u n="614" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0592">but apparently er even if a survivor uses their vest they get bitten and they turn into vampire anyway I didn't know that I was trying to cover myself <pause dur="short"/> didn't work and I got lynched so</u>
<u n="616" who="S0593"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0592">yeah but that's</u>
<u n="618" who="S0593" trans="overlap">so when you were playing this with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> did you kill him?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0592">no erm the first time when <pause dur="short"/> when he was a <foreign lang="ita">consign</foreign> he was erm <pause dur="short"/> I was on the same team as him anyway so I couldn't have killed him erm I was a member of the mafia he was he was just saying oh this sucks so much I can't even do anything I can't click anything and I said I said I would encourage you to leave but if you leave and you've still got a chance of winning then you'll get timed out and you'll have to wait until you get the next game</u>
<u n="620" who="S0592" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0592">so I said just wait it out <pause dur="short"/> erm we ended up winning anyway really easily erm <pause dur="short"/> we were on the same team and then <pause dur="short"/> and then I think when he was a jester I think I can't remember what I was when he was a jester I think I was a good role but I can't remember what no no no what was I? <pause dur="short"/> I think oh <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what I was I think I was a good role though erm he was a jester but I was just trying to give him advice on how to oh I remember what I was a doctor but I got killed night one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0593">oh</u>
<u n="623" who="S0592">it's annoying cos cos cos doctors can heal themselves once I was just frustrating that cos I didn't think I would use me heal for myself in the first in the first night but they ended up killing me so you know sucks erm <pause dur="short"/> ah yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0593">soon boo boos</u>
<u n="625" who="S0592">but I I was tell I was telling <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this is why he this is when he was saying oh I can't do that no I won't do it I told him to accuse some random person of being a member of the mafia <pause dur="short"/> erm because then <trunc>wha</trunc></u>
<u n="626" who="S0593">see at least one of my children has got scruples</u>
<u n="627" who="S0592">no cos that</u>
<u n="628" who="S0593">one of my twinnies</u>
<u n="629" who="S0592">that's that's that's just the way you get lynched cos they think that he's an executioner <pause dur="short"/> if you just accuse someone random with that much evidence they'll think oh this person's obviously a really bad executioner we should get rid of him and that as I said that's the simplest way to do it is to just accuse some random person of being a member of the mafia <pause dur="short"/> have I have had some times though where I've accused random people of being roles and have ended up being correct and then people have actually believed that I've been a sheriff of something I'm like no lynch me I'm not a sheriff I'm not on your side</u>
<u n="630" who="S0593">I remember you used to get quite frustrated on on this game sometimes you'd be like no no don't kill me don't kill me don't</u>
<u n="631" who="S0592" trans="overlap">it is <pause dur="short"/> it is frustrating sometimes cos you do get some you do you do get some people who are a bit dim and they throw away a an obvious chance to win and I'm not saying I've never done that obviously cos I have at some points you know what seemed obvious to other people wasn't so obvious to me but there have been instances where there have been some really really really obvious chances to win and someone has just thrown it away because they weren't thinking or they didn't read something properly</u>
<u n="632" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0592">erm <pause dur="short"/> what was I thinking of? and also you sometimes get people who cheat in this game where they're on a Skype call</u>
<u n="634" who="S0593">no</u>
<u n="635" who="S0592">no I know</u>
<u n="636" who="S0593">really?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0593">people cheat in games?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0592">yeah no basically</u>
<u n="640" who="S0593" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="641" who="S0592">what people do is they'll be in Skype call and I know I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I wasn't actually telling him outside information that would really affect the game</u>
<u n="642" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0592">erm <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't telling him information that would influence the game or give him an unfair advantage I was just trying to help him out with his role</u>
<u n="644" who="S0593">as you should</u>
<u n="645" who="S0592" trans="overlap">but you get but you get some people who will Skype each other and they will tell them outside information</u>
<u n="646" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0592">that they shouldn't know unless you like <pause dur="short"/> that they shouldn't know about unless they were told outside erm <pause dur="short"/> and you know sometimes you get people who are members of the mafia who rat out their teammates to their friends who are like a town role erm and say you know this person <pause dur="short"/> this person knows all the members of the mafia <pause dur="short"/> erm and we wonder how the hell did they know that? because one of the mafia told them <trunc>a</trunc> who we were erm and then I think one of the games I played yesterday <pause dur="short"/> the veteran he said oh I've got two roles and like that's not possible you can't have two roles he said oh I've got two roles I'm the investigator and the veteran he's said oh you can't be the investigator and the veteran I think he was using two accounts to play and cheating that way erm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well maybe</u>
<u n="649" who="S0592">but you can't do that that's that's cheating but</u>
<u n="650" who="S0593">no</u>
<u n="651" who="S0592">erm you know he he found out that someone was the godfather and he had no way of knowing that unless someone else had told him <pause dur="short"/> and so yeah we all reported him though and there is also a vigilante erm he was a town role who basically just shoots tries to shoot bad people sometimes it doesn't end well cos they'll end up shooting a town member and then they die afterwards cos they die of guilt erm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0593" trans="overlap">uh die of guilt?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0592">I think they kill themselves</u>
<u n="654" who="S0593">ah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0592">erm <pause dur="short"/> but but yeah and then this vigilante somehow knew how somehow knew to shoot me even though there's no evidence against me I'm like that's suspicious how did you know to shoot me in particular if you just randomly guessed like <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="656" who="S0593">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you you could just er maybe use a good random random guesser but however</u>
<u n="657" who="S0592">however there are so many other people he could have shot <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0593">maybe he just doesn't like lamps</u>
<u n="659" who="S0592">I don't think erm actually my name might no my name wasn't lamp that <trunc>ro</trunc> that round <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't no</u>
<u n="660" who="S0593">what's that other game you used to play that always looked fun was that erm one with the bubble where you had to go round collecting more bubbles</u>
<u n="661" who="S0592">oh Agar dot I O</u>
<u n="662" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0592">yeah it's fun</u>
<u n="664" who="S0593" trans="overlap">cos that that they used to you used to be so funny watching you playing that</u>
<u n="665" who="S0592">it's it's it's quite</u>
<u n="666" who="S0593">go away go away no no don't come near me no go away right I'm going over here I'm hiding over here</u>
<u n="667" who="S0592" trans="overlap">always</u>
<u n="668" who="S0593">no don't follow me go away <vocal desc="laugh"/> come here I want to eat you no no go away</u>
<u n="669" who="S0592"><unclear>always</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it's a fun I haven't played it in a while actually <pause dur="short"/> yeah hopefully I can play a game with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today if he's willing <pause dur="short"/> I think I don't know I cos I like the game and I want I've wanted to play it with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for a while</u>
<u n="670" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="671" who="S0592">erm cos it it's a fun game Town of Salem</u>
<u n="672" who="S0593">it's nice isn't it when when you've got something that you actually really enjoy and you want to share it with somebody that that you love or somebody who's company you really like</u>
<u n="673" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0593">and you just want to share the same fun and get them to have the same fun and with you or what have you you know? that that's always nice I think I always used to find it quite disappointing when other people just didn't wanna play the same games as me</u>
<u n="675" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0593">you know?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0592">and he he did seem interested cos he was asking me questions about how to play it and things like that so it's not as if he was completely fobbing it off or anything I think he was just a bit confused and maybe a bit self-conscious cos he didn't want to mess up I warned him I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know this is the internet if you make a mistake just be prepared for some people to call you an idiot because I've been called a idiot countless times on that game even though it it make it makes me mad because sometimes I appreciate that I've made mistakes I'm like okay fine you know I messed up but a lot of the time the mistakes that I made weren't necessarily my fault <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="678" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="679" who="S0592">but cos one time I was playing <pause dur="short"/> I was playing with people on a stream because the community manager of the game does a stream twice every week and so I like to play with people who are on that stream what had happened was <pause dur="short"/> I was the transporter and what the transporter does is they swap two people around each night</u>
<u n="680" who="S0593">right</u>
<u n="681" who="S0592">so let me try and explain this so let's say mafia target person A I decide to swap person A with person B</u>
<u n="682" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="683" who="S0592">so instead of person A dying person B dies cos I swap their places</u>
<u n="684" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="685" who="S0592">what had happened was I was a transporter the bodyguard and all protective roles were dead and the jailor was still alive so I was trying to protect the jailor and what I did is I swapped the jailor with a member of the mafia so that the mafia would kill themselves</u>
<u n="686" who="S0593">okay</u>
<u n="687" who="S0592">does that make sense?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0592">what had happened was there was a vigilante in the game who I didn't know about they had not revealed that they were a vigilante what happened was the vigilante was planning to shoot the mafia member that I swapped the jailor with and so the vigilante ended up killing the jailer and so the vigilante died because the vigilante is not meant to kill town members they kill themselves out of guilt</u>
<u n="690" who="S0593">right</u>
<u n="691" who="S0592">and I got blamed for it because I moved them but I had no idea I had no way of knowing that he was going to shoot that guy then people didn't seem to acknowledge that</u>
<u n="692" who="S0593">right</u>
<u n="693" who="S0592">do you understand where I'm coming from?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0593">yeah I do</u>
<u n="695" who="S0592">I cos I I had no way if he had told me all he had to do was whisper me and say I'm going to shoot this person do not move them I I would have been like fine I won't move them I will move them with someone else</u>
<u n="696" who="S0593">right</u>
<u n="697" who="S0592">but he didn't he neglected to tell me and then I got blamed for it <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I I I was like this is unnecessary you know I <trunc>did</trunc> it's not even my fault but the thing is is the that the vigilante was the person running the stream so I don't know if people are a bit aren't willing to point like point out or criticise how he is playing I didn't know he I didn't know it was him at the time and I was criticising him and I was saying you know you should have told me that you were going to shoot him I had no way of knowing <pause dur="short"/> you know he said he said oh the transporter screwed me over I'm like no I said how was I supposed to know that you you were going to shoot him? you didn't tell me you gave no indication that you were going you were going to do anything so how would I know that?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and what did he way?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0592">erm I mean I can't I got a bit upset then because people</u>
<u n="700" who="S0593">did you?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0592"><trunc>pe</trunc>people were calling me an idiot and basically saying I ruined the game for them which was unfair because <pause dur="short"/> I I would say it was both of our faults but it was more because he didn't communicate to me what he was doing <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> like you know I didn't think I didn't I didn't know what he was</u>
<u n="702" who="S0593">it's easy isn't it? I mean <trunc>pe</trunc> you would think that with <pause dur="short"/> an online game and with with people that you've never met before in your life <pause dur="short"/> that you would be able to not let their comments <pause dur="short"/> and things get to you but you do</u>
<u n="703" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I think I was <pause dur="short"/> I I think</u>
<u n="704" who="S0593">you do</u>
<u n="705" who="S0592">I think I was feeling quite down as it was</u>
<u n="706" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0592">and I think I was feeling a bit over sensitive and I I was playing that cos I I like to watch the stream to cheer myself up and I was playing it to cheer myself up and they kind of ruined it</u>
<u n="708" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0592">because they were basically just calling me an idiot you know saying I ruined the game for them even though I hadn't it was also the vigilante not thinking about telling you know the obvious transporter in the game what they were doing</u>
<u n="710" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but looking back on it was it actually worth <pause dur="short"/> being upset over?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0592" trans="overlap">oh I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I think what what the person said there was one person in particular who was like really really calling me an idiot apparently though they were an executioner and they were trying to convince people to lynch me they were saying oh this person's an idiot you know and they need to get lynched you know for the good of us and I was like you know you don't need to do that that's not necessary you know if you need to insult people to try and get them to get lynched you're a bad executioner</u>
<u n="712" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0592"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0593" trans="overlap">it's kind of <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="715" who="S0592"><vocal desc="cough"/> okay</u>
<u n="716" who="S0593">are you alright?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0593">yeah?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0592">sometimes when I talk too much my throat gets dry and then I end up coughing</u>
<u n="720" who="S0593">yeah so does mine <pause dur="short"/> do you want erm a drink? shall I get you a drink of water?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0592">no I'm okay</u>
<u n="722" who="S0593">yeah? <pause dur="short"/> no it it can be very very hurtful even with people that you know you really should think oh I really don't give a rat's ass what you think</u>
<u n="723" who="S0592">I think I was also getting mad because I was getting mad and upset because they weren't seeing it from my point of view they they're they're only thinking oh this transporter messed it up because the vigilante was shooting but they didn't consider that I had no idea what the vigilante was doing I had no way of knowing</u>
<u n="724" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0592">it's like if I had a way of knowing he had if he had told me and I did it anyway then I would understand why people called me an idiot</u>
<u n="726" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0592">but there was no indication what he was doing</u>
<u n="728" who="S0593">oh</u>
<u n="729" who="S0592">so I</u>
<u n="730" who="S0593">but looking back on it you you know I'm sure you can kind of look back on it and think why on earth did I ever get upset over that?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0592">I mean yeah and you know later on cos I was saying you know I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't appreciate that you know I've been called an idiot for this because I didn't I had no way of knowing</u>
<u n="732" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0592">you know I was kind of saying that you've kind of ruined my night now because you've just kept calling me an idiot you know even though it wasn't really my fault</u>
<u n="734" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0592">and it wasn't the person on the stream by the way calling me an idiot by the way he's nice I think he just also got frustrated because he wasn't expecting me to move erm the people and you know erm but he said he said don't worry you know you did the best with the information you had and you didn't you know he admitted that he hadn't said anything <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="736" who="S0593">perhaps erm he just had a plan in his head and it didn't go the way he wanted it to go</u>
<u n="737" who="S0592">obviously</u>
<u n="738" who="S0593">and he didn't like it you know so</u>
<u n="739" who="S0592">but you you you know it's a <trunc>go</trunc> it's all good and well having a plan in your head but if you don't tell people who might affect your plan what you're doing things like that happen</u>
<u n="740" who="S0593">well tough luck really isn't it?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0592">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah but</u>
<u n="742" who="S0593">have you seen these things on Facebook it says if you could sit on this bench and chat with only one person past or present who would it be?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0592">er I've probably seen something like that</u>
<u n="744" who="S0593">who would it be?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0592">oh I have no idea erm</u>
<u n="746" who="S0593">no neither do I</u>
<u n="747" who="S0592">I I don't know I don't know anyone past who when you say past does it imply that maybe they're dead?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0593">they're dead? I suppose that's what it implies but it doesn't have to be it could just be someone you knew in the past</u>
<u n="749" who="S0592">maybe <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't know who I'd speak to I don't think there's anyone in the past that I'd particularly admire or want to speak to</u>
<u n="750" who="S0593">no <pause dur="short"/> I I have to say I'm I'm the same</u>
<u n="751" who="S0592">or maybe I'd talk to someone when they were younger maybe if they were quite old now maybe I'd speak to them when they're younger <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0593">oh that's a different way of looking at it</u>
<u n="753" who="S0592">oh I don't know if they're not dead maybe they're just old now and then you could go back in the past and speak to them</u>
<u n="754" who="S0593">but it could be somebody that you went to school with</u>
<u n="755" who="S0592">maybe there's no one in particular that I went to school with either that I would speak to not that I don't still speak to now</u>
<u n="756" who="S0593">well yeah I'm exactly the same I kind of think I have there is no one particular person that I would want to sit and just chat with</u>
<u n="757" who="S0592">and then it said then did it did it say future?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0593">no <pause dur="short"/> past or present</u>
<u n="759" who="S0592" trans="overlap">no? <pause dur="short"/> oh I was about to say if it said future that doesn't make much sense does it? cos how how how would you know who to speak to in the future? or I think maybe I'd like to speak to Robin Williams</u>
<u n="760" who="S0593">oh now that's a good one</u>
<u n="761" who="S0592">cos he you know is quite funny and yeah</u>
<u n="762" who="S0593">yeah and he's quite he's got quite a lot of wisdom as well <pause dur="short"/> had</u>
<u n="763" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I do I do <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's a shame isn't it? what happened</u>
<u n="764" who="S0593">it is a shame <pause dur="short"/> what did he killed himself because he's got Parkinson's?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0592">I think he was also depressed</u>
<u n="766" who="S0593">which kind of comes hand in hand with Parkinson's</u>
<u n="767" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0593">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was a bit concerned about your auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because you know with this <pause dur="short"/> stuff she's got going on and even a neurologist isn't a hundred percent sure what it is she's got</u>
<u n="769" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0593">I actually think she's got more than one thing going on <pause dur="short"/> and but the way she walks is very very much like somebody with Parkinson's <pause dur="short"/> however the neurologist hasn't picked up on it so</u>
<u n="771" who="S0592">mm mm don't know</u>
<u n="772" who="S0593">do you know what I found interesting about the fact that you're interested in the neurological side of things</u>
<u n="773" who="S0592">what?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0593">I wanted at one point to <pause dur="short"/> do further training in my nurses' training</u>
<u n="775" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="776" who="S0593">and do neurology</u>
<u n="777" who="S0592">I I mean I I do find it I find it very interesting I think maybe cos I'm more <trunc>s</trunc> I think I consider myself quite a scientific person anyway</u>
<u n="778" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="779" who="S0592">erm I do yeah and</u>
<u n="780" who="S0593">you're quite you you're quite intuitive as well so</u>
<u n="781" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0593">don't lose your intuition</u>
<u n="783" who="S0592">no I no I won't there's yeah there's been countless times I I I'm kind of going like there's been countless times in the game where I have felt something really strongly but have not acted on it cos I was afraid that I was gonna be wrong but actually I was correct</u>
<u n="784" who="S0593">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you're quite intuitive in life as well</u>
<u n="785" who="S0592">yeah I I was just giving an example</u>
<u n="786" who="S0593">yeah you know so you're more you're more spiritual than I think you'd like to admit because you don't want to people to think you're a bit cuckoo</u>
<u n="787" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="788" who="S0593">yeah? am I right or wrong</u>
<u n="789" who="S0592">maybe a bit</u>
<u n="790" who="S0593">yeah you get to you get to a stage even if it takes you fifty-three years where you think I really don't give a monkey what you think <pause dur="short"/> this is me either like me as I am or walk away hurts sometimes especially when people throw you know when when people are cos everybody has got their gifts right and regardless of whether it's academic or spiritual or <pause dur="short"/> metaphysical or whatever everybody has got their gifts you know erm <pause dur="short"/> and when people have relied on you and your particular gift or gifts <pause dur="short"/> to get them through things and then they throw it in your face telling you that you're <pause dur="short"/> you're egotistical or you're you relate yourself or what have you that hurts</u>
<u n="791" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0593">that hurts you know they damn well use that gift enough</u>
<u n="793" who="S0592">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0593">that damn well hurts you know</u>
<u n="795" who="S0592" trans="overlap">I mean but it's not</u>
<u n="796" who="S0593">but you do get to the stage <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> where you think <pause dur="short"/> I am not gonna allow you to have me feel like this</u>
<u n="797" who="S0592">it's like when erm <pause dur="short"/> it's not it's not it's different than yours but it's not like people have used it you know the fact that I'm quite academic</u>
<u n="798" who="S0593">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0592">and you know especially in secondary school I'm I'm pretty certain there was a group of girls in particular who thought I was a snob because I did <pause dur="short"/> like I worked hard and I did well they thought I was up myself you know I thought I was up myself thought was better than everyone else</u>
<u n="800" who="S0593">that was probably true</u>
<u n="801" who="S0592" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but I I I never gave any indication to that I never you know treated anyone badly I never said oh you know I'm better than you you know cos I</u>
<u n="802" who="S0593">no</u>
<u n="803" who="S0592">but they they seemed to assume that and I I didn't think that was fair because they had never actually spoken to me or seen what I was like and the fact</u>
<u n="804" who="S0593" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you know what happens if you break down the word assume don't you?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0592">yeah make an arse out of you and me yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0593">yeah well that's all they were doing isn't it?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0592">I know but I don't I don't think that was fair</u>
<u n="808" who="S0593" trans="overlap">but it does hurt and it's not fair I I agree with you it does hurt and it it isn't fair but <pause dur="short"/> at the end of the day <pause dur="short"/> as you get older this gets easier <pause dur="short"/> you have choices to make you can either let their pettiness and what you know is wrong <pause dur="short"/> to get to you <pause dur="short"/> or you can say well you know I'm sorry I know the truth in my heart I know the truth <pause dur="short"/> so I'm not gonna let your misconceptions your misjudgements get to me</u>
<u n="809" who="S0592">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0593">erm you know it is something that is hard to do when you're younger but you you can <pause dur="short"/> as you get older and you practice it you can do it <pause dur="short"/> you it it is possible to do</u>
<u n="811" who="S0592">yeah should probably go and get dressed now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0593">I'm just wondering if it's worth it?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0592">I don't think dad will be happy if she's not</u>
<u n="814" who="S0593">W A L K yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0592" trans="overlap">is he is he coming back this evening?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0593">no he won't be back till tomorrow afternoon</u>
<u n="817" who="S0592">oh</u>
<u n="818" who="S0593">if he was coming back this evening he'd be able to take me to my interview tomorrow</u>
<u n="819" who="S0592">ah that's a good point isn't it?</u>
<u n="820" who="S0593">mm</u>
<u n="821" who="S0592">I didn't think about that</u>
<u n="822" who="S0593">I haven't made the soup yet</u>
<u n="823" who="S0592">no well maybe we should just leave it</u>
<u n="824" who="S0593">she didn't go O U T yesterday</u>
<u n="825" who="S0592">no <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="826" who="S0593">well it's a bit if ifwe take her for erm a W A L K don't wanna say the word we'll have to walk quite a while for her to get a decent walk</u>
<u n="827" who="S0592">no</u>
<u n="828" who="S0593">erm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0592">you just said the word</u>
<u n="830" who="S0593">I know I know I'm sorry it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0592" trans="overlap"><trunc>ma</trunc>maybe we should just play with her and maybe just get her to <unclear/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0593" trans="overlap">erm well we if take her down to the park we're gonna lose the ball</u>
<u n="833" who="S0592">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0593">I feel mean now</u>
<u n="835" who="S0592">so do I <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0593">look at her</u>
<u n="837" who="S0592">well maybe I could start the soup or something <pause dur="short"/> you just tell me how to make it</u>
<u n="838" who="S0593">what and I go out on my own with the dog? <pause dur="short"/> no chance lady</u>
<u n="839" who="S0592"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0593">not happening</u>
<u n="841" who="S0592">okay well then maybe the soup's going to be a bit late</u>
<u n="842" who="S0593">the soup's going to be a bit late come on get your glad rags on</u>
<u n="843" who="S0592">okay</u>
<u n="844" who="S0593">you're not getting out of this</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
