<text id="S8G6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:44</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-05-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0416 S0417</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home Cork</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Equality Vote, Ireland, Politics, School, Birthdays, Birthday Parties, Joking, Marriage, Embarrassing Mothers</topics>
		<activity>Conversation about equality vote</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0416">
				<exactage>12</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bristol, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0417">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>not currently working, caring for toddler</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>some French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0417">so what did you think of the equality vote?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0416">erm I thought I don't really know the results</u>
<u n="3" who="S0417">I think it's erm going to be a yes</u>
<u n="4" who="S0416">oh erm I hope it's going to be yes cos all all my friends and stuff say it's yes say yes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0417">do they?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0416">yes</u>
<u n="7" who="S0417">didn't you say that some people in your school wanted a no?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0416">well yeah but they they seem like the unmature ones and they haven't really they're not very smart</u>
<u n="9" who="S0417">do you think they're a bit homophobic? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0416">I don't know just don't think they're clever enough to to know that just cos you're gay doesn't mean you're not an actual person it just means you're gay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0417">were they? what were they against? people being gay or people having kids if they were gay?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0416" trans="overlap">people people being gay they just said just cos it's wrong they have no real valid point they just it's just eh their take on it erm I hope that when they get older they have a different view on it</u>
<u n="13" who="S0417">yeah how many boys do you think are are like that? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0416">out of my whole year?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0417">mm hm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0416">thirty <pause dur="short"/> thirty forty</u>
<u n="17" who="S0417">really? who are against it?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0416">there's about fifty that are not against it</u>
<u n="19" who="S0417">so thirty were against it that's quite a lot</u>
<u n="20" who="S0416">mm hm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0417">what would you have voted for?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0416">I would have voted yes if I could have</u>
<u n="23" who="S0417">yeah?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0416">cos I think gays should have the same right to marry as anyone else</u>
<u n="25" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0416">cos marrying can be a really good thing for someone</u>
<u n="27" who="S0417">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why do you think marriage would be a good thing for the people?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0416">erm <unclear/> it's kind of like it's kind of like you you share a bond with each other and you really like love each other and you give yourself to each other and all that</u>
<u n="29" who="S0417">and why would that be different than them just being boyfriend or girlfriend or?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0416">erm I think because boyfriend or girlfriend is kind of easier to just break up I think with marry you really are sure that you're never going to break up and you really you just love each other that much that you'd want to spend the rest of your life with them</u>
<u n="31" who="S0417">it's something to do with commitment then?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0417">would you get married?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0417">really?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0416">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I'd do it in like a religious place though unless they were religious</u>
<u n="37" who="S0417">yeah where would you get married?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0416">I don't know a beach? <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> beach sounds like the best place if it's not going to be a church</u>
<u n="39" who="S0417">when do you think's a good age do you think to be married?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0416">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> thirty thirty something? <pause dur="short"/> if not then like <pause dur="short"/> forty</u>
<u n="41" who="S0417">forty thirty?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0417">and you have do you ever want to have kids?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0416">sorry?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0417">want to have kids?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0416">probably cos well a lot of what I've heard from a lot of people is <trunc>ki</trunc> their kids are like their favourite thing in their whole life like that's pretty cool</u>
<u n="47" who="S0417">yeah that's pretty cool isn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0416">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0417">well you're a pretty favourite part of my life <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know it might even be above ice cream but I don't know it depends</u>
<u n="50" who="S0416" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="51" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah I would like to be married one day <pause dur="short"/> what kind of erm? what do you think? do you think you'd need to be have a good job and have a good house and things before you're married?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0416">erm I think <pause dur="short"/> I think you'd need to have a stable life before you're married you don't <trunc>nece</trunc> I don't think you necessarily have to have a good job or a good house you can just have I it doesn't really matter I think as long as you are committed to your partner then that's what marriage is about and not about a good house or a good good <unclear/> like not about having a rich house or anything just about commitment <unclear/> and just loving each other</u>
<u n="53" who="S0417">do you think they might need <trunc>sa</trunc> stability though?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0416">I think stability would be a very a very big factor in it I think it'd be hard to marry if you didn't but I don't think iId let anything stopping marriage <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0417">I've <trunc>ba</trunc> a lot of people getting married and then they're they want kids so they want to bring up kids in a stable way <pause dur="short"/> don't they?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0417">they're not <unclear/> kids about the same time</u>
<u n="58" who="S0416">yeah but I don't think that should stop you from having kids cos if like</u>
<u n="59" who="S0417">you've got to be able to afford to have them <unclear/> pay for them</u>
<u n="60" who="S0416">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="61" who="S0417">they need somewhere to live and enough food</u>
<u n="62" who="S0416">yeah as long as you've got <unclear/> enough food then I think it's fine I don't think there should be any law or <trunc>what</trunc>what or whatever to just to say you can't have kids or marry and that is the situation cos if that brings happiness to your life</u>
<u n="63" who="S0417">yeah but do you <trunc>th</trunc> I think sometimes it's selfish though to just have kids when you can't afford to house them or pay for them</u>
<u n="64" who="S0416" trans="overlap">yeah but obviously so you can pay for them and house them</u>
<u n="65" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0416">but</u>
<u n="67" who="S0417">cos you've got to <unclear/> cos you can't just be asking other people even that even if that means through the government other people</u>
<u n="68" who="S0416" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0417">it's not very fair</u>
<u n="70" who="S0416">I know</u>
<u n="71" who="S0417" trans="overlap">how many <trunc>k</trunc> how many kids would you want? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0416">two that would be good preferably a girl and a boy</u>
<u n="73" who="S0417">yeah what would you? what would you teach the boy and the girl do you think?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0416">to be <trunc>go</trunc> to be kind to others and stuff and you <trunc>sh</trunc> do what do what you want and then you know? like have a good life</u>
<u n="75" who="S0417">would you have any rules?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0417">what kind of rules would you have?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0416">obviously like bedtime and stuff that you can't be going to bed at one o' clock in the morning and stuff</u>
<u n="79" who="S0417">what other kinds of rules? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0416">well feel like there's millions of rules but I don't think I could go through all of them</u>
<u n="81" who="S0417">what about? what would you do if they were being mean to other people at school?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0416">erm if they were being mean to someone else at school <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I think I I'd punish them in some way</u>
<u n="83" who="S0417">how would you punish them?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0416">I'd punish them for two days by <pause dur="short"/> no one day by erm one day by maybe not letting them either do their favourite sport or their favourite game but then but then after that's like expired I'd talk to them and I'd talk to them about it and make them understand why you shouldn't be mean cos otherwise it can hurt them and then like you should also treat other people like how you'd like to be treated</u>
<u n="85" who="S0417">what if they just said rubbish and didn't ignored you</u>
<u n="86" who="S0416">erm if they did that then <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what I'd do I don't think I can just make my mind up what I'd do right now I'm not even an adult yet</u>
<u n="87" who="S0417">no <pause dur="short"/> does it feel like a long time ago then when you were a child yourself?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0417">or does it feel like yesterday?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0416">I am a child</u>
<u n="91" who="S0417">yeah but like oh okay when you were like younger toddler and things does that feel like long long time ago?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0416">yeah that feels a long time ago</u>
<u n="93" who="S0417">can you remember much about it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="95" who="S0417">no? <pause dur="short"/> you don't remember going to the park and the graveyard?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="97" who="S0417">no?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0417">erm do you remember your room with a big leaf on top of your bed?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0416">yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="101" who="S0417">well that was before you were four <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0416">that's I <trunc>re</trunc></u>
<u n="103" who="S0417">is there any favourite memories that were your first memories?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0416">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I remember going to Disneyland for the first time that was probably one of them eh that was probably one of my earliest favourite memories trying to think <pause dur="long"/> I don't know I can't think of anything earlier maybe if you reminded me of something earlier? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0417">erm do you remember going to nursery school?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0416">yeah I remember someone pushing me off the slide and then I had to go to hospital</u>
<u n="107" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0416">but that's all I remember</u>
<u n="109" who="S0417">yeah that wasn't very</u>
<u n="110" who="S0416">and then I remember going into like the sleep room and it'd be all dark and then you'd go to sleep <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0417">do you remember playing in the garden there?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0417">do you remember sitting round and having your beaker of juice? and your sandwiches for lunch?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0417">and do you remember <unclear/> you had some mates there? <pause dur="short"/> do you remember you had a birthday party and we went to a playground and and you had a pirate pirate ship?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0416" trans="overlap">mm yeah I remember that I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't actually remember that I remember photos I remember photos</u>
<u n="117" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0416">I don't remember it then <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0417">yeah that was quite fun <pause dur="long"/> so do you think do you think all society should be equal? everyone should be able to marry whoever they like?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0416">yes <pause dur="short"/> well as long as both of the people want to marry</u>
<u n="121" who="S0417">your top's inside out</u>
<u n="122" who="S0416">indeed</u>
<u n="123" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we'll have to change it</u>
<u n="124" who="S0416">not right now</u>
<u n="125" who="S0417">no not right now <pause dur="short"/> so what are you looking forward to this summer?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0416">swimming a lot I'm going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0417">mm hm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0416">with my best friend and there's also a lake rented out got a lake rented out that no one uses which my dad's girlfriend rented out and it's like a lake and there's diving boards into the lake and you can like that'll be really fun</u>
<u n="129" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0416">I don't know what else we're doing there but I imagine it'll be fun</u>
<u n="131" who="S0417">and you're still going to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0416">yes I am I'm looking forward to that as well see see all the nice things</u>
<u n="133" who="S0417" trans="overlap">you're lucky you've got loads of holidays</u>
<u n="134" who="S0416">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think we might go to something else as well if we have time</u>
<u n="135" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0416">so I'm looking forward to that</u>
<u n="137" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0416">also looking forward to camping <unclear>no actually no I can't</unclear> camp I'm looking forward to going over to my friend's house for a sleepover <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="139" who="S0417">when's that?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0416">that is somewhere somewhere after the exams not sure of the date exactly</u>
<u n="141" who="S0417">whose friend's house?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0416">erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0417"><unclear>okay</unclear> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0416">yeah <pause dur="short"/> iId say that's it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0417">and do you know any more about the birthday party?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0416">erm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0417">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0416">eh no well you said I can't go</u>
<u n="149" who="S0417">I said I <trunc>ca</trunc> you can't you can't be kind of unsupervised <pause dur="short"/> but where you have to let me know a bit more about it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0416">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's just like you just go there then you go up to the cinema and you come out of the cinema then you go home</u>
<u n="151" who="S0417">cos if it's just the cinema that's okay or if you have a bit to eat or something?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I'm pretty <trunc>su</trunc> I'm pretty sure that's what they're doing they're like before going to the cinema or after they're like going to like Starbucks or something which is in the in the place and just getting a drink and then going to the cinema come back and then <unclear/> there something</u>
<u n="153" who="S0417">yeah I'm sure you could do some of that so just just keep me up to date</u>
<u n="154" who="S0416" trans="overlap">yeah but that that that would be unsupervised</u>
<u n="155" who="S0417">well I'm sure some of it could be unsupervised I'm just not happy about you wandering around beforehand and afterwards like unsupervised <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0416">so so are you okay with this? are you? are you okay with this?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0416">I I go into <anon type="place"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s there and everything and everyone's there and we go to get like I don't know what let's just say let's just say we go to get something to eat and drink before the cinema we go we go somewhere erm all together we get something we eat it and then we go to the cinema then we watch the cinema then we go out the cinema then I wait to be collected</u>
<u n="159" who="S0417">yeah but what I'd probably do is say hang around the shopping centre while you're having something to eat before you go into the cinema so that I'm around there</u>
<u n="160" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0417">I'm not necessarily sat down with you the whole time but just <pause dur="short"/> when you go in and then to the to the cinema afterwards <pause dur="short"/> and then pick you up after the cinema that's probably okay I imagine</u>
<u n="162" who="S0416">so you're saying you'll walk around in the shopping centre?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0417">well we'll see but yeah something like that yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0416">will all of my friends know you're there?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0417">yeah well so what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? if that's your choice</u>
<u n="166" who="S0416">but</u>
<u n="167" who="S0417">if erm if that if <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0416">we <trunc>a</trunc> we also need to bring money for the cinema and popcorn and things and the bite to eat before</u>
<u n="169" who="S0417">yeah but you have to do you have to get times for me next week don't you?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0416" trans="overlap">June six</u>
<u n="171" who="S0417">I know but like times</u>
<u n="172" who="S0416">oh okay</u>
<u n="173" who="S0417">that kind of thing have you had any more thoughts about what you <trunc>m</trunc> might like to do for your birthday?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0417">no?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0416">no everything I thought would <unclear/> is go over to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house and have a have a sleepover or something? but you said that's my birthday so I can't do that</u>
<u n="177" who="S0417">you're having a sleepover anyway somebody else's <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0416"><unclear/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0417">you're having a sleepover anyway <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0416">it's just <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0417">it's just what? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0416">nothing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0417">if it's like one of your mates saying can I have a birthday over here? sleepover over here? and he has his birthday over here it's just not really very polite</u>
<u n="184" who="S0416">no <unclear>I could</unclear></u>
<u n="185" who="S0417"><unclear/> give something else you like to do</u>
<u n="186" who="S0416" trans="overlap">it doesn't <trunc>ne</trunc> it doesn't need to be my birthday over there it doesn't need to be all about anyone there it's just <unclear/> I just want to do something that I like and that would be going round my friend's house doesn't need to be for my birthday it's just that's what I would like to do and it doesn't <trunc>ha</trunc> I don't <trunc>ha</trunc> I don't have to celebrate my birthday there</u>
<u n="187" who="S0417" trans="overlap">you're you've been at <pause dur="short"/> well I'd have I've said I would let you have a sleepover so isn't that the same thing?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0416">okay so I can?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0417">you can have a sleepover at somebody's house</u>
<u n="190" who="S0416">okay so not two?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0417">hm?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0416">so not two sleepovers during the summer?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0417">well why don't people come around here?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0416">because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s asleep <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s asleep and it's really really kind of bad to have a sleepover here</u>
<u n="195" who="S0417">why is it bad?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0416">because it's just can't be as loud cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s asleep and like you have the TV you have the TV for most of the evening so then we couldn't use the TV and we'd all just be up in my room with not much space and they'd all have like sleeping bags and be all cramped up in my room so that'd be really but if I went to my friend's house we could like bring sleeping bags and sleep in their living room we could go on the Xbox we could be as loud as you want</u>
<u n="197" who="S0417">I see but <unclear/> something else you might like to do do you think there might be something at erm <anon type="place"/> like a laser thing or something? I think I don't know whether people might have to pay</u>
<u n="198" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it's just you said you said that erm can't do anything that involves money <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0417"><unclear/> haven't got much money <pause dur="short"/> no I mean it'd be like the cinema like you're you're paying for your own cinema aren't you? with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0417">so maybe if if everybody pays for their own <unclear>laser crystals</unclear> or something I don't know we could just find out couldn't we?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0416">yeah I'd like to go paintballing</u>
<u n="203" who="S0417">not paintballing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're too young to do that anyway and it's too like that would mean driving a long way and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0417">it's a hard life isn't it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/>? no that costs way too much <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="207" who="S0417">think about it must do something okay?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0416">can't really think of anything I'd like to do <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0417">aw I don't know what about?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0416">I can think of tons of things that I'd love to do but can't do</u>
<u n="211" who="S0417">could always have another cinema <trunc>d</trunc>date at <anon type="place"/> a different film</u>
<u n="212" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0417" trans="overlap">for your birthday a second time meeting up</u>
<u n="214" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0417">erm well you could <pause dur="short"/> yeah find out if there's anything at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0416">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0417" trans="overlap">that's like suitable cos I think they've a roller-skating thing as well</u>
<u n="218" who="S0416">I don't like roller-skating I'd like to either go go-karting laser tag or <anon type="place"/> go to the cinema</u>
<u n="219" who="S0417">don't they have a laser tag at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they do</u>
<u n="221" who="S0417">that might be something different if you're going to the cinema one time and if you're having a sleepover another time maybe be cool if you want to go laser tagging another time</u>
<u n="222" who="S0416">okay I'll go laser tag</u>
<u n="223" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just find out and see ask your mates if it would be okay for them to pay and then just</u>
<u n="224" who="S0416">I don't know how much laser tag is <pause dur="short"/> I need to find that out</u>
<u n="225" who="S0417">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> might not be too bad <pause dur="short"/> could ask the girls if they want to go as well?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0416">don't <unclear>think</unclear> they'd come</u>
<u n="227" who="S0417">could ask them?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0416">did ask they won't come</u>
<u n="229" who="S0417">they might like laser tag <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might be up for it? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might be up for it</u>
<u n="230" who="S0416">I bet you ten euro <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not up for it</u>
<u n="231" who="S0417">well what about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0416">erm I bet three euro <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not up for it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0417">aw there's no harm trying though is there? maybe your mum would be up for it hm?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="235" who="S0417">I've played it before <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0416">yeah but</u>
<u n="237" who="S0417" trans="overlap">would I would I cramp your style? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0416">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0417">you just go round going <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0416" trans="overlap">it would it <trunc>woul</trunc> it would be really weird</u>
<u n="241" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> like that</u>
<u n="242" who="S0416">that would really be embarrassing</u>
<u n="243" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really? what? having your own dear mother there would be embarrassing?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0416" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0417">how so?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0416">yes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0417">I wouldn't be embarrassed if you came to my birthday</u>
<u n="248" who="S0416">yeah that's because it's it's like you having your birthday with all like vintage things and me going oh yes oh yes vintage shoes something like that it doesn't work we and then all my friends would make fun of me <unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> tell them I'd beat them up if they made fun of you</u>
<u n="250" who="S0416" trans="overlap">they would beat me up if that happened</u>
<u n="251" who="S0417">no they wouldn't because they'd be so scared of me <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="253" who="S0417">they'd be like oh my god got to keep on the good side of that one because like she's going to come down on us like a ton of bricks <pause dur="short"/> what if I'll beat them all if I beat you all at laser tag then they won't <trunc>me</trunc> make fun of me</u>
<u n="254" who="S0416">you won't beat anyone</u>
<u n="255" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you have so little faith in me</u>
<u n="256" who="S0416">I know that's cos you hate guns you hate killing you hate everything to do with guns and killing and laser tag is guns and killing but without paintballs <pause dur="short"/> and lasers</u>
<u n="257" who="S0417">well to be fair I don't think anybody dies</u>
<u n="258" who="S0416">no nobody dies in paintballing either</u>
<u n="259" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah but maybe we better check on that <unclear/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0416" trans="overlap">paintball is just <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>las</trunc> okay laser tag and paintball are just Black Ops IRL tone down the killing and violence laser tag is level one paintball is level two</u>
<u n="261" who="S0417">actual killing is <trunc>le</trunc>level three is it?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0416">yeah it's war</u>
<u n="263" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I see so I'm not sure about <unclear>this escalation</unclear></u>
<u n="264" who="S0416">paintballing is probably the the best one to do cos that's the most cool thing <pause dur="short"/> cos you don't kill each other and you just can go through the woods and there'll be like a tank that'll fire like massive paintballs at you</u>
<u n="265" who="S0417">then there's then there's war would you like to go to war?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0416">no I'm not stupid you get nothing out of war <pause dur="short"/> there are people in my class that think they should go to war but they're they're they're as dumb as bricks</u>
<u n="267" who="S0417">dumb as bricks?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0416">bricks aren't smart</u>
<u n="269" who="S0417">any of them them your friends?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/> not really</u>
<u n="271" who="S0417">so what like some of the people in your class? do they really get on your nerves?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0417">who really gets on your nerves?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0416">one guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he left the school but he did get on my own nerves cos he was just so <unclear/> he always used to lie and he was just <pause dur="short"/> anything that all the cool people used to say he used to copy and try and be like them like lying like said he got detention even though he didn't <pause dur="short"/> and then <unclear/> punch me and try get in fights with me</u>
<u n="275" who="S0417">well that's not very nice did you tell him his mum beat him?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0416">stop</u>
<u n="277" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what's the matter?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0416">it's like no</u>
<u n="279" who="S0417">is it embarrassing? am I embarrassing you? where's the fun of being a parent if you can't embarrass your kid? spend so long bringing you up and giving you all this stuff and it's all quite hard work so you might as well get a bit of enjoyment out of it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0416">you <vocal desc="sigh"/> you got <trunc>ups</trunc> you got upset when I accidentally embarrassed you I didn't mean to</u>
<u n="281" who="S0417">no that was different that was actually kind of putting me down I mean I'm teasing you by saying I'm going to beat your friends to stick up for you it's different <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0416">yeah but how do you know I won't get the same feeling you did?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0417">I'm not doing the same as you did</u>
<u n="284" who="S0416">yeah I didn't even mean it I didn't even know what I was doing so you might not <unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0417" trans="overlap">but putting on my voice and complaining that I was erm funny with you about the computer and just being really kind of <vocal desc="misc"/> that's not that wasn't very nice that was quite mean doesn't <trunc>mea</trunc> doesn't mean you meant to be mean I understand that you didn't mean to be mean but you were mean</u>
<u n="286" who="S0416">and you might not mean to be mean and like cos I might get the same feeling when all my friends are making fun of me it's not a good feeling maybe it's a good feeling for you maybe</u>
<u n="287" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><trunc>ho</trunc>how was I making fun of you? by saying I was going to <trunc>be</trunc>beat your friends?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0416">it's not making fun of me it's just my friends are making fun of me cos of that</u>
<u n="289" who="S0417">but I'm telling you I'm not saying it in front of you and your friends that's different I'm telling you here</u>
<u n="290" who="S0416">it's just my friends that would be a thing that my mum <unclear/> with me and my friends I'd like</u>
<u n="291" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0416">make fun of me</u>
<u n="293" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> I'm not going to go it's okay</u>
<u n="294" who="S0416" trans="overlap">okay okay</u>
<u n="295" who="S0417">I was having <unclear/> with you</u>
<u n="296" who="S0416">that wasn't fun <unclear/> find it fun it's just very cliché and <unclear/> kind of heard it all before so no offence but</u>
<u n="297" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I see</u>
<u n="298" who="S0416">it's not like it was unexpected <unclear>humour</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0417">I see</u>
<u n="300" who="S0416">it's kind of <pause dur="short"/> not really <trunc>humrio</trunc> humorous <unclear/> in my opinion sorry</u>
<u n="301" who="S0417"><unclear/> you telling me your mum's not funny</u>
<u n="302" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I'm just sharing my opinion <unclear/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0416">okay then you are <unclear/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0417">am I funny?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0417">am I really humorous?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0417">should I be on stage?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0417">am I like the best mum ever?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0417">in the whole universe? <pause dur="short"/> if I acted a breakdance in front of you and your mates you'd just be wow</u>
<u n="314" who="S0416">you'd trip over your leg</u>
<u n="315" who="S0417">even if I tripped over my leg</u>
<u n="316" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0417">I see if I tripped over my leg what would happen? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0416">I'd go up to my room and just play on my laptop well first I'd help help you up <unclear/> go up to my room try forget it</u>
<u n="319" who="S0417">put your head in your hands and cry?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0416">no <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't cry for that no reason to</u>
<u n="321" who="S0417">I see <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0416">I'd be a bit annoyed</u>
<u n="323" who="S0417">would you? why?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0416">cos if my friends were there then they would make fun of me I'd feel quite sad that would make me sad</u>
<u n="325" who="S0417">so you'd <trunc>cu</trunc> succumb to the rule of the mob peer pressure</u>
<u n="326" who="S0416"><unclear/> you're thinking from like a media or TV show erm level cos like as always <unclear/> and they always embarrass the teenager or boy and they go oh and all their friends make fun of them and they're just like er and then you don't really feel sorry for them cos they're TV characters but I'm a real person and I would actually feel really sad</u>
<u n="327" who="S0417">you're a real person?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0416">yeah that's not my point <pause dur="short"/> it like is <unclear/> I would actually feel really sad you'd probably feel happy cos she'd be like the mum on the TV the funny mum that you'd laughed at but I'd actually be kind of sad <pause dur="short"/> cos things aren't like TV in real life</u>
<u n="329" who="S0417">I don't want you to be sad son</u>
<u n="330" who="S0416">then don't do it</u>
<u n="331" who="S0417">I won't do it</u>
<u n="332" who="S0416">okay cool thank you <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0417">so <pause dur="short"/> shall we stop <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
