<text id="S8K9">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:39:03</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The countryside, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>moving house, work, Oman</topics>
		<activity>Couple go for a walk in the countryside.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> so we're finally going then</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">I know <pause dur="short"/> it's almost difficult to believe now</u>
<u n="3" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you think they've booked the ticket?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0024">hmm?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144">well they should tell us on Saturday shouldn't they</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024">Saturday yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they're on holiday today so <pause dur="short"/> holiday tomorrow</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he said he's passed it on to someone called V</u>
<u n="8" who="S0024">yeah who's this? See I was confused cos he used so much text speak in his email <pause dur="short"/> I was trying to work out whether V was some sort of code for something else</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0024">I was like what? I mean surely her whoever's name it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> it isn't just a V is it <pause dur="short"/> so and we don't know who they are so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it's probably difficult to pronounce</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024">I was wondering if it meant we <pause dur="short"/> we will buy your ticket</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what with a German accent?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024">yeah once we've got that ticket <pause dur="short"/> see the thing that worries me is getting back in in August</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">and you know how quickly we can ask them <pause dur="short"/> look when are our? When are the August? When's the August break? Cos you said we could have August off <pause dur="short"/> when can we book our flight back for?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024">I mean should we ask that before we go?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144">well maybe we should send an email just</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024" trans="overlap">there's a few things you know</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's all been agreed upon before</u>
<u n="22" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but I don't want to sound like a cow <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to sound like <pause dur="short"/> cos already there's been so many emails especially from me saying well what about this and what about that? Because because of</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they haven't been very forthcoming with information</u>
<u n="24" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no not at all <pause dur="short"/> and they it seemed like they were quite offended by my questioning so it's like oh do you just take it on faith</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's quite a big thing just moving half way across the world</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024">yeah yeah they should understand that <pause dur="short"/> but if you look at erm who works in that department <pause dur="short"/> I mean there there's a lot of <trunc>p</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people from all over the world but from English speaking countries you've got the <trunc>In</trunc> Indian lot <pause dur="short"/> and then erm you've got erm it looks like somebody may be from Eastern Europe actually <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> she looks quite funky anyway <pause dur="short"/> er got all these colours and looks really nice</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="28" who="S0024">and er then I don't know <pause dur="short"/> there's there's the bloke at the top <pause dur="short"/> sounds like he's got some sort of Western name <pause dur="short"/> and then two women</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="30" who="S0024">that's it</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144">what in the department?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0024">well no and all the rest are from India or from Oman or from the maybe a few other places</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh really? So there's no other English people there?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">there's just <pause dur="short"/> it looks like there might be three</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">but they might who knows where they're from? I don't know</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">ah well it's time to get excited now though</u>
<u n="38" who="S0024" trans="overlap">there's probably <pause dur="short"/> well there probably are more <pause dur="short"/> there probably are more <pause dur="short"/> they've just got names that I don't recognize <pause dur="short"/> but like their recruitment thing it doesn't look like they're that experienced with getting people over <pause dur="short"/> it's not the colleges of technology and they're just like yeah get loads and loads of erm people from English speaking countries to come</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024">they seem this university seems more local <pause dur="short"/> we want to support the local <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's what they say on their thing</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024">omanis get preference to anybody else apart from maybe the English language speaking courses</u>
<u n="43" who="S0144">well that's good</u>
<u n="44" who="S0024">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it should be interesting <pause dur="short"/> the guy at the top <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten his name now <pause dur="short"/> I was trying to look at their names so that when we meet them I'll be able to remember at bit easier <pause dur="short"/> you know what it's like</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0024">you have like</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144">well you get introduced by to a hundred people</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024" trans="overlap">forty <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then you're <trunc>e</trunc> and then you have to try and remember everybody</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">and then you introduce yourself to someone and they say oh we've already met</u>
<u n="50" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144">oh sorry</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I  I might  I might keep just having a look at the <trunc>pic</trunc> cos they've got the pictures and the names and just every day have a look and read through <pause dur="short"/> you never know it might help when when it comes to meeting them in person</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0024">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's it's going to be exciting</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024"><unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0144">but you said that there's no direct flight</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024">there's a direct <pause dur="short"/> well from what I can see there's a direct flight from Gatwick</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">really? That's strange I thought Heathrow would go</u>
<u n="60" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah there was the erm Gulf Air <pause dur="short"/> but Gulf Air has just been bought out by Bahrain and they're not doing the flight</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">Gulf Air's been bought out by?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024">Bahrain</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">Bahrain?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">well it said something like that</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0024">well that might not be true <pause dur="short"/> it said something along those lines <pause dur="short"/> I think that's what I read</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">oh so we're going to have to go to Bahrain first?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024"><trunc>N</trunc> no <pause dur="short"/> there's plenty of airlines that go there but you know if you could take Qatar Air you stop in Qatar and and then go to Muscat <pause dur="short"/> if you take erm er I've forgotten the names <pause dur="short"/> the other big</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">Emirates</u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">Emirates <pause dur="short"/> is that Dubai?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144">er</u>
<u n="72" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0024">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it Emirates stops in Dubai and I'm really worried <pause dur="short"/> some of them are like four or five hours wait in the middle of the night</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144">ouch</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">it's a longer flight than I thought</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0024">I thought it was only six hours</u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">is it longer than that?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's at least eight</u>
<u n="81" who="S0144">oh shit <pause dur="short"/> oh well the good thing I suppose is we're only gonna be working five miles from the airport</u>
<u n="82" who="S0024">yeah I'm happy about that <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad we didn't take the Salalah job <pause dur="short"/> like just the big</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah that's quite nice just for going on holidays or coming back here</u>
<u n="84" who="S0024">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144">Don't have to piss about do we</u>
<u n="86" who="S0024">and just having the big city so near</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144">yeah and if</u>
<u n="88" who="S0024">all the amenities that you can get in the bigger city than you can in a little place</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144" trans="overlap">if there's a direct flight to Gatwick we can stay at your sisters'</u>
<u n="90" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> which is maybe what we should have told them <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0024">we should have said whichever one's easiest</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think cos that Omani Air go from Gatwick</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0024">like the the price range is crazy <pause dur="short"/> it goes from like er four hundred pounds to British Airways which is one thousand four hundred pounds <pause dur="short"/> british Airways is like three times the price of any of the others</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah British Airways are expensive</u>
<u n="98" who="S0024">yeah but none of the plane <pause dur="short"/> the I've never been on a really really good British Airways plane</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> I know they're rubbish</u>
<u n="100" who="S0024">I think</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144">the best ones are well the Middle Eastern ones</u>
<u n="102" who="S0024">Qatar</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144">Qatar <pause dur="short"/> emirates</u>
<u n="104" who="S0024">yeah and I read about Omani Air and they seem alright too</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144" trans="overlap">they're nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0024">but they do have like the second hand planes from the others but</u>
<u n="107" who="S0144">do they serve alcohol on the on these ones?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> doubt it</u>
<u n="109" who="S0144">you need alcohol for an eight hour journey on a plane <pause dur="short"/> god I hate flying</u>
<u n="110" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but can you imagine <pause dur="short"/> like here's a possible scenario <pause dur="short"/> is that they pick us up from the airport and take us straight to the school <pause dur="short"/> that's a possible scenario</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144">ah no surely not</u>
<u n="112" who="S0024">and do you remember how wrecked we were? Not wrecked we were just really tired when we did that flight from Thailand to Korea</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144" trans="overlap">Korea <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0024">and we didn't know where we were <pause dur="short"/> we didn't know what we were talking about <pause dur="short"/> I I have no memory of it</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> I think that's probably the most exhausted I've ever been in my life actually</u>
<u n="116" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144">I don't know</u>
<u n="118" who="S0024">why? I don't know</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144">I don't think the weather helped either cos we went from about thirty degrees to to zero</u>
<u n="120" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ah it was cold <pause dur="short"/> yeah I remember that with that agent <pause dur="short"/> they lent us some money</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144" trans="overlap">we didn't have a coat did we</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024">no we didn't even have any money</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">and then you got Bird Flu</u>
<u n="124" who="S0024">or whatever it was yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144">it was a bit of a disaster that wasn't it</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh god yeah that was awful <pause dur="short"/> few weeks</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">yeah well well they're flying us on Tuesday</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144">so then we've only got Wednesday before the weekend anyway</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024">ah <pause dur="short"/> right so I I reckon they'll be alright actually</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144">so Wednesday they might just let us settle in</u>
<u n="132" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144">erm hopefully and</u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">or pop into the school <pause dur="short"/> have a look around</u>
<u n="135" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hope they don't expect us to start teaching on like the first day</u>
<u n="136" who="S0024">erm I I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> I I think if they've got the classes covered already then they're just going to say you know leave it this week</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd like some time just them kind of showing us the ropes <pause dur="short"/> at British Council we got a week didn't we</u>
<u n="138" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm mhm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144">I can't see them giving us a week</u>
<u n="140" who="S0024" trans="overlap">more than that <pause dur="short"/> I think we got ten days induction didn't we?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't see that kind <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't they'd have an induction process in place <pause dur="short"/> cos like you said they're not used to flying people over</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024"><trunc>W</trunc> yeah but hopefully because the the acting head of the department looks like he's British or er or foreign anyway he should understand that the process <pause dur="short"/> you know of moving abroad and stuff so hopefully he'll do something nice</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024">oh God</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144">well Indian food</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well you never know until you get there <pause dur="short"/> it could be a disaster or it could be wonderful</u>
<u n="147" who="S0144">ah but proper food again though</u>
<u n="148" who="S0024">food yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I won't be cooking for a while</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144">and you've got all those hikes as well <pause dur="short"/> and the turtles</u>
<u n="150" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it will take us quite a while to go down</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and frankincense</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024">when when is the turtle season?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144">it's all year I think</u>
<u n="154" who="S0024">no it can't be</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">it must be one part of the year that they come up to the beach</u>
<u n="157" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no idea</u>
<u n="158" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it should be <pause dur="short"/> exploring again</u>
<u n="159" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's going to be good isn't it</u>
<u n="160" who="S0024">just worried about a house as well <pause dur="short"/> we had such a beautiful house in Tunisia</u>
<u n="161" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0024">oh such a beautiful house</u>
<u n="163" who="S0144">well I'd be happy with an apartment <pause dur="short"/> like a modern apartment I think</u>
<u n="164" who="S0024">I'd be happy with a modern apartment if we can get it furnished and if there's</u>
<u n="165" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah well it has <pause dur="short"/> we have to get it furnished</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we will won't we</u>
<u n="167" who="S0144">oh <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024">if there's some sort of erm gym or hopefully a swimming pool near by <pause dur="short"/> that would be nice because if you imagine how hot it is right it's going to be hard hard hard work for us to go you know exploring in the markets all day <pause dur="short"/> but you need some sort of refreshing activity like swimming</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0024">and like all of their swimming pools are going to have to be closed off because you know and they'll <pause dur="short"/> they might even have women's hours and men's hours and we'll have to go separately</u>
<u n="171" who="S0144">that's true</u>
<u n="172" who="S0024">apart from in the big hotels</u>
<u n="173" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0024">so</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144">ah I hadn't thought of that</u>
<u n="176" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">and the same with the gym as well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144">might have men's hours and women's hours for that</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144">they probably would actually wouldn't they</u>
<u n="182" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> unless they have erm <pause dur="short"/> or they might have two separate rooms</u>
<u n="183" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0024">yeah and I think we're gonna have a lot more of a divided lifestyle from what we're used to</u>
<u n="185" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">we're used to doing everything together</u>
<u n="187" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they've even got restaurants haven't they where you have to go in different rooms</u>
<u n="188" who="S0024">yeah but we won't go in them <pause dur="short"/> they they haven't got that many in Oman <pause dur="short"/> that's more of a a Saudi thing</u>
<u n="189" who="S0144">yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think around Muscat it will be fairly</u>
<u n="190" who="S0024">yeah it's gonna be fairly open</u>
<u n="191" who="S0144">fairly Westernised</u>
<u n="192" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've seen  I've seen  videos of tourists walking around there in their shorts and stuff</u>
<u n="193" who="S0144" trans="overlap">especially as we're near the airport</u>
<u n="194" who="S0024">like typical tourists do</u>
<u n="195" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0024">I wouldn't mind buying a few more outfits <pause dur="short"/> still looking for a tunic <pause dur="short"/> can't find tunics anywhere here</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024">you know something that will go with all of my skirts or something <pause dur="short"/> cos that's important to feel comfortable isn't it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024">at work straight away <pause dur="short"/> cos you know what you know people might not say anything but they judge they they don't mean to but you can't help judging people by how they look can do you</u>
<u n="201" who="S0144">no you can't help it no</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024"><trunc>Y</trunc> you if I'd like</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">it's quite important as a teacher to give the right image</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024" trans="overlap">if they didn't approve of something I was wearing and I was only wearing it because I didn't have anything else you know</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">say like our baggages didn't arrive or something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know and you turn up at school <pause dur="short"/> that's an immediate impression <pause dur="short"/> immediate</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">impression on you no matter what the circumstances <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144">what turning up in hot pants and smelling of gin?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">well and drinking on the plane</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144">yeah and getting duty free bottles clanking</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024" trans="overlap">clanking <pause dur="short"/> in the see through bags</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144">hello</u>
<u n="214" who="S0024">hello erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah actually that's a good point <pause dur="short"/> on our erm hand luggage we should make sure we've got a a big bag</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah we don't no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we should buy any booze actually</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144">well if we do it would have to go in the main luggage cos I'm not carrying it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024">you can't put it in the main luggage</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> when we get to the airport</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024">you can't cos duty free is the other side <pause dur="short"/> so you've already checked in your bags</u>
<u n="221" who="S0144">no I mean when we arrive in Muscat</u>
<u n="222" who="S0024">oh there might be some just as you come out?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0144">or put the not so your not holding it in your hands</u>
<u n="224" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ah okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's doable isn't it <pause dur="short"/> we can do that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that will be alright <pause dur="short"/> they'll wonder what on earth they've got themselves into if we like totter off the plane with a couple bottles of gin each</u>
<u n="225" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0024">and we don't even drink that much <pause dur="short"/> we're just being prepared</u>
<u n="227" who="S0144">it's got to last us all year</u>
<u n="228" who="S0024">right so there's a couple of things we need to write to him about <pause dur="short"/> one is I'm really sorry but we don't want to stay in single accommodation at the school with the students</u>
<u n="229" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0024">sharing toilets with them</u>
<u n="231" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="232" who="S0024">that's just sounds like a a summer school</u>
<u n="233" who="S0144">not when we first get there <pause dur="short"/> god no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0024">that sounds like a summer school to me and that sounds like a nightmare</u>
<u n="235" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no I don't mind paying for a hotel until we find somewhere</u>
<u n="236" who="S0024">well we're just going to have to forfeit the costs aren't we</u>
<u n="237" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0024">I mean they take  they take  some of the money off for that accommodation anyway <pause dur="short"/> it's not like they're giving it to us for free</u>
<u n="239" who="S0144">yeah yeah I saw that</u>
<u n="240" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see we were treated so good before <pause dur="short"/> like er lots of people they don't understand that we're not getting a free accommodation and stuff like that this time <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not very friendly induction is it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="242" who="S0024">it's not like you remember when we went to Tunisia? Wow they're gonna help us out with a hotel for a week <pause dur="short"/> oh relax</u>
<u n="243" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0024">it kind of calms you down a bit doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> lets you</u>
<u n="245" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0024">oh they're being so nice <pause dur="short"/> I mean and they they even said do you need any? Do you need to borrow any money? We can get it for you right today and you can pay it off from your pay check <pause dur="short"/> I mean really really made it comfortable</u>
<u n="247" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> here's Salma <pause dur="short"/> she'll go through the newspapers and phone up all the  all the  landlords</u>
<u n="248" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0144">and we've got a driver to take you around</u>
<u n="250" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0144">we're not going to have any of that <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we are anyway</u>
<u n="252" who="S0024">we'll be lucky if we <trunc>e</trunc> if we do but er</u>
<u n="253" who="S0144">yeah we just need to speak to as many people as we can cos that's the main thing for me is finding a house as quickly as possible</u>
<u n="254" who="S0024">well especially if we're paying for a hotel</u>
<u n="255" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0024">oh my God</u>
<u n="257" who="S0144">yeah the first three months is going to be pretty tough</u>
<u n="258" who="S0024">I mean and if there's no hotels right near the college and we have to get a taxi every day or what you know <pause dur="short"/> I mean we won't know that until we arrive you know is there somebody in town who can pick us up and take us to work for a few like until we get settled</u>
<u n="259" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah well that works itself out though doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> there's no point</u>
<u n="260" who="S0024">yeah but taxis are hard to get in Oman</u>
<u n="261" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0024">you don't wave them down <pause dur="short"/> it's not Tunisia <pause dur="short"/> or it's not Asia</u>
<u n="263" who="S0144">can't you?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0024">it's they're not so many <pause dur="short"/> everybody has their own car so there's less taxis <pause dur="short"/> unless people drink <pause dur="short"/> you know in Tunisia they still drank quite a lot didn't they and so they didn't want to drive or something <pause dur="short"/> and the women travelled on there own quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> so you'd get a lot of the women getting taxis and a lot of the students getting taxis to school because like the whole family was working</u>
<u n="265" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well surely that's the same isn't it? I mean how are the students going to get to school?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0024">they've probably all got their own cars they're they're university students <pause dur="short"/> cos you used to get the teenagers you know getting taxis everywhere</u>
<u n="267" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know but we'll see won't we</u>
<u n="268" who="S0024">mm yeah there's no point speculating</u>
<u n="269" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="270" who="S0024">find out when we get there but that is important that we can go home <pause dur="short"/> not home <pause dur="short"/> back to a place together and discuss our day and you know any woes that have come up or any good things we can talk about before the next day</u>
<u n="271" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I agree <pause dur="short"/> I don't won't to be going into a dorm room</u>
<u n="272" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Cos we're not <trunc>e</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah we won't even have a phone <pause dur="short"/> we won't even have a phone</u>
<u n="273" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0024">right <pause dur="short"/> so are you gonna do that part?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0024">can you?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do what?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0024">email them</u>
<u n="281" who="S0144">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0024">yeah if you can email</u>
<u n="283" who="S0144">oh what's that smell? That's horrible</u>
<u n="284" who="S0024">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> all the drains have flooded from the rain</u>
<u n="285" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> should be fine <pause dur="short"/> it's just always going to be a bit worrying isn't it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">well of course it is</u>
<u n="288" who="S0024">it's just this big break <pause dur="short"/> I think if we'd have gone straight away then er it would be a different story wouldn't it</u>
<u n="289" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos well I've slowed right down <pause dur="short"/> just my thinking and everything</u>
<u n="290" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it's the whole pace of life</u>
<u n="291" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's one because I haven't been doing anything <pause dur="short"/> and two because I've been in the countryside where not much is going on</u>
<u n="292" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144">and then we're going to be straight into a hundred miles an hour again</u>
<u n="294" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> well we have to speed it up this week</u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">how? Which way are you going?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">this way <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to speed it up a a little bit</u>
<u n="297" who="S0144">have we got time to go this way? It's getting dark</u>
<u n="298" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> speed it up a little bit and I don't know <pause dur="short"/> keep busy cos our bodies are already already going to be in the shock of jet lag so yeah I don't want to feel it too much do you</u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">what are you most looking forward to about?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024">I'm looking forward to all the shops and the markets <pause dur="short"/> markets <pause dur="short"/> I just love souks <pause dur="short"/> even if it's a busy souk I don't care <pause dur="short"/> I just  I just  love the vibe</u>
<u n="301" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024">you know like the big big busy ones I can only do once a month or something <pause dur="short"/> but at least they're there if you want to</u>
<u n="303" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what the big malls?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024">no the massive souks</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144">oh yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024">in the medina or something</u>
<u n="307" who="S0144">I don't think they're going to be tourist markets either so that's good</u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">Oman's becoming more popular as a tourist place</u>
<u n="309" who="S0144">yeah but it's not going to be like Tunisia where you just hassled</u>
<u n="310" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Muscat will be <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no I doubt it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144">I can't see that</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024">yeah well I think they're quite chilled out people aren't they</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's gonna be more authentic <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0024">well by the sounds of it <pause dur="short"/> generalising <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why I'm a bit worried about how my emails have been taken as well <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0024">they might be like what's she on about?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">I don't know Dawn</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">you know she seems a bit highly strung or something <pause dur="short"/> it's like I'm not really <pause dur="short"/> I'm usually fairly chilled out <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah the souk and I'm not looking forward to the wide empty streets and I'm hoping there's more trees on those streets than Google shows <pause dur="short"/> google doesn't show very many <pause dur="short"/> like remember in in Carthage those er big streets but they had trees lining them</u>
<u n="319" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah like boulevards yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0024">they're beautiful really</u>
<u n="321" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0144">yeah that was a very residential area though</u>
<u n="324" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0144">I can't see this being so residential <pause dur="short"/> I think it's going to be lots of apartment blocks</u>
<u n="326" who="S0024">apartments <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0144">intersected by fairly busy roads</u>
<u n="328" who="S0024">yeah not <pause dur="short"/> well they've got the big villas but obviously we won't be able to afford a villa</u>
<u n="329" who="S0144">I don't know it's funny isn't it <pause dur="short"/> what you you get the impression of somewhere before you've been there</u>
<u n="330" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0144">and then you get there <pause dur="short"/> a guess some of it gets confirmed but some it's just completely wrong isn't it</u>
<u n="332" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> and then if you think Tunisia still had a lot of apartment blocks and lots of people we know lived in apartment blocks</u>
<u n="333" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure at all <pause dur="short"/> there's just no information about <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've seen some lovely little pictures <pause dur="short"/> people playing football on the beach and stuff like that but then the beach is empty apart from a few footballers <pause dur="short"/> it's like well</u>
<u n="335" who="S0144">yeah I don't think they'll be many women on the beach</u>
<u n="336" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I would love erm <pause dur="short"/> I would love that we we manage to find somewhere with a little private part that I can sit out in the sun with my shorts on or something</u>
<u n="337" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0024">I'm not too fussed about sunbathing with a bikini or that's okay I can deal with that <pause dur="short"/> and if we want we can go to a hotel to do that if we really want to</u>
<u n="339" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0024">but I what I missed from Tunisia is erm <trunc>e</trunc> you know a little private garden space or or a big enough balcony <pause dur="short"/> sit and sit with your shorts on <pause dur="short"/> nobody can see you</u>
<u n="341" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0024">and you can sit and there's enough room for a table so you can sit and play cards or you can sit and listen to music <pause dur="short"/> you can sit and eat your breakfast <pause dur="short"/> breakfast <pause dur="short"/> I'd love to have breakfast on on a balcony</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">it sounds like I'm a right snob now <pause dur="short"/> well that's what I would like to aim for <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so you're not looking at an apartment then <pause dur="short"/> you're looking at er like a little villa</u>
<u n="346" who="S0024">well there's plenty of apartments where you know it might be overlooking a big wide space so nobody can actually see you anyway</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024">so <pause dur="short"/> that is possible <pause dur="short"/> I'm I'm not going to strip off <pause dur="short"/> I'm not gonna do what what somebody did in what one of our friends did and sunbathe neigh on naked on her roof thinking that nobody was watching them and then the builders <pause dur="short"/> wake up to four builders on the other building staring at her <pause dur="short"/> I shan't be doing that <pause dur="short"/> oh and erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024">shall we email <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and say hello we're coming? You know</u>
<u n="351" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0024">I mean I know he doesn't like in Seeb but it will be nice because there's the British Council crowd</u>
<u n="353" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0024">and then we've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I'd like to meet and that's the Muscat College</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0024">not Muscat Muscat College of Technology crowd</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024">so that's a few contacts <pause dur="short"/> it's nice to have isn't it</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">yeah it's nice to have a couple people there</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144">I'm just looking forward to the food</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">I know you are</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144">and the location <pause dur="short"/> I mean you're only a short flight from India really</u>
<u n="364" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144">and Dubai</u>
<u n="366" who="S0024" trans="overlap">see</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144">Dubai's just down the road</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah and Dubai <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> four hours drive that is isn't it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">mind you that is just a big shopping centre isn't it</u>
<u n="370" who="S0024">what I'm hoping is that they do some sort of girly activities <pause dur="short"/> like they're <pause dur="short"/> if they've got the whole Indian culture there <pause dur="short"/> there should be a yoga class do you think?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144">oh yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024">oh I hope</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">oh definitely</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024">I just really hope there will be <pause dur="short"/> yeah I can't see why there wouldn't be</u>
<u n="375" who="S0144">no they've yeah they've got a massive Indian community <pause dur="short"/> there's going to be <trunc>y</trunc> erm yoga</u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the only girls</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144" trans="overlap">probably all the different types</u>
<u n="378" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0144">they'll probably be like ayurvidic stuff as well</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there is already <pause dur="short"/> I've already found my ayurvidic shop <pause dur="short"/> I have <pause dur="short"/> they do all sorts of therapies and I reckon we're gonna live just round the corner</u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm excited about that <pause dur="short"/> that part of it</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024">that side of it we just didn't <pause dur="short"/> mind you we thought we'd get belly dancing and drumming in Tunisia and it wasn't really belly dancing classes or anything was there</u>
<u n="385" who="S0144">belly dancing <pause dur="short"/> it's not Tunisian</u>
<u n="386" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I know but they take a lot of the they they did have belly dancing</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144">yeah only in the tourist hotels</u>
<u n="388" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144">it's nothing to do with Tunisia</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024">no but</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">and none of the dancers were Tunisian</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">but I thought you know because nearby culture that they'd be</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I thought they'd be drumming <pause dur="short"/> I was a bit gutted there wasn't much drumming though</u>
<u n="394" who="S0024">well you've got the darbuka but it's only at weddings</u>
<u n="395" who="S0144">yeah yeah it wasn't like groups of guys hanging around on the street corners jamming</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> they were really surprised when you took your drum to the beach weren't they <pause dur="short"/> they loved it</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024">it's like they'd never thought of that before <pause dur="short"/> why doesn't anybody?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0144">well they're for weddings aren't they like you said</u>
<u n="400" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0144">I don't think Oman's going to be much cop for music</u>
<u n="402" who="S0024">oh I thought it would be better</u>
<u n="403" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it might have some Indian</u>
<u n="404" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> indian influence to Arabic music is really nice <pause dur="short"/> I like it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><trunc>Mi</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0024">I heard some stuff erm before</u>
<u n="407" who="S0144">and if you're doing like ayurvidic stuff I can get back into my tablas</u>
<u n="408" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0144">hopefully they'll be</u>
<u n="410" who="S0024" trans="overlap">or you could do some yoga too</u>
<u n="411" who="S0144">yeah well I wouldn't mind doing yoga</u>
<u n="412" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0144">but there should be some tabla teachers</u>
<u n="414" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well are you going to take your tablas?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0144">they're a bit heavy aren't they</u>
<u n="416" who="S0024">well I suppose you could always check it all out and then when we came come back in August maybe</u>
<u n="417" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no I'll check it out first <pause dur="short"/> I mean if it's a teacher you know he's probably got a spare set anyway</u>
<u n="418" who="S0024">yeah but you want to take them home and practise <pause dur="short"/> oh that's another thing about the house</u>
<u n="419" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0024">you know something fairly soundproof so that we can play our music and and not have to if we're watching a movie ah turn it down <pause dur="short"/> ah turn it up <pause dur="short"/> ah turn it down <pause dur="short"/> do you remember?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah that's important for me <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0024">ah that used to be such a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> and creep not creeping around but it's just</u>
<u n="423" who="S0144">you're just aware of it all the time aren't you</u>
<u n="424" who="S0024">yeah aware of somebody else hearing you after after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said do you like kung fu movies? I was like no <pause dur="short"/> why? She said oh it always sounds like you're watching kung fu movies <pause dur="short"/> I was like what? I don't know where that came from</u>
<u n="425" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="426" who="S0024">I don't even like action <trunc>f</trunc> films but there's always some sort of big loud clatter involved somewhere along the line</u>
<u n="427" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I suppose any movie <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0024">kung fu <pause dur="short"/> I have to write to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and tell her what we're up to</u>
<u n="429" who="S0144">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0024">and the kids <pause dur="short"/> we should send them</u>
<u n="431" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0024">I'll wait until we get our <pause dur="short"/> well I'll write an email saying we're going <pause dur="short"/> when if we finally get these tickets and then erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm not counting see I can't get excited yet</u>
<u n="433" who="S0144">yeah there's just been so many ups and downs hasn't there</u>
<u n="434" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it feels like I it feels like it's time to get excited and I have been <unclear/> but</u>
<u n="435" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah but I've I've got so excited literally three or four times and then gone again cos we got other news and it's just like what? It's been up and down up and down hasn't it</u>
<u n="436" who="S0024" trans="overlap">there was that day <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0144">so I don't want to allow myself to get too up before I'm on the plane really</u>
<u n="438" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no there's several things that I'm a little bit worried about to be honest <pause dur="short"/> like I I reread the email of the offer</u>
<u n="439" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> what the second offer?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and you know <pause dur="short"/> the second offer <pause dur="short"/> and you know how they upped it by a hundred Omani Rial</u>
<u n="441" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0024">yeah and but there's all this writing underneath it saying ah but this is subject to you being available to start in February term <pause dur="short"/> if not it may it it will be</u>
<u n="443" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0024">I don't understand it all <pause dur="short"/> it's a load of babble underneath and can you imagine if we get there after all this time and they go sorry we're cutting your wage <pause dur="short"/> it would just like you can't do that and if they point out the clause <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>w</trunc> this this if we're really really tired when we get there and they shove a contract under our nose and say sign it</u>
<u n="445" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well surely no I mean <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0024">we're going to have to say I'm going to take this back and read it over night</u>
<u n="447" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0024">we've just to have that</u>
<u n="449" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh definitely</u>
<u n="450" who="S0024">you can't trust people these days <pause dur="short"/> it's sad to say but you just can't <pause dur="short"/> like we've got in trouble so many times</u>
<u n="451" who="S0144">what do you mean these days?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0024">well not these days <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> well we've just got we're too trusting</u>
<u n="453" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no well it's an important thing isn't it</u>
<u n="454" who="S0024">I like to be trusting because I like to have faith in people but I think you you have to check everything</u>
<u n="455" who="S0144">you can't jump in blindly that's foolish</u>
<u n="456" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you know what it's like where if you're really tired off the plane <pause dur="short"/> here's your contract it's exactly the same as before <pause dur="short"/> and then everybody stands around you waiting for you to sign it so</u>
<u n="457" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's happened before hasn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0024">like oh oh oh and you're reading it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and if you're really tired you can't pick out all the details <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm a little bit worried something like that might go wrong but</u>
<u n="459" who="S0144">well we'll cross that bridge when we get to it</u>
<u n="460" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0144">it's not going to stop us going now is it</u>
<u n="462" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> no I mean I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't want to even know about it at the moment because I don't want to change my mind about going</u>
<u n="463" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> well with big things like this you know there's always an element of fear involved and you've either got to say I'm not going to do it or you do it</u>
<u n="464" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0144">and we've always done it before and it's always worked out</u>
<u n="466" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0144">and we've got no alternatives cos we're not exactly stay here</u>
<u n="468" who="S0024">no well we're not now cos we turned down that job so it's obvious we didn't want to stay</u>
<u n="469" who="S0144">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> we don't <pause dur="short"/> in our hearts</u>
<u n="470" who="S0024">deep down</u>
<u n="471" who="S0144">yeah we don't want to</u>
<u n="472" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0144">I've still got a couple of years of adventure left in us yet</u>
<u n="474" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0144">I think this might be the last one though</u>
<u n="476" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> could be <pause dur="short"/> well hopefully we're be able to save a bit of money at the same time so that we can come back or</u>
<u n="477" who="S0144">well that's the thing isn't it <pause dur="short"/> we can't come back at the moment</u>
<u n="478" who="S0024">well we could <pause dur="short"/> it's possible but I reckon we'd be broke</u>
<u n="479" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well we could but yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0024">even if we had a good job it would be tough starting up <pause dur="short"/> that's the problem here <pause dur="short"/> it's tough starting up</u>
<u n="481" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0024">but then it's tough going over there and finding apartments and stuff</u>
<u n="483" who="S0144">yeah but it's more exciting isn't it</u>
<u n="484" who="S0024">yeah it's more exciting than like moving to Cambridge or moving to Oxford or</u>
<u n="485" who="S0144">yeah I don't know I quite like being in a position where it's quite I don't know quite scary or quite full on</u>
<u n="486" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0144">Cos it makes you feel alive</u>
<u n="488" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0144">kind of invigorates all of your senses and heightens your perceptions</u>
<u n="490" who="S0024">yeah it does feel good</u>
<u n="491" who="S0144">whereas here just feel a bit numb</u>
<u n="492" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I got a little rush when we read the next <trunc>e</trunc> the latest email <pause dur="short"/> did you?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0024">I got a little <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't a massive rush but a little <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't like I handed in my dissertation or something <pause dur="short"/> or handed in a piece of coursework walked down the stairs and went whoop <pause dur="short"/> hooray <pause dur="short"/> free</u>
<u n="495" who="S0144">yeah well I didn't feel like that when I gave my dissertation in <pause dur="short"/> I crashed</u>
<u n="496" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I was just thinking that</u>
<u n="497" who="S0144">it's funny cos I remember we all went down the pub with everyone else</u>
<u n="498" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0144">and we all just sat there like urgh <pause dur="short"/> no one could even string a sentence together</u>
<u n="500" who="S0024">that <trunc>dis</trunc> that was just too short a time they gave us to do that</u>
<u n="501" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0024">should have been spread out over the year or something</u>
<u n="503" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0024">can I have one of those things?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0144">quite dark <pause dur="short"/> what things? Mint?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0024">yeah that's the thing I meant</u>
<u n="507" who="S0144">what time is it? About eight?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's dark</u>
<u n="509" who="S0144">that's another thing that's going to be different <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be what time is it?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0024">dark?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0144">it gets dark earlier doesn't it?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0024">does it?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0144">I think so</u>
<u n="514" who="S0024">they don't have summer time <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="516" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well hopefully it won't get</u>
<u n="517" who="S0144">well that's cos we're quite far north really here aren't we</u>
<u n="518" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0144">the further south you get the darker it gets</u>
<u n="520" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah the shorter the day <pause dur="short"/> it's thirty-one at the moment</u>
<u n="521" who="S0144">thirty-one?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's alright <pause dur="short"/> I can manage that but it's going up from now to</u>
<u n="523" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that's doable <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's when it gets to forty-five that I struggle</u>
<u n="524" who="S0024">but thirty-five <pause dur="short"/> like some of their days this week have been thirty-five</u>
<u n="525" who="S0144">okay <pause dur="short"/> well that's that's pretty hot isn't it</u>
<u n="526" who="S0024">that's like maximum for me <pause dur="short"/> that's like truly maximum</u>
<u n="527" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that's like <pause dur="short"/> that's about as hot as hot as it gets here isn't it? Really?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0024">oh I don't think we get to thirty-five do we?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0144">er I think so</u>
<u n="530" who="S0024">Don't know</u>
<u n="531" who="S0144">well what's a hundred?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0144">I can never remember</u>
<u n="534" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="535" who="S0144">is it late thirties or forty or something is it? Don't know</u>
<u n="536" who="S0024">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> anyway it's going to be hot hot hot</u>
<u n="537" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0024">and I'm going to be wearing more clothes</u>
<u n="539" who="S0144">yeah well that's going to be a bit of a shock to the system isn't it</u>
<u n="540" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but hopefully breezy <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> we're going to have to try on all our work clothes</u>
<u n="541" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> gonna have to <trunc>u</trunc> get used to going from air con <pause dur="short"/> outside <pause dur="short"/> back to air con <pause dur="short"/> outside</u>
<u n="542" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I always used to get cold doing that</u>
<u n="543" who="S0144">yeah it's not very nice is it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0024">my nose was always blocked <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> if it's good quality air con</u>
<u n="545" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0024">it's alright but some of that stuff is bad isn't it</u>
<u n="547" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0024">mum wants to play a game <pause dur="short"/> are you going to play a game?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0144">er yeah I could do <pause dur="short"/> I just want to get these er things put in Dropbox and sent off</u>
<u n="550" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0144">and then yeah I'll be ready</u>
<u n="552" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0144">well I'll start uploading it and cos it takes ages doesn't it</u>
<u n="554" who="S0024">yeah</u>
</body>
</text>
