<text id="S8LS">
<header>
		<rec_length>2:37:35</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0060 S0086 S0171</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Travelling, relationships, films</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting, eating dinner</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0060">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Reading, Berkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Civil engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner; German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0086">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cuckfield, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0171">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Reading, Berkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Admin Assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0060">yeah no whatever <pause dur="short"/> I'm not fussed</u>
<u n="2" who="S0171">what do you want?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0060">well if you're going to make some squash I'll have some squash</u>
<u n="4" who="S0171">I'll make some squash</u>
<u n="5" who="S0086">so what did you go and see at the movies?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0171">we went and watched</u>
<u n="7" who="S0060">John Carter</u>
<u n="8" who="S0171">that's it</u>
<u n="9" who="S0086">ooh the effects look really good <pause dur="short"/> did you see it in 3D?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we didn't realise it was 3D until we went did we?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> till they gave you specs</u>
<u n="12" who="S0060">I think you did you just didn't tell me</u>
<u n="13" who="S0171">no I had read that it was 3D but then I hadn't actually really remembered that</u>
<u n="14" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0171">we got to the ticket thing she goes ooh it's 3D would you like 3D glasses?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0086">that'll be twelve pounds please</u>
<u n="17" who="S0171">that'll be twelve pounds</u>
<u n="18" who="S0060">it was  it was  The ticket was a tenner each</u>
<u n="19" who="S0086">yeah it's a joke isn't it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0171">it was</u>
<u n="21" who="S0060">I was like hang on we're going to pictures we're not buying the film</u>
<u n="22" who="S0171" trans="overlap">but it was  it was  a Saturday that we went <pause dur="short"/> it was a Saturday that we went so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0086" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0060">yeah I know but you know so</u>
<u n="25" who="S0086">and 3D is more expensive</u>
<u n="26" who="S0060">I can I mean I can remember back in the day when I used to go to the cinema a lot it was three pound or something</u>
<u n="27" who="S0086">I know <pause dur="short"/> gone are those days</u>
<u n="28" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0171">or bargain Tuesday for seven pound fifty that's what I remember</u>
<u n="30" who="S0086">Tuesday's are still cheap <pause dur="short"/> cineworld is still cheaper on Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> and obviously Orange Wednesdays as well</u>
<u n="31" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> can't believe it was a tenner</u>
<u n="32" who="S0171"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you want a pint <trunc>gla</trunc> pint glass or a normal glass?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0086" trans="overlap">ooh that would be <pause dur="short"/> yeah a pint would be lovely my love</u>
<u n="34" who="S0060">but no it was a good film actually</u>
<u n="35" who="S0086">was it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0060">it wasn't  It wasn't</u>
<u n="37" who="S0171" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I didn't I wasn't all that keen on it actually</u>
<u n="38" who="S0060">but I don't know whether it's from a book but if it is I imagine the actual the story in the book would be a lot lot better <pause dur="short"/> the they didn't really <pause dur="short"/> they could have you know <pause dur="short"/> you could tell there was probably a lot more toe the story in different bits and they just sort of moved on cos the <pause dur="short"/> the story they're telling there wasn't a great deal to it</u>
<u n="39" who="S0086">really? It just sort of relied on the on how it looked</u>
<u n="40" who="S0060">yeah but no</u>
<u n="41" who="S0086">but Avatar was like that though <pause dur="short"/> they spent so much money on the effects that they just sort of forgot the story line <pause dur="short"/> I mean unobtainium</u>
<u n="42" who="S0060">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0086">how long did it take them to think that up? Two seconds <pause dur="short"/> it was essentially just Fern Gulley wasn't it? The twenty first century <pause dur="short"/> I mean I like Fern Gulley but you know I don't think it's ground breaking particularly but quite entertaining <pause dur="short"/> I think John Carter didn't it looked a lot like Star Wars? That sort of desert scene</u>
<u n="44" who="S0060">they've they've tried to sell to on saying it's the the Star Wars for the next generation <pause dur="short"/> but it's definitely not that</u>
<u n="45" who="S0086">it's not</u>
<u n="46" who="S0060">it's not <pause dur="short"/> it hasn't got the big sort of galaxies scope <pause dur="short"/> it's it's basically well they kind of <pause dur="short"/> there's there's a lot of in the first one is obviously where it sort of it if nothing else it's sort of setting a scene for a bigger story to come sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> em but even then it's not going to be anything <pause dur="short"/> yeah no</u>
<u n="47" who="S0086">anything on the same scale</u>
<u n="48" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="49" who="S0086">well I meant to go and see the first Star Wars in 3D but I didn't get around to it <pause dur="short"/> it would have been really good on the big screen</u>
<u n="50" who="S0060">I went when eh <pause dur="short"/> when they brought out what was it? The second one</u>
<u n="51" who="S0086">the second new one</u>
<u n="52" who="S0060">yeah there was a <pause dur="short"/> you could go and watch the five back to back through the night kind of thing</u>
<u n="53" who="S0086">oh god</u>
<u n="54" who="S0060">it was  it was  when I was at college I think <pause dur="short"/> so we went and watched that through the night and it was like oh</u>
<u n="55" who="S0086">yeah I think they did that just recently with Harry Potter</u>
<u n="56" who="S0060">did they? Oh my god</u>
<u n="57" who="S0086">they did yeah <pause dur="short"/> my friend went to watch all five <pause dur="short"/> and one Saturday night they did like one to three and then they did four to six</u>
<u n="58" who="S0060">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0086">and then seven's in two bits isn't it so <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was a bit epic cos they just get longer and longer</u>
<u n="60" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I remember going to see the the eh Exorcist at midnight cos it when it had come back after having been banned</u>
<u n="61" who="S0086">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0060">it was I think that was my first year at eh at uni we all trooped off down to the cinema at whatever in the morning or or yeah it was the last showing sort of thing to watch the Exorcist <pause dur="short"/> and it was like comic <pause dur="short"/> it really was</u>
<u n="63" who="S0086">it hasn't aged well has it</u>
<u n="64" who="S0060">no no <pause dur="short"/> I mean it was that you know this film has been banned it had to come back <pause dur="short"/> we all trooped down there to watch it <pause dur="short"/> I don't  I don't  think I'd ever seen it before <pause dur="short"/> but I mean literally we were just in stitches laughing throughout the thing it was</u>
<u n="65" who="S0086">yeah it's not scary</u>
<u n="66" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="67" who="S0086">it's funny that these things get banned <pause dur="short"/> but then I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether it's because I hate masks but Texas Chainsaw Massacre <unclear/> but I think it's still really scary</u>
<u n="68" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're right <pause dur="short"/> there's a new one coming out which is very much that sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> smiley <pause dur="short"/> it's called</u>
<u n="69" who="S0086" trans="overlap">thanks love <pause dur="short"/> smiley</u>
<u n="70" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0086">is it mask <unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0060">yeah its em <pause dur="short"/> very much of the sort of Scream Texas Chainsaw Massacre kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> it's all about <pause dur="short"/> and a bit like em I suppose IT and those kind of ones <pause dur="short"/> but it's of a his face is like</u>
<u n="73" who="S0171" trans="overlap">I'm going to start on the hard stuff</u>
<u n="74" who="S0086">oh nice</u>
<u n="75" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as though he he's got no face and his eyes and his mouth are like cut into it with a knife or something so it's sort of a a sort of bloody cut on his face but it's just no face <pause dur="short"/> he's got the shape of a face but no features apart from these knife cuts to make his eyes and his mouth</u>
<u n="76" who="S0086">Jesus</u>
<u n="77" who="S0060">and it looks one of your films that does Smiley</u>
<u n="78" who="S0086">yeah you like a gruesome horror don't you?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0171">I do <pause dur="short"/> but I've never heard of Smiley</u>
<u n="80" who="S0060">yeah well it's a new one I've seen it advertised <pause dur="short"/> but eh <pause dur="short"/> that's a perfect <pause dur="short"/> I mean eh one of the little computer games we play Minecraft there's loads of YouTube videos of people playing it cos they build loads of stuff and it's you know all sort of creative stuff <pause dur="short"/> and because you do that the load cos they've got loads of subscribers and they've got loads of videos up <pause dur="short"/> they're part of YouTube so they get paid for it because they put adverts <pause dur="short"/> so there's always this you know you get five seconds before you can get to the video you want <pause dur="short"/> and so often it's an advert for a film and you ooh start and then you start looking at that and eh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0086">oh that's clever</u>
<u n="82" who="S0060">but eh but yeah that was one of the ones <pause dur="short"/> but there's some good ones</u>
<u n="83" who="S0086">Smiley</u>
<u n="84" who="S0060">that one em <pause dur="short"/> I asked you to look at <pause dur="short"/> prometheus</u>
<u n="85" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0060">that looks like that's going to be really good</u>
<u n="87" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0060">Ridley Scott <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> very Alien <pause dur="short"/> I think although I I don't know for definite but it looks like it's asked around the alien space craft or the aliens that have the spacecraft where they find the alien first of all</u>
<u n="89" who="S0086">oh okay</u>
<u n="90" who="S0060">do you remember the one that is kind of looks like an elephant? Kind of you probably can't remember</u>
<u n="91" who="S0086">oh right no</u>
<u n="92" who="S0060">they find the massive there's a huge big alien in the spaceship where they find the alien eggs in the very first film</u>
<u n="93" who="S0171">in the very first film <pause dur="short"/> what is the very first film?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0060">alien</u>
<u n="95" who="S0171">alien <pause dur="short"/> oh that right okay</u>
<u n="96" who="S0086">the one where John Hurt's on the bed and the alien comes out of his chest</u>
<u n="97" who="S0060">yeah where he eh on the breakfast table isn't it? Yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0086">that's <pause dur="short"/> my mum watched that when she was eight and a half months pregnant with me <pause dur="short"/> I was her first born <pause dur="short"/> she watched that and she was like holy cow <pause dur="short"/> oh my god  Oh my god  I've got a life coming out of me in a matter of weeks</u>
<u n="99" who="S0060">well it looks <pause dur="short"/> it's gone back to that sort of dark sort of thing with that <pause dur="short"/> so it's really cool <pause dur="short"/> that should be good</u>
<u n="100" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> he's made yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort of hit and miss films for me <pause dur="short"/> some of them are really good and some been just a bit cheesy</u>
<u n="101" who="S0060">he's made his name of the back of that hasn't he?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like Gladiator</u>
<u n="103" who="S0060">yeah that's a good one <pause dur="short"/> but there was talk of a new Gladiator wasn't there? But I've never I've not seen <pause dur="short"/> there's a couple of</u>
<u n="104" who="S0171">are you not thinking of the series?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0060">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> there was talk of Gladiator Two effectively <pause dur="short"/> but I never saw anything more of it <pause dur="short"/> cos it you know any film that's really successful like that they're going to make a sequel aren't they <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> well no I don't know cos it wasn't a successful film <pause dur="short"/> like Wrath of the Titans after Clash of the Titans</u>
<u n="106" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0060">Cos you want to go and see that don't you?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0171">I do want to go and see that yes</u>
<u n="109" who="S0060">I reckon it's just going to be pure cheese</u>
<u n="110" who="S0171">yes</u>
<u n="111" who="S0086">he is a bit of a hottie</u>
<u n="112" who="S0060">well actually it's all sold on him being a good looking guy</u>
<u n="113" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0171">the other one it's em obviously come out very well is eh is it Taylor Lautner <pause dur="short"/> from the Twilight series</u>
<u n="115" who="S0086">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's done a lot of films on the back of that though hasn't he?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> loads</u>
<u n="118" who="S0060">that's what I was saying yesterday cos what was the film?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0171">Bellamy</u>
<u n="120" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0171">he's in Bellamy</u>
<u n="122" who="S0060">that's Robert Pattinson isn't it?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0171">oh is it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0060">yeah you're thinking of the other one</u>
<u n="126" who="S0171">oh yeah I'm thinking yeah I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> yeah was thinking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't I? Rather than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0060">loads of stuff <pause dur="short"/> but I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't think the stuff at the cinema or the films that have come out in the last sort of while have been all that good</u>
<u n="128" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> I haven't been to see any blockbusters for a while <pause dur="short"/> had a very cultural evening with my mum on Thursday we went to the ballet</u>
<u n="129" who="S0060">oh</u>
<u n="130" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0086">madame <pause dur="short"/> yeah well she said I want to go to the ballet therefore you have to get me tickets and you must come <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="132" who="S0171">you have no choice</u>
<u n="133" who="S0086">and birthday girl prerogative you just have to do it <pause dur="short"/> but actually it was really good <pause dur="short"/> it was you know the Arts Picture House they televise you know plays or ballet and the show it to you <pause dur="short"/> so rather than spend forty quid one the ballet which you probably won't enjoy you spend ten pounds and you get to drink during it so that's fine</u>
<u n="134" who="S0060">oh that's good</u>
<u n="135" who="S0086">so we did that but actually I was really surprised I really enjoyed it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether it's just because it was Romeo and Juliet so I knew the story <pause dur="short"/> I didn't have to try and work out what the hell was going on</u>
<u n="136" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0086">em so you know and it was very it was really beautiful <pause dur="short"/> by the end everyone was like mm <pause dur="short"/> and they finished dancing and then the curtain came down and the two leads came out and they were clinging on to each other cos it had been such an emotional experience <pause dur="short"/> and it is really definitely you <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't done any cultural things for ages so it was nice actually</u>
<u n="139" who="S0060">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I can always remember when I was doing the doing my GCSEs and that doing English literature and we used to go down to the eh to the theatre and to opera supposedly to broaden our eh</u>
<u n="140" who="S0086">expand your mind</u>
<u n="141" who="S0060">horizons <pause dur="short"/> it was very much like that with opera <pause dur="short"/> mostly Italian opera as well where you had if you didn't know what the blooming thing was about in the first place you didn't know what was going on</u>
<u n="142" who="S0086">yeah you're screwed and it lasts for four hours</u>
<u n="143" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> I can remember going <pause dur="short"/> we went all the way over the Stratford to the  to the  theatre there and what was it we watched? It was Taming of the Shrew or something like that <pause dur="short"/> but the blooming <pause dur="short"/> to get all the way over there for the  for the  showing and blooming the drive back it blooming it was blooming evening <pause dur="short"/> it was so late by the time we got back I was like bloody hell we're not going to do this regularly</u>
<u n="144" who="S0086">did you enjoy it?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0060">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was very good <pause dur="short"/> but he</u>
<u n="146" who="S0086">yeah there's something about seeing live theatre actually isn't there?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos that was <pause dur="short"/> ah who was doing it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0086">RSC maybe? If it was Stratford?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0060">no I'm trying to think who was in it <pause dur="short"/> I think it was em what's her name? Did the Darling Buds of May</u>
<u n="150" who="S0171">I haven't got a clue</u>
<u n="151" who="S0060">what's her name? Was in Entrapment</u>
<u n="152" who="S0171">oh Catherine Zeta-Jones</u>
<u n="153" who="S0060">Catherine Zeta-Jones <pause dur="short"/> I think it was her <pause dur="short"/> I think she was the shrew I think</u>
<u n="154" who="S0086">mm that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> I would never think of her as a stage actress</u>
<u n="155" who="S0060">I'm pretty sure it was her</u>
<u n="156" who="S0171">I suppose you've got to start somewhere</u>
<u n="157" who="S0060">it was a long time ago though so my memory may have totally failed me</u>
<u n="158" who="S0171">it must have been before <pause dur="short"/> it must have been before her acting career then</u>
<u n="159" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="160" who="S0086">the thing is I think it takes a lot more to do stage doesn't it? Cos you've only got one chance to do it <pause dur="short"/> whereas if you're used to doing a lot of TV then eh</u>
<u n="161" who="S0060">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> everything that's on the telly and you know cinema and that it's all about you know <pause dur="short"/> it's all perfect lighting perfect sound edited dubbed <pause dur="short"/> you know tweaked to be perfect</u>
<u n="162" who="S0086">yeah you can do as many takes as you need to</u>
<u n="163" who="S0060">whereas eh <pause dur="short"/> but eh</u>
<u n="164" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0060">there are <pause dur="short"/> the sort of stage actors are usually a lot lot better they can put across stuff a lot better</u>
<u n="166" who="S0086">so you've been working Saturdays then my love <pause dur="short"/> yeah? Busy</u>
<u n="167" who="S0171">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> we've em historical records has just gone through the roof</u>
<u n="168" who="S0060">been grumbling every single time but when she got her wages through she was like ooh</u>
<u n="169" who="S0086">Rich</u>
<u n="170" who="S0171">yeah it was a bit like that</u>
<u n="171" who="S0060">so it's reasonably <pause dur="short"/> cos I come and pick you up at the shop on Friday didn't you? Didn't I? and she'd try to hide stuff underneath the food it was like</u>
<u n="172" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0171">actually no no no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0060">it was like get the trolley is full and then there's just like a layer of food across the top</u>
<u n="175" who="S0171">no no <pause dur="short"/> what was I actually trying to hide? Cos it's very difficult to hide it</u>
<u n="176" who="S0060">A printer</u>
<u n="177" who="S0171">right</u>
<u n="178" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0171">it's very difficult to hide a printer</u>
<u n="180" who="S0060">we was like <pause dur="short"/> the printer's in the bottom and there's stuff all over the top of it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0171">it was one of those shallow trolleys that we use <pause dur="short"/> we weren't using the deep trolley <pause dur="short"/> it was shallow trolley</u>
<u n="182" who="S0060" trans="overlap">thank goodness <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0171">but eh yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0060">I was like what on earth do we need a printer for? Oh it was a bargain <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="185" who="S0171">it was <pause dur="short"/> it was seventy quid it was now thirty-four ninety-nine</u>
<u n="186" who="S0060">when did when when did we last need to print something? Never</u>
<u n="187" who="S0171">I thought I'll have that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0086">did you need a printer?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="190" who="S0171">yes we did</u>
<u n="191" who="S0086">it's only a bargain if you needed it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0060">oh yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0171">yes we did <pause dur="short"/> it's a scanner as well</u>
<u n="194" who="S0060">all you've done is stick it on the coffee em the dining room table haven't you?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0060">we haven't got anywhere to put it let alone use it</u>
<u n="197" who="S0171">well it's there</u>
<u n="198" who="S0060">alright <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="199" who="S0171">Don't you moan at me <pause dur="short"/> you're allowed to moan at me</u>
<u n="200" who="S0060">no we're going to meet up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> two of our well originally my friends</u>
<u n="201" who="S0171">yeah they're your mates yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0060">but eh we over the last few weeks we were trying to meet up with them but something has always come up</u>
<u n="203" who="S0171">it's a bit like you</u>
<u n="204" who="S0086">yeah I'm pretty useless</u>
<u n="205" who="S0060">and eh we he phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Friday night hadn't I?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0171">well last week I was not interested at all <pause dur="short"/> because</u>
<u n="207" who="S0060">no you weren't feeling very well and</u>
<u n="208" who="S0171">yeah it was Saturday and</u>
<u n="209" who="S0060">she was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't very well and she kind of said well I've still got a but fluey bug so if you come round and get ill don't blame me kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="210" who="S0086">charming</u>
<u n="211" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0060">well I mean fair enough</u>
<u n="213" who="S0086">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0060">but eh I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on Saturday no Friday night and I said right we're going to come over</u>
<u n="215" who="S0171">oh you're talking about this week?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0060">midday <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> pick you up <pause dur="short"/> and we're going to go into town have something to eat go to the pictures and he was like yeah ok fair enough <pause dur="short"/> I'll</u>
<u n="217" who="S0171">I'll let  I'll let  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> know when she comes in</u>
<u n="218" who="S0060">I said well I if we haven't heard you we'll assume from you will see at twelve <pause dur="short"/> and then about</u>
<u n="219" who="S0171">I think it was about half ten wasn't it? Half nine half ten</u>
<u n="220" who="S0060">yeah half nine something like that <pause dur="short"/> we got a text from him and he was said oh <pause dur="short"/> got up this morning and had a massive row with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's not speaking to me and so we can't really meet up</u>
<u n="221" who="S0171">so we can't really go out yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0060">we phoned just as we going out I phoned right and said look we're only  now</u>
<u n="223" who="S0171" trans="overlap">one last chance</u>
<u n="224" who="S0060">how are things going sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> and he sounded like he was really in the dog house <pause dur="short"/> he was <pause dur="short"/> cos he's South African and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s Italian</u>
<u n="225" who="S0171" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s Italian</u>
<u n="226" who="S0060">so they're both very fiery to start with</u>
<u n="227" who="S0171">and they have a baby as well <pause dur="short"/> but at the moment it's over in Italy</u>
<u n="228" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0086">the baby's in Italy</u>
<u n="230" who="S0171">yeah she's gone over with eh with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum</u>
<u n="231" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they have she's what? A year and two months or something like that?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0171">yeah she's about a month older than William</u>
<u n="233" who="S0060" trans="overlap">January wasn't it? January thirty-first I think it was actually</u>
<u n="234" who="S0086">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not in Italy just the baby</u>
<u n="235" who="S0060">no no</u>
<u n="236" who="S0171">they needed a break</u>
<u n="237" who="S0060"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum  was over here and like helping out cos the were really struggling with that</u>
<u n="238" who="S0171">and they also had the wedding as well</u>
<u n="239" who="S0060">and yeah they did have the wedding but that was at <pause dur="short"/> just after New Year's wasn't it? So her mum's been over here helping them out a little bit <pause dur="short"/> but I think they kind of said that we need to have a bit of a break <pause dur="short"/> so they talked about it hadn't they? About her going back with her mum for a little bit to Italy for a little bit so they could have break and not worry <pause dur="short"/> obviously she will still worry but hopefully not you know massively so <pause dur="short"/> so she dropped her off a couple of weeks back didn't she? I think it was <pause dur="short"/> but yeah they've not been coping very well with sport of <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works quite long hours so he's</u>
<u n="240" who="S0171">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ends up staying at home with <unclear/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0060">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does like cos she works at <anon type="place"/> she does quite sort of shift work and all this kind of stuff so it's quite a lot of effort for them <pause dur="short"/> plus I don't know really whether either of them well I suppose <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't really or wasn't I think he's changed a lot <pause dur="short"/> wasn't really kind of a reliable family man shall we say</u>
<u n="242" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="243" who="S0060">he has changed for the better over the years but <pause dur="short"/> I mean their relationship now I've known them two now</u>
<u n="244" who="S0171">it's been volatile for quite some time</u>
<u n="245" who="S0060">for for years <pause dur="short"/> cos I used to work with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> well I still do but he now works in a different bit to me <pause dur="short"/> but eh we used to rent a flat well not a flat a house together out in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and that was when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> first met <pause dur="short"/> and eh I used to be the blooming agony aunt for both of them cos they used to row and <pause dur="short"/> they would go from everything was brilliant and you know to the total everything's off we're never going to speak to each other again <pause dur="short"/> we want to kill each other <pause dur="short"/> in a course of a couple of days</u>
<u n="246" who="S0086">mm it's quite extreme</u>
<u n="247" who="S0060">and yeah <pause dur="short"/> but eh <pause dur="short"/> but no they I mean they're lovely <pause dur="short"/> but eh they are a bit eh <pause dur="short"/> up and down aren't they?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0086">some relationships are like that and it just it takes one of you to sort of say actually is this? Can? Is this sustainable? Like can you carry on with this?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0060">well they they had got to the point</u>
<u n="250" who="S0171">they had done that hadn't they?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0060">where they'd sort of said look this isn't going to work</u>
<u n="252" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0060">and eh they sort of totally split up <pause dur="short"/> but they ended up getting back together as <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's worked out I mean that was it must be they must have been together six or seven years now <pause dur="short"/> it must be <pause dur="short"/> on on and off for the first few years <pause dur="short"/> but they must have been that long now <pause dur="short"/> I mean they bought the house together a year and a bit ago <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> so the bought a house and had a baby all about the same time <pause dur="short"/> that's quite stressful</u>
<u n="255" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0060">and then got married</u>
<u n="258" who="S0171" trans="overlap">and then got married</u>
<u n="259" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they moved in and they had to be out of the place they were in on New Year's day or something like that or Christmas day one or the other I can't remember what it was now <pause dur="short"/> and it was the the house where I used to live with with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and eh <pause dur="short"/> I was saying why don't you blooming speak to the landlady and say look can we have a few extra days sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> I was like she's not get anyone moving in on blooming new year's <trunc>ev</trunc> New Year's day or whatever <pause dur="short"/> but they ended up they moved everything on New Year's eve and New Year's day didn't they? So I mean I gave them a hand with a few bits and pieces but <pause dur="short"/> a lovely place they've got it's out near em out through <anon type="place"/> and out the other side of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> the village is well it's kind of there's like three houses isn't there that's about it <pause dur="short"/> but em</u>
<u n="260" who="S0171" trans="overlap">that <unclear/> had to be careful <pause dur="short"/> when they first moved in it wasn't all that liveable was it?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0060">no <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="262" who="S0171">Paddy had to do a lot of work on it</u>
<u n="263" who="S0060">it'd been em <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it's like a bungalow isn't it really? A sort of a</u>
<u n="264" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0060">and it had sort of been <pause dur="short"/> they'd obviously the original owners had sort of done one room and then probably left <pause dur="short"/> and then another occupant had done another room and so it was nothing matched</u>
<u n="266" who="S0086">oh god</u>
<u n="267" who="S0060">you know it was all the doors were different different sizes different colours different styles <pause dur="short"/> all the rooms were a bit higgledy-piggledy weren't they? And everything <pause dur="short"/> none of this <pause dur="short"/> there were sort of bits of skirting board were there or not there <pause dur="short"/> and all sorts of <pause dur="short"/> and eh they spent the first cor must be six months sort of working on the house <pause dur="short"/> but thankfully both of them are very practical <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> although she works at <anon type="place"/>'s she actually does em like restoration and em <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why she doesn't do it still now cos she made a fortune out of it <pause dur="short"/> but she does like restoration murals and sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0086">wow</u>
<u n="269" who="S0171">she used to go to em various different countries didn't she? She would be hired by people</u>
<u n="270" who="S0060">to go</u>
<u n="271" who="S0171">that own like these massive villas</u>
<u n="272" who="S0060">she did a lot of work in eh</u>
<u n="273" who="S0171" trans="overlap">and she'd do mural and paint <unclear/> and so on</u>
<u n="274" who="S0086">yeah well especially <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0060">it was Dubai <pause dur="short"/> she got flown out to Dubai</u>
<u n="276" who="S0086">oh god</u>
<u n="277" who="S0060">to do murals in this you know mansion house kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> and eh she does a load of restoration work and stuff doesn't she? But I don't think she does much of it any more to be honest <pause dur="short"/> but she did until a few years back <pause dur="short"/> but eh there's a few  a few  of the restaurants in town actually where eh the murals <pause dur="short"/> she's done them <pause dur="short"/> eh the one</u>
<u n="278" who="S0171">yeah the one that I've seen is em</u>
<u n="279" who="S0060">the one on <anon type="place"/> Square isn't it? Sorry okay disaster</u>
<u n="280" who="S0171">isn't it brilliant how you try and have a conversation and join in on the conversation and you think of something to say and then he's just de de de</u>
<u n="281" who="S0060" trans="overlap">sorry sorry</u>
<u n="282" who="S0171">em yeah you know where the <anon type="place"/> Square is <pause dur="short"/> there's a I can't even remember what it's called now but there's a an Italian place</u>
<u n="283" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0060">it's underground</u>
<u n="285" who="S0171">under <pause dur="short"/> no it's not underground <pause dur="short"/> no yeah the mural is it's downstairs in the basement</u>
<u n="286" who="S0060">yeah it's got a basement is the <trunc>rest</trunc> part of the restaurant's downstairs</u>
<u n="287" who="S0086">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0171">you know where the  You know where the Disney Store is <pause dur="short"/> when you're coming out there</u>
<u n="289" who="S0086">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I know where it is <pause dur="short"/> not La <trunc>Stra</trunc> Is it <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0171">it's right on the end on the corner</u>
<u n="291" who="S0086">yeah I know where you mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0171">they usually have all the canopies out and <pause dur="short"/> canopies? You know get the tables</u>
<u n="293" who="S0060">isn't it further on than that?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="295" who="S0060">no okay <pause dur="short"/> but anyway</u>
<u n="296" who="S0171">although the Disney Store has closed down now but</u>
<u n="297" who="S0060">yeah but it's there <pause dur="short"/> cos we went there for his birthday didn't we?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0171">yeah no her birthday</u>
<u n="299" who="S0060">was it her birthday? I thought it was his</u>
<u n="300" who="S0171">oh no no it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> no it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="301" who="S0086">so she paints murals?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0086">oh wow</u>
<u n="304" who="S0060">she drew all of the <pause dur="short"/> cos it was em <pause dur="short"/> it was a beach scene or something wasn't it or?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0171">something like that <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't in a very big room either so I don't really know what they were going to do with it but</u>
<u n="306" who="S0060">it's sort of the private function room with a bar wasn't it? A sort of little private area <pause dur="short"/> but it was right across the walls all that sort of side <pause dur="short"/> it was nice <pause dur="short"/> but she's good at that kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> so she did all the sort of decorating and all the sort of filing and fixing and stuff and I mean <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went through and sort of ripped out all the doors and I think redid all the doors and did all the the sort of <pause dur="short"/> they put a wood floor throughout</u>
<u n="307" who="S0086">wow they must have spent quite a lot of money</u>
<u n="308" who="S0060">and all this sort of stuff <pause dur="short"/> eh they got it I think they got a decent mortgage and the price of the house was quite low cos it obviously needed a lot of work so they did that <pause dur="short"/> but it's got a huge garage it's like em <pause dur="short"/> it must be four or five car garage</u>
<u n="309" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0060">that they basically use it as a sort of storage base</u>
<u n="311" who="S0171">yeah cos they've got eh they've got a couple of cars haven't they? But they park them out the front</u>
<u n="312" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've got a nice sort of long drive that leads to it</u>
<u n="313" who="S0171">well you can always convert them you know over time</u>
<u n="314" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think originally that's what it was built for was you know it was a tiny little <trunc>bun</trunc> well it's not tiny it's quite big bungalow really isn't it?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0171">it is yea</u>
<u n="316" who="S0060">but it's a bungalow <pause dur="short"/> and then there was the bigger sort of garage and it was kind of you could see that they were thinking we'll live there and build a garage and then that will become the hone sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> but I think they never got permission to do it cos you have to get</u>
<u n="317" who="S0171">planning permission</u>
<u n="318" who="S0060">planning permission to convert it don't you?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0171">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've got a nice garden though <pause dur="short"/> it's got a little pond in it</u>
<u n="320" who="S0060">yeah they have yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's a really nice place actually</u>
<u n="321" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0060">but it is a bit out in the wilds <pause dur="short"/> a bit away from everything</u>
<u n="323" who="S0086">yeah you'd have to drive everywhere</u>
<u n="324" who="S0171">yeah it's it's literally it's on a  it's on a  main road and there's only three houses <pause dur="short"/> it's not <trunc>ev</trunc> you couldn't even deem it a village it's just a</u>
<u n="325" who="S0086">there's not even like a local shop</u>
<u n="326" who="S0060">nothing <pause dur="short"/> no nothing</u>
<u n="327" who="S0171" trans="overlap">no there's nothing there at all</u>
<u n="328" who="S0060">the nearest is <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it's <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0171"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0060">but <anon type="place"/> I suppose really</u>
<u n="331" who="S0171">but every time we go down there we always end up driving past it and have to come turn around and come back again</u>
<u n="332" who="S0060">yeah it's one of those where the entrance is it's all sort of hedge and everything all along there and then the entrance is like in it <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="333" who="S0171">he built some reflectors don't he? Outside to try and help people fine it but no <pause dur="short"/> and of course because it's on the right hand side of the road <pause dur="short"/> because you're doing sixty down there cost it's obviously a main road you can't be crawling along at twenty miles an hour watching out for the reflectors you know</u>
<u n="334" who="S0060">so when you're going down there you sort of you go ah there it was damn it</u>
<u n="335" who="S0171" trans="overlap">so every time we go down there <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's literally we're like a spilt second away from it oh damn it we missed it <pause dur="short"/> fuck <pause dur="short"/> so then we've now got a a turning point which is nasty to come out of</u>
<u n="336" who="S0060">well no thankfully</u>
<u n="337" who="S0171">it's like some sort of farmer's front gate or sommat <pause dur="short"/> and we're using that to kind of get back out</u>
<u n="338" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah there's a <pause dur="short"/> it's like a quarry or something isn't it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> place that's obviously closed down in the evenings or whatever <pause dur="short"/> just turn around in there and come back</u>
<u n="339" who="S0171">and then as we're coming back again it's like we're right wait for it  wait for it  is it coming? Very soon</u>
<u n="340" who="S0060" trans="overlap">well it's easy  it's easy  to see that coming that was it's easier to see isn't it? But eh</u>
<u n="341" who="S0171">I don't know is it?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0060">but eh yeah it is yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0171">I always miss it</u>
<u n="344" who="S0060">Cos I can always see the house first whereas you come the other way and it's not till you're already passed it that you can see the house cos if the way it is <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> so it's eh yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0086">it sounds nice <pause dur="short"/> I've been thinking about moving out of the city just cos it's so expensive <pause dur="short"/> you know even just to rent cos I can't afford to buy</u>
<u n="346" who="S0060">well I mean here renting</u>
<u n="347" who="S0171">we got a deal on this place</u>
<u n="348" who="S0060">was was</u>
<u n="349" who="S0171">we were lucky</u>
<u n="350" who="S0060">it was just their own stupidity but thank</u>
<u n="351" who="S0171">no it was not their stupid they were nice</u>
<u n="352" who="S0060">we we gained  we gained  from it <pause dur="short"/> this place is less than we were paying for a two bedroom flat in town</u>
<u n="353" who="S0086">and you've got a three bedroom house</u>
<u n="354" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0086">nice</u>
<u n="356" who="S0060">well I it was a hundred quid or something like that less wasn't it? I think <pause dur="short"/> from memory</u>
<u n="357" who="S0086">A hundred quid less a month</u>
<u n="358" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0086">Jesus</u>
<u n="360" who="S0171">yeah it was</u>
<u n="361" who="S0086">but you can't cycle from here can you? Into town</u>
<u n="362" who="S0060">you've tried it haven't you?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0171">not oh god no</u>
<u n="364" who="S0086">you nearly died</u>
<u n="365" who="S0171">that's hilarious <pause dur="short"/> that's fucking hilarious <pause dur="short"/> no when we <pause dur="short"/> I cos we'd left the bike at the flat my bike at the flat <pause dur="short"/> and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh no it'll be alright I'll just cycle it that's fine <pause dur="short"/> I'll cycle it <pause dur="short"/> and yeah it took me about three hours</u>
<u n="366" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0171">and I'd gone up through <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and come out that way</u>
<u n="368" who="S0060">Cos the the only way</u>
<u n="369" who="S0171">and when you come out on to the main road at <anon type="place"/> between that connect to <anon type="place"/> and you know the other end the other side <pause dur="short"/> it's you're this close to fucking great big lorries</u>
<u n="370" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so unless you want to try</u>
<u n="371" who="S0086">yeah that's the thing</u>
<u n="372" who="S0060">unless you want to ride on the A14 <pause dur="short"/> you've got to like go out and round</u>
<u n="373" who="S0086">through the villages</u>
<u n="374" who="S0171">through the sticks yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that was fucking terrifying <pause dur="short"/> I had to walk the last bit</u>
<u n="375" who="S0060">but there's a there is  there is  a cycle path isn't there with with a little lit up cycle path but it doesn't come all the way round</u>
<u n="376" who="S0171">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I ended up I think at the time I ended up using the the busway before the busway was actually built they'd just tarmacked it</u>
<u n="377" who="S0060">yeah you can use that yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0171">like they tarmacked it</u>
<u n="379" who="S0060">there's there is a cycle path that goes out I think it goes out somewhere near <anon type="place"/> but it then doesn't carry on round <pause dur="short"/> so you're then on just tiny little roads to come round the top side in from em <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0171">yeah I was <unclear/> bike <pause dur="short"/> I ended up walking cos I couldn't <pause dur="short"/> cos you can't cycle on the on the  road you can't <pause dur="short"/> it's just not possible <pause dur="short"/> so the only thing you've got left to choose is grass and unfortunately the grass was not helpful <pause dur="short"/> but eh</u>
<u n="381" who="S0086">yeah I think <pause dur="short"/> because you know cycling obviously quite popular I the city there's lots of websites that tell you all the cycle routes in and around the city <pause dur="short"/> so I think what I'll probably try and do is look at that map and then try and find somewhere that I can do that</u>
<u n="382" who="S0060">the best thing to do is to go to you know where</u>
<u n="383" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> my geography is shit</u>
<u n="384" who="S0060">I was just going to name a pub in town actually <pause dur="short"/> so you're you're bound to know that</u>
<u n="385" who="S0086">oh yeah well I night know that</u>
<u n="386" who="S0060">em <pause dur="short"/> it's what's it called <pause dur="short"/> it changed name to I can't remember what</u>
<u n="387" who="S0171">yeah he's just about to name a pub that he can't remember what the name of the pub is</u>
<u n="388" who="S0086">and it's also changed names</u>
<u n="389" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the one in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> on the riverside</u>
<u n="392" who="S0086">well that's where I live <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but all of those are closed</u>
<u n="393" who="S0060">so what's the pub <pause dur="short"/>?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0086">the <anon type="place"/> is probably what you mean <pause dur="short"/> cos that changed names <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0060"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0086">yeah that's closed</u>
<u n="397" who="S0060">is it really?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> all of the pubs apart from the <anon type="place"/> have closed in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0060">oh no</u>
<u n="400" who="S0086">all of the locals blame it on the gypsies <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure we can blame everything on the gypsies <pause dur="short"/> much as everyone would like to <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/> has closed down <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/> has closed down <pause dur="short"/> there was one on the high street apparently before my time was closed It's all boarded up <pause dur="short"/> just before you get down to <anon type="place"/> high street Tesco's it's just before there <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so why would I have gone there?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0060">not because it's a pub but from there there's a cycle path that goes out all the way out to</u>
<u n="402" who="S0086">goes past <anon type="place"/> doesn't it on the right?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0060">yeah but what's the? What's where the train station is?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0060"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then it carries on <pause dur="short"/> well it doesn't carry on but then you carry on up there <pause dur="short"/> I know that's there because I built it</u>
<u n="406" who="S0086">ah nice</u>
<u n="407" who="S0060">so I know there's a few guys a couple of guys who actually work for the council that live there and cycle in all the way down into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0086">really from <trunc>Wa</trunc> from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/> is really nice <pause dur="short"/> I don't think yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's probably cheaper than <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but there's it's got a couple of nice pubs</u>
<u n="411" who="S0060">really?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0086">iIt would have been nice mum used to live in the black house on the river which is also known as the X files house apparently <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0060">alright</u>
<u n="414" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> and from there you just have to walk around the river and round that bend you've got to the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so it would have been really nice to have a little bridge over there cos the only other bridge is the one by the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so you've got to walk and if you walk on that other side it's all fields is like a <unclear/> common <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I could do that <pause dur="short"/> definitely look into doing that <pause dur="short"/> cos if you lived in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean that would be fine</u>
<u n="415" who="S0060">there's loads of places out here up for rent now</u>
<u n="416" who="S0086">I know it's just  it's just  the em having to rely on the bus</u>
<u n="417" who="S0060">well it's not that bad <pause dur="short"/> but you've got a car now</u>
<u n="418" who="S0086">it's my dad's car <pause dur="short"/> I mean I basically have a car</u>
<u n="419" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0086">but it's my dad's car <pause dur="short"/> if I <pause dur="short"/> the only reason I can use it so much is that</u>
<u n="421" who="S0060">you'll probably find out that the money you could save you'd probably be able to run a car anyway</u>
<u n="422" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0060">Cos it made a <pause dur="short"/> well it's made a big <trunc>di</trunc> I mean we're on a different tax bracket out here <pause dur="short"/> so we pay less tax</u>
<u n="424" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0060">yeah less council tax</u>
<u n="426" who="S0086">how's that? Oh council tax yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0060">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> em less council tax <pause dur="short"/> I'll be honest and say the bills are actually a bit less as well despite it being a three bed that we're trying to heat and everything <pause dur="short"/> but the rent being that lower</u>
<u n="428" who="S0086">that's good</u>
<u n="429" who="S0060">I mean  I mean  the silly thing is as well for me for the car <pause dur="short"/> I'm usually driving south down to London most days <pause dur="short"/> but it actually takes me less time to get from here to London than it did from town to London <pause dur="short"/> you know it's <trunc>an</trunc> it's another I think it's about another fifteen minutes <pause dur="short"/> sorry another fifteen miles further than we were <pause dur="short"/> and it probably takes about fifteen minutes less</u>
<u n="430" who="S0086">nice</u>
<u n="431" who="S0060">to get down there <pause dur="short"/> and it makes a big difference <pause dur="short"/> it's surprising <pause dur="short"/> you know just doing the bit in and out of time <pause dur="short"/> cos we used to live em behind the cinema actually behind cinema</u>
<u n="432" who="S0086">I <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0171">what's that road?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0060">and to get out from there it eh <pause dur="short"/> you know and it's not far <pause dur="short"/> but eh it takes a while</u>
<u n="436" who="S0086">yeah you just get jams don't you that's the thing</u>
<u n="437" who="S0060">I suppose where you are at the minute you are quite close out to the fourteen aren't you?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0086">yeah it's a really good location I'm in at the moment <pause dur="short"/> in terms of getting out but</u>
<u n="439" who="S0060">you've got places like <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but they're a bit far out again</u>
<u n="440" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/> is not a cheap as I thought it was going to be like</u>
<u n="441" who="S0060">no cos it's all new <pause dur="short"/> or the new bit out to the north is ordinary obviously but the original bit n the middle <pause dur="short"/> but that's all old people so you know you've got to wait for them to die</u>
<u n="442" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0060">but em</u>
<u n="444" who="S0086">yeah it's it's I need to look into it really <pause dur="short"/> I just eh <pause dur="short"/> you know I turn thirty this year</u>
<u n="445" who="S0060">my goodness</u>
<u n="446" who="S0086">oh my god</u>
<u n="447" who="S0060">yeah I've got that to look forward to next year</u>
<u n="448" who="S0086">you're a spring chicken</u>
<u n="449" who="S0060">yeah I'm only twenty-nine</u>
<u n="450" who="S0171">what's that?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0060">I said I'm only twenty-nine I've got thirty next year</u>
<u n="452" who="S0086">he's not he's lying to me isn't he?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0171">no that's that's my age dear <pause dur="short"/> that's my age <pause dur="short"/> I'm twenty-nine this year <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="454" who="S0060">what am I this year <pause dur="short"/> thirty-three or thirty-four?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0171">thirty <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know</u>
<u n="456" who="S0060">thirty-three won't it be? Yeah thirty-three</u>
<u n="457" who="S0171">FB</u>
<u n="458" who="S0086">is that your phone?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0060">yes</u>
<u n="461" who="S0171">my little widget</u>
<u n="462" who="S0060">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0171">expensive widget and awkward as well</u>
<u n="464" who="S0086">I really wanted the iPhone but when I cancelled cos I me <pause dur="short"/> I was on one of these pay monthly sim only things <pause dur="short"/> my phone was literally disintegrating <pause dur="short"/> it was prehistoric <pause dur="short"/> it looked like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my first phone <pause dur="short"/> I mean <pause dur="short"/> so em <pause dur="short"/> but I was only paying ten pounds a month <pause dur="short"/> so I called Vodafone who I've been with for about seven years <pause dur="short"/> it was a massive saga I'll just cut it short <pause dur="short"/> and they managed to get me to sign up for this the Samsung Galaxy S one lovely really good <pause dur="short"/> and I said well I was thinking about the iPhone and they said well actually the the Samsung is better rated on their on our website <pause dur="short"/> and did a bit of research and actually it is like a lot of their apps you get on the iPhone you have to pay for and they're free for other phones and it's better coverage and this that and the other and I was like okay fine <pause dur="short"/> so I signed for it so it's now twenty-six pounds a month but that's with internet and stuff and it is and it's a phone that works <pause dur="short"/> whereas the other phone was a bit of the lottery <pause dur="short"/> some calls it would allow <pause dur="short"/> some texts it would allow <pause dur="short"/> it was  it was  it kept me on my toes it was funny</u>
<u n="465" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the unpredictability kept you excited</u>
<u n="466" who="S0086">yeah it was really exciting yeah <pause dur="short"/> so then that arrived the next day all lovely <pause dur="short"/> downloaded loads of exciting stuff <pause dur="short"/> was like playing with all the apps <pause dur="short"/> cos my last phone didn't have any of this <pause dur="short"/> I was like the internet? What? On my phone? Oh my god <pause dur="short"/> I'm living in the twenty-first century <pause dur="short"/> turns out I could probably communicate with aliens on my new phone <pause dur="short"/> couldn't call anyone on my phone though</u>
<u n="467" who="S0060">really?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0086">when I called someone it was fine on my end but there was a really bad echo on theirs <pause dur="short"/> the would just hear themselves back <pause dur="short"/> mum went mental she was like it's so bad <pause dur="short"/> I was like call Vodafone <pause dur="short"/> oh we're really sorry you've called within the one week we'll send a new one out tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> nothing arrived <pause dur="short"/> so a week went by so I said well nothing's arrived <pause dur="short"/> oh well it's not in stock at the warehouse <pause dur="short"/> fine thanks for letting me know that's really <unclear/> Could you send one out tomorrow? Eh not tomorrow but we'll get one out to you by the end of the week <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> didn't send it to my work address as I requested they sent it to my mum's address <pause dur="short"/> no one was there to sign of it so they took it away again <pause dur="short"/> had to call them again <pause dur="short"/> oh yes madam we'll come out tomorrow with a new phone really sorry about that <pause dur="short"/> they never turn up <pause dur="short"/> they didn't turn up anywhere <pause dur="short"/> call them again well actually why don't you send your phone back to us <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> send me a parcel a like a bag to put it in</u>
<u n="469" who="S0060">yeah and I'll send it to you</u>
<u n="470" who="S0086">and I said ah that never arrived <pause dur="short"/> my phone wasn't in the post room because had my phone and they arrived out of hours so missed them had to call again <pause dur="short"/> so this is about the sixth time I've tried to arrange or them to collect the phone <pause dur="short"/> by this time I'm furious <pause dur="short"/> so they finally come and collect the old one I've not got the the one that works <pause dur="short"/> but it just took me ages to get hold of someone who I could actually complain to <pause dur="short"/> cos first of all they said oh there's no one here <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to escalate the call to someone they'll call you back <pause dur="short"/> they never called back <pause dur="short"/> next person oh no you've got to log a complaint on the website <pause dur="short"/> and I said is it one of those emails that goes into ether and no one responds <pause dur="short"/> oh no madam we always respond <pause dur="short"/> so then I finally got someone to call me back and he said I'm very sorry <pause dur="short"/> and I said well actually the service that you get when you call Vodafone everyone is very apologetic <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm very sorry madam they've absolutely got that in hand and then it never turns up <pause dur="short"/> and you think well what you're saying is great but it never actually materialises <pause dur="short"/> I'm very sorry madam there's obviously communication problems there could we offer you <unclear/> Well the money isn't you know going to cover this the pain that you've suffered but you know can we offer you some money <pause dur="short"/> well actually yes that would be very nice thank you</u>
<u n="471" who="S0060">yeah that would be fine thank you very much</u>
<u n="472" who="S0086">so I couldn't use the phone for the first month <pause dur="short"/> he said well you have been sending texts <pause dur="short"/> okay well yes I've been sending texts but I can't call anybody <pause dur="short"/> yes okay so <pause dur="short"/> so we will give you the <unclear/> for free <pause dur="short"/> it's just such a hassle <pause dur="short"/> they're there to make your life easier <pause dur="short"/> I've been with Vodafone for seven years</u>
<u n="473" who="S0060">well the thing I always say about this you know <pause dur="short"/> my paying for calls and my paying for this is paying your wages <pause dur="short"/> you know it's not I'm not doing you a favour you're meant to be sorting it out for me</u>
<u n="474" who="S0086">absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0060">yeah we've transferred over to Virgin now for our phone and broadband and everything</u>
<u n="476" who="S0086">oh yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0060">and I'll be honest and say that while occasionally it ends up grinding to a halt and just being silly it's ten times better normally than BT ever was</u>
<u n="478" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0060">and eh yeah customer service is a little bit hit and miss whereas BT you might as well not have bothered phoning them <pause dur="short"/> em but eh but no we had em <pause dur="short"/> what day was it last week darling? Was it at the weekend or?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0171">eh I think it was Wednesday actually</u>
<u n="481" who="S0060">was it?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0171">Cos they said about <unclear/> on eh Saturday</u>
<u n="483" who="S0060">oh that was it yeah and it had gone got completely there was nothing <pause dur="short"/> and we couldn't the TV box which you know obviously uses to broadband to to get the that was down as well <pause dur="short"/> so I phoned them up and said oh we've got this problem <pause dur="short"/> no it must have been Monday Monday or Tuesday</u>
<u n="484" who="S0171">no it couldn't have been Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> oh actually I don't think it happened all at once</u>
<u n="485" who="S0060">it was Monday</u>
<u n="486" who="S0171">wasn't it? So it was Tuesday</u>
<u n="487" who="S0060">Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> and I phoned them up and said you know blah blah blab blah blah <pause dur="short"/> so we're listening and we're checking if there's a a network problem or the areas gone down oh no no <pause dur="short"/> they said are the lights on on the box? I said yeah they are <pause dur="short"/> are they blinking? Yes they are <pause dur="short"/> just let me check <pause dur="short"/> so I'm on hold it was silent <pause dur="short"/> it was one of those I was like</u>
<u n="488" who="S0086">I hate it when they get silent</u>
<u n="489" who="S0060">hello who's there? Oh yes oh right okay <pause dur="short"/> so he comes back <pause dur="short"/> oh there's definitely no network problems <pause dur="short"/> it must be a problem with your router <pause dur="short"/> we'll get an engineer <pause dur="short"/> okay fine <pause dur="short"/> she said right the next available engineer and it was like Saturday <pause dur="short"/> and was like but it's Tuesday</u>
<u n="490" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0060">well that's when the next <pause dur="short"/> so what am I  what am I meant to do all week? Oh well I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm so okay so what's going to get sorted out <pause dur="short"/> and they ended up they phoned back the next day or the day after didn't they and said oh we've cancelled it and nuh nuh nuh cos it was a network problem in the area it's like oh right</u>
<u n="492" who="S0171">no what it was darling was there was an automated voicemail that they left on the phone</u>
<u n="493" who="S0060">yeah the voicemail thing</u>
<u n="494" who="S0171">saying <pause dur="short"/> we have tried to fix your area <pause dur="short"/> if you still need an engineer <unclear/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0060">the way  The way  they figure out as to whether there's a network error is if once it gets passed a threshold number of complaints</u>
<u n="496" who="S0086">oh right  <pause dur="short"/> encouraging</u>
<u n="497" who="S0060">and then it's there's a problem with the network and they have to send someone out to look at the network</u>
<u n="498" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="499" who="S0060">so obviously ours was one of the first calls rather them one of the later ones where they could have just said yeah it's a network problem it will come back on when it comes back on sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> but eh yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0086">how long were you without it?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0060">oh like a day in the end <pause dur="short"/> but eh</u>
<u n="502" who="S0086">it's annoying though isn't it?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0060">no they're a lot lot better <pause dur="short"/> I mean it uses the same blooming infrastructure as BT but it's what are we  what are we  thirty meg or something like that darling at the minute?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0171">yeah we are yeah we're paying for that anyway</u>
<u n="505" who="S0060">yeah we're paying yeah we're paying for twenty but we're getting thirty</u>
<u n="506" who="S0086">wow</u>
<u n="507" who="S0060">em but with BT which is using the same stuff we were getting lie one or two at most</u>
<u n="508" who="S0086">they do say Virgin is the best yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've already said they are actually going to double it <pause dur="short"/> so we should be getting I think they're saying well they're saying a minimum of double but they're expecting it to be fifty megs em from sometime later in the year because it's just well Richard Branson is trying to say now he's leading the way so he's just basically said look we're going to give everyone that's buying from us now double what they've got now</u>
<u n="510" who="S0086">bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> how are they going to do that?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0060">I think it's just that do you know what I mean? The stuff can always take it but they've sort of drip feed it out really to show that they you know people would buy better each time sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> it's the same as Microsoft isn't it you know? A new version of Window's every five minutes <pause dur="short"/> it's not because they've come up with a new thing <pause dur="short"/> it's just that they they drip feed out for yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0086">they want us to pay for it</u>
<u n="513" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if they'd come out with Windows seven in nineteen eighty you would never have bought windows three point one would you but eh</u>
<u n="514" who="S0086">ah hilarious <pause dur="short"/> bloody technology <pause dur="short"/> so how are the wedding plans coming along?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0060">well we were talking about it last night weren't we? That you need to start eh</u>
<u n="516" who="S0171">there's lots of talking going on</u>
<u n="517" who="S0060">you need to start booking some viewings</u>
<u n="518" who="S0171">and lots of ordering going on</u>
<u n="519" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> woman know your place</u>
<u n="520" who="S0060">that's it</u>
<u n="521" who="S0171">it is a bit like that <pause dur="short"/> but eh but know <pause dur="short"/> we're going to keep <pause dur="short"/> but I cos I've been working on Saturday's you know I can't and won't</u>
<u n="522" who="S0060">you don't reckon you're going to need to work now are you?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0171">well I do need to work <pause dur="short"/> I reserved a <unclear/> with work yesterday that I should have gone and done</u>
<u n="524" who="S0060">well there's other people at work</u>
<u n="525" who="S0171">there was two <pause dur="short"/> actually there's probably guaranteed to be one probably not so much with the second <pause dur="short"/> cos he hasn't actually done any Saturday overtime at all</u>
<u n="526" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="527" who="S0171">whereas <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the guaranteed one <pause dur="short"/> cos he's been doing Saturday weekends the same as I have <pause dur="short"/> but eh historical records manager himself em if he did turn up yesterday it was his first Saturday overtime he's down at all</u>
<u n="528" who="S0086">really? And it's  And it's  their department that's kicking off?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0171">it's it's them <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's their responsibility</u>
<u n="530" who="S0086">so what's going on? Why is it so busy?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0171">because originally the vocational qualifications of historical records was based in Coventry <pause dur="short"/> eh they closed them down to save money</u>
<u n="532" who="S0086">right so where are they now?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0171">so we had two weeks' worth of training in November before they were officially closed down and made either redundant or seconded <pause dur="short"/> and eh we've been picking up the pieces ever since November or the start of December <pause dur="short"/> em and it's been absolutely manic <pause dur="short"/> because the GQ and the VQ two different processes <pause dur="short"/> so they're two different things you've got to try and remember <pause dur="short"/> and eh VQ I picked up quite easily em <pause dur="short"/> and eh and the VQ stuff I ended up doing before the exec stuff em I did a lot of post work in the morning <pause dur="short"/> so when it would all come in I would sort it all get it all done <pause dur="short"/> so I ended up becoming the eh the VQ post pro <pause dur="short"/> em and then we had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> start as a temp em <pause dur="short"/> which was before our  started for the winter series <pause dur="short"/> and the idea was we were going to have two temps come in em one was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and we had a one a week later called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was difficult</u>
<u n="534" who="S0060">those weren't the words you used the other day</u>
<u n="535" who="S0171">well I it was the kindest words <pause dur="short"/> and eh and then there was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ended up being I was obviously training him on VQ post so he naturally sat next to me <pause dur="short"/> but the idea was was that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was supposed to be doing VQ and  because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't wasn't guaranteed to be starting or at least a temp for in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>' position was supposed to be someone starting <pause dur="short"/> eh but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ended up starting and she was my ex-checker but I couldn't get her to do anything</u>
<u n="536" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0171">em <pause dur="short"/> I ended up chucking her all over the  stuff but she couldn't even pick that up <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> she <trunc>c</trunc> she couldn't log them either and</u>
<u n="538" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> she just a bit simple was she?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0171">I was like Jesus <pause dur="short"/> jesus wept <pause dur="short"/> em so that wasn't working too well and then of course I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> breathing down my back with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> breathing down <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s back</u>
<u n="540" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0171">about how the stats were crap</u>
<u n="542" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0171">so I'm now working longer hours and longer days <pause dur="short"/> then cominghome to get a belly ache from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying you shouldn't be doing it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="545" who="S0171">Cos I was unpaid <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't being paid for it</u>
<u n="546" who="S0060">yeah that that</u>
<u n="547" who="S0086">oh really well no that's not on</u>
<u n="548" who="S0060">yeah that's what I was grumbling about</u>
<u n="549" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0060">and especially as you told me you were getting it <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="551" who="S0171">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> no I never once lied to you</u>
<u n="552" who="S0060" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0171">when I was working on VQ as overtime that was overtime</u>
<u n="554" who="S0060">mm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0171">it's just like it office politics is bollocks</u>
<u n="556" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0171">because it was  it was  a case of if I wanted to finish at five but then do extra time if I did VQ I'd be paid for it if I did  I wouldn't</u>
<u n="558" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0171">and eh it was  that was suffering because I was having to do VQ if I wanted to be paid</u>
<u n="560" who="S0086">God that's weird though</u>
<u n="561" who="S0171" trans="overlap">so I went go bollocks to that then <pause dur="short"/> I'll just do  And</u>
<u n="562" who="S0086">what is the point of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean generally in life</u>
<u n="563" who="S0171">just generally in life I don't know</u>
<u n="564" who="S0086">Cos is he helping at all?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0171">he's trying to but he's he's obviously managing me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0171">em ad he'll <pause dur="short"/> the the one thing that really pees me off with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is that he expects me to do things for him immediately</u>
<u n="568" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="569" who="S0171">and I I</u>
<u n="570" who="S0086" trans="overlap">he's got no concept of how busy you are</u>
<u n="571" who="S0171">my mentality is is generally to be rude <pause dur="short"/> and I don't actually mean to be but I am <pause dur="short"/> most of the time I'm rude to him <pause dur="short"/> I'm like yeah it can wait  yeah it can wait  You know and I was like I can't remember what I'm doing <pause dur="short"/> and then I get he knows I'm going to do it <pause dur="short"/> it's not you know I mean I'll get it done within five minutes</u>
<u n="572" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0171">em but sometimes it's it's it's he'll start passing things over to me <pause dur="short"/> cos you know those you won't I don't know if you ever saw them but the the dividers the the pin boards that divide our desks?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0086">oh right</u>
<u n="575" who="S0171">he'll slop a bit of paper over it <pause dur="short"/> just leave it there <pause dur="short"/> yeah sure I'll do that <pause dur="short"/> and it's other things like MIRs right?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0171">we're in the <trunc>mid</trunc> in the midst of VQ last <trunc>wi</trunc> this week just gone we've had two two people seconded to other departments and we've lost two</u>
<u n="578" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0171">we've got half of the team that was left come own with a cold</u>
<u n="580" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0171">and then of course half of those guys that were had a cold were not coming in cos they were sick</u>
<u n="582" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0171">em <pause dur="short"/> and then we had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go on eh leave for the back end of last week</u>
<u n="584" who="S0086" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0171">so there was that there was me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still turning up late <pause dur="short"/> em <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> oli was off sick we had a new temp we still had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and that was about it <pause dur="short"/> but then we've got to <trunc>co</trunc> we're supposed to be covering GQ and VQ as well as MIRs</u>
<u n="586" who="S0086" trans="overlap">oh really? mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="587" who="S0171">and eh yeah it's been a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> and Neil will say to me I'm in the middle of trying to do VQ or searching or something</u>
<u n="588" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="589" who="S0171">em and he'll say oh there's an MIR in <pause dur="short"/> pick it up to Neil <pause dur="short"/> and he does he does pick them up but he's kind of gotten to a stage where he cheats now <pause dur="short"/> cos he'll pick them up look at them and if it's not a deleted mark support so it's not something really really easy <pause dur="short"/> he'll ask me to pick it up <pause dur="short"/> or he'll give me the MIR tell me to <trunc>inve</trunc> vestigate it and then he'll resolve it off</u>
<u n="590" who="S0086">he's a horror isn't he?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0086">he only really liked doing the interesting ones the difficult ones</u>
<u n="593" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0086">you know he would cherry pick</u>
<u n="595" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0086">the ones that he wanted to do <pause dur="short"/> that's what I always used to find really frustrating about him</u>
<u n="597" who="S0060">just a thought <pause dur="short"/> have you actually asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whether she likes mushrooms or not?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0171">I have already kind of asked if she's allergic to anything</u>
<u n="599" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0060">oh okay</u>
<u n="601" who="S0086">I do like mushrooms now <pause dur="short"/> I didn't eat them until about a year or so ago</u>
<u n="602" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0086">I I'm a growing <unclear/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0171">okay well let's tell you what's on the menu then</u>
<u n="605" who="S0086">yes please</u>
<u n="606" who="S0171">eh we've got creamy mushrooms</u>
<u n="607" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="608" who="S0171">em</u>
<u n="609" who="S0086">yum</u>
<u n="610" who="S0171">yes well we we we like it yum <pause dur="short"/> it was an experiment that right</u>
<u n="611" who="S0086">is it a Philadelphia experiment?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0171">it <trunc>w</trunc> it has  It has  Philadelphia in it</u>
<u n="613" who="S0086">I know how you like Philadelphia</u>
<u n="614" who="S0171">Cos wasn't there a phase when you cooked everything with Phili</u>
<u n="615" who="S0171">there was</u>
<u n="616" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0171">Cos I had the Phili cookbook</u>
<u n="618" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0060">yeah there was a Phili cookbook and</u>
<u n="620" who="S0171" trans="overlap">phili cookbook and I went absolutely mental for Phili <pause dur="short"/> and but eh but no this <pause dur="short"/> this <pause dur="short"/> I think I ended up I'm an experimental cooker don't like instructions <pause dur="short"/> so although Phili the Phili book obviously helped but I don't like</u>
<u n="621" who="S0060">the only reason you don't like instruction is cos they are not detailed enough <pause dur="short"/> so when it's</u>
<u n="622" who="S0171">is he calling me stupid?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0060">yeah pretty much yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0171">no it's cos if it  if it  doesn't say exactly the way to like turn the spoon over to do something <pause dur="short"/> you you throw a fit</u>
<u n="626" who="S0171">anyway and then after that</u>
<u n="627" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0086">we're going to have some gnocchi with some garlic bread</u>
<u n="629" who="S0086">oh that sounds delicious</u>
<u n="630" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> but it's a  it's a  creamy creamy pesto sauce <pause dur="short"/> so it's it's just like pesto</u>
<u n="631" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0171">em</u>
<u n="633" who="S0060">but a sauce</u>
<u n="634" who="S0171">but no cos no cos pesto is a comfit</u>
<u n="635" who="S0086" trans="overlap">with cream in it</u>
<u n="636" who="S0060">yeah right okay yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0171">but it's a creamy version rather than</u>
<u n="638" who="S0086">okay so what do you have that on the gnocchi?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0171">yeah stir it in</u>
<u n="640" who="S0086">ooh</u>
<u n="641" who="S0171">and there's some garlic bread for a bit of dunking</u>
<u n="642" who="S0060">that's it</u>
<u n="643" who="S0171">you've never complained about it so</u>
<u n="644" who="S0060">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I'm <trunc>ea</trunc> I'm easy to please</u>
<u n="645" who="S0171">well I don't know about that <pause dur="short"/> with your demands</u>
<u n="646" who="S0060">ha <pause dur="short"/> demands?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0171">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's usually clean up <pause dur="short"/> put the dishwasher on <pause dur="short"/> make me tea</u>
<u n="648" who="S0060">ah no demands <pause dur="short"/> you've now got it that you do that without me needing to instruct you any more so that's nice</u>
<u n="649" who="S0171">I am perfect wife material then</u>
<u n="650" who="S0060">it's <trunc>take</trunc> it's taken a few years but I've got her now to</u>
<u n="651" who="S0086">oh dear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="652" who="S0060">the training is almost complete</u>
<u n="653" who="S0086" trans="overlap">it's not okay</u>
<u n="654" who="S0171">well don't forget there is still another two years yet <pause dur="short"/> I can change my mind</u>
<u n="655" who="S0060">well</u>
<u n="656" who="S0171"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0060">save me a few quid that would <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0171" trans="overlap">well yes save a few quid yourself <pause dur="short"/> and I'm happy with my half anyway so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0086">just thinking about the  Have you booked a venue? You were looking at venues weren't you?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0060" trans="overlap">no that's <pause dur="short"/> yeah we've got to sort it <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="661" who="S0086">wasn't there on at <anon type="place"/> you were keen on? Or have I made that up?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0060">there's one yeah they're one there and there's one out to the south of the city which I can't think of now <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> what's the name of the one where we went to?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0171">the one what darling?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0060">venue</u>
<u n="665" who="S0171">venue?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0060">wedding venue</u>
<u n="667" who="S0171">wedding venue <pause dur="short"/> we haven't been to one yet</u>
<u n="668" who="S0060">no where we've been already for the do for your work <pause dur="short"/> was it your works do?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0171">oh Chilford Hall?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0060">yeah Chilford Hall that was quite nice</u>
<u n="671" who="S0086" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> where's that?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0171">eh it's out in the middle of nowhere em</u>
<u n="673" who="S0060">chilford</u>
<u n="674" who="S0086">chilford</u>
<u n="675" who="S0060">but it's it's basically south of the city</u>
<u n="676" who="S0171">okay it's em out in the rolling hills</u>
<u n="677" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0171">it's quite nice it's just a it's kind of a massive <unclear/> But it</u>
<u n="679" who="S0060" trans="overlap">but it looked <trunc>ex</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean I looked at what they offer though and it looked expensive for what we'd get</u>
<u n="680" who="S0171">do you know what?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0171">I was on the bus</u>
<u n="683" who="S0060">you weren't</u>
<u n="684" who="S0171">I was <pause dur="short"/> going through <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0060"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0171">do you know the  Do you know the  school? Probably don't actually <pause dur="short"/> you might know the school  But there's a a really posh private school</u>
<u n="687" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0171">em and on the the <trunc>ro</trunc> eh <anon type="place"/> road where <anon type="place"/> road meets <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="689" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0171">em there's a whacking great banner that for first of April eh April fools day so I don't think I'm actually going to do with it <pause dur="short"/> em but they've got a wedding fair on</u>
<u n="691" who="S0060">ah right okay</u>
<u n="692" who="S0171">oh April fool's day</u>
<u n="693" who="S0060">there we go</u>
<u n="694" who="S0171">and I'm assuming it's in in the private school</u>
<u n="695" who="S0060">right</u>
<u n="696" who="S0171">or on the grounds or</u>
<u n="697" who="S0060">somewhere in there</u>
<u n="698" who="S0171">somewhere round there <pause dur="short"/> but eh but yeah I was quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0060">Cos we were talking about going to the one in February didn't we but we never went</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="700" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> exciting <pause dur="short"/> so are you leaving all the planning to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0060">pretty much yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0086" trans="overlap">sounds sounds wise</u>
<u n="703" who="S0060">I yeah I took the decision early on that no matter I actually said she wouldn't really pay any attention to it unless it was exactly what she was thinking anyway</u>
<u n="704" who="S0086">well absolutely</u>
<u n="705" who="S0060">so I uh <pause dur="short"/> but now obviously it means that I get grumbled at for not doing enough towards it but if I did anything she would probably grumble about that <pause dur="short"/> so I'm I'm kind of doing the getting grumbled at but doing nothing option rather than do stuff and still get grumbled at</u>
<u n="706" who="S0086">yeah that's more frustrating yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's a woman's prerogative</u>
<u n="707" who="S0060">well that's it</u>
<u n="708" who="S0086">so that's fine</u>
<u n="709" who="S0060"><unclear/></u>
<u n="710" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> good stuff I've got a couple of wedding coming up <pause dur="short"/> I've got a wedding in Belfast</u>
<u n="711" who="S0060">oh right</u>
<u n="712" who="S0086">and a wedding in Brighton within two weeks of each other</u>
<u n="713" who="S0060">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="714" who="S0086">but I I'm quite good now I've just said no to all hen parties <pause dur="short"/> bear that in mind Hannah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0171">what's that?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0086">I I've been saying no to all hen parties <pause dur="short"/> I think I might make it a rule of my life</u>
<u n="717" who="S0171">why?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0086">Cos one of them was in em Barcelona for a start</u>
<u n="719" who="S0060">right</u>
<u n="720" who="S0086">which I think if you're the hen <pause dur="short"/> that's lovely cos you're only going to have one hen party and you can make everyone do what you want to do</u>
<u n="721" who="S0060" trans="overlap">but if you've gone to ten already <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0086">yes but if it's <pause dur="short"/> but I will have two within two weeks of each other and one was in Barcelona and one was recording a song in a studio and then cocktail making and dinner and</u>
<u n="723" who="S0060">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="724" who="S0086">it the Barcelona trip would have cost four hundred pounds <pause dur="short"/> and plus then flying to Belfast of try the wedding <pause dur="short"/> and she was getting married at some well she is getting married in an amazing venue and the hotel is hundred and forty pounds a night</u>
<u n="725" who="S0060">oh really?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0086">but luckily my housemate's coming with me and we've sacked off that option <pause dur="short"/> she works for em Crown Plaza in town</u>
<u n="727" who="S0060">oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0086" trans="overlap">and she can get employee discount on Holiday Inn's and Crown Plaza's</u>
<u n="730" who="S0060" trans="overlap">oh good <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0086">so there's one in Belfast city and we'll get it for nine pounds a night</u>
<u n="732" who="S0060">wow</u>
<u n="733" who="S0171">nice</u>
<u n="734" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0060">that's good</u>
<u n="736" who="S0086">wicked</u>
<u n="737" who="S0060">you left the fridge open</u>
<u n="738" who="S0171">I have left the fridge open <pause dur="short"/> aren't you amazing? It's amazing how you actually understand what that noise is</u>
<u n="739" who="S0060">I did it the other day when I was stood</u>
<u n="740" who="S0171" trans="overlap">I wonder what it is when you leave the fridge open <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what <unclear/> for you to get up and <unclear/> come and close it</u>
<u n="741" who="S0060">yeah I was stood there with the door open talking to her yesterday and it wasn't until it started beeping I was like oh I'll shut the door now <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0171">ah that's what that is</u>
<u n="743" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> now that is good <pause dur="short"/> we were going to go eh we went <pause dur="short"/> was it Barcelona or Madrid we were meant to go to for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wedding?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0171">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="745" who="S0060">it was Barcelona I think wasn't it?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0086">this wine's beautiful</u>
<u n="747" who="S0171" trans="overlap">somewhere sunny</u>
<u n="748" who="S0060">and eh we looked at it and oneand obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with her flying thing but</u>
<u n="749" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0060">the money to go for their wedding it was like bloody hell you know</u>
<u n="751" who="S0086">people are so selfish</u>
<u n="752" who="S0060" trans="overlap">be lovely for your wedding wouldn't it but</u>
<u n="753" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's like people getting married in Thailand <pause dur="short"/> my cousins got married in Thailand <pause dur="short"/> I think it was deliberately</u>
<u n="754" who="S0060" trans="overlap">I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> they were quite ah we said well <pause dur="short"/> you know we're not gonna come sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> mm it's our wedding why can't you come? Like cos it's going to cost us like a grand or something to come</u>
<u n="755" who="S0086" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="756" who="S0060">and yeah it would be nice if it was like we were having a holiday anyway</u>
<u n="757" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0060">eh but eh but yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0086">yeah that's it it is like the cost of a holiday isn't it?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0086">excuse me <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I got quite a god deal on a hotel in Brighton as well <pause dur="short"/> I mean it is essentially just like a little bed <pause dur="short"/> it's a single bed in a</u>
<u n="762" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0086">room it's a B and B <pause dur="short"/> and I'll only be there to put my head on the pillow</u>
<u n="764" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0086">so <pause dur="short"/> that'll be fine</u>
<u n="766" who="S0060">no it's something we've had to think about for ours is that obviously most of Hannah's family is sort of</u>
<u n="767" who="S0086">far far</u>
<u n="768" who="S0060">Scotland <pause dur="short"/> most of my family is sort of down in Berkshire or on the South coast</u>
<u n="769" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0060">and it's kind of you know wherever we pick you know we've got to make sure that there's somewhere everyone can stay that's a reasonable</u>
<u n="771" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="772" who="S0060">price if they want to stop over and things like that and</u>
<u n="773" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0060">you know so <pause dur="short"/> that was why <pause dur="short"/> what was the other place? We're going to look at the one you really want for the wedding</u>
<u n="775" who="S0171">I want to go to eh Hotel Felix</u>
<u n="776" who="S0060">Felix that's it <pause dur="short"/> and eh no sooner had she mentioned this to my mum than she's been obviously looking at it and apparently there's a deal they do where when you book</u>
<u n="777" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="778" who="S0060">em for a wedding function there they give you three rooms as part of the three you know three rooms for the night as part of the thing</u>
<u n="779" who="S0086" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="780" who="S0060">so my mum went so that would be one room for you or room for me and your dad and one you know like <pause dur="short"/> right okay I can see how this is going</u>
<u n="781" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="782" who="S0060">but uh</u>
<u n="783" who="S0086">nice nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah well it's an expensive business getting married</u>
<u n="784" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's surprising the difference in price with some of the ones we've seen <pause dur="short"/> there's some where you're getting virtually nothing and it's</u>
<u n="785" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0060">really expensive and others where you're getting way more for a lot lot less <pause dur="short"/> and it's like</u>
<u n="787" who="S0086" trans="overlap">really? You're noticing a real difference</u>
<u n="788" who="S0060">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0086">mm that's interesting</u>
<u n="790" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's surprising</u>
<u n="791" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0060">but eh</u>
<u n="793" who="S0086">that's really strange <pause dur="short"/> you'd think that people would you know kick off about that</u>
<u n="794" who="S0060">I think a lot of it they they do it on the name of the venue and you know they can sort of say oh you know but eh</u>
<u n="795" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> but at least round here you know you sometimes do get discounts on Travelodge and Premier Inn <pause dur="short"/> like I noticed in Brighton because it's you know hen parties and stag dos and whatever like it's always popular and the Travelodge is never less than a hundred pounds</u>
<u n="796" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0086">even when they do these special nine pound a night things</u>
<u n="798" who="S0060">oh yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0086">you never get it I mean unless you're there during the week <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> it's never very cheap <pause dur="short"/> bloody weddings <pause dur="short"/> I've got time to eh prepare myself for yours then if it's two years <pause dur="short"/> if you were thinking April fourteen were you?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0060">the nineteenth of April</u>
<u n="801" who="S0086">nineteenth of April</u>
<u n="802" who="S0060">twenty-fourteen</u>
<u n="803" who="S0086">which is your parents wedding anniversary?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0060">yes</u>
<u n="805" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> disconcerting that is <pause dur="short"/> you alright darl?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0171">yeah <pause dur="short"/> your mum was well chuffed when we told when we like when she found out there</u>
<u n="808" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0086">and she was waiting for you to guess why it was an important date</u>
<u n="810" who="S0060" trans="overlap">it was yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0171">Cos <unclear/> got quit freaked out when she said that</u>
<u n="814" who="S0060">I'm glad it was you on the open to her not me actually cos she would've had a go at me for not remembering</u>
<u n="815" who="S0171" trans="overlap">yeah cos if it was you she would've she probably would have killed you</u>
<u n="816" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and her birthday's the day after</u>
<u n="817" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="818" who="S0060">like no <pause dur="short"/> yeah the day after that's right yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0171">oh that's another thing that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps telling me <pause dur="short"/> is that he thinks that his parents like me more than they like him</u>
<u n="820" who="S0086">aw</u>
<u n="821" who="S0171">so that could well be that might well be why I managed to get away with it</u>
<u n="822" who="S0060">they definitely grumble at me and not at you <pause dur="short"/> I get grumbled at</u>
<u n="823" who="S0171">that's cos they know I'm a sensitive soul</u>
<u n="824" who="S0060">Ohh <pause dur="short"/> you're the one that gets all the special food all the things sorted for you</u>
<u n="825" who="S0171" trans="overlap">I do yes they are very accommodating</u>
<u n="826" who="S0060">whereas me I just get whatever's gong</u>
<u n="827" who="S0171">like she'll em most of the time she'll know that <pause dur="short"/> she'll always get chicken <pause dur="short"/> if she's doing a roast she'll get chicken for me</u>
<u n="828" who="S0060" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0171">everyone else will have beef or lamb or whatever but she'll get me some chicken</u>
<u n="830" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0086">is that the only meat that you like?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0171">I'm a bit fussy cos I've been kinda <pause dur="short"/> I don't know my mum was an awful cook</u>
<u n="833" who="S0060">if she can get away with it yes it's the only meat that she'll eat</u>
<u n="834" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm the same I don't really beef and or lamb <pause dur="short"/> I like sausages</u>
<u n="835" who="S0171" trans="overlap">my mum used to cook it and she used to cook a lot of stews <pause dur="short"/> and I hated them</u>
<u n="836" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="837" who="S0171">cos she would chuck anything in them and did hated them</u>
<u n="838" who="S0060" trans="overlap">yeah you see that's where the idealized mum because she was she's very good at cooking <pause dur="short"/> so she would cook all sorts of different things and it was good</u>
<u n="839" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0060">so our our <pause dur="short"/> I mean I <trunc>w</trunc> I I wasn't I was a fussy eater when I was a kid <pause dur="short"/> but you know over the years and stuff you know I'll just eat anything you know? I can't think well no that's a lie <pause dur="short"/> there's only one thing that I can say now that I would rather not eat <pause dur="short"/> I would rather starve than eat and that's celery <pause dur="short"/> I absolutely cannot stand it</u>
<u n="841" who="S0171" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't like celery</u>
<u n="842" who="S0086">yeah it's not nice</u>
<u n="843" who="S0060">it just tastes bad</u>
<u n="844" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what you'd eat sprouts?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I never used to but yeah I'll eat sprouts <pause dur="short"/> they're alright</u>
<u n="846" who="S0171" trans="overlap"><unclear/>sprouts <pause dur="short"/> he has a competition with his aunty every year at Christmas</u>
<u n="847" who="S0060">yeah at Christmas <pause dur="short"/> my aunty she we usually go round to to my granddad's my aunty lives with my granddad and eh for Christmas like evening meal <pause dur="short"/> and eh <trunc>th</trunc> she cooks sprouts with it not because she likes sprouts but because it's you know you should have sprouts</u>
<u n="848" who="S0086" trans="overlap">tradition <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0060">and eh me and her always have a competition that we we have to eat the same number of sprouts that the other does</u>
<u n="850" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="851" who="S0060">and for years it's always been I I didn't like sprouts and she didn't like sprouts but like like it doesn't fuss me anymore <pause dur="short"/> so I'll I'll always have another one to force her to have another one you know? But yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0086">apparently they're nice if you sort of pan fry them and with <trunc>ba</trunc> <trunc>ba</trunc> bacon inside</u>
<u n="853" who="S0060">yeah if they get <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've had them and they've been very very nice <pause dur="short"/> but I've had them sometimes and they've just been a bit you know</u>
<u n="854" who="S0086">yeah you can <trunc>p</trunc> over boil them <pause dur="short"/> apparently they're better for you if you do cos it releases like an anti-oxidant thing and they're good for you <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure how true that is <pause dur="short"/> my dad was threatening to get them in because he was on this <pause dur="short"/> he's been reading these books about food to help prevent cancer <pause dur="short"/> he's in his sixties own and he's just reading all about it</u>
<u n="855" who="S0060">it's a bit late now</u>
<u n="856" who="S0086">well this is it <pause dur="short"/> so every morning for about a month he had blueberries on his porridge cos he found out that blueberries are supposed to prevent you getting cancer <pause dur="short"/> whether I don't know if there's any truth in it but fine <pause dur="short"/> and then he found out that</u>
<u n="857" who="S0060">yeah but the thing is you've got to have been eating it your whole life</u>
<u n="858" who="S0086">exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's too late just to have it for a few weeks and right that's it</u>
<u n="859" who="S0060">sorted</u>
<u n="860" who="S0086">never getting cancer <pause dur="short"/> lovely</u>
<u n="861" who="S0060">I've had my blueberries for a week <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="862" who="S0171">do you two want another drink?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0060">I'm alright</u>
<u n="864" who="S0171" trans="overlap">no you've got a have one <pause dur="short"/> alright okay</u>
<u n="865" who="S0060">no I'm fine thank you</u>
<u n="866" who="S0171">you don't <pause dur="short"/> do you want anything?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0086">I wouldn't mind a cheeky vino if we're about to eat soon it's probably okay</u>
<u n="868" who="S0171">yeah? Is that alright</u>
<u n="869" who="S0086">thank you <pause dur="short"/> you're being a very good hostess</u>
<u n="870" who="S0171">I'm trying <pause dur="short"/> I was saying to I was trying to remember what that  what that that programme is called <pause dur="short"/> you know the Channel Four programme</u>
<u n="871" who="S0086">come Dine With Me</u>
<u n="872" who="S0171">that's it</u>
<u n="873" who="S0086">love it</u>
<u n="874" who="S0171">I was saying to hi before we <trunc>ca</trunc> cos he was such a cheeky sod <pause dur="short"/> he was sat here looking at me going so what are we going to do?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0060">what's the plan?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0086">what with life?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="878" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what the hell are we going to do</u>
<u n="879" who="S0171">Elizabeth's coming <pause dur="short"/> what are you going to do? Cook some food <pause dur="short"/> talk <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> what I am supposed to be doing? I said I'm not like this is not exactly Channel Four you know we're not going to win a grand at the end of it <pause dur="short"/> it's not like that</u>
<u n="880" who="S0060" trans="overlap">no you're meant to I said you're meant to plan out the evening <pause dur="short"/> you know have the eh have a comedian</u>
<u n="881" who="S0086">what's our evening's entertainment going to be</u>
<u n="882" who="S0171">well I'm not going to get some sort of</u>
<u n="883" who="S0086">belly dancing</u>
<u n="884" who="S0171">God no</u>
<u n="885" who="S0086">I'm most disappointed</u>
<u n="886" who="S0171">no you're not</u>
<u n="887" who="S0086">I love a bit of Come Dine With Me <pause dur="short"/> I'd quite like to do it but I can't cook <pause dur="short"/> I mean if people are happy with fish finger sandwiches then that's fine cos that's what I can cook</u>
<u n="888" who="S0171">ah do you know what I've had a seriously bad bad experience with fish fingers</u>
<u n="889" who="S0086">you haven't?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0171">I have?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0086">what did you have? What happened?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0171">it was disgusting <pause dur="short"/> I think I decided to cook <pause dur="short"/> I've not had fish fingers since <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know what the hell happened <pause dur="short"/> but we'd cooked them and we then tucked in <pause dur="short"/> I just had a mouthful of one and it's I don't even know it must have been off</u>
<u n="893" who="S0060">they were em</u>
<u n="894" who="S0171">yeah probably rotten more than off</u>
<u n="895" who="S0060">no no no <pause dur="short"/> well they were</u>
<u n="896" who="S0171">you ate them I don't know why?</u>
<u n="897" who="S0060">Cos I'm double hard</u>
<u n="898" who="S0171">obviously got the stomach for it</u>
<u n="899" who="S0060">what it was is they we had no food in so we thought well we'll defrost something from the freezer and we had these fish fingers in there <pause dur="short"/> but I think they'd been in there quite some time <pause dur="short"/> and when they came out they weren't we'd cooked them cos they didn't you know they don't look any different when they're frozen and eh they were just a little bit dodgy</u>
<u n="900" who="S0086">aw <pause dur="short"/> did they smell?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0060">eh they didn't smell but they did taste a bit weird</u>
<u n="902" who="S0171">they tasted disgusting</u>
<u n="903" who="S0060">with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> anything at all</u>
<u n="904" who="S0171" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Cos they were nice</u>
<u n="905" who="S0060">whenever something doesn't taste the same as it did the time before hat's it it's the end of that as a food</u>
<u n="906" who="S0086">game over <pause dur="short"/> aw</u>
<u n="907" who="S0171">yeah the thing is that is really annoying that really annoys me with him is that <trunc>fr</trunc> now since then at every opportunity I'll say to him have you checked that? Is it still in date? Is it alright? Does it smell alright? Even chicken  Even chicken  that we buy precooked from like Waitrose if it smells funny or if it's a bit watery I'll run it under his nose is that alright?  is that alright?  He'll be like yeah it's fine just eat</u>
<u n="908" who="S0086">it's really difficult with frozen foods though because obviously you don't know quite how long it's been there so all the dates are wrong <pause dur="short"/> so it could have been in there six months but it's frozen so it's okay but it might have been in there a year in which case chuck it</u>
<u n="909" who="S0060">no I I find quite often things like fish don't last very well in the freezer</u>
<u n="910" who="S0086">my fish fingers don't have the chance to last till they go off <pause dur="short"/> I'd cook a really good chilli the other day actually</u>
<u n="911" who="S0060">yeah?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I generally well I don't ever cook with beef mince <pause dur="short"/> my mum raised me as a veggie so we always used to use quorn or soya mince <pause dur="short"/> so that's what I cooked with <pause dur="short"/> like the smell of beef actually turns my stomach <pause dur="short"/> the smell of it frying yeah <pause dur="short"/> I could eat a burger but I'm not a massive fan <pause dur="short"/> normally have veggie</u>
<u n="913" who="S0060">no I was eh <pause dur="short"/> my years of college and then eh living away from home with work here there and everywhere <pause dur="short"/> my my idea of food is whatever will keep me alive of the longest with the minimum of effort into making</u>
<u n="914" who="S0171"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually does something that's good <pause dur="short"/> when he does do when he does cook with him just saying how he chucks everything in a pan and does it <pause dur="short"/> one thing he does do well is <trunc>tagli</trunc> your tagliatelle</u>
<u n="915" who="S0060">yeah that's cos it's easy</u>
<u n="916" who="S0171">yeah well cos he we have like chorizo onion mushroom and he just chucks it all in cooks it all and then just tosses it all together <pause dur="short"/> that's kind of unit food isn't it? You just kind of chuck it all in</u>
<u n="917" who="S0086">yeah everything in a pan <pause dur="short"/> one pan food</u>
<u n="918" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0086">my uncle came cos like my mum's birthday was yesterday <pause dur="short"/> and em he loves to cook which is brilliant cos none of us like cooking <pause dur="short"/> and he made a really nice risotto it was a pea a mushroom it was basically all we could find in Tesco like wild mushroom peas white wine <pause dur="short"/> but my mum and my sister are veggie so we cooked a pan of risotto and for me him and my brother he cooked this chicken <pause dur="short"/> and it's just really basic you just put it in a pan bit of butter bit of stock bit of mustard bit of black pepper bit of thyme <pause dur="short"/> it was amazing it was really really nice <pause dur="short"/> he's quite confident about what goes together <pause dur="short"/> I think when I try I put like Chinese five spice with thyme and it just or mint and everything tastes a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> I've got no comprehension of what like for Italian dishes you should use this and Chinese dishes you should use this <pause dur="short"/> it all just goes in together</u>
<u n="920" who="S0060">I always remember doing different stuff at at unit and I ended up <pause dur="short"/> literally there was a row well in fact I've done the same ere actually <pause dur="short"/> at the back of the cooker there was a row of all different sort of herb and spices and whatever and it would literally right what shall I do to add some flavour into it cos otherwise it's just totally bland <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0086">I've got a bit of thing with of having a dish of food that all tastes the same as well <pause dur="short"/> but that's quite difficult <pause dur="short"/> but that that's the thing about risotto or pasta that sort of puts me off <pause dur="short"/> I like it but I suppose after about half way through it's sort of</u>
<u n="922" who="S0060">A bit much of that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0086">all the same <pause dur="short"/> I suppose when you go to a restaurant they just give you quite a small amount don't they? I mean in our house there's four girls and one bloke ad the bloke is the one who does all the cooking <pause dur="short"/> it's hilarious <pause dur="short"/> I try as much as possible not to cook</u>
<u n="924" who="S0060">well that was why it always used to be good when I was living with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to b round there quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> and she's very very good a cooking and can like cook from nothing and it'll be amazing <pause dur="short"/> so it was you know whoever she was round it was we always knew we'd get a good feed</u>
<u n="925" who="S0086">I suppose when you go to a restaurant they just give you quite a small amount don't they? I mean in our house there's four girls and one bloke and the bloke is the one who does all the cooking <pause dur="short"/> it's hilarious <pause dur="short"/> I try as much as possible not to cook</u>
<u n="926" who="S0060">well that was why it always used to be good when I was living with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to be round there quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> and she's very very good a cooking and can like cook from nothing and it'll be amazing <pause dur="short"/> so it was you know whoever she was round it was we always knew we'd get a good feed</u>
<u n="927" who="S0086">yeah boys like that don't they?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0060">me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I mean <pause dur="short"/> I I was bad I'm not a good cook but compared with me sorry compared with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm like master chef <pause dur="short"/> when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had come he he'd came over from South Africa when did I first meet up with him? Seven years ago something like that <pause dur="short"/> and he'd only just come over <pause dur="short"/> and eh from his background in South Africa everything was done for him <pause dur="short"/> you know he never  he never had to cook for himself <pause dur="short"/> and so to be over here on his own kind of thin and having to cook it he had no idea what to do <pause dur="short"/> you know he couldn't cook to save his life <pause dur="short"/> so I was sort of showing him sort of basic stuff that I and it was like wow this is amazing</u>
<u n="929" who="S0086">ah bless him</u>
<u n="930" who="S0060">but then blooming <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's <trunc>ama</trunc> I mean she would make <pause dur="short"/> I can remember one time she cooked em tiramisu <pause dur="short"/> and it was in this like big eh sort of dish about this size and and that was our evening meal for like two days</u>
<u n="931" who="S0086">Jesus</u>
<u n="932" who="S0060">just tiramisu <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0086">yum</u>
<u n="934" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we never  We never  bothered cooking it was just now we'll just to <trunc>ea</trunc> to eat desert</u>
<u n="935" who="S0086">that's all your calories there</u>
<u n="936" who="S0060">well that was it  that was it  She was going for it but</u>
<u n="937" who="S0086">nice <pause dur="short"/> I love one of my friends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> live together and they both have girlfriends and they used to invite the girlfriends round because they lived in an absolute put <pause dur="short"/> the girls couldn't stand it so they would round clean up cook dinner <pause dur="short"/> the boys loved it it was absolute dream they would just sit there having a few can while the girls were in the kitchen <pause dur="short"/> I used to have such a go at them just say just you can't do this <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> think of the feminist movement <pause dur="short"/> you will set the feminist movement back about eighty years <pause dur="short"/> stop it <pause dur="short"/> they'd be like yeah but you haven't seen the house <pause dur="short"/> it's disgusting <pause dur="short"/> okay fine <pause dur="short"/> I love to clean I'm like Kim and Aggie I've got those eh Marigolds with like the <unclear/> and the feathers and the pearls <pause dur="short"/> amazing <pause dur="short"/> in fact actually I <trunc>nomina</trunc> nominate charity as em <anon type="place"/> you know on Mill road <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> is in <anon type="place"/> on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0086">and they're a  they're a  charity that help young mums and that sort of thing</u>
<u n="940" who="S0060">oh I know yes yes</u>
<u n="941" who="S0171">ding ding round one</u>
<u n="942" who="S0086">thank you so much this looks lovely <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> yummy</u>
<u n="943" who="S0060">thank you darling</u>
<u n="944" who="S0086">they've got a charity shop and they need help organising it an cleaning and sorting <pause dur="short"/> absolutely my favourite thing in the world <pause dur="short"/> I'm I've got a bit of OCD <pause dur="short"/> and eh I can't wait I've signed myself up <pause dur="short"/> they give us seven hours a year volunteering so it's basically like a holiday out of the office just to go and volunteer</u>
<u n="945" who="S0060">oh that's good</u>
<u n="946" who="S0086">so yeah it's em can't wait for that</u>
<u n="947" who="S0171">it's the first time I've tried this bread</u>
<u n="948" who="S0086">so it's garlic bread is it?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0171">no not this one no this is just a a plain kind of <pause dur="short"/> it went dry though</u>
<u n="950" who="S0086">the mushrooms are delicious</u>
<u n="951" who="S0171">thank you</u>
<u n="952" who="S0060">alright?</u>
<u n="953" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="954" who="S0060">what?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0171">what do you think of the bread?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0060">it's nice</u>
<u n="957" who="S0171">yeah?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0060">mm</u>
<u n="959" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> ooh</u>
<u n="960" who="S0060">just need a bit of balsamic vinegar and some oil you know dunk it in</u>
<u n="961" who="S0171">do you think I'm a chef <pause dur="short"/> do you think I'm in a  in a  <trunc>re</trunc> in a restaurant or something love?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0086">just call you Delia</u>
<u n="963" who="S0060">that's it</u>
<u n="964" who="S0171">most of the mushrooms are chestnut mushrooms <pause dur="short"/> which has started to be a bit of an experiment as well cos usually I would just buy the normal plain mushrooms and em I decided to be a bit more experimental a few weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> and thought well I'll give those a go see what they're like</u>
<u n="965" who="S0086">I never used to be able to eat mushrooms <pause dur="short"/> I like mushroom soup and mushroom sauce but the actual mushrooms are too big and squidgy and I just didn't like the texture <pause dur="short"/> that's the whatever I don't like it's usually the texture as opposed to the taste <pause dur="short"/> but em one day I just said to myself come on man up</u>
<u n="966" who="S0060">it's just a mushroom</u>
<u n="967" who="S0086">it's just a mushroom <pause dur="short"/> you like mushroom taste <pause dur="short"/> come on get it down you <pause dur="short"/> and I did it actually <pause dur="short"/> strange <pause dur="short"/> I think it was in paella or something so <pause dur="short"/> I think that helps if it's with something else</u>
<u n="968" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="969" who="S0060">yeah when I was a kid I didn't used to like mushrooms but I'll eat them raw</u>
<u n="970" who="S0171">yeah he's a bit freaky like that</u>
<u n="971" who="S0086">there was em a Come Dine With Me episode where she cooked all raw food <pause dur="short"/> bit of a health reason probably <pause dur="short"/> apparently it's much better for you <pause dur="short"/> but you'd never have a hot meal would you? If everything was raw</u>
<u n="972" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="973" who="S0086">so you haven't been out in the sunshine then?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0171">I try to avoid it</u>
<u n="975" who="S0086">aw</u>
<u n="976" who="S0060">I got a text message from you on was it Wednesday? Saying I've seen a bee if there's bees about there's wasps about</u>
<u n="977" who="S0171">sure enough Friday there's a wasp</u>
<u n="978" who="S0086">yeah I can't stand wasps but his weather is just amazing <pause dur="short"/> it's so</u>
<u n="979" who="S0171">I like <pause dur="short"/> I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday cos we'd gone out we had a few minutes to wait out for the film to start</u>
<u n="980" who="S0060">it was lovely</u>
<u n="981" who="S0171">and we were sitting outside in the sun <pause dur="short"/> it was really nice <pause dur="short"/> and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I hate the fucking sun I bloody hate sun I can't stand it <pause dur="short"/> and I went well actually no that's a lie cos I like the sun <pause dur="short"/> it's just what comes with it that I don't like <pause dur="short"/> then I can go out for a fag and be terrified</u>
<u n="982" who="S0060">no <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't like hot hot weather <pause dur="short"/> but I do prefer what we've been having the last sort of week or so <pause dur="short"/> it's been nice</u>
<u n="983" who="S0086">yeah cos you can sit out in it <pause dur="short"/> it <trunc>was</trunc> the sun's warm but it's not too overpowering <pause dur="short"/> it's not that sort of heat where you can't move</u>
<u n="984" who="S0060">no I suffer unfortunately with the sort of low sun <pause dur="short"/> especially like sort of driving at morning and evening into the sun sort of and eh <pause dur="short"/> I end up with very very bad eyes <pause dur="short"/> it's bad at the minute <pause dur="short"/> I must go the doctor and say I've got very very dry eyes</u>
<u n="985" who="S0086">oh no</u>
<u n="986" who="S0060">and eh sort of when I wake up in the morning it's like I've just been cheese grating around my eyes in the night they're so sore</u>
<u n="987" who="S0086">oh no</u>
<u n="988" who="S0060">but eh <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> the bright sun doesn't help but</u>
<u n="989" who="S0086">have you had that before</u>
<u n="990" who="S0060">when I  When I  was little em I used to suffer with this eh I can't remember what it's called now but <pause dur="short"/> basically my my eyes were very photosensitive so like if I was out playing like during the day <pause dur="short"/> when it got to the evening and then sort if it was getting darker my eyes would burn <pause dur="short"/> it would feel like they had em 'scuse me like hot grit in them</u>
<u n="991" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="992" who="S0060">I used to have like cream and I used to wear sunglasses all the time <pause dur="short"/> even like an overcast day I'd have to wear dark glasses and stuff <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean I don't get it anywhere near as bad now as I used to <pause dur="short"/> but I still do get it <pause dur="short"/> you can sort of you know driving with it sort of bright now I know I'm going to be sort of have bad eyes that night sort of thing</u>
<u n="993" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> rubbish <pause dur="short"/> I used to feel really sorry for the kids at school who had really bad hay fever <pause dur="short"/> you know and as soon as the summer term starts they let you go out in the grass and the playing friend and there was a kid <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and he was he couldn't he like even just looking at the grass his eyes would start to stream</u>
<u n="994" who="S0060">really?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0086">he had to stand on the playground and everyone else was off playing in the grass <pause dur="short"/> sad little face and juts really used to suffer from it</u>
<u n="996" who="S0060">unfortunately I do think that's a symptom of the way we live these days that you know we've spent so many years just pouring disinfectant over ourselves and you know that <pause dur="short"/> just not got any tolerance of anything you know <pause dur="short"/> it's awful <pause dur="short"/> I mean I I suffer very badly with the with dust allergies so I take anti-histamine which works brilliantly <pause dur="short"/> for years I used to just say no it's all mumbo jumbo it doesn't make any difference it's trying to sell you something <pause dur="short"/> em I tried it for a few weeks and I mean I I would I would have like sneezing fits and my eyes would be streaming <pause dur="short"/> and now hardly anything at all is it?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> well only when you remember to take them</u>
<u n="998" who="S0060">well yeah when I forget to take them it it get a bit <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> makes a big difference but I mean like you say there's people out there now that even the slightest hint of anything they're blooming a wreck <pause dur="short"/> but eh you know all these peanut allergies and all this stuff now that everyone has to be so aware of <pause dur="short"/> you know it was never even heard of didn't exist but it's getting worse and worse and worse <pause dur="short"/> more people more allergies and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I mean they reckon blooming globally reducing the blooming male sperm count because of the amount of oestrogen in water <pause dur="short"/> because so many women are taking the pill and it obviously get puts back into the  into the water supply <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="999" who="S0086">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> blimey <pause dur="short"/> it's funny</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0171">that's alright <pause dur="short"/> women will always rule the world</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0171">that's one way of doing it <pause dur="short"/> putting some hormones in the system</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0060">Cos there's so much you know goes through it the water supply through</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0171">you all done mrs?</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0060">you know all that recycling yeah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0086">I'm done that was delicious thanks love <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0086">it's like when you see the anti-bacterial sprays isn't it? With mum and their babies <pause dur="short"/> you think babies need germs actually <pause dur="short"/> they need to build up a resistance</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0060">well I can remember when I was a kid being taken round to the kid that had chicken pox or the measles or whoever so that you'd catch it <pause dur="short"/> you know? But now it's all about you know keeping them all in a little cotton wool cocoon and not exposing them to it <pause dur="short"/> and then you see guys when they get into their thirties you know twenties or thirties or forties getting something that when you're that age it you know <pause dur="short"/> like chicken pox and things like measles especially it can do horrible stiff to you when you're older</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0086">when you're an adult absolutely <pause dur="short"/> doesn't it do things to your testes</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0060">yeah measles does <pause dur="short"/> and chicken pox can cause you to get shingles and things like that</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0086">elephantitis of the balls</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0086">it's not what you want</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0060">not really</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0086">not when people are going to be seeing them <pause dur="short"/> or or just carrying them around <pause dur="short"/> that must be quite a hardship <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you need a hand?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0171">oh no I'm alright love <pause dur="short"/> it's not actually me that cooks it it's the the oven</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0086">ooh lovely</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0060">but no</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0086">ah DVDs <pause dur="short"/> how many DVDs do you think you've got?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0060">far too many</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0086">you've got loads <pause dur="short"/> did you watch them?</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0060">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0171">how any of these should I do? Shall I do one or shall I do tow <pause dur="short"/> is one going to be enough?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> yeah probably <pause dur="short"/> probably I would only have a <trunc>t</trunc> a couple of bits</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0171">you'd eat the whole thing wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0060">no no no I knowing you I'll end up with the two ends <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's fine <pause dur="short"/> you two can share the middle</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0171">yeah? Then I'll just do the one</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0086">Cos I was like this <pause dur="short"/> I got into a real habit it's almost like an addiction you know you see a movie and you buy it  and you buy it and you buy it  and I really had to stop myself</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0060">yeah no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got that <pause dur="short"/> anything anything she sees at Tesco's that she thinks ooh that might be we get it</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's easily done through and I just I was getting to the point where I thought I'm never going to watch these again what am I doing? But it's it's collectables <pause dur="short"/> I'm like with books though I'm the same the books <pause dur="short"/> and nowhere to put them which is why I'd quite like my own little bedsit</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0060">well that's why there's there's booked everywhere that's that's me stacking book up everywhere</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0086">running out of space <pause dur="short"/> you just you have got a lot of things haven't you? DO you need more shelving units?</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0060">yeah I I won  I own  like one or two things</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0171" trans="overlap">yeah extreme needs</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0171">yes of course you do <pause dur="short"/> yeah everything else is all mine <pause dur="short"/> right if you're going to excise me I'm going to go outside for a cigarette <pause dur="short"/> I shall not be a moment <pause dur="short"/> don't be rude</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0060">me? I'm never rude <pause dur="short"/> no we've got em <pause dur="short"/> we knew that we didn't have much storage space so we bought two two or three I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> of those book cases so we've got one upstairs that's got loads of stuff on it <pause dur="short"/> but eh <pause dur="short"/> that's what one so the back bedrooms virtually is just a blooming storage repository <pause dur="short"/> bookcases and cabinets and stuff to keep everything</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0086">well that's the thing cos I for a while I was moving all the time so I basically just had a handkerchief on a stick you know I was really getting really ruthless <pause dur="short"/> I was culling everything <pause dur="short"/> but then it gets to a point where you think I've got to want this stuff and I eventually I hopefully will actually have a home rather than just a room <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing about house sharing you don't I don't feel like I can spread out <pause dur="short"/> I mean we don't have a living room <pause dur="short"/> if we did I don't think I'd put any of my stuff in it</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0060">when eh <pause dur="short"/> before I moved here with with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean the stuff I had at Regency Square I hardly had anything at all really <pause dur="short"/> but eh but since then we've kind of filled you know expanded to fill the space that we've got sort of thing</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0060">with the eh</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0086">well you you would do as well</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0060">I know I mean <pause dur="short"/> I mean like we were saying earlier I really struggle to see the point of of moving from where we were <pause dur="short"/> it was like well you know it's a great place it's big enough for what we need blah blah blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but having since moved out here I mean it's a lot lot better</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's good that you're noticing a difference</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0060">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there it was always helter skelter hustle bustle and you know busy streets lot of noise <pause dur="short"/> whereas out here it's all very calm and relaxed it's a lot easier to get to <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> yeah if we go into town or whatever you know well if it's during the day we get a bus but if we're going in for a you know going to the bar or something in the evening or something it's what? Twelve quid or something for a taxi which is nothing in the grand scheme of things <pause dur="short"/> you know it's a few pints of beer</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0086">that's really good actually? Is that how much it is? About twelve quid?</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what was the  What was the  <trunc>bu</trunc> the taxi for you the other day?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0171">oh</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0060">to get home</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0171">it's usually about fourteen pound but</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0086">that's really good though</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0060" trans="overlap">fourteen pound alright</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0086">that's really good though cos for me to get a cab from where I am on <anon type="place"/> costs about eight nine pounds</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0171">God <pause dur="short"/> I think the last time I caught a taxi though he actually charged me less <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if he's just being nice or if he's  or if he's  cos he <trunc>do</trunc> charged me twelve <pause dur="short"/> by the time we got in</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0060">yeah I <trunc>r</trunc>I was just saying twelve cos I thought that was what you paid last time</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0171">yeah it was the last time yeah</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0060">but eh where I was at at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> that used to be like twenty-two pound or something like that</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0086">jeez</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that that was back in the days when we used to go into town a lot more often</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0171">yes those were the days <pause dur="short"/> I cannot anymore park <pause dur="short"/> eh</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0086">we're grownups now</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0171">yeah we're grownups now <pause dur="short"/> we don't get  any more <pause dur="short"/> but eh but no I remember cos with taxis it depends on where they go <pause dur="short"/> and most of the time I mean obviously they're allowed to use the the bus ways you know the bus barriers they can get through them <pause dur="short"/> and I think that's probably what he did differently <pause dur="short"/> was when he come out of town</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0060">oh so he took the short cut</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0171">he went  he went  a slightly different way <pause dur="short"/> and although the other  the other  taxi took me <pause dur="short"/> you know the the road that runs between Lloyds and <trunc>TS</trunc> eh Lloyds and Boots</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0060">yeah I know where you mean</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0171">he was taking me through that way <pause dur="short"/> whereas the last taxi had taken me straight through via the bus route</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0060">well I always used to think that em going out in <anon type="place"/> was cos we were you know once you go across the A fourteen it becomes more expensive <pause dur="short"/> if you cross and go outside of the town sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> but eh</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0086">Taxis man <pause dur="short"/> they're a joke <pause dur="short"/> I mean when and when it snowed you know six weeks ago or whatever it was <pause dur="short"/> my friend lives in <anon type="place"/> but she was in the city <pause dur="short"/> we were going to meet on the Saturday night but she was with her fella during the day <pause dur="short"/> I think I was home waiting to hear from her and then the snow started it started on Saturday night didn't it?</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0086">early evening <pause dur="short"/> and I thought ah I'll just wait for her to text me but I won't come and meet I'll get her to some here just get a cab <pause dur="short"/> and then it started snowing quite heavily and I hadn't heard from her so I gave her a ring it was about seven o'clock and I said where are you? She said oh we're in the pub we're just we had dinner and we got carried away <pause dur="short"/> sorry where are you <pause dur="short"/> and I as like oh I'm at home it's snowing <pause dur="short"/> she's like what? She got out of the pub and she was like holy moley I had no idea it was going to snow <pause dur="short"/> and I was like are you being serious <pause dur="short"/> she said no I didn't check the weather forecast <pause dur="short"/> like how are you going to get home? She's like yeah <trunc>ho</trunc> how how am I going to get home? mm <pause dur="short"/> I may as well look at the buses and then I'll call you back <pause dur="short"/> walked to the bus station on <anon type="place"/> no buses <pause dur="short"/> no signs no nothing <pause dur="short"/> and I said just get a cab home and we'll meet another time <pause dur="short"/> and the cabs weren't going <pause dur="short"/> they wouldn't even leave the city <pause dur="short"/> and so she got a cab to mine <pause dur="short"/> next morning managed to get a cab but not until later in the day cos if all that snow <pause dur="short"/> panther charged her <pause dur="short"/> I think they wanted to charge her and extra ten pounds going between because it's instead of going from to go from my house rather than from town <pause dur="short"/> even though normally it would cost about <trunc>s</trunc> like seven or eight pounds to get from mine to town <pause dur="short"/> wanted to charge her an extra ten pound <pause dur="short"/> so the cab home to Haverhill cost thirty-five quid</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> taxis in <anon type="place"/> are a joke <pause dur="short"/> so expensive <pause dur="short"/> the meter starts at like four pounds doesn't it? So bad</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0060">no that that Saturday you are talking about we were out and about <pause dur="short"/> and we'd come back and there'd be no sign of anything we were home and we were going out on the Sunday <pause dur="short"/> and we got up the next morning and it was like <pause dur="short"/> what on earth's happened here kind of things</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> there was loads of it wasn't there?</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0060">em well we'd got we we it was fine for us coming out on the Sunday <pause dur="short"/> and we drove out down <pause dur="short"/> and literally all round the loop road there was cars parked up on the verges where they'd obviously the the main road had been eh cleared but no one could actually get in to their road o they just pared there and walked <pause dur="short"/> so there was just a long line of cars all the way round and we're like this is weird <pause dur="short"/> so we drove out round isn't it? Do you remember that?</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0171">what's that?</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0086">the abandoned cars</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0060">all the cars that were parked along round the <unclear/> road in the snow</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0171">ah god yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you know the last time it snowed <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't really a lot was it?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0060">no no</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0171">not really</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0086">it was more flowy</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0171">well there was em abandoned cars up on the top of the hill again</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0060">yeah?</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0171">there was hardly nothing <pause dur="short"/> hardly a bit of snow and they go in and <pause dur="short"/> ah bugger it and just abandon their cars</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0060">yeah but unfortunately these days any bit of snow is just used as an excuse now ah it's snowing I can't get to work <pause dur="short"/> I can't do this can't do that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I remember last last January the year before last rather <pause dur="short"/> yeah year and bit <pause dur="short"/> and eh I was I had to go for eh <pause dur="short"/> we had we have our monthly like commercial reviews at <unclear/> the regional office <pause dur="short"/> and for me I normally I would leave at five and would <trunc>h</trunc>get there for seven so I can miss all the traffic on the M25 and eh I'd left and it was when I mean all the real bad snow <pause dur="short"/> and I left at five and I got there at eight <pause dur="short"/> l and I sat outside cos waiting for someone to turn up to open it up and everything <pause dur="short"/> and it got to half past ten and no one had turned up <pause dur="short"/> so I just want oh bugger that I'm going to go <pause dur="short"/> and it took me it only took me two hours to get home because obviously by half past ten all the people that were going to try had tried and just it was done <pause dur="short"/> no one else was travelling <pause dur="short"/> so it was clear <pause dur="short"/> em but I mean there were people that were that lived almost in walking distance of the office and they just hadn't even bothered to come in <pause dur="short"/> I'm like I've driven a hundred miles and I've got there <pause dur="short"/> where is everybody else? You know people that were really close to the office and didn't even bother to try and go in <pause dur="short"/> you know really peed me off <pause dur="short"/> but eh I mean I can remember when eh good few years ago <pause dur="short"/> when was that? Nine years ago now? Yeah will have been nine years ago when the M eleven ended up in shit because of the snow and they hadn't gritted anything <pause dur="short"/> and I was working at Harlow at the time but living out on the M four <pause dur="short"/> and eh I'd left and it was I'd left at sort of basically said oh we need to get gone otherwise we're going to get stuck <pause dur="short"/> and I'd left at three o'clock or four o'clock something like that <pause dur="short"/> I'd come out onto the M11 going south and there was nobody <pause dur="short"/> I mean there was snow everywhere but it was like where is everybody? What's going on? And it was cos it was closed further up where it had just been totally whited out <pause dur="short"/> and it was so bad that people were stuck in their cars like over like twenty-four hours <pause dur="short"/> and they were in their cars and they were running out of fuel where they would have it left of tick over to keep warm and things like that <pause dur="short"/> and it was like days before all of them were eh clear <pause dur="short"/> but I mean thankfully I was sort of ahead of the storm so to speak so I got home and everything fine but <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've never it's never been well they've they've always been more prepared for it now <pause dur="short"/> but then they'd done absolutely nothing before the snow <pause dur="short"/> they knew it was coming but they'd done nothing cos they didn't think it was really going to be as bad <pause dur="short"/> and like suddenly the whole of the M eleven was totally out of it <pause dur="short"/> totally gone</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0171">well that's what they did this year didn't they? After last years <pause dur="short"/> they ended up stocking up on extra salt and extra grit and then they've not not really used it now cos it's not been that bad</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0060">well they haven't needed to but <pause dur="short"/> the whole thing is everyone every year moans saying oh well how can you know place like Norway and Sweden and all this cope and it's cos they have a lot more often a lot more regularly <pause dur="short"/> so they pay to have stuff in place <pause dur="short"/> well we can all pay more taxes and have snow ploughs and grit and all this sat there doing nothing for eleven months of the year and maybe do something for a month maybe</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0086">absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0060">and eh</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0171">well it's not even month though is it?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0060">well no it's not <pause dur="short"/> few weeks if that</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0171">it doesn't last a month</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0060">and it's like well <pause dur="short"/> you know people aren't going to do it <pause dur="short"/> they'll moan and gripe about it but if you actually said them okay well</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0086">give us some more money then</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0060">okay an extra hundred pound a month in tax and we'll have it all sorted for you everybody would be up in arms <pause dur="short"/> oh well don't need it rah</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0086">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> be interesting to find out what they do about the privatisation of the roads <pause dur="short"/> they were talking about that last week</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0060">yeah that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> yeah they've <trunc>be</trunc> they've been saying well no no existing roads will be made into toll roads</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0086">yeah loads of new roads</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0060">so so there's going to be a lot of new roads go up <pause dur="short"/> to say there you go use this</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0171">more work for you then darling</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0060">well it will be <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's it all started with the M six toll which we built <pause dur="short"/> you know that was one of the first eh Dartford crossing obviously is a toll <pause dur="short"/> but the Dartford crossing is the one I still curse them because when that was built it was that it would only operate as a toll until it paid off the bills</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0171">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0060">em but they obviously realised they were going to make too much money out of it so it's it's operated as a toll ever since <pause dur="short"/> cos they long long ago paid off the bills</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0086">paid off the builders yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they're saying the the if they do expand the A14 it will be paid for the tolls <pause dur="short"/> do you think that's what's going to happen?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0060">they've had one the book plans for doing it for so long but there's always been so much protest over what would have to be done cos it goes through so many middle of the nothing places and eh it's been put back and put back and put back and put back <pause dur="short"/> you know but I mean the there's some very basic stuff that they could do which would make it so much better <pause dur="short"/> you know getting rid of all of these at grey junctions so like Catthorpe Interchange and all of those junctions where you're coming down everything's coming down to nothing <pause dur="short"/> and then winds through a tiny little bit and then go again <pause dur="short"/> you know get rid of them and make them grade separated junctions where the A fourteen carries on and it's just people then come off <pause dur="short"/> and it would make it a lot easier <pause dur="short"/> but eh <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I think they're going to have to get a lot more money just to overcome all the the protest and wooha there is in the different areas and yeah probably the only way to do that is to to say oh yeah we're going to have it operated and maintained by a company that's going to fund it <pause dur="short"/> you know so I wouldn't be surprised if you know probably some of my lot end up coming up with something of how they could do it fund it and operate it <pause dur="short"/> you know PFIs are a lot of the things these days so <pause dur="short"/> just having a taste see if it was poisoned</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0171">if it was poisoned I think the pair of us would be in a lot of trouble</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0060">we might have keeled over <pause dur="short"/> be interesting to see if they do anything to A ten <pause dur="short"/> on the way to Norwich <pause dur="short"/> cos that roads <trunc>pre</trunc> pretty em pretty slow isn't it? If you get stuck behind a tractor you're screwed</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0060">well they were going to build this new town weren't they? Em <pause dur="short"/> somewhere</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0171">Don't we go down the A ten to go down to Reading?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0060">no the A one</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0171">oh</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0060">the A ten does go all the way down there <pause dur="short"/> just between what's the next bridge up can't remember what it is on the A10</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0171"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0060">no no you're going the other way</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0086">you're going south</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0060">North</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what it was now but there was plans to do that</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0086">Ely is the A ten isn't it?</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0060">sorry?</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0086">Ely is on the A ten isn't it?</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0060">Ely yeah but not that far up <pause dur="short"/> em and there was a load of hooha saying well you know you've got all these plans for building it <pause dur="short"/> it was like ten or twenty thousand new houses they were going to build <pause dur="short"/> and it was like there was all these plans for building and this but you've not got any plans to improve the A ten <pause dur="short"/> so where are all these people going to go? They're going to commute down to Cambridge or they're going to come to Cambridge to get on the train to go into London <pause dur="short"/> you know where are they all going to come? They're going to come down on the twenty ten twenty miles of the A10 <pause dur="short"/> which already is pretty chock-a-block every day <pause dur="short"/> em but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean they were talking I don't know whether it's going to happen <pause dur="short"/> of building a new train station to the south of Cambridge to act as a commuter station <pause dur="short"/> so instead of everyone having to come into Cambridge to get a <trunc>bu</trunc> eh to get a train rather it would go there and and get a commuter line down but <pause dur="short"/> I've not heard any more about that <pause dur="short"/> but eh</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0086">I think they should do that with the students <pause dur="short"/> you know they're building loads of em new flats and houses in the C B one quarter <pause dur="short"/> they're building them for students <pause dur="short"/> well students can fuck off quite frankly <pause dur="short"/> put them in a little village with a bus a couple of times a day <pause dur="short"/> and you know</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0060"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> there's loads of what do they call it? I can't <pause dur="short"/> there's some name which basically means cheap and nasty but it's not</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0086">housing association?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0060">no cos they don't <pause dur="short"/> nothing is called the housing association anymore</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0086">oh right</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0060">it was em a type of housing they call it now <pause dur="short"/> what's it <trunc>ca</trunc> what do they call it? Cos when we were there building the riverside bridge they were <trunc>do</trunc> there's a big housing development on the south side of the river isn't there <pause dur="short"/> and it was all about how certain ones of them were going to be priced as you know for getting a decent amount of money and there was other ones they were having to build as part of the planning permission <pause dur="short"/> and it was called this other thing and I can't remember</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0086">affordable housing?</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0060">no it wasn't  it wasn't  It was something <pause dur="short"/> I can't think what it was</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0086">welfare housing</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0060">but yeah it basically meant it <trunc>ma</trunc> it basically meant affordable <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't it was a you know a bit of a phrase I can't remember what it was <pause dur="short"/> cos we were talking to them cos obviously why we while we were there working and everything <pause dur="short"/> and they were saying ah yeah you know because it <trunc>w</trunc> at the time I was sort of thinking oh maybe I could you know buy something here and that <pause dur="short"/> and but when we were talking to them it was like ah yeah you wouldn't want to look at any of these <pause dur="short"/> and I was like why is that oh well just you know <pause dur="short"/> the one's over there that were' going to be charging out at sort of three hundred grand cos they're going to have riverside frontage and this that and the other <pause dur="short"/> they use all the nice materials and all the cheap chit gets put into these ones over here <pause dur="short"/> and it's like really looks bad <pause dur="short"/> but eh but yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0086">that's bad but that's how they get away with it <pause dur="short"/> cheeky <pause dur="short"/> they should be building houses with solar panels as well really shouldn't they?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0060">did you read? There was a thing in the news <pause dur="short"/> some little old couple has been told they've got to remove twelve thousand pounds worth of solar panels that they put on their house cos they never got planning permission to do it and it doesn't fit in with the local</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0086">no way <pause dur="short"/> they won't you know postdate the planning permission? They won't agree to it?</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0060">said they wouldn't agree to it <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't ever wouldn't even agree to if they'd applied so they had to remove it</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> twelve grand <pause dur="short"/> that's a killer</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0060">it was basically they'd they'd done it because it would get them</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0086">would save them</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0060">they would have no need to to rely on the national grid anymore <pause dur="short"/> and the local council turned around and said no it's doesn't doesn't fit with the local area and you got to remove it all</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0086">that's rubbish <pause dur="short"/> that's the sort of thing you see on Grand Designs isn't it? When they do all these lovely things and they're like yeah planning permission is you know it's just waiting for the sign off <pause dur="short"/> and you think that's dangerous</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0060">I always remember when we built eh the <unclear/> at the junction at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> we had the offices and the sort of compound in that little <pause dur="short"/> well they call it the teardrop <pause dur="short"/> it's basically that bit of horrible scrubby land on the side of <anon type="place"/> as you drive into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1143" who="S0086">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0060">and there the guys had planning supposed planning permission there for a development there because he wanted to sell it to eh like Travelodge or something like that <pause dur="short"/> he obviously never got permission cos obviously they built on the south side by what was <anon type="place"/> or whatever it's now <pause dur="short"/> but eh but yeah so that stays as a horrible little bit of scrub land with its ponies and whatever on it <pause dur="short"/> as the entrance to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1145" who="S0086">oh charming <pause dur="short"/> yeah <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> one of my colleagues just bought a house in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> she says it's nice but I'm</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0060">some of its  Some of its  quite new but</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0086">it's new that's what  that's what  puts me off <pause dur="short"/> I don't I don't  really want to end up anywhere new <pause dur="short"/> I need somewhere with a bit of character but needs must</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0060">Cos you've got what's it called? The berries <pause dur="short"/> the strawberries and blackberries and all the roads round the top end are called</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0086">oh are they? I don't know it that well <pause dur="short"/> I mean is it supposed to be a little village in it's own right? Is it supposed to have it's own</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0060">yeah yeah yeah it's got everything <pause dur="short"/> well I mean there's big Tesco's there <pause dur="short"/> eh but it's a village in it's own right so it's got like a few little shops and things</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0086">has it got a school?</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0060">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember ever seeing one in honesty but it's got like there's a a doctors a you know a chiropractors and a you know takeaways and pubs and you know all that kind of palaver <pause dur="short"/> em and there's a little sort of business estate <unclear/> it's actually not really a business estate but there's a sort of industrial business bit there <pause dur="short"/> and obviously just across the A fourteen is the science park and everything</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0086">yeah yeah it is a great location</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can walk across now actually <pause dur="short"/> well there a bridge there's a pedestrian bridge across</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0086">is there? Oh that's quite good</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> literally you can go north to south across the A14 across the pedestrian bridge</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0086">oh that's good <pause dur="short"/> cos I was thinking about going you know <anon type="place"/> and that's not very far from me so I must find out where the bridge is</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0060">well it's right there <pause dur="short"/> right on the junction</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0086">is it?</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0060">literally right there</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0086">so as you drive past the science park approaching the roundabout</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0060">it's on your right</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0086">it's on your right <pause dur="short"/> oh ok</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0060">you can literally you can walk on the science park <pause dur="short"/> up and across the bridge and into Tesco's virtually <pause dur="short"/> you have to cross two roads but you do get there <pause dur="short"/> you go straight across</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0086">oh that's quite good</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0060">literally as you go <trunc>un</trunc> if you're on the A14 <pause dur="short"/> you go under the the junction and it's literally right there as you go through the big arch little architecturally done bridge</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0086">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to investigate</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's been there oh a good long while now</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0086">I never pay much attention <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I've ever <pause dur="short"/> I think I've only been to <anon type="place"/> a couple of times that was on my driving lessons <pause dur="short"/> when I started to learn the area</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0060">it's alright but it is quite expensive <pause dur="short"/> it's not cheap <pause dur="short"/> because it's right next to the science park so they charge a lot for the convenience <pause dur="short"/> you alright?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0060">you're looking at me in that kind of I want you to do something kind of way</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0171">didn't want you to anything but it's good to know that he knows what that looks like <pause dur="short"/> no cos I don't want the the sauce to</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0060">ain't going to burn if you sit down rather than stand up is it</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0171">yes because I'm about to disappear again</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0060">alright okay okay</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0171">silly boy <pause dur="short"/> don't understand the laws of cooking</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0060">I try not to if I'm honest with you</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0086">I can't believe it's Sunday night again already</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0060">I know it goes quick doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0086">it has such an effect on you losing an hour <pause dur="short"/> so confused this morning <pause dur="short"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> my boss is on secondment in New York for three months</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0060">oh right</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0086">yeah lucky cow <pause dur="short"/> I'm very jealous but I think it's all go <pause dur="short"/> you know they're <pause dur="short"/> she's on secondment because some another colleague has gone on maternity leave <pause dur="short"/> and her statutory maternity leave over six weeks <pause dur="short"/> so you literally have your baby recover enough to stand up and not want to kill yourself and then go back to work</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fire it out and straight back</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0086">yeah you know <pause dur="short"/> but they em <pause dur="short"/> I think it's because also the Press is a started off as UK company even though it's global now <pause dur="short"/> if you are you know an employee living in another country there the you get certain benefits rather than six weeks you get three months <pause dur="short"/> so eh which they don't need to offer you but you do get other perks as well <pause dur="short"/> but em <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty intense <pause dur="short"/> so she's left for three months cover and three months <trunc>l</trunc> maternity <pause dur="short"/> it's quite nice you can go for a long coffee break long lunch <pause dur="short"/> but it's pretty busy at the moment <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> try to keep my head above water with the new job pretend like I know what I'm doing <pause dur="short"/> say words and hope that they're the right ones <pause dur="short"/> say yes in all in the meeting and then go back to your desk and cry</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0060">oh no</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0086">what have I agreed to <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it's good though</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0060">well as long as it pays the bills</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0086">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> this was the year that I cleared my overdraft which I'm practically there so that's good <pause dur="short"/> and I'm putting money aside <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking my birthday is in December <pause dur="short"/> my best mate turns thirty-three weeks before <pause dur="short"/> so we're thinking that we'll go to New York <pause dur="short"/> cos I've never been</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0060">very nice</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0086">I've been to states but I never made it to the East coast so</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0060">you never made it to the East coast? You fly over the East Coast to get to the other side</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I flew to Texas where it snowed</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0060">oh no in Texas</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0086">hilarious</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0060">brilliant</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0086">they had a centimetre of snow <pause dur="short"/> the entire airport ground to a halt <pause dur="short"/> they did not know what to do with themselves <pause dur="short"/> they put themselves up in a hotel at night a really nice hotel and then we flew <pause dur="short"/> but because we were flying to Canada <pause dur="short"/> so our flight was really cheap because we went down to Texas and then back up again</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0060">so hang on you you flew flew to Texas where it was snowing <pause dur="short"/> was it like tropical in Canada or something?</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0086">no cos it was <pause dur="short"/> when was it it was March? Em <pause dur="short"/> it was this time four years ago <pause dur="short"/> and got to Canada it was snowing <pause dur="short"/> and then worked my way down the west coast and the across and the down into Mexico and then down into Cuba and then from Cuba flew home</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0060">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0086">so I never got as far <pause dur="short"/> any further than Illinois</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0060">Cos Cuba Cuba is virtually the East coast anyway <pause dur="short"/> you can see the East Coast from Cuba <pause dur="short"/> when we were in Florida we were down I the quays and we were looking out going oh that's Cuba over there and we we were using and aching as to whether or not we should go across from Florida to Cuba <pause dur="short"/> but it was a <trunc>lo</trunc> then it was a load of hassle to sort out getting into Cuba <pause dur="short"/> and we didn't bother</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0086">yea you've got to pay  you've got to pay  to go from America as well <pause dur="short"/> I mean I <trunc>th</trunc> it's impossible for a an American citizen to fly from America to Cuba <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a massive hassle doing it as a British traveller <pause dur="short"/> they charge you a hell of a lot</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0060" trans="overlap">when we tried to do it I mean this was a long time ago <pause dur="short"/> it was a load of hassle and we said oh we're not bothered</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0086">which is why I went into <trunc>M</trunc> Mexico and flew from there and it was much easier <pause dur="short"/> and they don't stamp your passport now when you leave Cuba for for American nationals so they can't tell that's where they've been with the embargo <pause dur="short"/> I demanded a stamp on my passport <pause dur="short"/> but em yeah but they don't stamp</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0060">no I I did Florida and all down that side <pause dur="short"/> that was nice but <pause dur="short"/> I would have liked to go to like Texas and all that but eh</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0086">Texas is mental</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0060">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0086">well we went <pause dur="short"/> we saw quite a lot of the south <pause dur="short"/> we went across into Illinois and then down into Louisiana and Alabama and Mississippi <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was yeah it was crazy <pause dur="short"/> really really crazy and we ended up in New Orleans which is where I the last place I was when I before I flew to Mexico and we went to a jazz festival <pause dur="short"/> and we'd only <pause dur="short"/> we went we wanted go for a week <pause dur="short"/> the girl I was with <pause dur="short"/> em but we could only get a night two nights was it even just the first night in the hostel? And after that it was fully booked because of the jazz festival and like it's fine  it's fine  we'll figure it out when we get there <pause dur="short"/> then when we got there we though shit <pause dur="short"/> new Orleans is quite a scary place actually <pause dur="short"/> it's quite <trunc>da</trunc> bits of it are quite dangerous <pause dur="short"/> and eh we didn't have anywhere to stay <pause dur="short"/> so the first night we're like oh it's fine we'll just we'll go we'll get a shower we'll go to a bar and we'll make a plan <pause dur="short"/> so we went to a bar <pause dur="short"/> there's a guy serving he's like hi girls how are you? And I was I'm English obviously the girl I was with is Australian <pause dur="short"/> and immediately people will talk to you because you're weird you've got a funny accent <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> and this guy owned the bar he was called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he was like oh my god you haven't got anywhere to live? Well I've got a spare room come and stay at mine and we were like holy Christ no way like he's going to be a weirdo</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0060">he's a psychopath</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0086">such a nice guy though <pause dur="short"/> we were the thing is <pause dur="short"/> we agreed we were going to stay in this house at like three in the morning <pause dur="short"/> we were so so drunk and we got stumbled back to the hostel <pause dur="short"/> the next morning <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s phone is ringing but it's a new phone so she doesn't realise for like ten minutes <pause dur="short"/> we're like what the hell is that noise? And it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>saying right girls I'm going to come pick you up in half and hour and we were like A who is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0060">who the hell are you?</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0086">B where are we going? C what the like I don't even know my own name right now <pause dur="short"/> so we try and like shower it's about thirty degrees it's so so hot <pause dur="short"/> and eh he picks us up <pause dur="short"/> he's already got us a ticket for the jazz fest <pause dur="short"/> we go he takes us round he introduces us to his friends <pause dur="short"/> we get the music is amazing <pause dur="short"/> we see Robert Plant he's like one of my favourite musicians <pause dur="short"/> it's fantastic there's just so much to do <pause dur="short"/> there's like carnival going on it's amazing <pause dur="short"/> he puts us up in his place <pause dur="short"/> no rent you know he doesn't charge us anything <pause dur="short"/> takes us out for dinner tells us good places to go <pause dur="short"/> he's so nice invites us to a party the last night I was there <pause dur="short"/> it was amazing it's just <pause dur="short"/> and people are like that in the States actually I I think often we had preconceived ideas that everyone was going to hate English people and they're going to be really either be stupid or you know really ignorant and eh <pause dur="short"/> they weren't they were just really <pause dur="short"/> really really nice people actually</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0060">no we had the same thing in Florida</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0171">you really enjoyed it when you went didn't you?</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we we'd only been in the country a couple of days and we were like what <pause dur="short"/> we had  we had  no accommodation booked it was just we'll find somewhere when we go wherever we go <pause dur="short"/> and eh we decided we want to find something you know get a drink about figure out what we were going to do <pause dur="short"/> and TGI Fridays <pause dur="short"/> oh we know TGI Fridays we know what we're going to get <pause dur="short"/> so we go in TGI Friday's and we're just stood at the bar having a drink and there's this couple sat beside us and we just got talking to them and they they were Puerto Rican <pause dur="short"/> and one of the guys that was with us he was Portuguese so obviously the language is similar so we got talking and we then all <unclear/> And they were saying you know come and stay with us you know we'll we'll put you up for a couple of nights and that's something you know <pause dur="short"/> we're going to do this and that and the other you can come with us <pause dur="short"/> and it's like you know we'd never met these people before <pause dur="short"/> you know foreign country <pause dur="short"/> and eh there was loads loads of people that were just the same <pause dur="short"/> we were over there at St Patrick's Day and there was just this massive street party and they close off the street and eh just have a massive party <pause dur="short"/> and eh I don't know what it's like there now but I mean booze was so ridiculously cheap its eh <pause dur="short"/> I can still remember <pause dur="short"/> radio one we were when we had gone back to Miami we were on South Beach and Radio One were going a thing there and I can remember just getting totally slaughtered <pause dur="short"/> there's a video somewhere of me just being well projectile vomiting on to the beach</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0086">wow</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0060">and the two of us the two guys we'd been drinking like most of the day and we were real bad and the other's had come and met us <pause dur="short"/> and eh the guy that was with I can't remember what the hell is his name I can't remember his name now <pause dur="short"/> but he'd been alright when I was chucking up but so far gone <pause dur="short"/> and he bought em as we were leaving the bar so that I could be sick on the beach he bought a bottle of eh like Don Perignon or something like that <pause dur="short"/> it was like a <trunc>hun</trunc> it was a hundred and twenty dollars or something <pause dur="short"/> and the footage of me vomiting there on the sun lounger then pans across to him with this bottle of Bollinger doing or whatever it was doing this on it <pause dur="short"/> and then two minutes later he's vomiting up this hundred and twenty dollars worth of Champagne or whatever it was on to the beach</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0086">ah bless <pause dur="short"/> that's not what you want</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0060">well no we we were there two or three week I think we were there in Florida <pause dur="short"/> and I mean we didn't do any of the sort of em we didn't go to MGM any of the the like Disneyland or any of the sort of touristy places <pause dur="short"/> but there was just absolutely tonnes to do <pause dur="short"/> it was really really good</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0086">I'd love to go to Florida <pause dur="short"/> I've been watching a lot of Dexter</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0086">so definitely would love to go to Miami <pause dur="short"/> it's very it is a very strange to be <pause dur="short"/> like it's a mix of like really old people and young people going to theme parks</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was going to say yeah <pause dur="short"/> when you're on the eh sort of all the beaches like south beach and everything is all very fancy and all very you know done up sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> but then there's a lot of other bits of it which were very sort of much older and very different styles <pause dur="short"/> but no Miami was really nice <pause dur="short"/> really enjoyed down in to the quays em and eh the Everglades the everglades was really nice</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you go on one of those boats with a propeller?</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0060">yeah yeah their boat yeah</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0086">nice</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> went out to an alligator farm and all of this but eh <pause dur="short"/> but we'd gone eh it was spring break <pause dur="short"/> so obviously the whole of America has descended on Florida anyway <pause dur="short"/> we didn't quite realise this before we  before we  got there <pause dur="short"/> but eh but no it was really good <pause dur="short"/> but eh it was about when we got there it was thirty degrees and about eight per cent humidity <pause dur="short"/> and we'd gone first we'd gone up in further north in Florida before coming down into the Everglades and the down into the quays <pause dur="short"/> and we were just due to drive back to Miami to get the flight home <pause dur="short"/> when in the quays it had got to I think it was like forty degrees and hundred per cent humidity <pause dur="short"/> and it had just got the the point where I was starting to go no I'm going to die if we don't leave sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> em but eh once we got out of the quays and back up to like Miami it was nice <pause dur="short"/> but eh</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0086">yeah that's intense <pause dur="short"/> you can't really have a holiday like that can you? Cos you can't really move</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0060">well I mean I would have expected <pause dur="short"/> I mean I suffer usually in the heat but it until it had got to that point it had been fine</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0060">because everywhere's air-conditioned <pause dur="short"/> you know as soon as you step in a door or somewhere it's like cold you know so it's only when you're out and about and there was just so much I mean there was so much to do <pause dur="short"/> I mean there was only I think there was only one night I mean given that it was em spring break you know so there's loads of people there was only night where we had any trouble at all finding something to somewhere to stay <pause dur="short"/> you know and literally we would  we would  just drive pick somewhere to go and we would drive there do something during the day and then in the evening try and find somewhere to stay <pause dur="short"/> I think it as only one night in sort of three weeks where we had any trouble and I think that was the first night down into the quays <pause dur="short"/> we ended up staying at this really <pause dur="short"/> if if we hadn't have been a a group of of youngsters probably pissed at the time it was one of the places it's a lot of em like holiday camp you know trailer park kind of place <pause dur="short"/> you would never have though to stay there <pause dur="short"/> and it was eh but it was hilarious the the two guys that ran the place and all this and it was hilarious <pause dur="short"/> but eh we were convinced that we'd got carbon monoxide poisoning from the blooming eh the air conditioning unit that was just going <vocal desc="misc"/> in the room all night sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> but eh but no I mean it was really good <pause dur="short"/> but I mean the only I always say the only trouble with eh America was the Americans but they were in honesty really good</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they are nice I do like them <pause dur="short"/> I mean they're all batty as hell <pause dur="short"/> I mean even before I was travelling with my Australian friend cos I met her when I was in San Francisco and we carried on together <pause dur="short"/> even before I met her the Australians <trunc>co</trunc> the Americans can't tell the difference between an English and an Australian accent so wherever you go ah you're Australian <pause dur="short"/> no I'm British oh that's so great do you know the Queen? Et cetera et cetera et cetera <pause dur="short"/> no I don't know the queen <pause dur="short"/> there's actually sixty millions of us you know funnily enough don't know the queen <pause dur="short"/> but it was lovely <pause dur="short"/> had a really good time and it was the last <pause dur="short"/> until last year when I went to Croatia and Berlin in like a long holiday that was the last sort of big holiday that I'd had <pause dur="short"/> I think that's why maybe I've got itchy feet <pause dur="short"/> well actually no that's not true <pause dur="short"/> I did go to Australia just over a year ago for a month <pause dur="short"/> okay yeah I am lying <pause dur="short"/> which was amazing I got back I was like right that's it I'm moving out there <pause dur="short"/> not really because it was an amazing place <pause dur="short"/> it was lovely and it's pretty and the people are nice and I've got friends there <pause dur="short"/> but it's just a really good place to explore that part of the world you know you just feel I don't need to go that far <unclear/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0060">I got loads loads of friend and workmates have gone either New Zealand Australia and just gone don't need do come back</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0086">yeah well New Zealand is much I think is much prettier and maybe it's more like home <pause dur="short"/> you know it's it's really green and luscious which Australia isn't <pause dur="short"/> but it's pretty none the less <pause dur="short"/> but it's just expensive to live there <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose it's all relative if you're working <pause dur="short"/> ooh is this me? Thank you so much</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0171">grubs up</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0060">thank you darling</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0171">no you <pause dur="short"/> can you take you? Ah <pause dur="short"/> in your hand</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0060">I'll take it</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0171">so I can put mine down</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0086">delish wow</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0060">but yeah</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0086">so are you going to have a holiday this year?</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0060">em well</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0086">England here we come <pause dur="short"/> going to see your mum</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0060">we're going  We're going  up to Orkney to see Hannah's mum</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0086">oh nice</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0060">in two</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0171">two weeks <trunc>yeste</trunc> eh two weeks Friday</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0060">two weeks <pause dur="short"/> but we're only up there for like a week <pause dur="short"/> but apart from that we've got nothing planned have we darling? But</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0060">so that'll be nice then so that's Easter is it?</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0171">easter bank holiday</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0060">yeah yeah we start travelling up <pause dur="short"/> well we're not going go on the Good Friday are we?</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0060">leave the good Friday as a chill out work day and start travelling on</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0171">on the Saturday</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0171">yeah I can't wait <pause dur="short"/> I need a break from work as well</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> bit too <unclear/> How is your sister doing?</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0171">tall</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0060">really?</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0171">tall and long hair</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0060">mm <pause dur="short"/> how old is she now <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>fif</trunc> fourteen?</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0171">she's twelve <pause dur="short"/> no she's not <pause dur="short"/> she's thirteen now isn't she? Yeah she's just turned thirteen in October</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0060">yeah thirteen</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0171">so she's just hit the teens <pause dur="short"/> mum was saying that she's em that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s now taller than her <pause dur="short"/> which she doesn't like too much</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0060">but that wouldn't take much cos your mum's not yeah <pause dur="short"/> your mum's not that tall</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0060">we'll see the new house won't we?</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0086">oh have they moved?</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0171">yeah when we last went up there's em there was an empty plot of land behind my grandparents place <pause dur="short"/> and em my mum took us round there to look at this nice bit of land <pause dur="short"/> and she says yeah they're doing a new housing development in there and that she'll be one of the first people to get a house in there</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0086">nice</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0171">and eh she moved in what? July?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0060">yeah it was back then wannit? Basically they I mean they live in basically council housing <pause dur="short"/> and the council obviously built newer housing cos the stuff there has been there years and years and years and years and years</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0171">surviving the weather of course</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0060">yeah it was very much you know survival style housing sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> they built a lot of modern houses and they've just been <trunc>per</trunc> you know moving them from the old stuff into the new <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what they're going to do with the old ones now <pause dur="short"/> whether they're going to get rid of them or?</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0171">well from what I spoke <pause dur="short"/> when I when mum was saying about when she moved out there was already someone moving in to her old her old bungalow <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but for some reason a lot of people want to live up there <pause dur="short"/> there's not a lot of work to do up there but</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0086">I know <pause dur="short"/> what do people do</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0171">well</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0086">can you farm? Is there farming?</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0171">there's a bit of farm land up there <pause dur="short"/> but you can't do any forestry work up there because Orkney is practically bare for threes</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> I was going to say are there any trees? A few</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0171">there's a  There's a  forest down the road from mum's old place isn't there <pause dur="short"/> but that's on private land <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> but yea apart from that there's absolutely nothing that I've seen anyway <pause dur="short"/> you might get the odd tree here and there that's kind of been forgotten about <pause dur="short"/> I think they were chopping them all down but</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0086">there's very very little <pause dur="short"/> I mean I I was saying one of the</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0171">there are lo lots of sheep <pause dur="short"/> there' a lot of sheep</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0060">I can't  I can't  imagine what the next generation up there would do if they would not leave</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0171">yeah I don't know what Charlie's going to do when she grows up yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0060">you know because there's literally nothing <pause dur="short"/> there's not enough people and not enough happening <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0171">although <pause dur="short"/> although the only thing they've got up there is where Mark used to work which is my step dad <pause dur="short"/> em he used to work on an oil rig that's up there</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0171">and Em</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0060">well it's an oil terminal isn't it?</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0171">yeah oil terminal yeah <pause dur="short"/> and there's a lot of jobs going on there but only if you can hack the bouncing of the little <pause dur="short"/> it's just a little dingy boat that they take you out</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0060">basically in between all the islands is the oil terminal <pause dur="short"/> where everything comes in from all the oil rigs</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0060">and eh</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0171">when when you're sailing in and out on the  on the  mainland ferry on the actual ferry you actually go past it and you've always get the you know you know it's there because they they light the flare and em the fire goes up and</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0060">obviously the only way to get to it is by boat <pause dur="short"/> so there's a tiny little you know literally</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0171">dingy</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0060">dozen man <pause dur="short"/> dingy right to get you out there</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0086">and do they have to be based on that</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0060">yeah and there' slots lots of people work on it <pause dur="short"/> it's one of the main sort of</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0171">it's the only employee well</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0060">employers yeah</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0171">yeah man employee <pause dur="short"/> but otherwise if you're into farm land into farming obviously that again is all private <pause dur="short"/> so if you own a farm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0060">farm farming only takes you know only covers employment for a very small <pause dur="short"/> compared with the amount of land it takes up it's a very small employer isn't it? Of people</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0171">and then of course there's the people that rely on tourism <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are the people that we stay with when we go up and they have their own B and B business <pause dur="short"/> and obviously they then therefore rely on the tourism that goes in up there <pause dur="short"/> which there is a lot of tourism up there that's I think that's got to be Orkney's main <pause dur="short"/> main income</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0060">yeah it must be hard in the winter months <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to make enough money in the summer to sort of tide you through <pause dur="short"/> I think what they do in the west say like in the winter months we go down to the seaside towns <pause dur="short"/> everything is boarded up</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean my mum seems to enjoy it <pause dur="short"/> she's working in Tesco's <pause dur="short"/> there's a Tesco's up there <pause dur="short"/> she's a check out</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0060">yeah finally</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0171">lady</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0060">there's been a Tesco's up there for like a year at most <pause dur="short"/> it's <pause dur="short"/> there hadn't been one up toil now</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0086">wow <pause dur="short"/> it is a nice part of the world <pause dur="short"/> my uncle <pause dur="short"/> bit of a strange man generally <pause dur="short"/> everyone he meets becomes a firm friend <unclear/></u>
<u n="1317" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0086">he's got one of the faces <pause dur="short"/> everyone wants to talk to him <pause dur="short"/> and he's sort of the good side of alcoholism <pause dur="short"/> you know not far away from the bad side</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0060">right</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0086">and eh he's got a friend called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who own s an island in Scotland <pause dur="short"/> as you do  As you do  He inherited it from his father <pause dur="short"/> and on the island <pause dur="short"/> it's off the <trunc>sk</trunc> em Paris <pause dur="short"/> lewis is It Lewis and Harris <pause dur="short"/> they were islands on the west coast</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0060">Harris is not</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0086">Harris</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0086">so it's you would go I think you'd get the train up to sky you get the train to Skye or is Skye an island?</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0060">Skye is an island</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0086">so you get the train up somewhere the you have to go up to Skye by boat and then from there you have to go to Harris and then from Harris</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0060">that's why you call it the Isle of Skye</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0086">and then from Harris <pause dur="short"/> that's probably why they call it the Isle of Skye <pause dur="short"/> so it's about one train journey and then I think there's a train over a bridge to and island and then there's a boat from an island to an island and then there's another boat from an island to and island</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0171">oh god</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0086">and what you were saying about you know the next generation moving away <pause dur="short"/> that's what they do <pause dur="short"/> as soon as they get old enough they all move away <pause dur="short"/> so it's that sort of generation that's are like in their forties and fifties and all they do is they just go toe the pub and get absolutely shit faced <pause dur="short"/> so it's nice to go and visit it's relay really pretty it's really nice from what I've seen <pause dur="short"/> haven't been myself bit then I don't know how sustainable it is and what's going to happen to it once that generation dies</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0086">Cos they haven't got anything there themselves they have to import everything</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0060">well it's like I was saying for me there'd be absolutely nothing for me to do work wise</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0171">no not even <unclear/></u>
<u n="1335" who="S0060">there's so  There's so  few people the building that goes on there is the very very bare minimum <pause dur="short"/> you know there's nothing happening</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0171">even the original roads that they built are still like new <pause dur="short"/> there's no pot holes there's no fading of white lines is there?</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean the roads have been there for you know year upon year upon year and it's almost as though they've only just gone down <pause dur="short"/> cos there's so few people driving on them <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's what? Twenty thousand people? Something like that</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0171">I don't know how many <pause dur="short"/> I don't know but it's sort of its small</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0060">it's certainly declined from what it used to be <pause dur="short"/> it used to be more people back in eh <pause dur="short"/> well back a hundred years there used to be quite a lot of people but it em <pause dur="short"/> I think it started declining in sort of the eighties and sort of</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0086">what made your mum live there?</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0060">getting away from her</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0171">I wouldn't be surprised by that</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0060">em no she was getting away from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad <pause dur="short"/> and although well I <pause dur="short"/> well I that's what I think she went up there for <pause dur="short"/> she tells me otherwise she tells it's because nana and granddad's accident <pause dur="short"/> em cos nan decided that she was going to em drive down to said main road that's rarely used at seventy miles an hour and then pass out</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0086">oh my god</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0171">yeah <pause dur="short"/> granddad was fully awake</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0060">sat in the car beside her</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0171">sat in the car next to her <pause dur="short"/> and eh thankfully</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0060">can you imagine <pause dur="short"/> driving on a road sixty mile and hour you <trunc>dr</trunc> you're a passage and the driver passes out on the</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0086">shit <pause dur="short"/> why did she pass out?</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0171">we don't know <pause dur="short"/> she em <pause dur="short"/> it's not a common occurrence for her but she's an old lady now she's you know got pushing on ninety I think now <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> and she'd thankfully probably would have done her more damage than anything else <pause dur="short"/> and consequently she's still like it but <pause dur="short"/> ooh excuse me <pause dur="short"/> thankfully she was driving long a particular part of the road that em has road field and then se <pause dur="short"/> em and thankfully she managed to when she did pass out em she thankfully managed to plough herself into one of the hay bales that was there in the field <pause dur="short"/> otherwise if she if that hay bail was not there she would have ended up in the sea</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I knocked it off <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thankfully rather than ending up in these they got stuck in a hay bail</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0171">granddad was absolutely bricking himself</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0086">God someone was watching down on them that day</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> but no my my nan <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> even to the day she today she wears a neck brace and her head just crumples like that</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0086">really</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0171">em but em <pause dur="short"/> and she's got a real bad ass attitude as well but <pause dur="short"/> she em my nana and granddad are of that era <pause dur="short"/> same kind of era as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum and dad in that once you're married that's it <pause dur="short"/> and em and they've been married for about fifty years now I think and he and my nan is a right old bitch <pause dur="short"/> she's really horrible</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0060">yeah unfortunately your nan where as a people get older or some of them anyway the the sort of wiring in their brain starts to decay a little bit and she's turned into</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0171">A monster</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0060">a horrible old harridan who absolutely torments your granddad</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0171">the one thing that she was doing was shortly after I moved up there and obviously shortly after they'd had this accident <pause dur="short"/> naturally my nan was talked she's not allowed to drive for obvious reasons but she did not like this <pause dur="short"/> and eh and it was down to my mum em because obviously she couldn't leave it to my granddad cos granddad is just pants for my nan <pause dur="short"/> em so she'd taken nan's car keys em and was keeping them to prevent her driving <pause dur="short"/> cracking idea <pause dur="short"/> and mum was <trunc>say</trunc> the amount of ties that my mum <pause dur="short"/> and she my mum never calls me I usually end up calling her <pause dur="short"/> and when I would call her she would be in <trunc>fl</trunc> in in tears and so really upset because my nan my nan would be slagging her off something chronic <pause dur="short"/> calling her all the names under the sun just to get her bloody car keys back</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0060">when we first went up there and eh</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0171">nan's always been civilised to us though hasn't she? She's been</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0060">yeah but even first time I'd met them and you hadn't seen them for years <pause dur="short"/> and your nan was well she wasn't red but she was very much</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0171">oh her own</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0060">couldn't couldn't care whether you were in the room or not kind of thing</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0086">God</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0060">and eh was couldn't get us out of the door fast enough relay could she?</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0171">no I mean <pause dur="short"/> another example of how nasty my nan is <pause dur="short"/> my granddad is losing sight in his eyes <pause dur="short"/> and em <pause dur="short"/> to the point where rather than kind of you know when you turn out of and old <trunc>fa</trunc> fashioned television and it does the the line and the dot in the middle <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit like that</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0060">yeah he's basically just got sort of his vision is down to like</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0171">A sliver</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0060">a little slither across his vision</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0086">ah bless</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0171">and it's getting worse and my nan treats him like a bloody dog</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0171">and a slave yeah <pause dur="short"/> make cups of tea <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I want a cup of tea please <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> where dinner <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0086">he has to make the dinner and he can't even see <pause dur="short"/> that must be dangerous <pause dur="short"/> poor granddad</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0171">yeah I mean my granddad</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0060">it's even worse cos he used to be em he used to be like a graphic designer so you know everything was with his eyes and he does well he still does but he used to be you know do a lot of photography and things like that so obviously a lot of what was his life is obviously virtually gone</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0060">so but it's very hard <pause dur="short"/> I mean up there they're very isolated anyway aren't they <pause dur="short"/> I know they've got their friends around there but you know they're two old people you know and it's not easy for them to get around at the best of times you know so <pause dur="short"/> I <unclear/> it's a very the weather up there is never very good</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0060">so I mean for me I would always you know you get you know you're isolated already cos of your age and your frailty and if it's always bad weather or it always seems like it's bad weather and you know it must get quite depressing for them I would of thought I mean when we went when we first went up there foolishly I went first in January <pause dur="short"/> and it was so cold <pause dur="short"/> I mean it there was a constant gale blowing across the way wasn't there? Always <pause dur="short"/> I mean I was  I was  in like eh like three or four layers and then like a great big coat over the top woolly hat and a scarf around like this <pause dur="short"/> and I was still cold when I was out in the wind wasn't I? And we've got photos what I don't think I've coped them they must be on the old computer <pause dur="short"/> but eh there's photos where I'm I'm out taking photos of things there's photos from like framed by the car window where Hannah's taking it of me from within the car with the engine running to keep warm <pause dur="short"/> she's like I'm not going out there</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0171">I'm not up for <unclear/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0060">we went to eh Skara Brae didn't we? And you stayed in the car cos it was too cold</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0086">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> it does seem like a crazy time of year to go <pause dur="short"/> was that your idea?</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0171">usually is my idea?</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0060">we even went <pause dur="short"/> we went back no when we went back for your mum's wedding in June?</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0060">that was alright wannit? It was quite nice <pause dur="short"/> it was a little bit windy but it was quite nice</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0171">it was better</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0060">yeah em but eh <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's not somewhere I would definitely think of as a holiday destination unless I had family there</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0060">ah but <pause dur="short"/> it's beautiful</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0086">I'm sure it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0060">but the weather I mean it is just battered off the North Sea</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0086">I'd quite like it if we could invent teleportation</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0060">to go for a visit and then</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0086">to go for a visit <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm sure it is beautiful but I wouldn't want to waste my week holiday somewhere where I wouldn't be warm <pause dur="short"/> not that I'm a sunflower anymore <pause dur="short"/> I used to be but <pause dur="short"/> just to know that it's worse weather there than it is here it</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0060">that's the thing so far you don't really know what's it like till you get there</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0086">it's like the jungle <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to go to the jungle just to have look around <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's fucking scary</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0060">back back to the normal world yeah</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0171"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1403" who="S0060">but eh but no I mean it's a really lovely place <pause dur="short"/> I mean we're very lucky we found it's a bed and well bed and breakfast for want of a better expression but really they they sort of treat you like you're part of the family you know? It's a lovely lovely place</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0086">that's nice</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0171">and they've just added a jacuzzi for sprig this year <pause dur="short"/> just in time for us to go up</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0086">yey</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0060">an outdoor jacuzzi you can't really see it working but</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0086">I suppose well they have them in Sweden don't they?</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0060">yeah that's true but they also flog themselves with birch and jump into icy pools</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0086">yeah don't do that <pause dur="short"/> that's dreadful <pause dur="short"/> have you not seen the Muppets? Swedish chef? Yeah I don't know how I'm going to last till the end of the year for a holiday <pause dur="short"/> I did it two years ago when I went to Australia and everyone was going off on a sunny holiday for the summer and was the only to be here</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0060">well we we've not really I mean we <pause dur="short"/> we did <pause dur="short"/> we went on a few holidays in the UK we went to Centre Parks and we did a few different <unclear/> and we already told you we got to have our honeymoon abroad so you got a <unclear/> So that's a good point actually we need do get some quiet sort of Scotland times so that you can get used to the idea <pause dur="short"/> I remember you saying you'd speak to the doctor about getting somewhat it's called?</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0171">valium</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0060">valium that's it</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0086">sledgehammer to the brain <pause dur="short"/> knock you out <pause dur="short"/> what you might find is it's more of the idea of it <pause dur="short"/> once you combat the idea you'll be alright <pause dur="short"/> like it is literally just telling yourself this is safer than crossing the road <pause dur="short"/> and how many times do you cross the road</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0086">do you play the lottery <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0060">you're more likely to win the lottery than die in a plane</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0060">so if you win the lottery the day before you fly <pause dur="short"/> maybe think again</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0086">yeah maybe walk passed that part <pause dur="short"/> get the car</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0060">but no</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0086">it was really funny actually my <trunc>si</trunc> my friend was saying to me the other day you've got the same chance of walking up to a stranger in the street and guessing their house number than you do of winning the lottery <pause dur="short"/> cos it's that it's the same sort of adds isn't it? Getting a a series of numbers <pause dur="short"/> you don't <pause dur="short"/> you'd have better odds of guessing someone's house number cos there are two</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0060" trans="overlap">you probably have yeah cos there are only going to be</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0086">well maybe three but you know it's not like the stakes where it's like five numbers</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0060">yeah no its <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've not done the lottery for years but I remember when I first started working we had a syndicate at work and for a year it was only the Saturday lottery then and for a solidly for a year there was I think it was like eight of us did it <pause dur="short"/> we used to pay into the syndicate and we used to have two tickets each and it was every Saturday for a year and I don't think even won a tenner</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0060">in all that time <pause dur="short"/> you know we <pause dur="short"/> it would've been better to just keep the money in our pocket type of thing</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0171">part from those bus drivers of course</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0086">did you hear there's a guy guy in the states I think it was</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0171">no no this was UK <pause dur="short"/> last</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0086">that he didn't  he didn't  tell them was it the UK? He didn't tell them that he he was the one who cashed in the syndicate <pause dur="short"/> he went and bought the ticket and they won <pause dur="short"/> and I'm sure this was in the states</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0171">no no this is a different story</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0060">no okay <pause dur="short"/> go on then you tell the story that you're going to tell</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0171">there was a bunch of bus drivers who had they had do the same thing they were buying lottery tickets together and they won the Euro Millions</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0086">how much did they win?</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0171">twenty-four million</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0086">shit <pause dur="short"/> how many bus drivers?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0171">I think there were eleven</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0086">ah nice</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0060">it's like two million each that is</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0086">ah that's better than a poke in the eye</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> so they all quite their jobs naturally <pause dur="short"/> so we have even less bus drivers <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if they were <anon type="place"/> based or if they were just Stagecoach based eh</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0060">Cos at em <pause dur="short"/> now I know that's not the same story it probably was the states cos I remember it being the states</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0171">yeah more than likely</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0060">one of the guys <pause dur="short"/> he used to go buy the ticket and all this <pause dur="short"/> and eh they won and he didn't tell them <pause dur="short"/> he told them that they didn't win <pause dur="short"/> and eh a week later <pause dur="short"/> now he went off saying he went off saying he was unwell or had an injury that he couldn't work and two weeks later then said oh he'd won it himself <pause dur="short"/> em and the next lottery</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0086">suspicious</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0060">and gave up work and everything <pause dur="short"/> but obviously they found out he's being done for fraud I think they were saying or something like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it was eh fourteen million dollars or something like that <pause dur="short"/> he was eh trying to heap it all for himself</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0086">bloody human</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0060">yeah they're terrible</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0086">fourteen million that'd be nice</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0060">yeah anything anything with that many noughts on it would be nice</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0171">Don't go by that clock by the way it's an hour late</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0086">yeah I know it is</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0171">hour early</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0060">hour early</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0171">hour hour early</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0086">hour early</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0171">I haven't got round to changing it yet</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0060">but no I mean <pause dur="short"/> what couldn't you do with a million quid</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0086">well I know <pause dur="short"/> well buy happiness that's what people say <pause dur="short"/> but I'm not convinced</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0060">ah what was the thing I saw today <pause dur="short"/> you can't buy <trunc>happ</trunc> happiness but you can buy tea</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0171">tea <pause dur="short"/> which is almost</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0060" trans="overlap">which is almost the same</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0171">that was <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0086">that was lovely</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0171">oh you're welcome</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0086">I'll just go and use your facilities</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0060">sorry the top <unclear/> actually</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0171">ooh feel like a stuffed pig</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0060">it's probably the only one with a door actually <pause dur="short"/> come here you</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0060">why? Come here</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0171">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm now going to relax and enjoy my wine</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0060">well relax here</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0171">no <pause dur="short"/> I want to relax please</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0060">is that that Pinot? Nice?</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0171">do you want to try it?</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0060">it tastes garlicky and pesto-y for a start <pause dur="short"/> because you've been drinking <unclear/></u>
<u n="1483" who="S0171">Don't mind <pause dur="short"/> I hate when the clocks go forward</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0060">why?</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0171">oh just I feel <unclear/></u>
<u n="1486" who="S0060">that's <unclear/> forward <pause dur="short"/> so six o'clock becomes seven o'clock</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0171">so we lose hours <pause dur="short"/> actually we lost an hours sleep last night</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0060" trans="overlap">last night</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0171">well surely that will mean that we won't actually get tired until eleven o'clock rather than ten <pause dur="short"/> there <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1490" who="S0060">I think so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> Oh dear <pause dur="short"/> I'm tired <pause dur="short"/> if I'd <unclear/> Earlier then you'd give name your hand wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0171">ow</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0060">big chunk of flesh</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0171">if you're just going to hurt me darling you're not getting nothing out of me</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0060">you're trouble you are</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0171">someone's got to be</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0060">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> too old for this</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0171">too old for what?</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0060">life</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0171">life? Crikey?</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0060">do you know what I got to thirty and realised that my body was staying to break down</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0086">oh dear don't tell me that</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0060">pretty much literally thirty and then I started to have aches and pains and groaning when I get up and sat down my knees are packing up my memory is going</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0060">pretty much literally I was literally thirty and then that was it</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0086">oh dear</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0060">they do  They do say  They do say that after twenty-five your brain <trunc>ste</trunc> you've got less brain cells alive each year than you did the year before after twenty-five that's what they say</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0086">what do they say sort about brain cells?</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0060">that after twenty-five you have less brain cells alive each year <pause dur="short"/> so after twenty-five have more</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0086">sop basically just get in the box now and kill yourself</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0060">that's it <pause dur="short"/> up to twenty-five you aver more each year and after twenty-five you have it's decreasing</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0171">you start losing them</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0086">that's really sad because by today's standards twenty-five is really young</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0060">well that's what they're saying is that the whole thing off now everyone's living longer but the longer you live the worse your standard of living will be <pause dur="short"/> you know it's eh <pause dur="short"/> now that pensions have been shown to be the fraud that they are</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0171">mm</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0060">you know what will you do?</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0086">the new pensions yeah <pause dur="short"/> work until we die until we they literally cart you out in a wheel barrow</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0171">send you out to the <trunc>knack</trunc> knacker's yard <pause dur="short"/> that's what they do with horses isn't it? Back in the day</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0086">glue factory</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0060">we we all were definitely born a couple of generations too early <pause dur="short"/> two two three generations ago we'd had it made <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> cos it was all boom everything as good and rosy <pause dur="short"/> they got all their pensions now all secured <pause dur="short"/> final salary <pause dur="short"/> you know all of them in the easy life</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0086">well they had the war <pause dur="short"/> and they had bad health care <pause dur="short"/> it's like in Life of Brian what did the Roman's ever do for us? Clean water the roads <pause dur="short"/> education</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0060">education <pause dur="short"/> bridges aqueducts clean water sewerage under floor heating</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0086">under floor heating <pause dur="short"/> all very important</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0171">making sure I've got no garlic in my teeth</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0060">no you don't have any garlic <pause dur="short"/> plenty of pesto though</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0171"><unclear/> pesto <pause dur="short"/> I am stuffed</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0060">yeah you look it</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0171">there a bit of a belly going on there</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0060">Cos you haven't got on that bike</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0171">neither have you</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0060">well we got it for you <pause dur="short"/> it was your birthday present</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0171">no we got it for us</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0060">ah no that's what it's now been because you were using it</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0171">no excuse me  excuse me  it's been ours since we bought <pause dur="short"/> since the idea</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0060" trans="overlap">it was it was it was  it was yours and I was going to borrow it</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0171">no it wasn't</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0060">and I have been on it more than you have</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0171">no you fucking haven't <pause dur="short"/> you lying little shit</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0060">I have been</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0171">you have not</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0060">I have been</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0171">you have not</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0060">how did you last go on it? Who was last to go on it?</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0171">yeah you were the last one it <pause dur="short"/> that doesn't make you the one that's been on it most</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0086">is this an exercise bike?</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0060">how many miles have you done?</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0171">Miles I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you can't</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0060">you see I've kept a low <pause dur="short"/> I've done more</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0171">it doesn't do miles it does kilometres</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0060">it depends what you set it on</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0171">no there was no option for miles</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0060">yes there is</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0171">no there isn't</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0060">this shows how little you've been on it that you haven't seen that there's not <pause dur="short"/> ow</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0171">I've been on it lots more than you and I'd rather that you didn't wind me up</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0060">alright <pause dur="short"/> trouble</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0171">see what I've got to put up with?</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0086"><unclear/> lock you bike outside?</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0171">yeah I would do if my bike wasn't covered in massive spiders</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0060">that's cos you don't use it often enough</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0086">why are there spiders living on your bike?</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0171">Cos it's in the garage</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0060" trans="overlap">Cos it's been say in the garage for so long and not being used</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0086">spider spider house</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0171">mm <pause dur="short"/> no that's where the spiders belong <pause dur="short"/> ew</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0086">spider babies <pause dur="short"/> in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1568" who="S0060">hoards of them <pause dur="short"/> like arms <unclear/></u>
<u n="1569" who="S0171">exactly <pause dur="short"/> like even when it was at  even when it was at  Regency it would be locked</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0060">there's so many that it's actually a spider powered bike</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0171">I'm not surprised</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0060">the pedals go round on their own</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0171">no but we use to have it locked up form a chain that was dangling down from the ceiling of our car port <pause dur="short"/> and it would be tied up locked up there <pause dur="short"/> and every single time I got on it I would check underneath the saddle to make sure there wasn't anything living in it <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing quite like cycling along with your bum hanging out for a spider to just go plup</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0060">this image of a spider crawling climbing into your crotch <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1575" who="S0171">it can happen</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0060">why? Why would a spider do that? When have you ever read one the news about this accident caused by a spider</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0171" trans="overlap">what? Look you think  you think you think  there's kind of like prejudice against what's a butt crack and what's a crack in the floor?</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0060">very much so</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0171">no <pause dur="short"/> anyway spiders are actually attracted to heat dispute what you say</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0060">alright alright</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0171">that's why they eat you when you're asleep</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0060">eat you <pause dur="short"/> you eat them</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0171">Don't give a shit <pause dur="short"/> that's why I have nightmares <pause dur="short"/> I have bad dreams about them <pause dur="short"/> and I have bad dreams about wasps <pause dur="short"/> weird cos I don't  I don't  I never remember it but apparently I'll know about it in the morning cos he'll sort of say to me <pause dur="short"/> actually you asked me that this morning and I didn't ask did I? He he usually says to me <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1584" who="S0060">you had a bad dream last night <pause dur="short"/> cos she'll literally just sit up in bed and just scream <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> literally</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0086">quite <unclear/> for you like</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0060">when it was when she first did it I was like shit what's going on? But now I'm so used to it that literally</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0171">just sits up grabs me</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0060">I'll sit up <pause dur="short"/> go like that and just lay back down and within a couple of minutes she's calmed down and falls back <pause dur="short"/> yeah she doesn't really wake up you know <pause dur="short"/> she's not awake awake <pause dur="short"/> and literally I'll lay lay back down with holding her like this it's fine  it's fine it's fine  Like you</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0171">did I have a bad dream last night then?</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0060">no</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0171">oh</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0060">I can remember you waking up one night screaming <pause dur="short"/> I go what's wrong what's wrong and you said oh em there's a spider there's a spider <pause dur="short"/> I said where? She said oh I saw it I saw it <pause dur="short"/> it's pitch black how can you see it <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0171">apparently that's exactly what I did</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0060">literally straight back to sleep when she was like oh yeah there can't have been one <pause dur="short"/> asleep</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0086">do you remember it? Do you think you were fully awake for it?</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0171">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember any of them <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember any of them <pause dur="short"/> sometimes if you're sometimes you'll remind me and it's the dream itself that I remember not the screaming and waking up but that I remember <pause dur="short"/> I remember that <pause dur="short"/> I usually just remember the nightmare</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0060">Cos sometimes you you burst out laughing in your sleep or your you'll say a word <pause dur="short"/> there' been times where I've kind of been <pause dur="short"/> I've sort of woken up and gone are we talking or were we having a conversation I've fallen asleep or something? You know I you know it's weird <pause dur="short"/> but eh</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0086">Don't think I've ever said anything apparently I make a noise I make a noise like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1599" who="S0171">that's what he does</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0086">which means I'm probably thinking about food</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0060">food yeah</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0171">yeah you do that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1603" who="S0060">I think it's cos I end up with a dry mouth</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0171">and it's really annoying <pause dur="short"/> cos I get really quite <trunc>pu</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but most of the time if I'm already asleep I'll sleep through it and I never hear it <pause dur="short"/> but if I'm like I've been sick I've not been very well <pause dur="short"/> so it's taken me an awful long time to go to sleep in the first place and the second he starts making that noise it's like I'm shot I'm never going to go to fluking sleep with him making that stupid noise <pause dur="short"/> and eh and other times I mean recently I've actually woken up in the middle of the night with you making that noise <pause dur="short"/> and usually I don't wake up when you make that noise</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0060">normally yes</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0171">usually I I beat him</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0060">wake up</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0171">or it's roll over or shut up</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0060">you're you're the worst in the morning <pause dur="short"/> if you've left your alarm on on like a Saturday or a Sunday your alarm will make me up it won't wake you up and I'll be left there going turn it off turn it off <pause dur="short"/> and then I'll roll over you and like knee to the back <pause dur="short"/> you're awake now oh the alarm's going off</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0171">no cos most of the time it doesn't even work <pause dur="short"/> the amount of times that he's been prodding me for quite some time he's like</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0060">she's so annoying</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0171">switch it up</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0060">if I've stayed up and she's already gone to bed and she'll be asleep when I come up she more often than not will wake up when I come in the room to go to bed <pause dur="short"/> but if I'm trying to get her awake in the morning she just sort of</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0086">you must be a deep sleeper</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0171">yeah I think I do yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean but at the moment I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> I've got a new phone it's a different tone it's different alarm <pause dur="short"/> I've got two different alarms on it</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0060">you've got two but one of them <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember which one it is but more often than not of late you've not it's not woken you up you've just carried on laying there and I'm going turn it off turn it off <pause dur="short"/> I'm going bad turn it off</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0171">that's probably the first alarm <pause dur="short"/> that'll be the first alarm <pause dur="short"/> cos there's on that goes off at six forty and then there's another one that goes off at six fifty <pause dur="short"/> and I think it's the six fifty that <pause dur="short"/> await for</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0060">no I have <pause dur="short"/> I must admit if I'm honest I can pretty much sleep anywhere any time on anything</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0171" trans="overlap">do anything</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0086">so are you already up by then? I thought you left really early</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0060">at the minute no I've I've been doing much more eh</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0171">reasonable hours</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0060">yeah reasonable hours of late <pause dur="short"/> apart from the odd time when I'm having to get out the door at sort of five in the morning or something but</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0086">God</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0060">if I was doing normal work that I do I probably have to leave about six I suppose <pause dur="short"/> but at the minute I'm usually sort of seven to half past seven <pause dur="short"/> get to work eight just after eight something like that <pause dur="short"/> but eh yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos where I'm doing em <pause dur="short"/> you know like development jobs so it's all offices and meetings and visits and things so it's a lot more flexible hours so you know I'll probably only do right till three or something like that and bigger off you know rather than seven till seven</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0086">yes yeah you've definitely done your time <pause dur="short"/> it's not like you're skiving <pause dur="short"/> I've realised I've let I have to get you to sign your soul to me</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0171">ah wicked</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0060" trans="overlap">ah to say that we consent</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0086">yeah that you consent but I think I've left them in Olive</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0060">we consent to having our voices recorded</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0171" trans="overlap">recorded</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0086">I'm not really a spy <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0060">we agree to the twelve pound per minute fee</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0086">you agree <pause dur="short"/> it's basically just you signing your soul to me <pause dur="short"/> that's all we're doing</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0171">devil Wears Prada and all that</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0086">what?</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0171">devil Wears Prada and all that</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I can't get out</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0171">oh pull the lever up <pause dur="short"/> pull the latch up <pause dur="short"/> pull the door</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0086">I don't have arm strength</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0060">no don't <pause dur="short"/> stop stop stop</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0171">anyone would think you'd been out of the door <pause dur="short"/> did I put it on the latch</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0171">oh</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0060">so no <trunc>ma</trunc> moaning about how hard you pressed it <pause dur="short"/> you're never going to get out</u>
<u n="1647" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1648" who="S0171">it's never going to work <pause dur="short"/> if you don't mind darling I might actually pop this door open for a minute <pause dur="short"/> are you warm?</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0060">I am a little bit warm yeah</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0171">oh I thought you might be</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1651" who="S0086">oh no no it's fine thank you <pause dur="short"/> sign me your soul <pause dur="short"/> you soul <pause dur="short"/> just very kindly fill in oh no hang on that's not right <pause dur="short"/> actually I wonder if I've even got any left <pause dur="short"/> we might have to use your new scanner</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0060">if it will work</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0086">that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> ooh no <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> hang on what have we got here? That's a blank one <pause dur="short"/> oh no I've only got one left <pause dur="short"/> maybe you and Hannah can sign the same one cos you're you know practically married</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0060">Cohabiting</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0086">Cohabiting exactly <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> maybe I've got another one here</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0060">does your new printer thing copy?</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0060">it does</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0060">so there we are we can copy it</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0086">em I don't want to do you out of paper though</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0060">we've got paper</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0086">I don't want  I don't want  to use up all your paper</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0060">paper is paper <pause dur="short"/> how many pages is it?</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0086">eh two pages</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0060">oh there you go that's not going to work is it? My goodness it's the end of the world</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0086">times are hard <pause dur="short"/> times are hard <pause dur="short"/> it's nice and warm in here</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0060">it certainly is we were just saying that but trouble we have is that it will em either be hot or cold</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0086">ah not a happy medium</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0060">yeah</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0171">it's getting a bit chilly out there isn't it?</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0086">but it's quite warm in here which is nice</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0171">yeah I leave the door open cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> moans when it gets too hot</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0171">I'll shut it <pause dur="short"/> I don't like the cold</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0086">well he's going to have to eat <trunc>i</trunc>his words You did need a printer</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0171">and I bought it just in time as well</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0086">it's a bargain <pause dur="short"/> absolutely So that was this week was it</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0171">eh it was Friday yeah</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0060"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1681" who="S0086">oh you've got it all set up have you? All plugged in</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0171">yeah it's all  it's all  going it's all good</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0086">what's that little decorative thing <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty <pause dur="short"/> leaves leaves</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0171">yeah it was plant <pause dur="short"/> it's deal now</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0060">it's a dead plant</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0086">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah this a</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0060">Hannah Hannah is brilliant</u>
<u n="1688" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1689" who="S0086">A likely event</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0060">Hannah is brilliant at getting past the <pause dur="short"/> and then come home</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0171">look after them for about a week</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0060"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1693" who="S0086">is it the table of death <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0060">it is pretty much the table of death</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0171">these weren't old by the way</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0060">there was  There was  a eh like a plant growers little green house that you grow our seeds in</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0171">oh yeah them</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0060">right up until it became too much hassle to bother with then it just sat there and slowly everything died</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0171">what are we signing <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> or?</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0086">just both both <unclear/></u>
<u n="1702" who="S0171">I like <unclear/> I like form filling forms <pause dur="short"/> eh can you grab me a pen please sweetheart</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0086">oh aren't you good <pause dur="short"/> you're helping people learn</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0171">right <pause dur="short"/> not that blue crappy one</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0060">yeah that's why I'm giving you the good one</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0171">it's a crappy one this <pause dur="short"/> what your black one what happened to your black?</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0060">you've got it somewhere</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0171">I've got it have I?</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0060">yes</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0086">in the very same place</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0171">please write the month in words <pause dur="short"/> why? Where are we? Twenty-fifth</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0060">twenty-fifth of March</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0086">do you see much of Stuart? I haven't spoken to him for ages</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0171">year no I see him all the time at work <pause dur="short"/> he's still working there</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0086">is it in the same building though?</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0171">yeah yeah he is <pause dur="short"/> he's to working for OCR though I think he's working for ESOL or CIE</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> he's got a proper job now hasn't he?</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0060">proper job</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0171">proper job</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0086">as I he's not a temp anymore</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0171">no</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0086">he was going to become a marine so I'm not sure what happened about that plan</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0171">no me neither</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0086">saw him at Christmas and that was the plan <pause dur="short"/> when I transferred all my numbers onto my new phone it swapped all of the names and all of the numbers</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0171">oh god</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0086">so I thought I was texting my house mate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to tell her off for breaking my frying pan</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0171">yeah</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0086">turns out I was texting <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he was like I didn't break your frying pan shut up</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0171">I'm sorry <pause dur="short"/> what's mother tongue?</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0086">you native speaker</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0060">native language <pause dur="short"/> english</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0086" trans="overlap">like native language yeah</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0060">or in your case Swahili</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0086">Swindonesque</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0171">swindonian</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0060">I don't have an accent or dialect <pause dur="short"/> I speak the queens English</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0086">queen's English Estuary</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0171">which country has my <pause dur="short"/> the UK</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0060">what what's my accent darling? Do I have an accent?</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0171">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're asking the wrong person <pause dur="short"/> I'm no good with geography</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0060">it's not geography</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0086">I think you could put southern</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0060">southern?</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0086">which encompasses quite a few em areas</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0060">I'll put accent English <pause dur="short"/> no that doesn't really apply does it</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0171">do I still have do I still sound Swindonian?</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0086" trans="overlap">I mean <pause dur="short"/> you can put the county <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0060">yes very much so</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0171">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> do I put Swindonian or do I just put Swindon</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0086">eh just put Swindon if you like</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0060">I am I do disconcertingly have a a lot of the people I associate with through work do tell me how I how posh I speak <pause dur="short"/> and given that I know I don't speak poshly it is worrying that that these people</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0086">where the hell do they come from then?</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0060">exactly</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0086">wow</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0060">how many years months have you lived there?</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0086">I've lived in <anon type="place"/> six</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0171">that's not five year here in <unclear/> four and a half <pause dur="short"/> well four <pause dur="short"/> you four <pause dur="short"/> oh no that must be five years <pause dur="short"/> no that can't be right <pause dur="short"/> two thousand and nine twenty ten twenty eleven <pause dur="short"/> yeah nine ten elven twelve yeah four <pause dur="short"/> four? Yeah four years</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0086">three <pause dur="short"/> since two thousand and nine would be three wouldn't it</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0171">no it was two thousand and eight <pause dur="short"/> it was two thousand and nine <pause dur="short"/> twenty ten</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0086">we met in two thousand and eight</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0171">yeah cos that was the first year I was here <pause dur="short"/> so two thousand and nine twenty ten twenty eleven twenty twelve it's four <pause dur="short"/> four bang on four years <pause dur="short"/> cos I moved here in April two thousand and eight</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0086">we worked that summer</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0171">yeah we did <pause dur="short"/> so many moons ago</u>
<event desc="phone rings"/>
<u n="1765" who="S0171">that'll probably be your mother</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0060">hello <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> we're alive we're alive <pause dur="short"/> no I'm fine <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah go on <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0086">where are the fish</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0171">dead</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You don't have much much luck do you with living things</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0171">no <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately in big mamma went absolutely devastated when she went but big mamma went about four months ago three months ago</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0086">you had her a long time though didn't you?</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0171">yeah she was she'd been there a long time <pause dur="short"/> and eh big mamma</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0086">were there any others</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0171">there were <pause dur="short"/> most of them were just little fish and some cleaners <pause dur="short"/> but no big mamma was my baby <pause dur="short"/> and I was absolutely devastated when she went absolutely couldn't stop sobbing</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0086">really? Were you attached to her</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0171">I was yeah <pause dur="short"/> I really did  I really did  miss her when she went <pause dur="short"/> and then I didn't know what to do with her <pause dur="short"/> cos em <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was obviously cuddling me and saying you know it's alright and she was always going to die eventually and all this kind of thing and eh then we I couldn't  I couldn't  decide whether I wanted to bury her which is quite sad or do the traditional with a fish and flush her <pause dur="short"/> and I couldn't I do I couldn't bear to flush her <pause dur="short"/> and I also couldn't bear to stick her in the garden either for fear of the cats getting her</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0086">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0171">and eh and I thought oh we'll have to flush her <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had gotten her out and eh put her on a  on a  bit of kitchen roll <pause dur="short"/> and I looked at her and said oh <pause dur="short"/> I was set off again <pause dur="short"/> and then yeah we flushed her in the end but</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0060">keep her yeah</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0171">I was so upset</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0086">how big was she?</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0171">she wasn't that big actually? She didn't end up being all that big I mean she was when she  when she  did go she was about that long nose to tail <pause dur="short"/> so she never really <pause dur="short"/> I don't think she ever got as big as she would have done <pause dur="short"/> because they were supposed to get quite big but but she never grew anyway really <pause dur="short"/> she didn't <unclear/> much anyway <pause dur="short"/> but we had her for a goof couple of years</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0086">did something happen or was it just her age</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0171">no <pause dur="short"/> I think she <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I never know knew how long she was supposed to live for <pause dur="short"/> but em it could have been anything but</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0086">so are you going to get another one?</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0171">I do want one yeah</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0086">is that why you're keeping the tank going</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0171">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we need to fill it up now which is why you can hear it</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0086">oh really?</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0171">but em but no it's not <pause dur="short"/> that's his mum <pause dur="short"/> she's em she had a burst eh blood clot in her eye</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0086">in her eye? Shit</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0171">yeah last week and eh and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying that she was naughty and that she'd eh left it a day</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0171">em before going to the doctors to the hospital and eh that eh they were inject the last time I</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
</body>
</text>
