<text id="S8Q3">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:17:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-06-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0416 S0417 S0418</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home Cork</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Religion, nuns, the matrix, scientology, friends.</topics>
		<activity>Discussion about religion around dinner table.</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, inquiring, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0416">
				<exactage>12</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bristol, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0417">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>not currently working, caring for toddler</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>some French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0418">
				<exactage>2</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Cork, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig></lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English/Irish (only just talking)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>toddler</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0417">okay so what do you think about <pause dur="short"/> religion?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0416">I think it's utter nonsense</u>
<u n="3" who="S0417">what? all religion? everything about it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0416">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0417">everything even though <pause dur="short"/> there's like huge aid going to poor countries that kind of thing through Christian organisations or</u>
<u n="6" who="S0416" trans="overlap">well I think I think most religions have a good cause but I think</u>
<u n="7" who="S0417" trans="overlap">there's Muslim organisations</u>
<u n="8" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0416">most religions have a good cause and I think that's probably why they were invented probably just for a good cause I I can see why I can see how it's good</u>
<u n="10" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0416">erm but</u>
<u n="12" who="S0417"><unclear>stop</unclear></u>
<u n="13" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I'm not doing anything</u>
<u n="14" who="S0417">okay</u>
<u n="15" who="S0416">erm but I think some people do go quite far and I think that is really kind of sad that people like nuns they like completely devote their whole life they don't see their family <unclear>or they're</unclear> not allowed to have kids anything like that and they just devote their life to god which might not even exist</u>
<u n="16" who="S0417">no but they choose to and who are you to say that that's not a good choice for them?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0416">eh <pause dur="short"/> it's just <pause dur="short"/> I don't think all nuns might might not they might not even like it they might just do it just because they could have a good spot in heaven or something like that and so they might</u>
<u n="18" who="S0417" trans="overlap">my <trunc>gre</trunc> my great aunt was a mother superior do you know what a mother superior is?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0416">erm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0417">she's like head of the nuns the church nuns</u>
<u n="21" who="S0416">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0417">she seemed to enjoy it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0416">yeah well I just don't believe it <pause dur="short"/> I just don't believe in it at all</u>
<u n="24" who="S0417">it isn't the same as saying erm well <pause dur="short"/> other people are saying well you should be religious cos you know? how can you be happy not having any spiritual fulfilment? isn't what you're saying the same as that? in a way you're saying you know what's best for other people?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0416">I don't know what's best for other people</u>
<u n="26" who="S0417">yeah but you're saying that nuns have a hard time</u>
<u n="27" who="S0416">ah no I'm just saying I don't think all nuns I think all the if they really really but I don't think all nuns do it because they like waking up every morning obeying to these very strict rules they kind of they might do it to not <unclear/> but some of them might do it just to get in heaven and be good in heaven and have a good spot in heaven so they might devote their whole life to something devote their life to aestheticism which means devoting your life to having a life of hardship and devoting yourself to god and erm <pause dur="short"/> to maybe maybe if heaven doesn't exist then <pause dur="short"/> it's not really a good life spent</u>
<u n="28" who="S0417">but none of us will ever know that will we?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0416">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0418"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0416">I don't know I think we'll I think we'll be able to know if it's true or not soon</u>
<u n="32" who="S0418"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0416">cos we'll be able to bring people back to life in the next hundred years maybe</u>
<u n="34" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0416">I I think we will</u>
<u n="36" who="S0417">back to life?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0416">like if it's if it's of a natural like heart stop working</u>
<u n="38" who="S0417" trans="overlap">okay I would imagine <unclear/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0417">hey hey I'd imagine they'd have no memory so we'd still wouldn't know whether there is there is a heaven or not</u>
<u n="41" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0416">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0417">yummy</u>
<u n="44" who="S0418">dog <unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0417">bye look bye</u>
<u n="47" who="S0416">it's just I don't think there's</u>
<u n="48" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0417">six</u>
<u n="50" who="S0418">six</u>
<u n="51" who="S0416">I think a lot of people just say there just is a heaven there just is with no evidence behind it</u>
<u n="52" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0416">there just is a heaven</u>
<u n="54" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0416">I understand why people believe in heaven</u>
<u n="56" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0417">uh oh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0416" trans="overlap">because death is scary <unclear>but like</unclear></u>
<u n="59" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0416">I'm not going to try and make people not believe in heaven because I don't want them to be sad about death or anything</u>
<u n="62" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0416">but in my opinion I don't think it's true and I'm not going to I can't really think that it is true because</u>
<u n="64" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0416">I don't think it's true</u>
<u n="66" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0416">I don't see any evidence in the whole world which can tell me any of it's true</u>
<u n="68" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0416">I think there probably might have been a man called Jesus or I don't know what his name was Jesus or whatever erm he was just like talking the word of god but I don't think he came back to life I don't think he survived forty days without food or water cos I'm pretty sure that's impossible that's more than a month so you'd literally die</u>
<u n="70" who="S0417">maybe he was being he was <unclear>feeding</unclear> on the <vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear>word</unclear> of god</u>
<u n="71" who="S0416">but the word of god would have to be made out of lush lush water <unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I don't know <unclear/> whether you feel that you you don't believe but that you you're not you don't you're not sure so you don't believe but you're not saying that there is or isn't a god or it's fairly definitely isn't anything</u>
<u n="73" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I'm not saying there is or isn't a god I'm thinking it's very <unclear>ah</unclear> I don't know very impossible but it's possible that erm our universe <unclear>solar system</unclear> or whatever could actually just be a little project that people even bigger than us are working on I don't know</u>
<u n="74" who="S0417">so you'd you wouldn't believe in heaven but you might believe there's some mad people up there using us as a project?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0416">erm I think</u>
<u n="77" who="S0417">that doesn't make sense to me</u>
<u n="78" who="S0416">in two billion years from now we could probably have the technology to create a solar system I'm saying that so if <pause dur="short"/> if it started off with just a rock and one guy or like one thing probably doesn't look like a human cos that would be very rare that we'd look the exact same</u>
<u n="79" who="S0417">mm mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0416">but and then and that first person would have survived two billion years before us and then they another like six trillion or whatever then we might have found out how to make a solar system <unclear/> therefore making us but I don't know what made them</u>
<u n="81" who="S0417">yeah but you're talking about <pause dur="short"/> you're talking in the same way that somebody might talk about god</u>
<u n="82" who="S0416">yeah but I just think a lot of people see god as like I think if there was a god</u>
<u n="83" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0417">hey stop doing that that's too loud</u>
<u n="85" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0416">sorry</u>
<u n="87" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0416">sorry</u>
<u n="89" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0416">say sorry</u>
<u n="91" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0417"><trunc>wan</trunc> you want some more?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0416">sorry</u>
<u n="95" who="S0417" trans="overlap">spaghetti</u>
<u n="96" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0417">there you go</u>
<u n="98" who="S0418">wow</u>
<u n="99" who="S0417">wow</u>
<u n="100" who="S0416">erm I think if there was a god I think there'd be no use praying to god because if there was a god I doubt it would be erm <pause dur="short"/> something that could actually think and <unclear/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0418" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="102" who="S0417">no no but do you see what I'm saying? if you're saying yeah I don't <unclear/> all these people believe god I just erm they're just deluded there isn't a heaven or isn't a and you say but maybe there's people were born <unclear>a billion years beforehand</unclear> just that that's just as impossible to prove as god so you're saying the same thing but in a different way can you stop clicking that pen? it's very annoying</u>
<u n="103" who="S0416" trans="overlap">sorry <pause dur="short"/> I'm not saying the same thing there's people that say god well like Christianity and all that stuff that's basically that is saying god is a real is definitely a real</u>
<u n="104" who="S0417">no I'm saying that your</u>
<u n="105" who="S0416">no no no please let me finish that god is a thing that people can talk to and pray to by putting their hands together and somehow talking to him wherever he is and and he answers their prayers even though there's about seven billion people on the planet probably about two of those probably at least one billion are praying at that time I don't know not one billion praying at that very time but a lot so yes I don't think he is listen to all of those at the same time if he was real <pause dur="short"/> and like</u>
<u n="106" who="S0418"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0416">it's it's always a god of</u>
<u n="108" who="S0418"><unclear>edge</unclear></u>
<u n="109" who="S0416">I don't think he'd be I don't think he or she or it would</u>
<u n="110" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0416">be smart like like us humans it just would've created I don't think it would have <unclear/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0416">or I don't think it would think I just think it would be existence like the universe it just existed <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't think you can bring people back to life or actually think or anything like going oh if he talks to me he's talking the English language that I know or whatever language you're talking in I just know this language and I'm going to grant this wish and bring back to life ta-dah <pause dur="short"/> I think if there was a god it would just exist <pause dur="long"/> death</u>
<u n="114" who="S0417">so is that what you believe?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0416">it's not what I believe</u>
<u n="116" who="S0417">so what do you believe?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0416">I believe I don't know what to believe</u>
<u n="118" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0418"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> <vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I don't believe in</u>
<u n="121" who="S0417">achoo</u>
<u n="122" who="S0416">I don't believe in religion anyway</u>
<u n="123" who="S0418" trans="overlap">oh oh</u>
<u n="124" who="S0417">oh look</u>
<u n="125" who="S0416">in a way I believe</u>
<u n="126" who="S0418">ah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0417">ah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0416">in a way I in a way I believe in my own religion that there was that there was just something that just existed and then just our universe was created under different circumstances we could create life and then we were created or dinosaurs and all that and then we were eventually created <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0417">but from what?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0416">I don't know I never said any</u>
<u n="131" who="S0417">but what what happened before before the universe then what was? what created the universe?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't think anyone knows for sure <pause dur="short"/> no one knows for sure</u>
<u n="133" who="S0417">I can understand a bit more of that thinking where you're you're thinking maybe more scientifically if there isn't evidence then you're not</u>
<u n="134" who="S0416">but I don't believe in Scientology cos Scientology is crazy</u>
<u n="135" who="S0417" trans="overlap">science is nothing to do with Scientology it's just their names are similar</u>
<u n="136" who="S0416" trans="overlap">you know Scientology believes that there was an alien mothership called Glorgon that like had a whole thing created the Earth and all that stuff</u>
<u n="137" who="S0417">they they called themselves Scientologists to try and give themselves a kind of credence</u>
<u n="138" who="S0416" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0417">but erm but yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0416" trans="overlap">you should look up <unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0417">ah better <unclear>clean you</unclear></u>
<u n="143" who="S0416">I believe in science though</u>
<u n="144" who="S0417">yeah I mean that's kind of what I believe as well</u>
<u n="145" who="S0416">cos I I <unclear/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0417">just to <unclear/> going off on a bit of a tangent maybe being part of some kind of</u>
<u n="147" who="S0418" trans="overlap">ten</u>
<u n="148" who="S0417">yeah ten very good</u>
<u n="149" who="S0416">it's no that was just me saying that it could be possible that we're just a creation of something else that has been created by something or whatever but</u>
<u n="150" who="S0417">yeah but you could you we could all have a theory and that all are untested and nobody would know and</u>
<u n="151" who="S0416">exactly I'm not saying it's true I'm saying that's what that's why I don't believe it because I was saying it's possible but I don't believe in it</u>
<u n="152" who="S0417">aha</u>
<u n="153" who="S0416">which is what I'm saying which I guess you could say is the same thing as just saying I don't believe in religion</u>
<u n="154" who="S0417">no it's not the same thing</u>
<u n="155" who="S0416"><unclear>well I find that</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0417">well I mean it doesn't mean that all religion is bad though is it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0416">I never said that <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0417">I'm alright you don't have to get defensive all I'm asking is <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what do you know about different religions do you think? do you know anything about Islam?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0416">not really I know a bit it's a bit crazy Islam as well</u>
<u n="160" who="S0418"><unclear/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0416">apparently their god</u>
<u n="162" who="S0418">yum</u>
<u n="163" who="S0416">their god Allah the one and only god</u>
<u n="164" who="S0418" trans="overlap">yum yum <unclear/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0416">Allah the one and only god which can't be depicted told erm told Muhammed to go er go and kill his child on top of a mountain</u>
<u n="167" who="S0417">yeah well so did Christianity</u>
<u n="168" who="S0416">mm?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0417">it's the same thing Muhammed <unclear/> the same</u>
<u n="170" who="S0416">yeah I know I'm not saying I'm not saying Christianity is any less weird than Islam</u>
<u n="171" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0416">I'm just saying they're all weird in my eyes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0417">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm just saying do you know much about it anyway whether you believe in it or not?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0416">mm mm not really</u>
<u n="175" who="S0417">no?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0416">no <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0417">do you have any friends? like is anybody at school a Muslim?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0417">who's who's a Muslim at your school?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0416">ah forget his name but I can't remember his name actually <pause dur="short"/> but yeah eh his name will come back to me</u>
<u n="181" who="S0417">yeah but is he in your year? or your class?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0416">yeah he's in my class</u>
<u n="183" who="S0417">okay does he have many friends there?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0416">kind of</u>
<u n="185" who="S0417">do you think it's hard for him? being the only Muslim boy?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0416">I don't know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0417">where's he from?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0416">erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't really know much about him kind of quiet</u>
<u n="189" who="S0417">yeah?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0416">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0417">you could talk to him one day if nobody else talks to him</u>
<u n="192" who="S0416" trans="overlap">I have talked to him</u>
<u n="193" who="S0417">yeah? does he talk back?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0416">kind of yeah just because he's mum I think you think this is erm if he's quiet and he doesn't talk very much you think he's instantly a great friend</u>
<u n="195" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you <trunc>di</trunc> you don't half <trunc>ar</trunc> argue quite a lot about me <unclear/> asking you</u>
<u n="196" who="S0416">sorry it's just cos</u>
<u n="197" who="S0417">you just don't know <trunc>someti</trunc> people who are shy you don't know what they're like until you've made a bit more effort <unclear/> yeah?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0416">I do make an effort with everyone</u>
<u n="199" who="S0417">yeah well fair enough okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm only asking</u>
<u n="200" who="S0416">it's just you've got to be kind of open to other people as well <pause dur="short"/> that's what I think</u>
<u n="201" who="S0417">so there are there any other people in your school with other religions?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0416">I guess so</u>
<u n="203" who="S0417">do you I mean do you know of any?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0416">not really</u>
<u n="205" who="S0417">any Buddhists or anything else at all?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0416">no not really <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0417">do you know anything about the Jehovah's Witnesses or?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0416">no</u>
<u n="209" who="S0417">do you get taught about other religions at your school or is it all about Christianity?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0416">no we get taught about other things</u>
<u n="211" who="S0417">well what? what kind of things do you get taught then?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0416">eh Islam Buddhism Hinduism Christianity</u>
<u n="213" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0416">all that stuff</u>
<u n="215" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0416">I'm not very good at religion</u>
<u n="217" who="S0417">mind you it's kind of it's interesting <unclear/>then you can understand other people you know where they're coming from and that's kind of quite an important thing <pause dur="short"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0416">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0418" trans="overlap"><unclear/> one <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
