<text id="S8Q6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0679 S0680</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s living room, Leeds </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>What to have for supper and other meals, Using passenger assistance on the railway, catching train at Leeds station, Using text messaging, Experiences of receiving text notifications</topics>
		<activity>Taking it easy after lunch</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0679">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kent, Margate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired (University manager)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0680">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Margate, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Mostly Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, West Yorks.</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>42 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- School</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0679">so what have we got planned for supper? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0680">well there's filled pasta spinach and ricotta</u>
<u n="3" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0680">with some variety of sauce</u>
<u n="5" who="S0679">what what do you think you've got?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0680">erm tomato and basil</u>
<u n="7" who="S0679">mm mm that's a good standby</u>
<u n="8" who="S0680">sweet tomato erm tomato and sweet pepper <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0679" trans="overlap">that's probably my overall favourite</u>
<u n="10" who="S0680">I don't think I've got a vegetable one</u>
<u n="11" who="S0679">oh I don't think I have that one is that the one we have in the summer?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0680">possibly</u>
<u n="13" who="S0679">which you no that was a that was a curry one I think</u>
<u n="14" who="S0680">oh we had the curry one yeah we I don't know if they make that anymore with the lentil</u>
<u n="15" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm that was very tasty I enjoyed that one and erm mm so if we have that today what have we got for tomorrow?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0680">we have some erm <trunc>ch</trunc>cheese and what are they? cheese and leek plaits</u>
<u n="17" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh yeah Linda McCartney well McCartney ones</u>
<u n="18" who="S0680" trans="overlap">cheese and leek plaits yes Linda McCartney ones the cheese and leek plaits with erm a random selection of sauces and vegetables</u>
<u n="19" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s steamed vegetables</u>
<u n="20" who="S0680">my steamed vegetables which will be be root parsnip carrot er <trunc>pars</trunc> I haven't got any celery unfortunately parsnip carrot there might be leeks certainly onion tomato er what else do I put in there? mushroom</u>
<u n="21" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="22" who="S0680">I quite often put the odd bit of sliced potato in there</u>
<u n="23" who="S0679">but not on this occasion</u>
<u n="24" who="S0680">I could do we haven't got any <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0679">that that little yes that does rather limit the range or so somebody informed me earlier</u>
<u n="26" who="S0680">I think I've used them all up haven't I?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><unclear/> so nice</u>
<u n="28" who="S0680">yes no I did reserve a couple and then I think I used them yes so possibly not potato on this <trunc>o</trunc>occasion but those erm new potatoes are very nice steamed</u>
<u n="29" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0680">I don't think I have any courgette</u>
<u n="31" who="S0679">it's not really the season for courgette is it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0680">well there's still quite a lot about but they get a bit marrowy</u>
<u n="33" who="S0679">yes that can easily happen in the garden with inattention</u>
<u n="34" who="S0680">mm so unless you buy the erm expensive little ones</u>
<u n="35" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0680">so that kind of thing if you fancy?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0679">yes that <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0680">I don't have any cabbage <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0679">one other meal one other tea left</u>
<u n="40" who="S0680">well if I can buy some Staffordshire oatcakes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh oatcakes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0680">we could have erm cheese tomato mushroom</u>
<u n="43" who="S0679">you could save a little bit of the sauce the pasta sauce</u>
<u n="44" who="S0680" trans="overlap">with a bit of pasta sauce</u>
<u n="45" who="S0679">we've done that haven't we?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0680">yes we could have that erm you still haven't had erm scrambled egg and</u>
<u n="47" who="S0679">oh no I've got a whole box of six</u>
<u n="48" who="S0680">beans on toast because I I only need a few eggs to erm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0680">do cooking</u>
<u n="51" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0680">cakey cookie things with so I won't be using for eating</u>
<u n="53" who="S0679">I may have to not have one of the other meals then</u>
<u n="54" who="S0680">no you might have to stay longer</u>
<u n="55" who="S0679">no I can't I I'm going I'm going back</u>
<u n="56" who="S0680">stay longer to er finish up your dinners</u>
<u n="57" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no just think of those men on the stations they well where is she? she's not sitting there she's not in either of the seats what do I do?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="59" who="S0679">they'd probably get a black mark if they don't have a passenger</u>
<u n="60" who="S0680">they might do</u>
<u n="61" who="S0679">although that that guy who didn't have to assist me when we came up seemed to be quite happy the fact</u>
<u n="62" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yeah he was he was quite happy yes he didn't have to do it</u>
<u n="63" who="S0679" trans="overlap">although he kept us company didn't he?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0679" trans="overlap">he thought he would entertain us if he couldn't assist us</u>
<u n="66" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes yes yes he entertained us on the way</u>
<u n="67" who="S0679">though he only had to go quite a short distance I feel back to his erm information points</u>
<u n="68" who="S0680">well if you had been in original coach B</u>
<u n="69" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0680">he would have been halfway to <anon type="place"/> practically cos that platform's ever so long</u>
<u n="71" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0680">if you think of the alphabet from B to</u>
<u n="73" who="S0679">oh yes A probably</u>
<u n="74" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="75" who="S0679">there isn't an A?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="77" who="S0679" trans="overlap">so the engine?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0680">yeah well it's not usually the A on that train it's B and it goes to I think it probably goes to M and <pause dur="short"/> lots of numbers lots of erm lots of letters so it is quite a long walk when you get in B so he might have thought he'd got <unclear/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0679" trans="overlap">but you have more than one platform presumably?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0680">what? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0679">the information point perhaps there's an information point at the end of each station</u>
<u n="82" who="S0680">well the <trunc>in</trunc> I think when you go to the information point it's probably the one that's next door to Marks and Spencer's</u>
<u n="83" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh it's somewhere just inside the door</u>
<u n="84" who="S0680">because otherwise you would have to go through the barrier to get to him</u>
<u n="85" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah but you've virtually got on the train haven't you by then?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0679">and I'm having assistance from other</u>
<u n="88" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0679">although how you're meant to get assistance from other</u>
<u n="90" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0679">to the information point is largely in the lap of the gods</u>
<u n="92" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0679">but I know how it's going to happen on this occasion</u>
<u n="94" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="95" who="S0679">and indeed I can probably manage myself</u>
<u n="96" who="S0680">cos the thing is if you get dropped off by a taxi <pause dur="short"/> I'm not entirely sure you can be dropped off at that entrance</u>
<u n="97" who="S0679">oh oh isn't that where we got the taxi from?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0680">we got it from but they all park in that road and come round</u>
<u n="99" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="100" who="S0680">to pick up people</u>
<u n="101" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0680">it's for picking up I'm not entirely sure</u>
<u n="103" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="104" who="S0680">if it's for dropping off</u>
<u n="105" who="S0679">obviously <unclear/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0680" trans="overlap">but they might be able to drop you off there cos originally that was the only exit but now erm they tend to drop you off at the back of the station</u>
<u n="107" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0680">and you have to walk you know where the ticket er the long row of ticket offices are? <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0679">I wasn't paying attention</u>
<u n="110" who="S0680">well as you came out as we headed for the exit to get the taxi off to the left and it's a bit chaos at the moment</u>
<u n="111" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0680">because they're erm got all that building work going on but if you go off to the left there's about sort of at least eight or ten ticket windows and you have to go past there and then down the stairs or the slope and there's all the restaurants and things you know and what was the information office that's no longer open the erm you know the <anon type="place"/> one and then you go out of a door at the very far end there which is the back of the station in <anon type="place"/> Street</u>
<u n="113" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0680">as in the river</u>
<u n="115" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="116" who="S0680">you know <trunc>ha</trunc> you know the <anon type="place"/> Hotel? that's part of the station? a big white building well</u>
<u n="117" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you know I've not been <unclear/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0680">vaguely white cos there's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="120" who="S0680">opposite <anon type="place"/> where the station is</u>
<u n="121" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0680">the station runs from behind it it must be very quite noisy staying in the <anon type="place"/> Hotel that white building or</u>
<u n="123" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0680">it's whiter than it used to be erm takes up that block more or less a lot of that block</u>
<u n="125" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0680">and the station is down the end of that and you go down and around a little roundabout to the back so it's quite a long way</u>
<u n="127" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0680">difference that's why if somebody's picking you up you've got to sort of tell them to go to that because if you're coming out on <trunc>fr</trunc>foot you tend to come out you and catching a bus you tend to come out the front</u>
<u n="129" who="S0679"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> picked me up didn't he? that was you</u>
<u n="130" who="S0680" trans="overlap">that was from the back</u>
<u n="131" who="S0679">you you and him</u>
<u n="132" who="S0680">yeah that was from the back</u>
<u n="133" who="S0679">that must have been about two thousand and seven or eight seven</u>
<u n="134" who="S0680" trans="overlap">about mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0679">I came up to that day conference about</u>
<u n="136" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> because you arrived early</u>
<u n="137" who="S0679">texting</u>
<u n="138" who="S0680">because you'd already <pause dur="short"/> you'd already got out onto the front there hadn't you? you were waiting by the car park <trunc>w</trunc>were you? I think you were waiting by the twenty minute car park</u>
<u n="139" who="S0679">I think you'd got there early too but maybe waited somewhere else I'm not sure well it all it all ended happily</u>
<u n="140" who="S0680" trans="overlap">we met up yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0679">without any difficulties</u>
<u n="142" who="S0680">was that when I you were at my house and I had I drove you</u>
<u n="143" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you drove me and dumped outside the er</u>
<u n="144" who="S0680" trans="overlap">dropped you in the university</u>
<u n="145" who="S0679">yes and then I went to that day texting conference</u>
<u n="146" who="S0680">and then when you finished you you just got down to the station didn't you? cos you were quite near the station there</u>
<u n="147" who="S0679" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0680">I didn't I don't think I picked you up</u>
<u n="149" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="150" who="S0680">I I can't remember if you walked or something</u>
<u n="151" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I got taxied or whatever</u>
<u n="152" who="S0680">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos we weren't quite sure when it was finishing</u>
<u n="153" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0680">I might have been at work or something</u>
<u n="155" who="S0679">well we don't know don't know but that was all about <pause dur="short"/> well how you use text messages</u>
<u n="156" who="S0680">well that was a while ago</u>
<u n="157" who="S0679">well no we still have text messages</u>
<u n="158" who="S0680">no I mean when they first sort of came in</u>
<u n="159" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well it was about how you used them to get people to appointments cos people had started experimenting with students</u>
<u n="160" who="S0680">oh like the</u>
<u n="161" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="162" who="S0680">doctors buzzing you and sending you more than you?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I mean doctors didn't do those days</u>
<u n="164" who="S0680">no well they overdo it now you get get two</u>
<u n="165" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0680">in rapid succession</u>
<u n="167" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh mm well how you could have bought them and you'd buy them in bulk the messages</u>
<u n="168" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="169" who="S0679">and then you send them out and I think they said that boys you know men</u>
<u n="170" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0679">students</u>
<u n="172" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0679">were four times as likely to come to their counselling interviews or their</u>
<u n="174" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0679">you know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0679">having to see somebody I think we're talking about further education maybe but I don't know</u>
<u n="178" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="179" who="S0679">whatever if you sent them a text message to remind them</u>
<u n="180" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="181" who="S0679">than if you didn't which obviously helps because of the <unclear/> wastes an awful lot of appointments I think girls were better I can't remember about girls</u>
<u n="182" who="S0680">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0679">the hospital's still sending fun messages that I think should be received on I think they're probably for a mobile phone but they erm send them out</u>
<u n="184" who="S0680">thinking they're going to an Iphone?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0679">well they don't know and they say press something and wait and oh and then they say we'll phone you again and they phone again</u>
<u n="186" who="S0680">oh I just get a text message</u>
<u n="187" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="188" who="S0680">saying you've got an appointment at <trunc>ei</trunc> at either your doctor or hospital is what the implication is they don't actually</u>
<u n="189" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0680">they don't send they're not particularly specific they're not</u>
<u n="191" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0680">they're just general</u>
<u n="193" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0680">these are general <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="place"/> come from <anon type="place"/> and the hospital definitely come from the hospital</u>
<u n="196" who="S0680">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="197" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0680">it's more like you have you have an appointment with a whichever trust it is you know</u>
<u n="199" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0680">or your GP so you've got to remember which it is yourself to some extent it's not very clear <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0679">I think it's a good idea in theory you have to get the timing right I think the <trunc>doc</trunc> the doctor's one oh the doctor's one always used to email as soon as you made the appointment</u>
<u n="202" who="S0680">yes which is not it confirms you've made it but it's not very helpful to <unclear/> to remind me</u>
<u n="203" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and I'm not sure now it might do it a day before or it might do it both but you see when I have my doctor phoning me she doesn't put an appointment in the system</u>
<u n="204" who="S0680">no she does it off her own bat</u>
<u n="205" who="S0679">I think she just writes a note on her desk to phone me</u>
<u n="206" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0679">cos on a couple of occasions I phoned up to check about the timing</u>
<u n="208" who="S0680">mm and nobody knew about it?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0679">and they said oh we'll just write the name down although she's very good at remembering who she has to phone but we'll add your name onto her list</u>
<u n="210" who="S0680">yes <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0679">but it's always worked she phoned here quite a lot in the summer didn't she?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="213" who="S0679">which was very good of her <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose we could try to resume activity in the kitchen</u>
<u n="214" who="S0680">I was just thinking which</u>
<u n="215" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0680">erm hopefully we'll remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at work</u>
<u n="217" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0680">took my well I think and he should have my email address because</u>
<u n="219" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0680">he had it but he took my email address again so that when he sends <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> notification of what work there is</u>
<u n="221" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="222" who="S0680">he can send me it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0679">oh is that what happened last time?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0680">which might have when he didn't <trunc>e</trunc> no he didn't send me an email cos he didn't</u>
<u n="225" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="226" who="S0680">know my thing and he he phoned me up</u>
<u n="227" who="S0679">but did it not happen last time?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0680" trans="overlap">no cos</u>
<u n="229" who="S0679">but was he intending to send it but didn't have your email so he had to ask you separately?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0680" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always used to ring me you see which is what he did</u>
<u n="231" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0680">or text me to ring her erm so I said reminded him that if he sent me an email I I was unlikely to have read it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0679">email and text would be better wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0680" trans="overlap">so I said if you send me an email can you just text to say you've sent me an email?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0680">which is what my neighbours do and then I'll make an effort to find a computer to look it up on</u>
<u n="237" who="S0679">mm mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0680">so it's not very helpful having emails</u>
<u n="239" who="S0679">no but it's</u>
<u n="240" who="S0680" trans="overlap">unsolicited</u>
<u n="241" who="S0679">it's better than not having the possibility of looking at the email at the same time isn't it?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0680">yes cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> kept texting me about other things but she didn't text me to say she'd sent me that email</u>
<u n="243" who="S0679">no well maybe she didn't think it was an action email</u>
<u n="244" who="S0680">no but she'd <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0679">well I'm going to switch off this recording now</u>
<u n="246" who="S0680">and we better go and do something</u>
<u n="247" who="S0679">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0680">do something practical</u>
<u n="249" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="251" who="S0679">what do you think we might do?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0680">can you get out of that chair?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0679">yeah I can probably do it</u>
<u n="254" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0679">I was just generally relaxing for a moment on the way</u>
<u n="256" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="257" who="S0679">so er let's have a look er that's what I'll do</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
