<text id="S8S2">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:56</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0218</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home, Leeds</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Celebrities, porn, daily activities</topics>
		<activity>Chilling with my boyfriend</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0218">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>no info</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0202">what are you looking at?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0218">I'm looking at celebrities and their porn star lookalikes</u>
<u n="3" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0218">one of the porn stars is called Page Turner</u>
<u n="5" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0202">that's good clever</u>
<u n="7" who="S0218">and this Alicia Keys Annette Keys <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="8" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0202">ah I wish them spots would bugger off <pause dur="long"/> and it's sent done</u>
<u n="10" who="S0218">done and done took a ride on the pussy</u>
<u n="11" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0202">I'll need to you to erm fill the consent form in soon</u>
<u n="13" who="S0218">why you been recording me?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0202">ah I don't know I there's still some recordings on the phone that I haven't loaded yet so I don't know until I listen to them</u>
<u n="15" who="S0218">I don't think I agreed to that unless I get the money</u>
<u n="16" who="S0202">shut up you get benefit for it it's paying for our wedding this you know?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0218"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0202">if you're going to sit all the if you're going to sit and fill all the forms in for me then you can I have some of the money</u>
<u n="19" who="S0218">come here</u>
<u n="20" who="S0202">no I'm going to tidy first and then I can relax</u>
<u n="21" who="S0218">er</u>
<u n="22" who="S0202">but if if you don't do that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0218">have you just farted?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0202">then feel free</u>
<u n="25" who="S0218">have you just farted?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0202">no why?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0218">sounded like you farted</u>
<u n="28" who="S0202">it looked like I farted</u>
<u n="29" who="S0218">sounded like you farted I said</u>
<u n="30" who="S0202">no it's the floor it creeks anyway I don't fart I'm a lady so you're not listening to me then</u>
<u n="31" who="S0218">you don't fart you're a lady creeks floor I don't believe any of it</u>
<u n="32" who="S0202" trans="overlap">just testing</u>
<u n="33" who="S0218">course I were listening</u>
<u n="34" who="S0202">well you never respond</u>
<u n="35" who="S0218">oh come off it do you know how many fucking questions I've asked you while you've been sat there that you haven't responded too? it must be at least ten</u>
<u n="36" who="S0202">shut up</u>
<u n="37" who="S0218">in half an hour</u>
<u n="38" who="S0202">shut up no one cares about what you have to say except Cambridge <pause dur="long"/> so tell me about your day</u>
<u n="39" who="S0218">oh you're interested now are you?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0202">well yeah I were busy filling all them bloody forms in</u>
<u n="41" who="S0218">you've just been watching gay millionaire trying to put some comments on it very unsuccessful</u>
<u n="42" who="S0202">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0218">just don't know what I was trying to I was trying to show em what what to prove or anything I thought I'd just give up</u>
<u n="44" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0202">that sounds productive</u>
<u n="46" who="S0218">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0202">oh I know I know I can't do it so I'm not going to find out how I'm just going to give up like</u>
<u n="48" who="S0218">I know how to do everything but at the end of the day I'm going to show em some stuff and they're going to be like well am I going to do it with this information or am I just gonna is it any worth worth it</u>
<u n="49" who="S0202">well it's up to them to do something but if they don't do owt with it then</u>
<u n="50" who="S0218">exactly that's what I've come up with so I'm going to make them do it make my job easy</u>
<u n="51" who="S0202">I suppose that's one way of doing it ah my back is killing</u>
<u n="52" who="S0218">why don't you get a bath?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0202">you what?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0218">why don't you get a bath?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0202">it's a bit late innit?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0218">I'm going to get a shower I think <pause dur="long"/> er girls with six packs er</u>
<u n="57" who="S0202">you what?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0218">girls with six packs</u>
<u n="59" who="S0202">oh I know it's vile innit? like how can anyone find that attractive I just don't understand like it's pretty disgusting and did you see that woman on Russell Howard's Good News? she was vile</u>
<u n="60" who="S0218" trans="overlap">what the bodybuilder?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0202">yeah she was absolutely vile I looked at her and the <trunc>fi</trunc> the first thought that came into my head was that of a man it's like you look like a man <pause dur="long"/> her boobs looked like fucking golf balls that's how hard they were her pecks like <pause dur="long"/> this wardrobe is not very big <pause dur="short"/> I can't wait to get my drawers it's doing my head in</u>
<u n="62" who="S0218">when's it coming?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0202">I don't know</u>
<u n="64" who="S0218">are they fucking making it or</u>
<u n="65" who="S0202">well that's what I paid for like fucking taking their sweet time with it <pause dur="long"/> like ah and get this right do you know how our light's broken?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0218">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0202">well they were a fucking electrician next door fixing their light why couldn't they do ours the same time?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0218">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0202">fucking pricks</u>
<u n="70" who="S0218">are you two on the same?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0218">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0202">it's Hive same as our well they're renting like like we are cos I rang her about well actually no I only rang yesterday but still you'd think they'd kill two birds with one stone instead of having to come out to the same address cos it technically is the same address <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0218">getting too old for this shit</u>
<u n="75" who="S0202">for what?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0218">ah just a comment</u>
<u n="77" who="S0202">oh sorry</u>
<u n="78" who="S0218"><unclear>somebody put there</unclear> reminded me of that Lethal Weapon</u>
<u n="79" who="S0202" trans="overlap">move your knee ah so nice to sit down</u>
<u n="80" who="S0218">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0218"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0202">I love that I lose track of how many times a day I'd like to turn to someone and say you can seriously be that this fucking stupid <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah it's so funny will the clothes set on fire if I put them on the radiator? <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah she actually asked that</u>
<u n="84" who="S0218">oh four are you recording something else?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0202">I'm recording now</u>
<u n="86" who="S0218">what? seriously?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0218">all this time?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0202">I've been recording for seven minutes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0218">and I've been shouting fucking <unclear/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0218">right <pause dur="short"/> did you just pick your nose?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0202">yeah I picked my nose</u>
<u n="94" who="S0218">don't eat it</u>
<u n="95" who="S0202">stop it you minger it's okay for me to do it but not you</u>
<u n="96" who="S0218">why?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0202"><trunc>beca</trunc> I'm going to hit you in the face go away <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="music"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0218">what's that?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0202">oh that is so cool</u>
<u n="100" who="S0218">what is it?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0202">watch it <pause dur="long"/> it's right cool innit?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0218">it is cool that <pause dur="short"/> we thought about doing that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0202">you what sorry?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0218">genius</u>
<u n="105" who="S0202">mm canoodling couple caught copulating in crisis carsie carsy</u>
<u n="106" who="S0218">who who <unclear/>? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0202">I don't get it ah what's happened to your phone</u>
<u n="108" who="S0218">I know you fucking broke it</u>
<u n="109" who="S0202">what I never broke it when did that happen?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0218">the other night</u>
<u n="111" who="S0202">when did you do that?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0218">don't know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0202">oh that's a right bad move</u>
<u n="114" who="S0218">I know it's shit isn't it?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0202">this is the moment a pair a star struck lovers were caught in the midst of a steamy romp in a Rock City toilet</u>
<u n="116" who="S0218"><shift new="singing"/> Rock City built this city on rock and roll <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0202">why would you have sex in a nightclub toilet like seriously why would you do that?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0218">it's disgusting innit? the amount of shit you see in there literally all over the walls on the toilet er disgusting <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0202">I just don't know why you'd do it I don't know what would possess you to go and shag someone in a fucking toilet</u>
<u n="120" who="S0218">no idea <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0202">so what you got what you got playing on this er what have you got playing this weekend?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0218">away Preston <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0202">erm Manchester?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0218">no Preston</u>
<u n="125" who="S0202">yeah that's near Manchester though innit?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0218">oh it's near Manchester <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="long"/> that way over <pause dur="short"/> over them there hills</u>
<u n="127" who="S0202">oh we've got the hamster this weekend</u>
<u n="128" who="S0218">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0202">we're looking after it for them</u>
<u n="130" who="S0218">you're fucking</u>
<u n="131" who="S0202">no I can't wait it's right cute</u>
<u n="132" who="S0218"><unclear>right</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> ha ha eight thousand calorie breakfast challenge</u>
<u n="133" who="S0202" trans="overlap">cos they're not in all weekend and we want it <pause dur="short"/> oh I saw that earlier</u>
<u n="134" who="S0218">yeah fucking hell I could do that</u>
<u n="135" who="S0202">cos they're all out this weekend and we really want one it's like a trial run</u>
<u n="136" who="S0218">you really want a hamster?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0218"><unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0202">not er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> listen to this just one more wank could kill me admits Avicii</u>
<u n="140" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0202">EDM country cross-over star Avicii has blamed a chronic porn addiction for the current health issues which have seen the twenty-five-year-old Swede put his music career temporarily on hold speaking from his plush Los Angeles mansion the two times Grammy-nominated producer emotionally revealed that he had no choice but to take a break for from music after doctors warned him of the serious long-term health issues associated with porn addiction <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> porn was always a way of me for way for me to escape the mundane reality of life admitted Avicii real name Tim Bergling it's tough growing up in Sweden we have long dark winters where it can be very hard to leave your house so for me the best way to deal with this was porn and the <trunc>ob</trunc>obvious masturbation that goes with it when I first broke onto the music scene I temporarily forgot porn I had girls throwing themselves at me so I literally just didn't have enough time or penises to even think about porn or jacking off continued a reminiscent Avicii things were going great for me I was healthy my success was growing and for the first time in my life I had enough money to make sure I had clean underpants on every day <vocal desc="laugh"/> things couldn't have gone any better then one day about a year ago I was feeling a bit down after listening to the massive version of my my album Truth so I decided to watch some porn he continued in a regretful tone the first time I want to watch something funny like a midget fucking a horse you know just to cheer me up a little but since I started watching it I got deeper and deeper into it before I knew what I was doing I was jacking off to granny foot fetish dot com in a public toilet</u>
<u n="142" who="S0218">er this isn't real is it?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0202">no of course it isn't</u>
<u n="144" who="S0218">it's not oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0202">of course it isn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> did you think it was real?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0218" trans="overlap">I thought it was yeah yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0202">you fucking idiot</u>
<u n="148" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0202">I've definitely watched some stuff that I'm not proud of there's something about sitting in a hotel room watching a middle-aged overweight woman sticking a pool cue so far up a skinny old guy's ass that it's practically coming out of his mouth that makes you pause for a moment and think hey is this really the route I want my life life to take?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0218"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I <trunc>tho</trunc> I did think you were being serious</u>
<u n="151" who="S0202">did you think I oh my god</u>
<u n="152" who="S0218">where is that from? who wrote it?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0202">I don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0218"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0202">what are you laughing at? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0218">rock bottom <pause dur="long"/> I <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0202">mm have you heard that Ed Miliband is getting a nose job?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0218">what so he stops talking through his nose?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0202">yeah basically that's why</u>
<u n="160" who="S0218">too right</u>
<u n="161" who="S0202">in eighteen seventy-one a <trunc>deven</trunc> a defence attorney accidently shot himself in the stomach while re-enacting a bar room brawl in order to prove the innocence of his client while demonstrating how the victim was shot by his own pistol the gun went off and the attorney suffered the same fate he died from his bullet wound but he still won the case <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0218"><shift new="singing"/> built this city on rock and roll <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="whistle"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0202">I really like the girl next door</u>
<u n="164" who="S0218">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0218">even the Geordie one man?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0202">yeah even the Scouse one</u>
<u n="168" who="S0218">the Scouse one you know hey mate I only live next door I've got a hamster living in my room</u>
<u n="169" who="S0202">called Donald</u>
<u n="170" who="S0218">called Don</u>
<u n="171" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0218">Donald?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0202">Donald</u>
<u n="174" who="S0218">Donald</u>
<u n="175" who="S0202">it's called Donald</u>
<u n="176" who="S0218">why? why is it called Donald?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0218">Donald seen that spider there</u>
<u n="179" who="S0202">what? spiders? where</u>
<u n="180" who="S0218">look at the size of that fucker?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0202">where the fuck is that?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0218">that's my mate that's in England</u>
<u n="183" who="S0202">yeah but where?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0218">right here</u>
<u n="185" who="S0202">no it's not where is it?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0218">dunno <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> do do doo <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0202">is it oh do you erm want to go with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0218">yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0202">but?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0218">how can I plan something for a years' time away?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0202">yeah well we're not going to plan it then but like obviously like January we'll plan it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0218">she said she's booking it before Christmas isn't she?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when god makes you pregnant stay pregnant when got makes you barren stay barren when god gives you a uterus maybe we'll listen to you</u>
<u n="194" who="S0218"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's you that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0202">what?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0218">eighty-seven <unclear/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0202">who counts their fries? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0218">absolutely bloody nuts</u>
<u n="199" who="S0202">Lisa Kudrow looks right old now doesn't she?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0218">who?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0202">Lisa Kudrow</u>
<u n="202" who="S0218">she always looked old <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0202">yeah but I mean like that's probably cos she had fucking loads of <trunc>sur</trunc></u>
<u n="204" who="S0218" trans="overlap">oh fuck that why does it do that?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0202">what? I'm talking you know you're just talking over me</u>
<u n="206" who="S0218">why have you forgot what you were going to say?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when she asks you to go deeper but you're all out of dick <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's you when we have sex</u>
<u n="208" who="S0218">shut up <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0202">you still owe me some earphones that what I want for my birthday</u>
<u n="210" who="S0218">erm do I?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0202">yes did you just fart?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0218">no creaky bed</u>
<u n="213" who="S0202">fucking lying bastard</u>
<u n="214" who="S0218">creaky floor</u>
<u n="215" who="S0202">you're not even on the floor</u>
<u n="216" who="S0218">that's the floor then</u>
<u n="217" who="S0202">oh my god you disgusting creature ah that fucking stinks</u>
<u n="218" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0218">oh where did that come from?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0202">er every time you have curry I don't know why I cook it for you any more</u>
<u n="221" who="S0218">it just gets</u>
<u n="222" who="S0202">oh my god it's getting worse</u>
<u n="223" who="S0218"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0202">stop wafting it's not getting any better</u>
<u n="225" who="S0218">something needs to happen</u>
<u n="226" who="S0202">my eyes are bleeding</u>
<u n="227" who="S0218"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0202">jesus fucking christ</u>
<u n="229" who="S0218">that didn't even <trunc>fe</trunc> that didn't even feel bad</u>
<u n="230" who="S0202">stop wafting it you're just making it worse</u>
<u n="231" who="S0218">do you know when do you when it's warm you know it's going to be bad but that was just normal</u>
<u n="232" who="S0202">that is disgusting</u>
<u n="233" who="S0218">it's awful innit?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0202">you should be ashamed of yourself</u>
<u n="235" who="S0218">I'll have to go for a shit in a minute</u>
<u n="236" who="S0202">ah please just go for a shit now cos it fucking stinks <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0218"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0202">ah <pause dur="short"/> I'm actually going to be sick</u>
<u n="239" who="S0218">it's not that bad</u>
<u n="240" who="S0202">go and light that fucking candle now</u>
<u n="241" who="S0218">I daren't light a match in here</u>
<u n="242" who="S0202">go and light <vocal desc="laugh"/> go and light the candle</u>
<u n="243" who="S0218">ah it'll be alright</u>
<u n="244" who="S0202">I'm not joking</u>
<u n="245" who="S0218">no it's the smell's gone</u>
<u n="246" who="S0202">do it now</u>
<u n="247" who="S0218">smells gone for me</u>
<u n="248" who="S0202">no it hasn't not for me go and light the candle</u>
<u n="249" who="S0218">you should get up here</u>
<u n="250" who="S0202"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm going to smack you in the face go light the candle</u>
<u n="251" who="S0218">where's your lighter</u>
<u n="252" who="S0202">it's on there</u>
<u n="253" who="S0218">go to get me it then</u>
<u n="254" who="S0202">I'm not going to get you the lighter for you to light the fucking candle</u>
<u n="255" who="S0218">why? <shift new="singing"/> built this city on rock and roll <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0202">go for a poor</u>
<u n="257" who="S0218">why have I got why have got that stuck in my bloody head?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0202">I don't fucking know ah it's getting worse</u>
<u n="259" who="S0218">it's not it's not</u>
<u n="260" who="S0202">it's getting worse</u>
<u n="261" who="S0218">it's definitely not</u>
<u n="262" who="S0202">it's getting worse</u>
<u n="263" who="S0218">it's not it just smells like jalfrezi</u>
<u n="264" who="S0202">ah we didn't have jalfrezi</u>
<u n="265" who="S0218">what did we have?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0202">we had rogan josh</u>
<u n="267" who="S0218">it's all the same innit?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="269" who="S0218">all based around curry</u>
<u n="270" who="S0202">ah you're disgusting go and light that candle it's scented it'll cover the sell</u>
<u n="271" who="S0218">there is no smell left</u>
<u n="272" who="S0202">yes there is I can smell it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0218">can you taste it?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0202">er</u>
<u n="275" who="S0218">where's your lighter?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0202">there's a lighter somewhere</u>
<u n="277" who="S0218">where's your candle?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0202">there's one that I've got like the candle's over there move it away from the blind cos it might set on fire</u>
<u n="279" who="S0218">it's empty that</u>
<u n="280" who="S0202">well there's another one like on the shelf down oh my fucking god it's actually getting worse <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's on the second shelf down the second one two <pause dur="long"/> ah fucking hell</u>
<u n="281" who="S0218">I don't know what you're talking about</u>
<u n="282" who="S0202">you could clear a conference room you</u>
<u n="283" who="S0218">I don't know what you're talking about</u>
<u n="284" who="S0202">with six thousand people in it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0218">I'm hard core I <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
