<text id="S8SH">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:38:56</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0679 S0680</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s living room, Leeds </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>The Great British Sewing Bee BBC tv programme, Mum’s sewing, Clothes Mum made for Sue in the 60s and 70s, 60s haircuts, Car parking in central London</topics>
		<activity>Chatting with sister, late Tuesday evening</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0679">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kent, Margate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired (University manager)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0680">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Margate, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Mostly Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, West Yorks.</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>42 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- School</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0679">so are <trunc>yo</trunc> are you enjoying this series of the Sewing Bee?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm yes in large part it's it's quite good entertainment but the some of the erm sewing is a bit er strange cos there's no kind of emphasis on the under finishing or anything like that cos it's just make it in the time</u>
<u n="3" who="S0679">especially with the alteration challenge</u>
<u n="4" who="S0680">yes which is you know fair enough they haven't got long but</u>
<u n="5" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0680">but some of them do seem a little on the ragged side and they do seem to use patterns</u>
<u n="7" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="8" who="S0680">you <trunc>kn</trunc> they do seem to follow a pattern rather than some of them'll modify patterns but er</u>
<u n="9" who="S0679">I think this time I think in <trunc>prev</trunc> I think previously they had a direct make or something as a on a particular week</u>
<u n="10" who="S0680">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0679">well they had to fit it directly on the person or they had to make a paper pattern I can't quite remember</u>
<u n="12" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0679">but there was something but there is one part I mean generally there's one part where they have to they're given a pattern and they have to make it up</u>
<u n="14" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="15" who="S0679">which is reasonable isn't it? cos that's <trunc>s</trunc>sort of like a blind challenge</u>
<u n="16" who="S0680">well it yes I mean they have been choosing their own patterns but and they had patterns for jackets and things but er you know some of the more simple stuff I suppose the er what do you call it? the revamping things</u>
<u n="17" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0680">is a bit more</u>
<u n="19" who="S0679" trans="overlap">alteration challenge</u>
<u n="20" who="S0680" trans="overlap">the alteration challenge is a bit erm a bit different on that but er</u>
<u n="21" who="S0679">they're sort of making something out of a pattern then aren't they? although some people make their own paper one</u>
<u n="22" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0679">but they tend to be a bit a lot of those tend to be more loose garments don't they?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="25" who="S0679">mm but and er</u>
<u n="26" who="S0680" trans="overlap">and they can be a bit thrown together</u>
<u n="27" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="28" who="S0680">and sometimes they don't always seem to have the use the material that appropriately I don't think like</u>
<u n="29" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I think mum would have a few things to say about it cos they have a big piece of material</u>
<u n="30" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="31" who="S0679">and they just pin things all over the place on it</u>
<u n="32" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0679">and er mum was very good wasn't she about erm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes well mum was a</u>
<u n="35" who="S0679">er making sure it went together as <trunc>s</trunc> in small er small as small a space as possible?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="37" who="S0679">but then it does depend on the pattern a bit doesn't it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0680">what the printed the design?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0679">the <trunc>patt</trunc> your repeat like on</u>
<u n="40" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0679">wallpaper you have</u>
<u n="42" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="43" who="S0679">repeats then</u>
<u n="44" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well it does to some extent on the other hand what I haven't seen them doing particularly is opening the material out <pause dur="short"/> erm and refolding it in a different way because mum used to refold her material so that you could get well you know one leg up one way and one leg up the other not put two legs following or something</u>
<u n="45" who="S0679">oh right</u>
<u n="46" who="S0680">you know so you would use</u>
<u n="47" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0680">so instead of getting a wasted bit in the middle</u>
<u n="49" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0680">if you well you had to put it against well no if you had to put it against the the er fold er against if you folded it in half to do it double to get the symmetrical shape</u>
<u n="51" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0680">well mum wouldn't fold it like they sort of seem to fold it in half and cut it against the fold so</u>
<u n="53" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="54" who="S0680" trans="overlap">you get a big scrap along the bottom</u>
<u n="55" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0680" trans="overlap">of the the selvedge er there whereas mum would only fold it as far down as she needed to cut the size so she'd then have an extra piece of material that was double the size of the scrap they're getting</u>
<u n="57" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="58" who="S0680">and you could then put another piece in it so you could cut possibly one bit and then from the bit that was left over that wasn't folded</u>
<u n="59" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="60" who="S0680">she could cut the other bit flat you know refold it down the middle and</u>
<u n="61" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0680">cut out the one the other way by erm moving it up or moving it down slightly cos I remember at school when we used to get <trunc>s</trunc> erm told well we used to have to follow a pattern like the pyjamas we made stripy pyjamas I think I did get the material from school in that case but for example with similar things like that</u>
<u n="63" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0680">the pattern a proper shop-bought pattern would say you need two yards</u>
<u n="65" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="66" who="S0680">erm mum would say you don't need <trunc>t</trunc> we we don't need to do it in two yards we can do it in</u>
<u n="67" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0680">a yard and a half or whatever it was and er we had to buy the patterns as well so mum used to pin the pattern on the material</u>
<u n="69" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="70" who="S0680">or show me where to pin it on the material</u>
<u n="71" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0680">erm and I'd take it to school like that and then at school I would put it on more carefully you know she wasn't doing it all for me but she would show so I could show the teacher where the bits went</u>
<u n="73" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0680">but you didn't actually need that extra half a yard</u>
<u n="75" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="76" who="S0680" trans="overlap">especially if you were buying some you know reasonably expensive material</u>
<u n="77" who="S0679">and anyway it saves the pennies and that was important</u>
<u n="78" who="S0680">and that was important but you see mum I mean mum was a tailoress really I know she did dressmaking but high standards cos she did make suits and well she made everything from the skin skin upwards</u>
<u n="79" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0680">outwards erm really cos in those in those days erm during during the war and <trunc>aft</trunc> after I mean they they made underwear and everything from</u>
<u n="81" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0680">if they could get a bit of parachute silk</u>
<u n="83" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0680" trans="overlap">they'd use that for underwear and ladies would go and buy a full matching set of something you know so they'd have the the slip and the knickers and everything and then they'd erm you know they would buy erm sort of an outfit</u>
<u n="85" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0680"><trunc>s</trunc>so mum could do all that and she could do I mean she that's what I mean she did tailoring in those days they had quite fitted jackets and things she could do tailoring and erm so on and being wartime those men's-wise baggy trousers they used to have</u>
<u n="87" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0680">on suits if you got an old pair of trousers you could make a a decent skirt out of it cos you've got</u>
<u n="89" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="90" who="S0680">four legs</u>
<u n="91" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0680">to play about with so you could cut it in a would it be a <unclear/>? you'd certainly make a panelled a six-panelled skirt or</u>
<u n="93" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0680">erm any of those sort of ones that you need seams in so erm she was dab hand at doing that from little bits of material and of course my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in her element when she was er came round because she loved sewing</u>
<u n="95" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0680">so mum and her would be patterning and looking at this that and the other sorting things out</u>
<u n="97" who="S0679" trans="overlap">did they make things together?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0680">er not really I don't think they actually made anything together but they talked about what they were doing</u>
<u n="99" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0680">I don't think she actually helped <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with anything and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was pretty good at doing things so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made a suede coat cos her father had got these erm skins</u>
<u n="101" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0680">from somewhere or other and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made a suede coat when they were fashionable in the sixties</u>
<u n="103" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0680">you know with the covered buttons and everything and it looked perfectly decent which is quite a a lot for a sort of sixteen-year-old or so</u>
<u n="105" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="106" who="S0680">to take on</u>
<u n="107" who="S0679">although one of those on the telly is <trunc>sixt</trunc></u>
<u n="108" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes she's not old is she?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I think her name might be Jade</u>
<u n="110" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="111" who="S0679">I don't think she's particularly old</u>
<u n="112" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="113" who="S0679">and she was saying the best thing she'd made was her prom dress</u>
<u n="114" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0679" trans="overlap">which looked particularly nicely made</u>
<u n="116" who="S0680">well I think she's yes she's a later sort of</u>
<u n="117" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0680" trans="overlap">teenager I think as well but you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was quite sort of confident about</u>
<u n="119" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0680">cutting this erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> expensive stuff up and well <trunc>sh</trunc> you know you she used to run up things to wear at the dance</u>
<u n="121" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0680">or same as mum did for me cos I used to draw it and she used to make it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0680">but er</u>
<u n="125" who="S0679">did you see things in magazines or shops? how did you get your ideas? or did you just do them you did you kind of know what people had and make one up?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0680">well I kind of saw bits of things I liked and made one up really</u>
<u n="127" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0680">erm cos I <trunc>kn</trunc> I well it's the same as now I never actually want to actually be wearing what everybody else is wearing</u>
<u n="129" who="S0679">well you certainly don't do that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you know er I wouldn't just want to be looking like everybody else but I like to take the kind of the the theme and erm <trunc>m</trunc> plus mum had provisos cos was <trunc>wha</trunc> I was only er like I wasn't allowed to down to the dance till I was seventeen I think it as yes and er mum had provisos as to what I could actually have so as to how low the front was and you know well not how how <trunc>sh</trunc>short the skirt was to some extent although they were shorter skirts so erm you know there was that to consider so I did have some quite a few dresses that had quite er a low neckline at the back you know</u>
<u n="131" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0680">up to up to your bra strap which was quite erm daring</u>
<u n="133" who="S0679">would you <trunc>d</trunc> you covered up in those days</u>
<u n="134" who="S0680">yes which you didn't go you <trunc>d</trunc>definitely did didn't show your straps like they do now and if you've got a if you've got a sleeveless dress you would have little er little poppers and loops to put under your bra to keep it</u>
<u n="135" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0680">on your straps</u>
<u n="137" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm I was looking at one er out of my summer clothing and wondering if I'd sewn that kind of arrangement in because it's always a bit awkward</u>
<u n="138" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0679">when I or whether it came and I couldn't couldn't decide</u>
<u n="140" who="S0680">no or or you would use erm a very little tiny gold pins</u>
<u n="141" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0680">erm as well they were useful and if you had a halterneck dress then you'd you'd have a a suitably shaped bra strap</u>
<u n="143" who="S0679">yes you wouldn't wear over-the-shoulder straps</u>
<u n="144" who="S0680" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="145" who="S0679" trans="overlap">which people do now like that lady I was talking <trunc>t</trunc>telling you about on the train</u>
<u n="146" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes oh I know</u>
<u n="147" who="S0679">who had this sort of quite it was a sort of the first hot it was the <trunc>hotte</trunc> I should think it was the hottest day of the year</u>
<u n="148" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0679">so far and she had this sort of vesty top and this sort of padded erm foamy sort of big cup bra</u>
<u n="150" who="S0680">like a Wonderbra? <unclear/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well I don't know do they push up? I'm not sure what a Wonderbra does but</u>
<u n="152" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I I think it's supposed to enhance one's potential</u>
<u n="153" who="S0679" trans="overlap">but it <trunc>th</trunc>there's some that really look as though they're made of bits of erm foamy material that is sort of</u>
<u n="154" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="155" who="S0679">bent over</u>
<u n="156" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="157" who="S0679">that sort of really er anyway it there was quite a <trunc>l</trunc> I could I could I could check it out quite carefully</u>
<u n="158" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="159" who="S0679">because of the way her her top <trunc>w</trunc>went</u>
<u n="160" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="161" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="163" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0680">so</u>
<u n="165" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I can remember you had some er some of your dresses did you have a lot of pinky a silky-looking one? I don't think it was silky</u>
<u n="166" who="S0680" trans="overlap">it was</u>
<u n="167" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I think it was a new fabric</u>
<u n="168" who="S0680">it was it was it was erm it could have been <unclear>Tricel</unclear></u>
<u n="169" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0680">and it it was a sort of apricot I suppose a pale apricot colour and that had a bit of sheen to it and was erm it was a fitted bodice it was sleeveless with a small er with a square neck but not too low</u>
<u n="171" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh a square neck yes</u>
<u n="172" who="S0680">it had a square neck er it was sleeveless and it came in under the it was fitted under the bust with a tiny band and that bodice was all erm it was ruched up it was lines of sewing and then pinched in to gather so it was all little ruches all the way over</u>
<u n="173" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="174" who="S0680">and it had the same binding on the erm edge of the sleeves and round</u>
<u n="175" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0680">er sleeve armholes</u>
<u n="177" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0680">and round the neck and it was square neck and the back and then it had a sort of A-line skirt not gathered or anything it was just an A-line as was per sixties</u>
<u n="179" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0680">and it was just a bit above the knee</u>
<u n="181" who="S0679">are you thinking of a plain one or one with a swirly pattern on?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0680">no I'm thinking of a plain one but</u>
<u n="183" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="184" who="S0680" trans="overlap">the material had got a slightly erm kind of embossed it wasn't <trunc>shin</trunc> it wasn't so shiny it did have a slight textured embossed tiny little</u>
<u n="185" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0680"><trunc>sq</trunc> er think on it and I also because I had my short short hair with a backcombed bit I used to have a little bow I had a little <trunc>bl</trunc> bow on a clip</u>
<u n="187" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0680">in the same material</u>
<u n="189" who="S0679">I always think of that being a a sort of a a kind of peachy orange actually</u>
<u n="190" who="S0680">well it yes it wasn't sort of loud the loud one</u>
<u n="191" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0680">I had which you probably liked was the one with the swirly different colours it that was pinky purplely</u>
<u n="193" who="S0679">oh with the belt?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0680" trans="overlap">white er swirly things cos it was like psychedelic I'm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="196" who="S0680" trans="overlap">the small</u>
<u n="197" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I was meant I was talking about</u>
<u n="198" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes the small</u>
<u n="199" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I thought the small-scale it's er small-scale swirls</u>
<u n="201" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0680">and it was all sort of like it was was <vocal desc="laugh"/> on the psychedelic era</u>
<u n="203" who="S0679" trans="overlap">with little white and grey and</u>
<u n="204" who="S0680">and yes</u>
<u n="205" who="S0679" trans="overlap">pink and</u>
<u n="206" who="S0680" trans="overlap">and and pinky mauvey</u>
<u n="207" who="S0679">and looking much nicer</u>
<u n="208" who="S0680" trans="overlap">swirly</u>
<u n="209" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><unclear/> sounds</u>
<u n="210" who="S0680" trans="overlap">swirly things it sounds horrendous but er and that had that again was sleeveless erm with just a plain-faced sleeve er underneath er er armhole underneath and it had a V-neck</u>
<u n="211" who="S0679">oh a V-neck</u>
<u n="212" who="S0680"><trunc>i</trunc>it had a V-neck with a collar on it like a</u>
<u n="213" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="214" who="S0680">a flat</u>
<u n="215" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0680">a flat <trunc>n</trunc>not standing up like a shirt collar but like a flat a quite a small collar roll collar at the back but the ends of it were slightly er a little bit pointy not the <unclear>the every so long</unclear> points you sometimes got</u>
<u n="217" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0680">and then that was erm had erm darts and darts from the waist so the bodice was fitted erm and it had a it was waisted and it had erm I think it it wasn't it had a slightly flared skirt because it that again was erm was it it wasn't it might have been Tricel there was another word for er it was a man-made fibre but it didn't screw up or anything it was and it was thin</u>
<u n="219" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0680" trans="overlap">it was very fine like a silky fine thin material</u>
<u n="221" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="222" who="S0680">er and it had a belt on it with a little buckle and the little pinky erm oblong curved it was it sort of it it was an oblong shape but it had a curve to it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0680">so it fitted against your waist and that was an old one of mum's from</u>
<u n="225" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="226" who="S0680">I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> nineteen thirties or something that er went round it and that was quite quite short</u>
<u n="227" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0680">and again I had a I think I had a ribbon that time I had a erm ribbony thing that I could do into a bow in the same material and it was it was very bright but it was very nice</u>
<u n="229" who="S0679">and you had one with a another belted one</u>
<u n="230" who="S0680" trans="overlap">and of course having said that it <trunc>ha</trunc> it did have a little pocket in it as well cos</u>
<u n="231" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="232" who="S0680">mother always tried to put a pocket in somewhere yes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and there was one for your cloakroom ticket</u>
<u n="234" who="S0680">well well one would have one's handbag but</u>
<u n="235" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="236" who="S0680">for one's hanky</u>
<u n="237" who="S0679">oh and you had another one with a belt didn't you? er it had more sort of erm if it seemed a bit more like a shirt</u>
<u n="238" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="239" who="S0679">a purple purple and yellow and</u>
<u n="240" who="S0680">no oh <trunc>n</trunc> are you thinking of the swirly one?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0679">not not the pink swirly one no erm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0680">I can't think which one that was</u>
<u n="243" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="244" who="S0680">with a belt</u>
<u n="245" who="S0679">but another one you had was like erm you had made nighties out of that erm slightly furry fabric</u>
<u n="246" who="S0680">furry fabric</u>
<u n="247" who="S0679">er you know like like the <trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc>you've got that apricot long nightie</u>
<u n="248" who="S0680">what was that?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0679">well it had little stripes across</u>
<u n="250" who="S0680" trans="overlap">brushed nylon?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0679">brushed nylon is that what you call it?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="253" who="S0679">it was like a big T-shirt with those pearl buttons on it</u>
<u n="254" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh I know what you mean yes yes</u>
<u n="255" who="S0679">and they had lots of different colours</u>
<u n="256" who="S0680">er yes that was a slightly velvety effect</u>
<u n="257" who="S0679">was that brushed nylon or am I rude about it?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0680" trans="overlap">with a printed erm well it's kind of like that but it was had a slightly erm velvety but it it was a kind of stretchy material and it was like a erm a big T-shirt only not like they wear now that's flappy with the off the shoulder it was erm a properly fitted your size erm <trunc>s</trunc> er like the top of a T-shirt erm but it had erm an oval sort of neck and it had a little placket with buttons I think at the front or</u>
<u n="259" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0680">and then erm it went carried on but it was quite narrow it wasn't a flappy T-shirt it was quite fitted on the hips narrow and short and it had got a sort of wavy a wavy pattern</u>
<u n="261" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0680">it wasn't a swirly one it was a wavy pattern</u>
<u n="263" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0680">and it was green and <vocal desc="laugh"/> orange and yellow and but it was very thin</u>
<u n="265" who="S0679">yes it was very pretty</u>
<u n="266" who="S0680" trans="overlap">lines it was very pretty and it it was quite a a clingy</u>
<u n="267" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0680">type thing and then I of course the fashion came in cos those were kind of <unclear>oh</unclear> <trunc>s</trunc> I'm talking sixty-seven sixty-eight kind of era and then erm also knitted dresses the well crocheted</u>
<u n="269" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0680"><trunc>d</trunc>dresses erm but you could also have a knitted dress with a holey pattern in a crocheted pattern in and it wasn't too holey and erm it had scallop crochet round the end and it was just like a erm <pause dur="short"/> I suppose like a a shift you know it was just erm it was just like a a vesty top only with a higher boat neck slightly cut in erm armholes and erm straight and thin erm just and it had scalloping round the edges and it was like erm <pause dur="short"/> not navy-blue a <trunc>sor</trunc> a warmer colour than that sort of midnight blue and of course it was very holey you're supposed to have tassels round the bottom but I never got the tassels and I had scallops instead and there was a twisted wool belt thing</u>
<u n="271" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0680">and you tie round but it was it was a bit holey so mum made a lining for it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0680">so I had a lined one cos she didn't</u>
<u n="275" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0680">think it was quite the thing</u>
<u n="277" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="278" who="S0680">to go round showing your holes through the skin through the holes so erm I had this lining which was it was lining material and it was very sort of erm er it was a what would you call it? erm I can't think of the name it was like a satin it got a sheen on it it was the same colour</u>
<u n="279" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh right mm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0680">as the dress but got a bit of a sheen so</u>
<u n="281" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0680">when the light caught it it was quite</u>
<u n="283" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0680">pretty in the holes and it also kept the shape of the dress better cos some people's <vocal desc="laugh"/> some people's crocheted dresses tended to sort of grow with them or</u>
<u n="285" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0680">get longer and things <vocal desc="laugh"/> bit like possibly a bit like knitted swimming costumes of the early fifties</u>
<u n="287" who="S0679">I think you did well not to have the tassels I think they're much overrated</u>
<u n="288" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="289" who="S0679">I'm not sure tassels would have looked very nice on it I think scallop was</u>
<u n="290" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0679">was probably better</u>
<u n="292" who="S0680">I always fancied one of those dresses that had that has erm possibly three or four inch er fringe that layers of fringe</u>
<u n="293" who="S0679">mm oh yes?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0680">you now those?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0679">somebody made one on one of the Sewing Bees I think didn't they?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes layers of fringe</u>
<u n="297" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0680" trans="overlap">so so it shakes about and you don't have to move much although I used to move quite a lot but you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0680">erm yes and and then what else do you remember? do you remember my camel and green?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="302" who="S0680">now</u>
<u n="303" who="S0679" trans="overlap">more a day dress wasn't it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0680">yes camel and green was camel and green was erm one of mother's creations thinking of erm er challenges for alterations <pause dur="short"/> I think I think the camel started off was going to be a pair of camel trousers</u>
<u n="305" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0680">for me</u>
<u n="307" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0680">because they were the thing at the time</u>
<u n="309" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0680">er cos this would have been er when did I go to college? this would have been late sixties erm and it was if of the era of the two-tone</u>
<u n="311" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="312" who="S0680">er so I thought I'd have this winter erm camel trousers but I don't know they didn't seem to be right so mum took them apart I mean she'd made them sort of very well but they just didn't seem to look right on me</u>
<u n="313" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="314" who="S0680">erm she'd fitted them you know when once they were</u>
<u n="315" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you did have your</u>
<u n="316" who="S0680">fitted</u>
<u n="317" who="S0679" trans="overlap">pantomime horse trousers didn't you later on?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well this is it yes they were they were corduroy trousers that looked like <vocal desc="laugh"/> the back of a pantomime horse even though I wasn't quite that broad across the <unclear>beam</unclear> anyway er mum</u>
<u n="319" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I think that was part of the problem actually</u>
<u n="320" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="321" who="S0679">wasn't it?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0680">yes mum er we had this pair of trousers and they must have been reasonably straight trousers er and mum made this panelled dress for me it was military-style and it had bottle green <trunc>s</trunc> long sleeves in fine wool erm er quite a fitted sleeve and it had a a yoke that was erm that had two points down along the front</u>
<u n="323" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0680">so it looked kind of a bit like a back of a military jacket front and back</u>
<u n="325" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0680">so that was a bottle green and then the rest of it was these trousers so where the point of the bodice came the yoke came there was a an over-sewn seam down each side and and at the back which also did the fitting for the front</u>
<u n="327" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0680">because you only needed narrow panels</u>
<u n="329" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0680">and because it was a shorter dress you could get it out of the trouser length</u>
<u n="331" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0680">erm so that was my camel and green and I wore it for my college interview</u>
<u n="333" who="S0679">oh and very appropriate for a</u>
<u n="334" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="335" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><unclear/> interview</u>
<u n="336" who="S0680">and erm as I say erm I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not so long back mentioned the camel and green cos you know as a creation it had a long zip down the back</u>
<u n="337" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0680">that was one of mum's things and then I had erm there was that very nice it was a long dress was it? I think it was a long dress originally the one in the little pattern that your work bag your er sewing bag is lined in</u>
<u n="339" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="340" who="S0680">that was a pretty one but</u>
<u n="341" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well we all had those long skirts didn't we?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes well this was a dress with a erm a square sort of piece and it had not lace round it</u>
<u n="343" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0680" trans="overlap">a square erm bit on the front erm yoke sort of erm a square thing and slightly puffed sleeves and long sleeves erm cuffs long cuffs long sleeves and it had grandma's lace round it</u>
<u n="345" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="346" who="S0680" trans="overlap">that lace was nanny <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s lace just a tiny bit let in cos it was the same colour as that was a Laura Ashley-type fabric</u>
<u n="347" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0680">little showery things and then mum shortened that for me I think</u>
<u n="349" who="S0679">I had a long skirt that eventually got shortened</u>
<u n="350" who="S0680">mm but</u>
<u n="351" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I I'm I I'm I'm wearing on the er driving test <trunc>photogra</trunc></u>
<u n="352" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah oh right</u>
<u n="353" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you know when I got back when I passed my</u>
<u n="354" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0679">driving test in nine seventy-nine</u>
<u n="356" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="357" who="S0679">so it would have been you know a few years later then</u>
<u n="358" who="S0680">yes and mum made lots of different skirts <unclear/> kilt erm you know just plain A-line and <unclear/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I had to wear</u>
<u n="360" who="S0680" trans="overlap">all sorts</u>
<u n="361" who="S0679">your red skirt to a party I went to when I was about thirteen</u>
<u n="362" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="363" who="S0679"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s party</u>
<u n="364" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0679">at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0680">what red skirt?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0679" trans="overlap">we had to go out and buy a jumper cos I didn't have anything at all suitable to go going to</u>
<u n="368" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="369" who="S0679">a party in</u>
<u n="370" who="S0680">mm what red skirt was that? I can't <trunc>reme</trunc></u>
<u n="371" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I don't remember it other than that</u>
<u n="372" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="373" who="S0679">but it wasn't my skirt so you</u>
<u n="374" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="375" who="S0679">it must have been</u>
<u n="376" who="S0680">I don't remember having a red skirt</u>
<u n="377" who="S0679" trans="overlap">obviously it was very short on you and I was a bit shorter because I was younger</u>
<u n="378" who="S0680">yes can't remember what one that was now</u>
<u n="379" who="S0679">can't remember if it had buttons on or not we had those both had blue and red dresses</u>
<u n="380" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0679">with erm buttons on because yours</u>
<u n="382" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes that's right</u>
<u n="383" who="S0679" trans="overlap">was quite subtle and mine was rather bright</u>
<u n="384" who="S0680">yes yes</u>
<u n="385" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I'm not sure I really liked it but erm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I think mine was a slightly darker navy</u>
<u n="387" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0680">oh and I remember in earlier days well earlier days probably sixty-seven erm <pause dur="short"/> in the era of erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>hip</trunc>hipster skirts I had that sort of wasn't purple it was more a dark violet coloured one with a wide belt and it <trunc>ha</trunc> it had father's army ex-army <trunc>sur</trunc> you know doing his military service wartime brass belt that I had</u>
<u n="389" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="390" who="S0680">on the front and that was very short</u>
<u n="391" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0680">and it was before tights came in</u>
<u n="393" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="394" who="S0680">so you wore stockings</u>
<u n="395" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0680">so and you had erm they were like erm erm lacy sort of openwork erm creamy colour was very popular</u>
<u n="397" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0680">and you had the creamy colour</u>
<u n="399" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0680">stockings and the shorter skirt which took some manoeuvring and then I had a creamy <trunc>t</trunc> colour sort of slightly openwork jumper I used to wear</u>
<u n="401" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0680">tucked in</u>
<u n="403" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0680">you know and then and it was the era of the pale lipstick as well the mascara and the pale lipstick and the backcombed hair yes I remember wearing that the trouble is some of these little skirts and I thought oh that's quite nice material and I couldn't get into them some years later and I unpicked them cos I thought they might nice material</u>
<u n="405" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0680" trans="overlap">make a cushion or something</u>
<u n="407" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="408" who="S0680">which I didn't which is a shame because erm you know these things come round again and there was very some very nice erm like <trunc>pl</trunc></u>
<u n="409" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you still might not fit into them</u>
<u n="410" who="S0680">I know very nice plaid er erm not plaid check material well there were some plaid we used to have some quite bright plaid ones erm and there was a bluey yellowy one and we used to get or mum used to help knit as well we used to knit a matching <trunc>jum</trunc> a jumper</u>
<u n="411" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="412" who="S0680">that knitted matches</u>
<u n="413" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="414" who="S0680">the the knitted erm with some sort of little erm <pause dur="short"/> detail on it that erm went with one of the colours so it was</u>
<u n="415" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0680">like an outfit</u>
<u n="417" who="S0679">I think you're wearing one of those but <trunc>pl</trunc> <trunc>br</trunc> quite bright plaid skirts on one of the first photographs we were in colour in</u>
<u n="418" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="419" who="S0679">in the garden</u>
<u n="420" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="421" who="S0679">because all the colours came out quite strange in those days on</u>
<u n="422" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="423" who="S0679">photographs</u>
<u n="424" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="425" who="S0679">but I think from when they were made not just</u>
<u n="426" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="427" who="S0679">gone off <trunc>af</trunc>afterwards</u>
<u n="428" who="S0680">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah of course kilts were in fashion cos we used to buy children's kilts when we were kids</u>
<u n="429" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0680"><unclear/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I had a red one from Marks and Spencer's and you had a whitish one didn't you?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0679">er well white background with</u>
<u n="434" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0679">colours on</u>
<u n="436" who="S0680">oh yes mine was a navy navy and white</u>
<u n="437" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0680">with a red line through I used to know what names these were but I've forgotten</u>
<u n="439" who="S0679">I don't think I knew that they had names in those days</u>
<u n="440" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="441" who="S0679">cos I had mine when I was little</u>
<u n="442" who="S0680">mm but well I used to have a kilt when I was little as well but in fact I have the pin <vocal desc="laugh"/> I still have the pin that I put in my</u>
<u n="443" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0680">older ones but er yes but er still</u>
<u n="445" who="S0679">so you didn't have a dress erm a sixties dress like those ones that they were calling colour block dresses?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0680">colour block dress</u>
<u n="447" who="S0679">it looked like Mondrian dresses</u>
<u n="448" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah the Mondrian ones no I didn't have one of those I didn't want one of those cos they were everywhere</u>
<u n="449" who="S0679">oh were they?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0680">yeah erm I well <trunc>th</trunc>there used to be a lot of black and white dresses <pause dur="short"/> and black and white was a thing and there was and there were also those ones with colour in I think <trunc>sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had one I remember erm don't remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> having one but I kind of missed out on those black and white</u>
<u n="451" who="S0679">that would be really more a Mondrian wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0680">with the colour in yes</u>
<u n="453" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0680">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had some shoes that were black and white <pause dur="short"/> two-tone you know?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0679">yeah two-tone</u>
<u n="456" who="S0680">erm that was a music style as well two-tone</u>
<u n="457" who="S0679">I think that's rather different rather later</u>
<u n="458" who="S0680">yes but it no it erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was it was early</u>
<u n="459" who="S0679"><unclear/> always think about this Midlands bands</u>
<u n="460" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes those Midlands bands but like erm they're very much like erm ska</u>
<u n="461" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0680">type of music <pause dur="short"/> but er and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and er not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="464" who="S0680">had er Mary Quant hairstyles they cos they were always going up to London buying oh I've forgotten what they're called those boots that had sort of holes rouleau loops and holes in them</u>
<u n="465" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="466" who="S0680" trans="overlap">in <unclear/> all had those</u>
<u n="467" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="468" who="S0680">and and even had some shoes made at was it Anello and Davide?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0679">really?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0680">yeah cos</u>
<u n="471" who="S0679" trans="overlap">gosh that was quite a posh thing to do to have</u>
<u n="472" who="S0680" trans="overlap">it is</u>
<u n="473" who="S0679" trans="overlap">shoes made</u>
<u n="474" who="S0680">it was quite posh they had erm because they were like erm I don't know whether they were like quite like granny shoes they were sort of plain ones with buttons with a strap and button over</u>
<u n="475" who="S0679">oh right are they called Mary Janes now those ones?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0680">er</u>
<u n="477" who="S0679">with a little</u>
<u n="478" who="S0680">they had a little heel they were much more delicate a bit like more like my <unclear>Minnie Moochers</unclear></u>
<u n="479" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0680">type of shoes erm and then erm they decided they were gonna have their hair cut</u>
<u n="481" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0680">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had got blonde and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had got dark hair and they had one of those off-centre Mary Quant with the sort of the point that's sort of over an eyebrow at a slant and then at the back you get a point down one side short haircuts they're all</u>
<u n="483" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="484" who="S0680">off off off <trunc>a</trunc>asymmetric maybe that's the right word</u>
<u n="485" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0680">and erm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0679">not just wonky you mean?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0680">no they were</u>
<u n="489" who="S0679"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0680">designed like that</u>
<u n="491" who="S0679"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0680">but you have to have a really good cut for it to keep falling in the right place I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had hers going going one way and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had the other <trunc>s</trunc> way</u>
<u n="493" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="494" who="S0680">you know they didn't have identical they had erm a matching <trunc>p</trunc>pair I'd forgotten about that yes as well so they had those I remember that I can't remember I think they had them done in London I can't remember</u>
<u n="495" who="S0679">gosh</u>
<u n="496" who="S0680">but er</u>
<u n="497" who="S0679">I expect it would cost a fortune to go up to London these days and have your hair cut</u>
<u n="498" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0679">it's although I mean perhaps it's no more expensive than having it cut in the <trunc>cen</trunc> in the centre of <anon type="place"/> which could be expensive enough</u>
<u n="500" who="S0680">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mind you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad had an account at Harrods for his suits</u>
<u n="501" who="S0679">really?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0679">so perhaps they were quite used to spending quite a lot because</u>
<u n="504" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0679">I mean I can't imagine mum or dad</u>
<u n="506" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="507" who="S0679">doing that</u>
<u n="508" who="S0680">well if you remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s had two older sisters so she was the young one so her parents were quite old</u>
<u n="509" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0680">comparatively you know</u>
<u n="511" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0680"><trunc>f</trunc>for the time erm there was a bit of a gap between she was the last one cos I remember going on their end-of-year outing as it were</u>
<u n="513" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0680">up to London in in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s erm little well it was a Mini but it was customised with a slopey back erm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0679">that sounds quite tricky being in a</u>
<u n="516" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0679">cut-down Mini</u>
<u n="518" who="S0680"><unclear/> well it's an old Mini you know it's not</u>
<u n="519" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0680" trans="overlap">one of these great tanks</u>
<u n="521" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="522" who="S0680">it was a little Mini</u>
<u n="523" who="S0679">I had a little Mini I know little Minis</u>
<u n="524" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I know yes</u>
<u n="525" who="S0679">there's not a lot of space but</u>
<u n="526" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="527" who="S0679">on that occasion we did manage to get six or seven people in in it</u>
<u n="528" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0679">for reasons that erm <pause dur="short"/> that must have been nineteen</u>
<u n="530" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0679">nineteen ninety because that was on the occasion of dad marrying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was sixty so that</u>
<u n="532" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah must have been yeah anyway we went up to London</u>
<u n="533" who="S0679">sorry I interrupt</u>
<u n="534" who="S0680" trans="overlap">in this in this thing I was gonna say we went up to London in this thing and we parked in the underground car park I can't remember where that was it wasn't Marble Arch I don't think so we were going along and all of a sudden we'd zoomed down this underground car park erm I can't think where it was now and erm we went and had lunch in Harrods cos he was going to order a suit</u>
<u n="535" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0680">and had a look round Harrods</u>
<u n="537" who="S0679">mm I did exactly the same thing in London because I went down to London with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s parents</u>
<u n="538" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="539" who="S0679">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s father worked at <anon type="place"/> cos <anon type="place"/> had offices at <anon type="place"/> so we were</u>
<u n="540" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="541" who="S0679">and that's just off Oxford Street or somewhere like that</u>
<u n="542" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="543" who="S0679">well presumably somewhere in the centre</u>
<u n="544" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well I could have been Park Lane this underground car park</u>
<u n="545" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0680">we were going along and all of a sudden</u>
<u n="547" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0680" trans="overlap">where are we going? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0679">and you're out busy in Oxford Street or Regent Street or something</u>
<u n="550" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="551" who="S0679">and then suddenly you end up in in at underground in a car park on a day when the car park was mostly empty because you know the workers weren't using it</u>
<u n="552" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh it was his works car park?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0679">yeah yes he</u>
<u n="554" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0679">it was a <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0679">where he worked</u>
<u n="558" who="S0680">ah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0679">I guess he must have driven down every day to have access to it</u>
<u n="560" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="561" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stayed in a hotel very near there</u>
<u n="563" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0680">that had an underground car park cos he's he <pause dur="short"/> you know he thought it was like journey to the centre of the earth this</u>
<u n="565" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0680" trans="overlap">thing cos he said I wouldn't have been able to I wouldn't have erm been <vocal desc="laugh"/> you'd have to blindfold me I wouldn't have been able to go down there it was awful</u>
<u n="567" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0680">but he he didn't go very <trunc>oft</trunc> he he decided it wasn't they it was too it cost too much for him to drive down there and pay parking all week so they used to send him on the train but er yes I remember something like that so I suppose if land's at a premium you just have to park your car down</u>
<u n="569" who="S0679">well yes yes</u>
<u n="570" who="S0680">downstairs as it were yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0679">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and well the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s were <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his father anyway on that occasion wanted to go off and see some presumably London football match</u>
<u n="572" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0679">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum went shopping and I went shopping</u>
<u n="574" who="S0680">yes <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="575" who="S0679">I suppose <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother was there somewhere too</u>
<u n="576" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0679">gosh that was a long time ago was it</u>
<u n="578" who="S0680">yes I remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum</u>
<u n="579" who="S0679">I mean they probably don't do the same thing now with parking because otherwise you'd have to go through the congestion charge every day probably wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0680">yeah I suppose so unless was he a government department? have they got</u>
<u n="581" who="S0679">no no no</u>
<u n="582" who="S0680" trans="overlap">some special</u>
<u n="583" who="S0679"><anon type="place"/> he worked for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0680">oh <anon type="place"/> that's right yes</u>
<u n="585" who="S0679">he worked on patents</u>
<u n="586" who="S0680">I don't know</u>
<u n="587" who="S0679">it's er it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother who's er worked for the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0680">right oh <pause dur="short"/> well well there we are</u>
<u n="589" who="S0679">yeah shall we erm have a will if you've got time shall we have a look at the beginning of the Sewing Bee? cos</u>
<u n="590" who="S0680" trans="overlap">we could do</u>
<u n="591" who="S0679">we didn't see all of it yesterday</u>
<u n="592" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0679">shall we <trunc>d</trunc> shall we have a go at doing that now?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0680" trans="overlap">we could do that yes I haven't actually heard back from my friend erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the great sewer who er if she's been watching that programme</u>
<u n="595" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0680">be interesting to hear what she thought about it</u>
<u n="597" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes perhaps it doesn't appeal to sewers I don't know</u>
<u n="598" who="S0680">I don't know</u>
<u n="599" who="S0679">it's quite good spectator sport and I found on the early ones erm they seemed a bit more informative I think it was having that person who was more of a teacher as the other judge</u>
<u n="600" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="601" who="S0679">cos I'm sure I sort of learnt things or thought about things</u>
<u n="602" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0679">whereas I don't really get the same I don't enjoy that new judge the</u>
<u n="604" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0679">female judge</u>
<u n="606" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="607" who="S0679">as much as the other lady</u>
<u n="608" who="S0680">no but the man's quite funny</u>
<u n="609" who="S0679">he he is he is actually coming out to be really quite a character on it</u>
<u n="610" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="611" who="S0679">he seemed a bit erm standoffish in the first series</u>
<u n="612" who="S0680">yeah mind you I mean it is to some extent it is erm depends how much you know about the subject because I I I used to <pause dur="short"/> get quite a little irks about the the Pottery Throw Down</u>
<u n="613" who="S0679">on yes</u>
<u n="614" who="S0680" trans="overlap">and what they were doing</u>
<u n="615" who="S0679">yes yes</u>
<u n="616" who="S0680">I think what are they doing? you know technique-wise <vocal desc="laugh"/> like should er <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know no if you do that it's it's bound to warp</u>
<u n="617" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0680">and things you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> but</u>
<u n="619" who="S0679">mm but all these things with the baking things they're not making it I mean the everybody who is on the Bake Off like the the the the erm not that Crème de la Crème one but the other one</u>
<u n="620" who="S0680">mm ordinary</u>
<u n="621" who="S0679">they can all make cakes well</u>
<u n="622" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="623" who="S0679">it's just if they can make cakes under time pressure</u>
<u n="624" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="625" who="S0679"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when somebody is <trunc>st</trunc> when there's those erm presenters are <trunc>s</trunc> er poking the ingredients</u>
<u n="626" who="S0680">yes and making</u>
<u n="627" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and breaking erm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0680" trans="overlap">breaking them yes</u>
<u n="629" who="S0679">Nadia's</u>
<u n="630" who="S0680">that</u>
<u n="631" who="S0679">cake lid or whatever it is</u>
<u n="632" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes Sue er whatsit</u>
<u n="633" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="634" who="S0680">yes her whatsit's sticking her finger in it</u>
<u n="635" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="636" who="S0680">yes yes</u>
<u n="637" who="S0679">erm and it's kind of it's it's it's it's all very different environment then</u>
<u n="638" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0679">do you remember on the Sewing Bee the erm <pause dur="short"/> the erm the woman who was deaf?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0680">no I've only seen this series</u>
<u n="641" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh have you? oh</u>
<u n="642" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I didn't see any of the well I only saw a brief bit of one the earlier series</u>
<u n="643" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0680">and I can't think what they were doing I think they were making a shopping bag or something I don't know</u>
<u n="645" who="S0679">yes they did they did</u>
<u n="646" who="S0680">I think that was the only one</u>
<u n="647" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0680">I saw</u>
<u n="649" who="S0679">they probably try and make it a bit more difficult and more varied each time</u>
<u n="650" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="651" who="S0679">erm but oh she was quite funny because she would always have a joke with erm er the guy</u>
<u n="652" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="653" who="S0679">judge and she would say oh he makes my heart beat you know he she used to do her</u>
<u n="654" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0679">sign language</u>
<u n="656" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0679">she she was a</u>
<u n="658" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0679" trans="overlap">teaching assistant thing it's like oh he makes and her her <trunc>s</trunc> her <trunc>s</trunc> her sign for him would be doing her</u>
<u n="660" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0679"><vocal desc="gasp"/> making her heart flutter</u>
<u n="662" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0679">which was quite funny because you know that was quite erm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="665" who="S0679">er I mean that it you know that was quite daring with him because he was very standoffish in those days</u>
<u n="666" who="S0680">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="667" who="S0679">whereas now he'd be part of it he says things like oh I'd like to wear that outfit</u>
<u n="668" who="S0680">oh yes those purple trousers</u>
<u n="669" who="S0679" trans="overlap">in yes yes</u>
<u n="670" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0679">anyway <trunc>l</trunc>let's</u>
<u n="672" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0679">let's have a go at looking at this then</u>
<u n="674" who="S0680">yes have a little</u>
<u n="675" who="S0679">okay <event desc="abrupt end"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
