<text id="S8WS">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:37:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2013-07-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2013</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2013_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0456 S0460</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Liverpool L8</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Aquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>welfare, work, police action, immigration, family</topics>
		<activity>Neighbours talking about current affairs.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0456">
				<exactage>44</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/ German</nat>
				<birthplace>Salzkotten</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>German</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scouse</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer (English Language and Literature)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0460">
				<exactage>85</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>80_89</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scouse</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>85</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0456">no because I'm I'm I'm a proper lecturer now actually</u>
<u n="2" who="S0460">oh are you? so you mean you get paid for nothing?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0456">I'm getting paid for nothing yeah I'm <unclear/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0460">you sound like an immigrant <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0456">I'm getting I'm even getting paid when I'm not working because you get</u>
<u n="6" who="S0460" trans="overlap">there's not many places</u>
<u n="7" who="S0456">paid every month</u>
<u n="8" who="S0460">and not many places will do that</u>
<u n="9" who="S0456">yeah well that's the thing that's what I said I would love to be here but the money comes from there and I can't be in two places</u>
<u n="10" who="S0460">even the dole won't give you money if you're not working now you've gotta go looking for a job at least haven't you?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0456">it is a month now that you have to <unclear/> it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="12" who="S0460">they're squeezing us bit by bit aren't they?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0460">got a lot to come yet it's gonna get worse and worse I think</u>
<u n="15" who="S0456">yeah and there's there's no</u>
<u n="16" who="S0460">I feel sorry for the kids of today</u>
<u n="17" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0460">I really do I mean I've got two granddaughters neither of them can get jobs and they only want a day job cos they're still at school you know? oh I don't know what they're gonna do? she's hoping they're going to university and get something there</u>
<u n="19" who="S0456">yes you have to you have to have some sort of qualification I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she she said yeah she wouldn't have liked going to uni and she had friends who went to uni and ended up just working at Boots and she was so glad to have an apprenticeship because you know that's that's some money coming in but also you know you get training you have all the experience</u>
<u n="20" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0456">erm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0460">and it's alright if you can get the apprenticeship <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> usually you've got to know somebody to get an apprenticeship you always have in this town anyhow all the people I know that erm have apprenticeships have either got relations or friends that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0460">that was what I was gonna ask you did you find out anything what happened yesterday?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0456">er</u>
<u n="26" who="S0460" trans="overlap">no?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0456">the police?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0456">yes yes some <unclear/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0460" trans="overlap">I I I thought I said to my well I either said I don't think I'll find out cos I haven't spoken to anybody for ages in this street</u>
<u n="31" who="S0456">no apparently there was an attempt to well an attack on two men and one is seriously injured erm just by the dentist well there's an off-licence near to the dentist on <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="32" who="S0460">well what was the seventeen bobbies here for then yesterday?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0456">well they nabbed somebody well they they think</u>
<u n="34" who="S0460" trans="overlap">I didn't see anybody coming out?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0456">no that that was</u>
<u n="36" who="S0460" trans="overlap">do you know what happened the night before did you hear <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0456" trans="overlap">that was the night before I didn't I thought last night was something <unclear>else</unclear>?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0460" trans="overlap">no yesterday afternoon</u>
<u n="39" who="S0456">in the afternoon?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0460">all afternoon they were there didn't you see them? the car the street was full of cars</u>
<u n="41" who="S0456">yeah was that yesterday afternoon? I was in the house</u>
<u n="42" who="S0460">I looked out the window I got up to look out the window seen all the cars and thought what's happening? and there was a line of bobbies queued up at the top you know by</u>
<u n="43" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0460">the <anon type="place"/>? all in civvies with police on the back so they were drug squads weren't they? <unclear>the next thing</unclear> the gate opens and whizz and the cars are going in and there were seven of them went in that way</u>
<u n="45" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0460">and the rest got out of cars here and they all went in the front door there was all cars there</u>
<u n="47" who="S0456">well I thought that was the one they'd tried to get in that night because I I went to bed really late <unclear/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0460" trans="overlap">well the one they tried to get in and that night they they got in because I they woke me up at half past four and I looked out the window and there was a big like er minibus type police car</u>
<u n="49" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0460">you know the yellow and blue?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0460">and I thought it was er paramedics at first cos all the doors were open</u>
<u n="53" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0460">anyhow when I seen three fellas coming out I thought they're not paramedics they're bobbies them and they come out and got in a car</u>
<u n="55" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0460">and just after that the helicopter came didn't it?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0460">yeah now I went out at half past six yesterday morning to a car boot sale a car pulled in just up there on the corner pulled into our street and stayed there while I come out the house got in the car and left <unclear/> and that was still there when I got to the bottom and when I got to the bottom there was another cop car coming in in the street so something serious must have happened but I never seen nothing coming out of that house I watched them for ages</u>
<u n="59" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0460">cos I'm a nosy <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0456" trans="overlap">you know I did I did at half one and I heard because</u>
<u n="62" who="S0460">no this was not <unclear/> I'm talking about yesterday afternoon I watched it</u>
<u n="63" who="S0456" trans="overlap">so I I just wondered whether yesterday afternoon they they just came back because they they didn't have any success earlier?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0460" trans="overlap">well altogether I counted there were seventeen went into that house and what are they doing? a <unclear>muggy</unclear> little house like that</u>
<u n="65" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0460">I don't know if they all fitted in to tell you the truth</u>
<u n="67" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0460">and I watched them for ages and ages cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said what was you doing? I said I've missed everything coming fucking down here</u>
<u n="69" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0456">yesterday afternoon <unclear/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0460">well they were there until about half past four five o'clock they were in the area at least four a clear four hours didn't you see a lot of cars there? <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="72" who="S0456" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0460">they all come out and like I say most of them were in civvies</u>
<u n="74" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0460">with the police jackets on you know like the black jackets?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0460">and they all had belts with all the gear on</u>
<u n="78" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0460">and er I seen them taking this big bag like that in</u>
<u n="80" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0460">but the only thing they brought out was a bag like that and I thought it can't be drugs cos when they raided</u>
<u n="82" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0460">that house over there</u>
<u n="84" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0460">that <unclear/> was full of drugs wasn't it?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0460">so it couldn't have been drugs and then what happened what got me <vocal desc="laugh"/> just after these all had gone she come out in her pyjamas talking to everybody and I thought the lazy cow must have been in her pyjamas all that while that they were <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I don't know what happens with that house and I've only ever seen a girl coming out of it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0456">no I didn't well that's that's one of the reasons why I called in someone told me yesterday who's gonna move opposite</u>
<u n="89" who="S0460">who?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0456">there there's some people who were evicted from lower down the street</u>
<u n="91" who="S0460">oh that's all we need someone</u>
<u n="92" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="93" who="S0460">being evicted they must have been evicted</u>
<u n="94" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0460">for a reason</u>
<u n="96" who="S0456" trans="overlap">and they they wanted you know not is it next door two doors down that is owned by by somebody and they wanted to move in there and he said no sod it you're not gonna come into my house not here but they wanted to move back into the street because they <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0460" trans="overlap"><unclear/> because next door's empty</u>
<u n="98" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0460">the house next door is empty and the house next door to that I don't know what's happened to the two <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lads but</u>
<u n="100" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0460">I believe the police were there the other week so</u>
<u n="102" who="S0456">yeah they they</u>
<u n="103" who="S0460" trans="overlap">they're always</u>
<u n="104" who="S0456">they wanted to get into one of those houses and the landlord said no I know who you are I'm not gonna have you</u>
<u n="105" who="S0460">well this one it couldn't be this one because it belongs to a mutual and they've been here every day</u>
<u n="106" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0460">putting plywoods and that</u>
<u n="108" who="S0456" trans="overlap">it's none of those houses</u>
<u n="109" who="S0460">it's the one next door is empty</u>
<u n="110" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0460">that was the one though <unclear/> wanted to buy when it was empty <unclear/> he offered him fifteen thousand no ten thousand for it and they wouldn't sell it it fell to rack and ruin and there's nobody's hardly ever been in there since yeah the guy here from Australia living in there he was fixing it up</u>
<u n="112" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0460">all he did was put wallpaper up and paint it and that was it</u>
<u n="114" who="S0456">well that was a bit like what happened there cos always so yes they have been evicted and the the other ones they only moved out a week ago so suddenly this is taken and I remember before they moved in there were at least a handful of people and they had viewings and nobody wanted to move in until they moved in</u>
<u n="115" who="S0460">that one they there</u>
<u n="116" who="S0456">yeah next to <unclear/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0460" trans="overlap"><unclear/> what do you call her one is</u>
<u n="118" who="S0456">right</u>
<u n="119" who="S0460">and then the</u>
<u n="120" who="S0456"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0460">one of them was <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0456">oh yeah no those were those were the tenants</u>
<u n="123" who="S0460">what like a priest?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0460">no I don't mean the I mean <trunc>the</trunc>them that lived there</u>
<u n="126" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0456">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0460" trans="overlap">he had trainers on though all the while</u>
<u n="130" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0460">he's got the right shoes with being a priest anyhow</u>
<u n="133" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0460">and they have they just moved out?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0456">they moved out just last week</u>
<u n="136" who="S0460" trans="overlap">it was up for sale for ages</u>
<u n="137" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0460">and then the sign went up last week was it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0460">to er let?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0456">no it's let</u>
<u n="142" who="S0460">yeah so that means someone's got it doesn't it?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0456">yes and the end them two the it's the people who got evicted lower down the street and they have a pit bull terrier that has attacked dogs and people and he he's got a speedboat but doesn't do a day's work</u>
<u n="144" who="S0460">yeah once you get someone who's been evicted they they won't like that her next door</u>
<u n="145" who="S0456">no no this is we we're all <trunc>u</trunc>up in arms I I er I I <unclear>sensed</unclear> well I heard but I still have to know <unclear/> no way and I've sent an email to the agents erm because if I want to I can sound very much like a lawyer</u>
<u n="146" who="S0460">can you?</u>
<u n="147" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0460">good on you let's hope you do then</u>
<u n="149" who="S0456">and I I said you know</u>
<u n="150" who="S0460" trans="overlap">how can you put people in who's been evicted you know they're not gonna pay the rent?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0456" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rang them because I wanted to ring and she rang them and all they've done was a credit check <pause dur="short"/> so much for references and I said hang on aren't there laws that you know if you've got neighbours <unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0460" trans="overlap"><unclear/> on private landlords is</u>
<u n="153" who="S0456">well yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0460"><unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0456">so I I sent an email to my councillor one of my three councillors as well saying what what can be done?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0460">you sent one to each one of them not just the one?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0456">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always owes me a favour because I I was the voice that made him being the candidate and then becoming a councillor</u>
<u n="158" who="S0460">oh he should do it <unclear/> off <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and go around and smash all the windows in the back</u>
<u n="159" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0460">it's taken them weeks to put them in cos he's got that</u>
<u n="161" who="S0456" trans="overlap">well they the they had erm the bathroom window is already falling apart because he's done nothing to it <unclear/> frames</u>
<u n="162" who="S0460" trans="overlap">now oh no I've <trunc>they</trunc>they've just moved in there and there hasn't been they just paint everywhere and that's it</u>
<u n="163" who="S0456">yeah and it's no wonder nobody wants to move in because it's it's it's it's a horrid place I mean the people there they were not very demanding of stuff they kept themselves to themselves</u>
<u n="164" who="S0460">oh yeah I mean</u>
<u n="165" who="S0456" trans="overlap">it's like</u>
<u n="166" who="S0460">that was fair enough I mean</u>
<u n="167" who="S0456">apart from the youngsters in the morning but you know that was</u>
<u n="168" who="S0460">I never seen them</u>
<u n="169" who="S0456">but they weren't you know they're not exactly demanding customers and if they think it's not good enough for them you can imagine what kind of people think yeah you either <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0460" trans="overlap">ever since the <trunc>c</trunc> them that first lived there really</u>
<u n="171" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0460">or maybe no she lives around the corner <pause dur="short"/> that house has been like that all the while there's something wrong wrong with her or something you know?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0456">you called her jinx and that was ten years ago</u>
<u n="174" who="S0460">the fella who moved in there that young lad he was dealing in drugs so</u>
<u n="175" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0460">well he was a dealer so but you couldn't prove nothing on him like that and they had all kinds of cars parked everywhere here so</u>
<u n="177" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0460">so <unclear>frigging hell</unclear> I hope they don't come here with a frigging dog like that I might have to start carrying a thingy <pause dur="short"/> stanley knife <pause dur="short"/> let one of them come near me and that wouldn't happen no messing I wouldn't let them bite me</u>
<u n="179" who="S0456" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> contact them and say you're not happy well as I said I I'll I'll ask <unclear/> because even even if I'm not here obviously I don't want something like that next door to an empty house or even if I find someone <unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0460" trans="overlap">well the first thing he's gonna do is rob everybody isn't he? if he's got a rottweiler like gotta keep it in the luxury it's used to haven't you? you can't feed it people's legs all the while like can you?</u>
<u n="181" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0456">yeah I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's the thing is he paid fifty-eight grand for for a piece of shite as it is</u>
<u n="184" who="S0460">who?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0456" trans="overlap">just the owner</u>
<u n="186" who="S0460">is that how much he paid for it fifty-eight?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0456" trans="overlap">and he wants seventy-four now so he doesn't make a loss seventy</u>
<u n="188" who="S0460">do you know how much they offered me for this two years ago? seventy-five</u>
<u n="189" who="S0456">yeah but this one's in good nick</u>
<u n="190" who="S0460">that's what I mean and it's got a bathroom on the back</u>
<u n="191" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0460">and that's all they are <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna move but I thought nah what's the point?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0456">yeah it's</u>
<u n="194" who="S0460" trans="overlap">too late in life to move really well</u>
<u n="195" who="S0456">but that's that's I think it's he he can ask for that if if you put some money in but you know it's erm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0460">christ it must be it must be a good house then if it's if it's seventy-four it's only a thousand pound less than this</u>
<u n="197" who="S0456" trans="overlap">well he he's in London where seventy-five is nothing for a property yeah you're probably</u>
<u n="198" who="S0460" trans="overlap">ah you pay that for a shed there</u>
<u n="199" who="S0456">yeah exactly but you know this is this is <unclear>a late</unclear></u>
<u n="200" who="S0460">yeah yeah you're right there but I mean I I thought mine was alright you know with having a bathroom at the back and three bedrooms and I thought well er I did <unclear/> gonna put it up for but I thought nah not worth it</u>
<u n="201" who="S0456">yeah yeah he bought the in what two thousand and seven or eight <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0460" trans="overlap">that that's right it was in <anon type="place"/> street yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0460">cos that fella one of them fellas has been in for ages <unclear/> and he put all them fancy windows in and all that you know? these big statue things you know what they all have like and lions and things like that <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but erm this one here is on and off empty the woman that was there for ages and I hardly ever seen her I mean I've never heard her</u>
<u n="205" who="S0456">okay</u>
<u n="206" who="S0460">and then one day she said hello to me and said my name and I said how do you know my frigging name?</u>
<u n="207" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0460">anyhow I started talking to her after that and then when once when I went out she said I'm moving you know and I said oh why? she said oh I'm getting harassed by everybody and I thought well when the window cleaner came I told him and he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was one of them that was harassed and that she owed me for three frigging weeks</u>
<u n="209" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0460">is what he'd said so she must have been with the rent and all so</u>
<u n="211" who="S0456">but that's the thing yeah if you</u>
<u n="212" who="S0460" trans="overlap">cos now the er they give it to you now don't they the rent? instead of paying it straight to the landlord you know if you're on the social like</u>
<u n="213" who="S0456">yeah but it's but you only get three-quarters because of the rent is yeah I looked at the rent size of that for a similar house six hundred a week</u>
<u n="214" who="S0460">where is this?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0456">it's it's also a terraced house I don't know where it was</u>
<u n="216" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0456">five hundred and eighty per month er not a week a month but it was the same setup two two bedrooms reception and bath</u>
<u n="218" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah and where was this here?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0456">it wasn't this one but it must have been</u>
<u n="220" who="S0460" trans="overlap">no I mean around here?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0456">somewhere in Liverpool yeah but it didn't the photo looked like <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0460" trans="overlap">well that's about average innit around you know excepting the the the <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah but it's five hundred six hundred a month christ</u>
<u n="224" who="S0460">how do you pay that when you're on the dole? or you mind you they pay it don't they? oh no they they're stopping that an all aren't they?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="226" who="S0460">I tell you what they won't let you live here</u>
<u n="227" who="S0456">or anywhere get on a boat</u>
<u n="228" who="S0460">now they're all coming here what would I wanna go there for they're all coming here aren't they?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0456">no no no that's what I mean get on a boat and just be on a canal or something</u>
<u n="230" who="S0460">oh I've gotta er a relation who's on the canal a long boat as they call them</u>
<u n="231" who="S0456">but as <unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0460" trans="overlap">a long boat or a narrow boat they call them</u>
<u n="233" who="S0456">narrow boat</u>
<u n="234" who="S0460">narrow boat he bought it he's a retired fireman he was married to my sister but she died he's married again now and he's got he comes up here to Liverpool a long boat he bought her here he got it made here made to measure <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went on it for a week and went down the bleeding canals it's great it's lovely if you ever want a quiet day go on a canal boat and it's really soothing you know what I mean? all the people wave to you as you're going up and down their garden you know? and like I say it's dead quiet <unclear>fucking</unclear> watching the little ducks and</u>
<u n="235" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0460">swimming in front of the frigging boat thinking it's gonna batter them like but it was good yeah I had a go at driving <unclear/> I'd be a sailor</u>
<u n="237" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0456"><unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0460">in the canteen</u>
<u n="240" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0456">yeah <unclear/> and he said it was great for us but obviously you know their child then there was I think seven or eight and she must have been bored out of her wits because probably much to do it's perfect for that and it's like ah relax just have another pint</u>
<u n="242" who="S0460">yeah it's alright if you've got plenty of money but <unclear/> go where you like <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0456">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0460">blinking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> son's moving soon to er South Africa</u>
<u n="245" who="S0456">you'll be an international family won't you? Australia South Africa</u>
<u n="246" who="S0460">I've said he's in Bahrain now he's been there nearly four years <pause dur="short"/> he works for the immigration you know? and er after four years they get moved</u>
<u n="247" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0460">well three years but you can stay an extra year and er that's where he's going South Africa oh what's the name of the town? it's next to the</u>
<u n="249" who="S0456">not Johannesburg?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0460">no next to next to it the second biggest town in</u>
<u n="251" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0460">I can't think of the name of it now and yeah that's where he's going I said that's the worse murder capital of the world you know South Africa he said I know he said but we've got we've got guards with us when we go anywhere we have a chauffeur with a guard and you know?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0456">bulletproof <unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0460" trans="overlap">and they're in a compound as well so</u>
<u n="255" who="S0456">still mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0460">they have to be in this place where he is Bahrain's the same they're in a compound they have guards on the like you know?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0460">but they've erm got their own pool their own maid and all paid for by the state like of course you know? so he'll be coming coming to England for erm a month</u>
<u n="259" who="S0456">see a bit of rain</u>
<u n="260" who="S0460">no two months they're coming for he's coming for a month he's got two kids now two little girls there's one of them there and erm he's gotta go for some more training in a month but he's gotta go to London so he's gonna live with my daughter in Weymouth you know for the month</u>
<u n="261" who="S0456" trans="overlap">and then he can just go by train</u>
<u n="262" who="S0460" trans="overlap">he can commute from there yeah it's a good still a good way but</u>
<u n="263" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0460">he can commute from there and er he's gonna stay there for the week and come home to Weymouth for the weekend you know? well he goes back like because he's got the kids with him and her like and she's gotta stay another month then so if she can go for training cos she used to be in the</u>
<u n="265" who="S0456" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="266" who="S0460">so she got the kids you know? she just stayed at home to mind the kids well one of them's three now no no nearly four so so that's what they're gonna do <pause dur="short"/> er go go there do this training go back and she'll start work again then so</u>
<u n="267" who="S0456">yeah well but yeah that's that's what it is it's having a job isn't it? you know this is why I'm in Finland because</u>
<u n="268" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah I have got relations in <unclear/> erm be South Africa next <unclear>only yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="269" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0460">and all over this er this country <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0456">it must be nice erm for all Christmas cards</u>
<u n="272" who="S0460" trans="overlap">eh?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0456">all the all the Christmas cards and the postcards</u>
<u n="274" who="S0460">yeah ah well one thing about them being in that thing you don't have to pay for the <trunc>p</trunc> it's the BPO</u>
<u n="275" who="S0456">oh <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah British Forces post office you know so every time I go there they say you have to pay? I said no</u>
<u n="277" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0460">so you can send parcels and everything you know so it's good</u>
<u n="279" who="S0456">parcels of Marmite</u>
<u n="280" who="S0460">I don't know how they'll go on in there <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> he's made up with it he used to be an immigration officer at first in Heathrow and then he wanted to move up so</u>
<u n="281" who="S0456">I've got a friend and he's he's an immigration officer</u>
<u n="282" who="S0460">is he?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0456">well yeah he is it is that he's not he's a bit cagey about what he is doing but <unclear/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah he's the same but he doesn't do immigration now he he he deals with the erm when they come up with forged passports and things like that you know and they wanna get to England and all this lark</u>
<u n="285" who="S0456" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0460">and he just goes no</u>
<u n="287" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0460">I said you're being brought up right haven't you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yes no no that's the thing is my friend yeah he's he can tell you about passports</u>
<u n="290" who="S0460">yeah yeah he's the same I think so that's what he must do and like I say he never talks well I haven't seen him</u>
<u n="291" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0460">since he left there I haven't seen the grandkids since well since they were born and they're four now one of them</u>
<u n="293" who="S0456">crikey</u>
<u n="294" who="S0460">so so I'm gonna try and get down and see them when they're here it's er September I think he said I'll go down to my daughter and cos it's her brother you know my daughter's brother <pause dur="short"/> no it's my daughter's not her brother it's her son innit? he's my grandson</u>
<u n="295" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yes I just thought otherwise it would have been</u>
<u n="296" who="S0460" trans="overlap">he's my grandson and the kids are my great granddaughters what am I talking about? I've got that frigging many of them</u>
<u n="297" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0460">they're coming out the woodwork they'll all be emigrating soon</u>
<u n="299" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0456">er it's going round and round and round I mean that's the thing my mum comes up to Finland next month er just for a week</u>
<u n="302" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0456">but you know she's retired now she's at er it it seems to be weird to be retired retired when you're in your mid-sixties but yeah she's worked for forty-eight years because she started when she was sixteen six</u>
<u n="304" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah I started when I was fourteen work</u>
<u n="305" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah and the same</u>
<u n="306" who="S0460" trans="overlap">I was telling the kids I said you've got it made then I said I used to work everybody worked forty-eight hours</u>
<u n="307" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0460">not forty and thirty-five forty-eight you had to work I worked in the shop at first and I had to work Saturday as well but you got a half a day off on the week and it was a Wednesday then you had to work forty-eight hours though I said there was no cars or nothing to take you to work you either got on your bike or walked or er you could either pay for the tram and you'd get on that or the back of a wagon but erm so they don't know what they've what they've got <unclear/> they're whinging about working so many hours and and the jobs they've got now are nothing to what most of them are just sitting in offices or sitting in a chair <unclear/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0456" trans="overlap">not making anything</u>
<u n="310" who="S0460">no</u>
<u n="311" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0460">I mean I worked in bloody Dunlop's and it was rough in there I worked in Leyland's and that was hard <pause dur="short"/> that's a good job I mean my my my son's got going <pause dur="short"/> jaguar Land Rover</u>
<u n="313" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0460">he he went on er Taekwondo a few weeks ago they leant him <unclear/> you know to go</u>
<u n="315" who="S0456">nice</u>
<u n="316" who="S0460" trans="overlap">for the weekend didn't have to put no petrol in an all it was full up when he got it he gave me a go in it frigging I thought we were gonna take off</u>
<u n="317" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0460">it didn't half go</u>
<u n="319" who="S0456">yes they look they look <unclear/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0460" trans="overlap">so so I liked that I I <unclear/> taxi you know what I mean? it's like getting into a frigging bus what did he have last week? he went last week to another place and they leant him er a Range Rover</u>
<u n="321" who="S0456">yeah even bigger</u>
<u n="322" who="S0460">oh it doesn't look as big as the <unclear/> like but it wasn't as posh but it was it was white an all-white Range Rover it was lovely he came here dropped stuff off here and he was he was only here a fortnight ago he had to go where way down to somewhere down the south right down south it took him three and a half hours to get there then you know so and er he went in that and the same thing they paid for the petrol so he said they're alright like at Fords if you've asked them you know?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0460">you got something like that like they're off next week for three weeks Fords shutdown</u>
<u n="325" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah summer break</u>
<u n="326" who="S0460">yeah they shut down as they call it</u>
<u n="327" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0460">they've always had that</u>
<u n="329" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah all the car manufacturers</u>
<u n="330" who="S0460">I <unclear/> when they built Fords</u>
<u n="331" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0460">that was empty ground for years and years and they were gonna build a car factory there and it took them about twenty years to build it good job <unclear/> in the end like innit? I mean all them fellas he took on how long have you been abroad now?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0456"><trunc>we</trunc>well since last summer one year</u>
<u n="334" who="S0460">last summer yeah and he must have been working then cos he's been there now just over two years now</u>
<u n="335" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0460">well he's on the books now so they were agency workers for so long <unclear/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0460">you can get rid of agency workers dead easy can't you?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah well every time you hear that you know there's layoffs you know like when it was Honda or or</u>
<u n="340" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0456"><unclear/> whoever and yeah the first lots to go are all the agency workers so they said well if we don't get rid of staff and all the agency workers don't get any</u>
<u n="342" who="S0460">no they just get that's it off you go <pause dur="short"/> yeah they look after them well there so well he seems to get everything when he asks can he lend it like he just tells them he's <unclear/> training to be and they're quite good you know so it's not bad like though when you see the car you think frigging hell I'd never tried one of them you know what I mean? <trunc>whi</trunc>which you wouldn't like you know what I mean? what the cheapest ones twenty-seven and a half grand innit?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0456">well that's about three houses</u>
<u n="344" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0460">he said they can't sell enough of them and they go up to fifty-seven fifty-eight thousand pounds and he said they can't sell enough of them they can't keep up to the demand for where do them Chinese get all this money from? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0456" trans="overlap">well they've probably they've probably get <unclear/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0460" trans="overlap">I thought they were all working in sweatshops <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah all the slaves</u>
<u n="349" who="S0460">picking the paper up this morning about in Ceylon is it where they make tea?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0456">yeah oh yeah the</u>
<u n="351" who="S0460" trans="overlap">did you see it in the paper this morning?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0460">twelve pence an hour</u>
<u n="354" who="S0456">twelve pence an hour</u>
<u n="355" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0460">frigging hell we'll soon be down to them</u>
<u n="357" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0456">well that was that was the the same thing with the last Tory government wasn't it? making things depressing wages so much that they could compete with China</u>
<u n="359" who="S0460">but they did away with the minimum wage didn't they? I mean there was a minimum wage in if you remember I don't know if you remember?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0456" trans="overlap">there wasn't one before Labour <unclear/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0460" trans="overlap">no there was but there was a minimum wage in the catering industry you know the barmen and staff like that?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0460">they had a minimum wage nobody else did and as soon as they got in they took that minimum wage away and said you</u>
<u n="364" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0460">so all the wages dropped in the</u>
<u n="366" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0460">industry and all catering and all that or whatever you call it like and that used to he used to work in them <unclear/> part-time you know and er he used to say <unclear/> seven until eleven I said no it isn't and so I said you you was there sometimes until half past eleven twelve o'clock and you were working for nothing he he wouldn't have it I said <unclear/> you're working nothing because they have to clear up</u>
<u n="368" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0460">that's not counted as being behind a bar you know what I mean? how many people must be doing that in these cafes and restaurants and bars?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah well in the <anon type="place"/> erm you know the pub? they would move you to the front at quarter past ten and they would make sure everybody's out by eleven rather than eleven and then drinking up because they only got paid until eleven</u>
<u n="371" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0456">and they still had to clear up and <unclear/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0460" trans="overlap">course they do I mean if they don't do it someone's gotta be paid to come in and do it the next night</u>
<u n="374" who="S0456">and yeah <trunc>tha</trunc>that's what it is <unclear/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0460" trans="overlap">and a cleaner won't do all that take all the glasses and things away for you</u>
<u n="376" who="S0456">this is why I stopped going</u>
<u n="377" who="S0460" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0456">because I thought it's not like a pub and that's what you're getting you know you're not paying them <unclear/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0460" trans="overlap">it's always been like that</u>
<u n="380" who="S0456">so long as you don't get <unclear/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0460" trans="overlap">it's not just now it's always been like that you know what I mean? cos I've always said about that about my daughter used to work in a pub in erm <anon type="place"/> road do you know where all the</u>
<u n="382" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0460">students are outside?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah yeah the big one?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0456"><anon type="place"/> house</u>
<u n="387" who="S0460">that's it and she worked she used to work in there and I used to say to her they they tell you your hours are seven until eleven I said but they're not <pause dur="short"/> I said who clears up after they've all gone home? and they won't close the bar until they've got to if it's eleven o'clock be closing at eleven you know what I mean though? but I'm too <unclear/> but er but she used to like it you know what I mean? if you like a job you're gonna stick to it like though</u>
<u n="388" who="S0456" trans="overlap">the same at Mcdonald's my girlfriend worked and it was the same yeah she said I couldn't I couldn't even imagine doing it now</u>
<u n="389" who="S0460">no aha ah they've got you now and it's getting worse innit? without a doubt it's getting worse it's like they're always saying about they're always going on and just talking but I don't even listen to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like</u>
<u n="390" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0460">I just have a <unclear/> and they're always saying about er about the wages the way they're paid low now and calling the unions for everything and I feel like ringing them up and saying sometimes and say have a look where all the unions were pretty strong and see what their wages are like I mean go through the car industry for a kick off and see what the wages are like compared to the shops and get buttons in them places I mean that you can't get better wages than Fords I don't think</u>
<u n="392" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0460">no really good wages I mean there's they don't I think it's twelve pound an hour the the fellas who work there I mean I don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is on that yet but he should be now because like I say he was on an agency but they got paid less</u>
<u n="394" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah yeah because obviously the agency got the money</u>
<u n="395" who="S0460">that's right</u>
<u n="396" who="S0456">yeah well then when when they had the big cable factory in er Widnes <unclear/> they were on forty pounds an hour and that was twenty years ago <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0460">and I read about them <unclear/> the RSPCA being on three thousand pound a week and I thought <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0456">yeah you can buy the Range Rover</u>
<u n="399" who="S0460">what was the other one the other day? er they were talking on talking about if this fella they oh they got an IT expert in</u>
<u n="400" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0456">eight hundred pound a day he was on I thought he's only got to work one week a year and that's it he's made isn't he?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0460"><unclear/> eight hundred pound a frigging day jesus christ there's only forty-four thousand pound a day a week like how can you manage</u>
<u n="404" who="S0456" trans="overlap">it's not about as much as a footballer</u>
<u n="405" who="S0460">how can you manage on that? yeah but footballers are few and far between aren't they? they are entertaining and you're paying you know if you don't like it you don't go you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0460">but erm I mean I think they're on too much money myself but cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0456">well yeah that's the thing if if sometimes you get to <unclear/> they had this thing you know one of these all these schools that turn into academies and <unclear/> that are academies</u>
<u n="409" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0456">and they are meant to be non not for profit but funnily enough all these bosses award contracts to their own firms</u>
<u n="411" who="S0460">that's right</u>
<u n="412" who="S0456">and and they then get money paid for really odd work</u>
<u n="413" who="S0460">that's the god innit now money?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0460">wherever you go the god is money</u>
<u n="416" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0460">people don't work because they like the jobs now they they're working cos they need the money you don't hear many people saying oh it's a good job this like I mean there wasn't many good jobs either like but I should imagine it's better working in a shop than a car factory</u>
<u n="418" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="419" who="S0460">I mean the wages are different but I should imagine it's a better type job and when I worked in that Dunlop's <unclear/> like a bleeding tyre when I was coming home from work I used to get on the bus and all you could smell was frigging rubber <pause dur="long"/> no messing there</u>
<u n="420" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0460">I mean what time is it?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0456">it's just after twelve I don't want to detain you for too long</u>
<u n="423" who="S0460">no I've got to go in a minute I've got to go out at erm one o'clock so I've got to get my dinner</u>
<u n="424" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0460">I'd offer you some but I haven't got any</u>
<u n="426" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0460">you'll have to go to the chippy</u>
<u n="428" who="S0456">I I'll just have a sandwich</u>
<u n="429" who="S0460">that's what I'm having a corned beef butty yeah so so I'll have to chase you anyhow</u>
<u n="430" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0460">like I say cos I go and see my mate every week he's got diabetes he lives down by er <pause dur="short"/> the old <anon type="place"/> where it used to be</u>
<u n="432" who="S0456">oh the the <anon type="place"/> buildings?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0460" trans="overlap">you know where they're building all them</u>
<u n="434" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0460">new buildings?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0460">erm <anon type="place"/> place <unclear/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0460">yeah yeah he lives just down there there's a car park there that charges er fifty pence an hour or something and it's always chock-a-block <unclear/> to say oh three pound a day or something and <unclear/> and there's a big old warehouse next to it and they built they're digging into this cellar and it's about ninety foot deep by the looks of it on the main road by a erm Chinese takeaway place</u>
<u n="440" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0460">er warehouses and all</u>
<u n="442" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0460">the supermarket <unclear/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that one yeah I've seen I've seen the hole</u>
<u n="445" who="S0460">yeah well <unclear/> just there and there was about four houses on the main road I said hey I said <unclear/> gonna do it all up aren't they? on the radio this week they're <trunc>ru</trunc>running er a bus service so what do they call they call some area? well it's named after the pub and they've they're running it from there into town because it's getting that busy at this end of Liverpool</u>
<u n="446" who="S0456">oh well that's good well er it's because you've got remember the the old warehouse that was turned into a gallery and they</u>
<u n="447" who="S0460" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="448" who="S0456">went bust</u>
<u n="449" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0456">but next door to it that is like a a pub-cum-bar-cum-something else now</u>
<u n="451" who="S0460">and we've got a big brand new building haven't we by where the old church and they're doing</u>
<u n="452" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0460">the church up as well now so</u>
<u n="454" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0460">and that warehouse it looks like it's gonna get knocked down the way they're</u>
<u n="456" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0460">going to town on it</u>
<u n="458" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0460">it's got all masts on it you know for the</u>
<u n="460" who="S0456">yeah the the mobile phone masts</u>
<u n="461" who="S0460">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0460">and that looks like that's gonna go cos I keep asking is that going? and he said I don't know he said but that cellar's not half going fucking deep</u>
<u n="464" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0460">he said if they're gonna bury <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0456">they dig a bit deeper they'll find old old English kings you know like in</u>
<u n="468" who="S0460">they won't live in Liverpool christ's sake</u>
<u n="469" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0456">I mean I'm not I mean I'm not <unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0460" trans="overlap">around here <unclear/> a few footballers</u>
<u n="472" who="S0456">yeah oh I don't know fishermen maybe</u>
<u n="473" who="S0460">I'll show you my leg</u>
<u n="474" who="S0456">oh christ what have you done?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0460">that's ten times better than what it was last week when I had the operation you see the <unclear/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0460">he said they have to do all the bone there as well <unclear/> he said that you've had that all my life and I was putting this cream on for years and it went all to a scab last week and they gave me antibiotics double strength four a day</u>
<u n="478" who="S0456">ooh christ</u>
<u n="479" who="S0460" trans="overlap">and I finish them tomorrow well that's all dead skin that now you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0460">so it had all big scabs on last week and on there it was in a terrible state <unclear/> eye on now he said if it's not better by tomorrow</u>
<u n="482" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0460">come back so but it looks better to me now oh it was in a terrible state it had a big scab on this morning and I've washed it all off and it looks like it's gone now so it looks like just dead skin to me so it's alright now to what it was oh it looked terrible last week</u>
<u n="484" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0460">and what happens I've caught it on the slide you see there?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0460">I caught it on something like a corner or something I I I knew I'd done something to it <unclear/> it'll be alright</u>
<u n="488" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0460">and it come up and that's what caused that to go like that because they've always said you be careful with your leg he said if anything happens to it he said come here like</u>
<u n="490" who="S0456">scary stuff yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0460"><unclear/> bypass <unclear/> fifteen years ago now I've had that since then since he took that main out on my leg</u>
<u n="492" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0460" trans="overlap">he said that's because you've got water on that as well and it builds up and the blisters come and they burst</u>
<u n="494" who="S0456">so I suppose your footballing days are definitely over</u>
<u n="495" who="S0460" trans="overlap">and he said I could drowned from the inside if I didn't take water tablets yeah so if you ever hear me <unclear/> you know what to do</u>
<u n="496" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0456">oh no</u>
<u n="498" who="S0460">get a pump out</u>
<u n="499" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0460"><unclear/></u>
<u n="501" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0456">don't say that</u>
<u n="503" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
