<text id="S8X7">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:46:16</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0046 S0086</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Injuries, tattoos, friendships</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting in the kitchen</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0046">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Labourer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0086">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cuckfield, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0086">you manned up?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="3" who="S0086">that's harsh man</u>
<u n="4" who="S0041">or <unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0086">what did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0041">hence why I look like shit this morning cos I spent the night and this morning just crying like a girl</u>
<u n="7" who="S0086">ah mate well you did look really em really away with the fairies this morning <pause dur="short"/> but I I had to go to mum so <pause dur="short"/> I had to leave <pause dur="short"/> I was worried about you</u>
<u n="8" who="S0041">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said I know it sounds stupid but I'm sick of having shit thrown at me every single time <pause dur="short"/> whether it's crazy <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or ill dad or stupid divorce or her stealing my savings or having to move job <pause dur="short"/> just I'm sick to death of it <pause dur="short"/> and then in the last minute you think well actually the whole point of this is in my control <pause dur="short"/> hit by a fucking bus <pause dur="short"/> like what is the luck of that? What is the luck of that?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> you think you'd be due a break now wouldn't you really? After all that shit <pause dur="short"/> once you've actually found something that you think now this is my career this is what I want to be doing</u>
<u n="10" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0086">oh mate <pause dur="short"/> well suppose the only thing you can do is take it day by day at this point</u>
<u n="12" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0086">go to the doctors tomorrow get the scan take a view on it <pause dur="short"/> are you just going to go to work in the morning or are you going to take the day off?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0041">I'm going to go to work in the morning because if I take the day off they won't pay me</u>
<u n="15" who="S0086">oh yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0041">nice <pause dur="short"/> so I'm going to go to work in the morning <pause dur="short"/> as soon as I get there I'm going to ring the doctors and I'm going to lie through my back teeth and say oh yeah just me I just need you to write me a letter to say that you're happy for the navy to put me forward for my medical <pause dur="short"/> not going to mention anything about needing to be mentally fit <pause dur="short"/> not going to mention that shit</u>
<u n="17" who="S0086">need to know information and they do not need to know that</u>
<u n="18" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> and if he says well what about the haematoma I'll say oh no no it's fine I've told them about it and as long as I go for my scan today and take my scan results to prove that it's just haematoma it's just a bruise really isn't it? And the fines the just need to okay for me to say yes I'm happy to put her forward for it <pause dur="short"/> and hope that he's daft enough to just do it</u>
<u n="19" who="S0086">to be honest if he's anything like my GP he'll be like who are you? What are you? Yes fine come and get this letter <pause dur="short"/> be like I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he's going to question it cos he sounds like he's not really that bothered <pause dur="short"/> he just was keen to get you out of the doctor's surgery really? He wasn't really engaging with you</u>
<u n="20" who="S0041">no so</u>
<u n="21" who="S0086">yeah well that sounds like a plan <pause dur="short"/> and then leave work at twelve one?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0041">one yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm just going to say to them if you don't want to do it we're going to have a problem cos I'm going to stab it open and you're going to have to deal with it as emergency so your choice</u>
<u n="23" who="S0086">yeah the fork actually turns out yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0041">I will literally use the fork</u>
<u n="25" who="S0086">the fork is actually a viable option <pause dur="short"/> who would have thought last week the fork would have been a viable option</u>
<u n="26" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just going to do it <pause dur="short"/> and I'll tell you what oh my god <pause dur="short"/> the solicitor sent me a letter</u>
<u n="27" who="S0086">national Accident Helpline</u>
<u n="28" who="S0041">well it's Gould Solicitors <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> they're fucking thick as pig shit</u>
<u n="29" who="S0086">oh no</u>
<u n="30" who="S0041">she got the statement wrong the time on it <pause dur="short"/> twelve PM she wrote</u>
<u n="31" who="S0086">Good <pause dur="short"/> wasn't it AM?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0041">yes yes <pause dur="short"/> something else was wrong <pause dur="short"/> I just thought fuck that and ripped it up <pause dur="short"/> sent her an email saying fuck off <pause dur="short"/> if I can't trust you to write a statement you've got no way of representing me not a clue no way <pause dur="short"/> so fuck off</u>
<u n="33" who="S0086">so is that someone that's appointed by National Accident Helpline</u>
<u n="34" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> no way <pause dur="short"/> can't trust them</u>
<u n="35" who="S0086">can you get someone from Tezza?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0041">I'm going to Barr Ellison</u>
<u n="37" who="S0086">okay fine</u>
<u n="38" who="S0041">and they have a <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling me they have an office within the hospital so tomorrow when I'm there I'm gonna go straight to Barr Ellison and do it through them <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> it's just ridiculous that somebody that you don't know that you know just didn't wasn't thinking properly can have so much of an impact <pause dur="short"/> and was sitting here thinking of <pause dur="short"/> you know when you have a problem you always think there is a way round his <pause dur="short"/> there is a way I've just got to find it <pause dur="short"/> and I was sat thinking there isn't one <pause dur="short"/> there's actually nothing I can do</u>
<u n="39" who="S0086"><unclear/> at this point <pause dur="short"/> this and it's all down to the hands of other people <pause dur="short"/> it's just that butterfly effect isn't it? Like if you had if you'd been on an <trunc>eig</trunc> an eight AM shift rather than a ten AM shift you know <pause dur="short"/> if the bus driver had stopped if you'd gone a slightly different route you know and all of those things</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041">if the GP had said keep off your feet</u>
<u n="41" who="S0086">yeah don't go swimming</u>
<u n="42" who="S0041">did I tell you I've got two haematomas</u>
<u n="43" who="S0086">yeah oh well I was there when they said <unclear/> leg <pause dur="short"/> cos actually there's a mark of the bar isn't there? Isn't there like a straight line on your leg? Well that's <pause dur="short"/> it's just mad like how it can have such an effect</u>
<u n="44" who="S0041">yeah just one thing just spirals <pause dur="short"/> I was speaking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was like I can't believe this is what you've got to accept <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe that that's the option <pause dur="short"/> there's got to be a way round it <pause dur="short"/> we've tried everything <pause dur="short"/> her Chris and I were all googling ways to do it I said do you know what if I knew a doctor and I thought <pause dur="short"/> I know every profession through uni <pause dur="short"/> I know lawyers I know opticians I know all sorts I know one of everything <pause dur="short"/> coders stupid computer people <pause dur="short"/> anything <pause dur="short"/> I don't know a doctor <pause dur="short"/> I don't know a surgeon</u>
<u n="45" who="S0086">I don't know a <trunc>d</trunc> do I know a doctor? Not that I could call up <pause dur="short"/> I mean I went on a few dates with a guy a <trunc>fe</trunc> two years ago <pause dur="short"/> don't think that really counts unfortunately</u>
<u n="46" who="S0041">Cos I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know they said six weeks if they cut it open <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that's bullshit <pause dur="short"/> six weeks in a C section cutting half your abdomen open</u>
<u n="47" who="S0086">really</u>
<u n="48" who="S0041">she said I'm telling you know if they cut that open say two inches three inches we're talking a week <pause dur="short"/> if you took the week off work kept your leg up you're talking a week and you'll be good to go</u>
<u n="49" who="S0086">well yeah cos when I had my knee cut open and it was all like that <pause dur="short"/> it probably was about ten days before I could walk on it <pause dur="short"/> and that was twenty stitches so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0041">we're talking six stitches if that</u>
<u n="51" who="S0086">yeah and that's if they do all of it</u>
<u n="52" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0086">it shouldn't be <pause dur="short"/> even if they had to scalpel it open say it's like that big <pause dur="short"/> they only scalpel off a little bit at the top and squeeze it out wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0086">how are they going to get it out are they just going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0041">they literally just scoop it out</u>
<u n="57" who="S0086">scoop what?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0041">okay cos they say they can't needle it because it's congealed <pause dur="short"/> what if they can? Cos there's something really squidgy <pause dur="short"/> there's not all of it congealed <pause dur="short"/> what if they vacuum it out with a syringe get most of it out? <trunc>Se</trunc> my body gets rid of the rest <pause dur="short"/> because as long as it's not this big heavy mass and all that's needed is the pulverised veins in there</u>
<u n="59" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">that's basically do my body's work for it</u>
<u n="61" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think they probably just want to get rid of it all or nothing because I suppose you would run the risk then of it <pause dur="short"/> a you open it so if you then train it could be in a bit of trouble <pause dur="short"/> also it might just fill it with blood again because there's still a pouch so <pause dur="short"/> did you speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about whether he's got em private health insurance?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041">no he's in shit in the divorce thing <pause dur="short"/> I just didn't want to</u>
<u n="63" who="S0086">is that actually is that this week or is it next week?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's this week</u>
<u n="65" who="S0086">this coming  This coming  week</u>
<u n="66" who="S0041" trans="overlap">they've had it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0086">they've had it? How was it?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0041">she was a douche <pause dur="short"/> she didn't even say hi to him</u>
<u n="69" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> had the gumption to say let's have half the divorce now and half the divorce when your invitation money comes through <pause dur="short"/> and she was so badly behaved during the hearing the judge actually said I think you'll find the compensation is in order because of pain and suffering to one person <pause dur="short"/> and quite frankly <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> I don't see any pain of suffering that has come your way the past thirty years <pause dur="short"/> so no we won't be doing that</u>
<u n="71" who="S0086">wow</u>
<u n="72" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0086">she must have really pissed him off <pause dur="short"/> well they must have just seen her for her true colours <pause dur="short"/> she's out there for money she's not upset because she thinks it's her right to have it <pause dur="short"/> means that she does but it's not <pause dur="short"/> she's not entitled to that money just because she happened to be married to him <pause dur="short"/> there's no love there it sounds like</u>
<u n="74" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="75" who="S0086">she's just out for his money</u>
<u n="76" who="S0041">and the whole time both only solicitors are supposed to speak and she was writing post it notes and wittering and whacking them in front of the solicitors face and really showing herself up and my dad just said the judge was paying him more attention than her completely blanking her and my dad didn't say anything</u>
<u n="77" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="78" who="S0041">but just because he must have been so fucked off with the way she was behaving <pause dur="short"/> and I said well if you think about it she's used to dealing with people that aren't as bright as her <pause dur="short"/> so the judge has seen her a billion times over <pause dur="short"/> gold-diggers come every week to him</u>
<u n="79" who="S0086">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="80" who="S0041">spot them a mile off</u>
<u n="81" who="S0086">well he's got to make a judgement call hasn't he? On the very small amount of time that he gets to spend with the people in front of him and the evidence he's got to make a call on who these people are <pause dur="short"/> and as you say he's seen that character a hundred time before so <pause dur="short"/> ah man <pause dur="short"/> well that's that's the start of it though</u>
<u n="82" who="S0086" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> at least my dad's happy</u>
<u n="83" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my dad's quite happy because it's a good judge <pause dur="short"/> basically they go away now <pause dur="short"/> they've got to answer loads of questions <pause dur="short"/> but mum's got to go and be see a consultant about her life expectancy <pause dur="short"/> so in the next hearing she's got to prove her life expectancy <pause dur="short"/> my dad thinks it's three years</u>
<u n="84" who="S0086">oh really?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0041">but we don't know how much of that is lies from her so she's going to have to prove it <pause dur="short"/> because if it's three years there's no way they're just going to order a <trunc>propor</trunc> a proportion of his pension because she'll only be able to claim it for three years and then it's going to go back on to the <unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0086">into the state yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0041">the state yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0086">shit three years though <pause dur="short"/> that's going to be fucking weird if that's the case</u>
<u n="89" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well her mother my grandma only made it to sixty-six and wasn't ill <pause dur="short"/> my mum's sixty this year <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> considering how ill she's been <pause dur="short"/> if it's been truthful <pause dur="short"/> if she's not been messing on <pause dur="short"/> then they reckon it's three years</u>
<u n="90" who="S0086">it's difficult to know with her isn't it?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0041">difficult to know whether she's lying or not yeah <pause dur="short"/> but she'll have to prove it in writing now</u>
<u n="92" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="94" who="S0086">shitting hell <pause dur="short"/> you're family eh</u>
<u n="95" who="S0041">fucking nutters aren't they? The lot of them</u>
<u n="96" who="S0086">but the thing is it's for you like there's no sort of relief <pause dur="short"/> there's no let up <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously you've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> which is quite nice but she's obviously been unwell as well and you don't want to burden her with your problems <pause dur="short"/> even though I know she would want you to <pause dur="short"/> to go to her because you don't have mum and dad at the moment</u>
<u n="97" who="S0041">she wants me to move back in with her</u>
<u n="98" who="S0086">does she?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I told her about work and she said you can't <pause dur="short"/> you know if this is if this navy thing is going to be next May you can't stay <unclear/> You can't stay living hand to mouth all the time and looking after your bank account <pause dur="short"/> so I'm going to start applying for new jobs but she said apply as far as <anon type="place"/> cos I'd rather you just come and live with me <pause dur="short"/> she said if you want to go and stay you can go and stay with us you can go and stay with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for the weekend <pause dur="short"/> and just stay with me during the week</u>
<u n="100" who="S0086">yeah that's it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0041">so <pause dur="short"/> and yeah I prefer not to do that cos that <pause dur="short"/> I prefer to just have my independence but</u>
<u n="102" who="S0086">well if needs must I mean if that's if you really can't stand the job <pause dur="short"/> like the thing is with this is that you thought there was an end light at the end of the tunnel <pause dur="short"/> like you're gearing up come the summer that's it I'm gone from the hotel it's gonna be good I'm going to start my new career <pause dur="short"/> now all that's toppling down a little bit <pause dur="short"/> not saying it's over</u>
<u n="103" who="S0041">yeah to a whole year from now</u>
<u n="104" who="S0086">to this time next year yeah <pause dur="short"/> and really if you've already been telling yourself it's pokey it's shit now but you know I'm going to out soon <pause dur="short"/> to then have to think could I do it for <trunc>a</trunc> another twelve months and really not just for your own sanity but financially it's not viable</u>
<u n="105" who="S0041">financially it's impossible yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0086">but that's not to say that there aren't marketing jobs or language jobs out there <pause dur="short"/> you know particularly over the summer if you think ah I'll just get a job for the summer you know teaching in a language school or something like that <pause dur="short"/> I don't see why that would be a problem <pause dur="short"/> and then you need to find something from September <pause dur="short"/> so just something that's a bit interesting</u>
<u n="107" who="S0041">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was working with her and was bar tending in the bar of the local pub like <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't pay board she said I wouldn't take rent from you because I'll pay the mortgage whether you're there or not <pause dur="short"/> she said obviously I'd put something towards food and electricity and that <pause dur="short"/> I said yeah but it's not the five hundred pound a month is it? She said oh no nowhere near <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="108" who="S0086">well that would be pretty nice and then at least you can concentrate on getting yourself fit</u>
<u n="109" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="110" who="S0086">Peterborough is quite far</u>
<u n="111" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0086">but you know I'll still be here <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will still be here you know he'll be here <pause dur="short"/> you've got places to stay <pause dur="short"/> I mean Emily has got a spare room hasn't she? Hasn't she got two bedrooms?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0041">no one bedroom <pause dur="short"/> she's got enough space though</u>
<u n="114" who="S0086">you know there's always going to be people that you can stay with if you come back to visit so <pause dur="short"/> that's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> I was planning to go to Japan on Friday night <pause dur="short"/> I had it all laid out <pause dur="short"/> talking to my friend in the pub on Friday and I was just like yeah that's it I'm going <pause dur="short"/> to Japan <pause dur="short"/> but then no but I'm not going to Japan because of the <pause dur="short"/> I'd forgotten about the radiation</u>
<u n="115" who="S0046">can you turn that off?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0046">I thought you were turning it off</u>
<u n="118" who="S0041">you'd forgotten about the radiation?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0086">in Tokyo <pause dur="short"/> well not in Tokyo in Japan</u>
<u n="120" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">radiation? What <pause dur="short"/> freeze <pause dur="short"/> freeze <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0041">did you mind pouring me some <unclear/> please?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0046">no help yourself <pause dur="short"/> it's alright <unclear/> ankle <pause dur="short"/> left one</u>
<u n="123" who="S0086">what have you done?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0041">well yeah I mean it's got this mark on it but it works pretty well</u>
<u n="125" who="S0046">bloody twisted my ankle</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041">we were playing earlier <pause dur="short"/> it's such a fun game <pause dur="short"/> basically we were in the garden <pause dur="short"/> I one person stood here with all the footballs and <unclear/> to get it into the park</u>
<u n="127" who="S0086">I want to see how my washing got very damaged</u>
<u n="128" who="S0041">one of the lads was stood at the back of the park chasing it in <pause dur="short"/> because if it was a double team chest in it was double point</u>
<u n="129" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="130" who="S0046">it was like the <trunc>or</trunc> the orange one was two for a chest in and two for the person who chested it in as well</u>
<u n="131" who="S0041" trans="overlap">for the orange ball <pause dur="short"/> it was really really funny <pause dur="short"/> it really proper cheered me up <pause dur="short"/> lying down the bottom of the garden</u>
<u n="132" who="S0046">it was like <pause dur="short"/> it was hard</u>
<u n="133" who="S0041">he was like yeah I'm going to lob in a <unclear/> throw from right back here and I was like I can't throw that far <pause dur="short"/> I'm just going to stand a little bit there <pause dur="short"/> and it fell down the crack in the pavement</u>
<u n="134" who="S0046">I done first I done the right foot in the gap</u>
<u n="135" who="S0086">shit</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">the crack is like that though <pause dur="short"/> it's massive</u>
<u n="137" who="S0086">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0046">and then I done the left foot and that left foot has done me in <pause dur="short"/> it does hurt a little bit now to be fair but</u>
<u n="139" who="S0086">have you put ice on it?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">ice</u>
<u n="141" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="143" who="S0041">do it  Do it Do it</u>
<u n="144" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you need to put ice on it cos it'll be massive by tomorrow</u>
<u n="145" who="S0046">I'll be alright I'm a man</u>
<u n="146" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0086">no cos you'll need to walk</u>
<u n="148" who="S0041">yeah no <pause dur="short"/> I'm a man as well</u>
<u n="149" who="S0046" trans="overlap">I'll play football and that still</u>
<u n="150" who="S0086">yeah no <pause dur="short"/> I'm a man as well <pause dur="short"/> I'm a man as well <pause dur="short"/> get ice on it</u>
<u n="151" who="S0046">you you you put any man to shame <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0086">it's quite a growth you've got going on there</u>
<u n="153" who="S0041">it's gonna have gone by tomorrow though <pause dur="short"/> say goodbye</u>
<u n="154" who="S0086">it'll be gone by tomorrow</u>
<u n="155" who="S0046">it better <pause dur="short"/> you'd better come home tomorrow and</u>
<u n="156" who="S0086">drained</u>
<u n="157" who="S0041">if they don't do it I'm going to say to them in A and E if you don't do this now watch me sit here and slice it open in front of your face and then you'll have to deal with it as an emergency</u>
<u n="158" who="S0046">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've got the longest throw off Toy Story over the head</u>
<u n="160" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'll do it <pause dur="short"/> he's on about the ball <pause dur="short"/> toy Story</u>
<u n="161" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you weren't here <pause dur="short"/> toy Story ball over here <pause dur="short"/> I got the longest throw</u>
<u n="162" who="S0086">was it very literal?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0046">well way to go</u>
<u n="164" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it went in</u>
<u n="165" who="S0046">oh did it?</u>
<u n="166" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you were there <pause dur="short"/> from up here <pause dur="short"/> toy Story</u>
<u n="167" who="S0046">it doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/> I've got very little left</u>
<u n="168" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">have some Buzz</u>
<u n="169" who="S0046">I think I've only got two left</u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">I will slice it I'm being deadly serious <pause dur="short"/> if I sit in A and E tomorrow and they say no I'm going to cut it there and then</u>
<u n="171" who="S0086">do it <pause dur="short"/> we'll just be in your way</u>
<u n="172" who="S0041">in fact I might actually take a knife with me <pause dur="short"/> I know that sounds like crazy people <pause dur="short"/> but then they're going to have to do something about it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0046">well no <pause dur="short"/> you'll get nicked for that <pause dur="short"/> don't do it</u>
<u n="174" who="S0041">you can't get nicked for that</u>
<u n="175" who="S0086">yeah you can</u>
<u n="176" who="S0046">it'd be  It'd be It'd be  my mate that that would be arresting you as well</u>
<u n="177" who="S0041" trans="overlap">for slicing your own leg?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0086">no for carrying a knife</u>
<u n="179" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="180" who="S0086">you can be em you can be arrested for carrying hairspray if you tell you them that you were using it for self-defence <pause dur="short"/> becauseyou're carrying a concealed weapon</u>
<u n="181" who="S0041">are you serious?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0086"><unclear/> He used to do self-defence</u>
<u n="183" who="S0046">you can get eight years for knife as well</u>
<u n="184" who="S0086">self-defence classes at school they used to tell us <pause dur="short"/> carry a rape alarm don't carry hairspray as a weapon because you'll be arrested yourself</u>
<u n="185" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0041">yeah I'm not doing that <pause dur="short"/> fucking shit</u>
<u n="187" who="S0046">I went past the memorial today</u>
<u n="188" who="S0086">what memorial?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0046">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> the one who got stabbed to death on off <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">it was in the newspaper</u>
<u n="191" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0086">oh shit</u>
<u n="193" who="S0046">yeah I went past his <trunc>meno</trunc> memorial today</u>
<u n="194" who="S0086">where where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="195" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> just off <anon type="place"/><pause dur="short"/> near the Co-op</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">yeah if you go off <anon type="place"/> you're going down towards the Grand Arcade and instead of going the main road way you turn left down that backstreet</u>
<u n="197" who="S0086">oh yeah by the Round by the <anon type="place"/> whatever it's called? Yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0046">something like that yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0041">yeah down there</u>
<u n="200" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">opposite <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0041">yeah so you get to the Co-op and the left and then when you come out you're opposite the road that goes towards the Grand Arcade</u>
<u n="202" who="S0086" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm with you yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ten</trunc> eh no</u>
<u n="203" who="S0041">yes you're in the right place <pause dur="short"/> it's opposite <anon type="place"/> but towards <anon type="place"/> way</u>
<u n="204" who="S0086">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> and he was stabbed?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0046">he was stabbed to death <pause dur="short"/> I'm surprised you didn't hear about it <pause dur="short"/> it's everywhere</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">did you not read it in the paper?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0086">I don't read the paper? When was it? Recently?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0046">two weeks ago</u>
<u n="209" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">two three weeks ago</u>
<u n="210" who="S0086">who was the one that the guy  the guy  that you died you knew who he was <pause dur="short"/> and he was stabbed</u>
<u n="211" who="S0046">yeah I knew him</u>
<u n="212" who="S0086">that was him?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0086">yeah I did know about that but I don't know where it was though</u>
<u n="215" who="S0046">went passed his <trunc>mem</trunc> memorial <pause dur="short"/> do you know there's there's about</u>
<u n="216" who="S0086">that was three week ago wasn't it?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0046">there's about five hundred quids worth of football shirts on it <pause dur="short"/> so and they ain't been touched</u>
<u n="218" who="S0086">football shirts <pause dur="short"/> why football shirts?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0041" trans="overlap">what left there?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0046">football shirts <pause dur="short"/> he was a football fan <pause dur="short"/> he used to train youths free of charge football <pause dur="short"/> and yeah there's football shirts galore there <pause dur="short"/> and they haven't been touched <pause dur="short"/> I'll tell you what that's a sign of respect right there that</u>
<u n="221" who="S0086">why was he stabbed?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0046">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> there was a <trunc>co</trunc> a load of commotion in town <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="223" who="S0041">Cos I remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to live up he was living up <anon type="place"/> somewhere in some flats</u>
<u n="224" who="S0086">the guy ta stabbed him?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0041" trans="overlap">Cos there'd been trouble there before <pause dur="short"/> no him</u>
<u n="226" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he</u>
<u n="227" who="S0086">do he didn't live in <anon type="place"/> he just happened to be there</u>
<u n="228" who="S0041">no yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0046">and eh yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0086">but the arrested the guy was it the same night or the same weekend?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0041">did they? Did they get him?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0046" trans="overlap">no they didn't they arrested someone</u>
<u n="233" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">they <pause dur="short"/> no they arrested  No they arrested  a few people</u>
<u n="234" who="S0086">oh right but they haven't</u>
<u n="235" who="S0041">but there have been quite a few incidents in the same area in <anon type="place"/> haven't there?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0046" trans="overlap">they've caught him now though <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0041">before he got stabbed</u>
<u n="238" who="S0046">but they hey have caught him</u>
<u n="239" who="S0086" trans="overlap">there's a rise in knife crime definitely <pause dur="short"/> it's quite scary</u>
<u n="240" who="S0046">they have caught him now and he is slowly being sentenced for you know <pause dur="short"/> he'll he'll he'll be put down for a very long time</u>
<u n="241" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">if not he's going to get fucked up</u>
<u n="242" who="S0046">eh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's eight years for knife crime full stop <pause dur="short"/> regardless <pause dur="short"/> any <trunc>ki</trunc> any kind of knife crime <pause dur="short"/> you know I I I could have got put down for for eight years</u>
<u n="243" who="S0041">you just don't I know it sounds well it might sound naïve cos I'm not from here but you just don't associate that with <anon type="place"/> at all</u>
<u n="244" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="245" who="S0046">you wouldn't would you?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="247" who="S0046">but now you've got to <pause dur="short"/> two of my mates got stabbed back in O five no O seven</u>
<u n="248" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh yeah you'd just started the bike</u>
<u n="249" who="S0046">I I I was with my fiancé and she let me out of the first night <pause dur="short"/> the first night she let me out on the loose</u>
<u n="250" who="S0086">what do you mean she let you out?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0046">she let me out lads night</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">ah <pause dur="short"/>  you're too strong</u>
<u n="253" who="S0046">lads night out <pause dur="short"/> it was the first time she'd let me out on my own basically <pause dur="short"/> we used to go out socially together anyway it was never a problem <pause dur="short"/> but it was the first time that she actually didn't go out at all cos she didn't feel up to it <pause dur="short"/> she told me I could go out myself <pause dur="short"/> I didn't crawl back until half past five and I was blood soaked</u>
<u n="254" who="S0086">you were?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0046">yeah cos I was helping my two mates that had been stabbed <pause dur="short"/> I was there with them <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't there with them <pause dur="short"/> I heard a load of commotion and me being in security I saw saw a lot of commotion <pause dur="short"/> I just walked over to have a little bit of a gander <pause dur="short"/> I was on the phone to my colleague that was in the control room that could control the cameras <pause dur="short"/> and what I saw was just literally a load of black guys running for a Ford Focus a six digit Ford Focus number plate <pause dur="short"/> and I said make sure you write this number plate down <pause dur="short"/> I think it was T six one O something and yeah <pause dur="short"/> anyway I got the number plate and the number late got traced and the guys got caught but they got away with it</u>
<u n="256" who="S0086">they got away with it? Why?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0046">they got away with it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> don't know how they got away with it</u>
<u n="258" who="S0086" trans="overlap">maybe they didn't do it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0046">there were so many people in that car they they can't have all got away with it to be fair</u>
<u n="260" who="S0086">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0046">one guy <pause dur="short"/> my mate <pause dur="short"/> my actual Mate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who I went to school with got got stabbed there <pause dur="short"/> he's only  He's only  got a little six inch scar <pause dur="short"/> em but the other guy that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mate <pause dur="short"/> we picked him up off the floor with basically half of his face hanging off</u>
<u n="262" who="S0086">they stabbed him in the face?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0046">no <pause dur="short"/> they were standing on his head <pause dur="short"/> so he was trying to keep his skin on on his face <pause dur="short"/> as as horrible as that sounds that's what we were trying to do <pause dur="short"/> we we were trying to look after his face <pause dur="short"/> and then he goes my tummy hurts  my tummy hurts  and we lifted his shirt up <pause dur="short"/> and there was a stab wound <pause dur="short"/> he'd been stabbed there and it had been slowly pulled up <pause dur="short"/> so he's got he's</u>
<u n="264" who="S0086">what the <unclear/> what's the matter with people?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0046">he he he's got a nice <trunc>ken</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well either way he's got a nice nice scar</u>
<u n="266" who="S0086">they're so lucky that no organs were punctures <pause dur="short"/> cos that would have been in game over</u>
<u n="267" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it was  it was literally straight <pause dur="short"/> I think it was there</u>
<u n="269" who="S0086">must not have been that deep</u>
<u n="270" who="S0046">and straight  and straight  up <pause dur="short"/> he he he's got a massive scar now like from nipple nipple to groin</u>
<u n="271" who="S0086">had like had they provoked it? I mean not that it's okay but were they <unclear/> or?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0046">it was all over a girl funnily enough <pause dur="short"/> it was  It was  black guys all over a girl <pause dur="short"/> this guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in a bad way <pause dur="short"/> like I'm I'm not being funny he was  he was  horrible <pause dur="short"/> and I I got to mention here because in the  in the  paper <pause dur="short"/> em I didn't want to give my name for obvious reasons</u>
<u n="273" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0046">Cos I worked in the city centre <pause dur="short"/> but I was just named as an off duty security guard</u>
<u n="275" who="S0086">where was this?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0046">just by the side of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> in front of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0086">shit</u>
<u n="278" who="S0041">do you know what's mental? I was saying to these earlier right <pause dur="short"/> when I went to see the navy person I'm sat in the office and I'm always the only girl there <pause dur="short"/> so I was looking out the window there's all people walking past in Peterborough and they're rough as fuck</u>
<u n="279" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">like they are rough as fuck <pause dur="short"/> I'm in my killer heels hooker heels <pause dur="short"/> people going to work in them <pause dur="short"/> you know tottering along the girls with like their boobs hanging out of their work shirts and <trunc>dr</trunc> like skirts up here full works for the office <pause dur="short"/> I was like holy fuck <pause dur="short"/> bleach blond hair like breaking off cos it's that shit I was like oh my god like you look horrendous <pause dur="short"/> but where I grew up it was like that <pause dur="short"/> I my friends that I've left at home would think that was acceptable <pause dur="short"/> so I've moved here and I've been here for three years now and I've kind of got a bit  got a bit  soft in my own age <pause dur="short"/> thinking that the people that live here are are general standard <pause dur="short"/> no they're not <pause dur="short"/> the farther north you go <pause dur="short"/> peterborough is the standard that I should be used to <pause dur="short"/> so I think <anon type="place"/> is quite safe and then you hear and you're like what the fuck because no matter how rough the people are <pause dur="short"/> and I mean I've told you about people sending for fighter from <unclear/> you would never see that <pause dur="short"/> never</u>
<u n="281" who="S0046">I've had two knives pulled on me in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> one one one was I think was about an eight inch serrated blade at <anon type="place"/> when it was Twenty-Two's <pause dur="short"/> I just went to the bar I was on my own and I guy standing next to me was getting some shit from a guy behind me <pause dur="short"/> and it was  it was  abusive stuff that he was saying to this guy <pause dur="short"/> and I was just I was trying to be friendly <pause dur="short"/> I was trying to sort of right cos I was still in my security days I was just trying to</u>
<u n="282" who="S0041">diffuse diffuse</u>
<u n="283" who="S0046">diffuse the situation <pause dur="short"/> so I thought I did <pause dur="short"/> next thing you know I'm getting a tap on the shoulder this guy pulls his suit jacket open and shows me this fucking blade</u>
<u n="284" who="S0086">shit</u>
<u n="285" who="S0046">that's strapped to his jacket</u>
<u n="286" who="S0086">what the fuck</u>
<u n="287" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="288" who="S0086">but you know that's where a girl got raped in the toilets while <trunc>kn</trunc> under <trunc>kni</trunc> at knife point <pause dur="short"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0046">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0086">yeah a couple of years ago <pause dur="short"/> a girl got raped there when it was Twenty-Two's</u>
<u n="292" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">the woman I shagged was with me at the time</u>
<u n="293" who="S0046"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0086">Doncaster is renowned <pause dur="short"/> people <pause dur="short"/> basically all the shops in Doncaster when I was eighteen turned from shops in to bars <pause dur="short"/> so people from as far as Newcastle were taking trips for stag dos and hen dos to come to Doncaster <pause dur="short"/> it was like as massive night out <pause dur="short"/> obviously I didn't know cos I'd moved away by that time <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> but they came from all over the place <pause dur="short"/> every single weekend it was rammed to fuck but you never heard of one stabbing ever and they were rough people <pause dur="short"/> really rough people <pause dur="short"/> you never heard of any of it</u>
<u n="295" who="S0046">that's weird</u>
<u n="296" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's like when I went to St <pause dur="short"/> ives for the first time <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously I I I came to know if you bump into someone you're going to have conflict <pause dur="short"/> my mate bumped into someone <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's big but this guy was bigger <pause dur="short"/> he's like the other guy was like sorry mate I didn't mean to he's like alright <pause dur="short"/> I mean like <unclear/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0041">that is one thing you hear like</u>
<u n="298" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">all night he was like <pause dur="short"/> he said to me in the morning no offence I thought it was going to be a shit night but it was a fucking amazing night <pause dur="short"/> excuse my French</u>
<u n="299" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you are being dictated <pause dur="short"/> you've got to sign a <trunc>do</trunc> sign a disclaimer before you eh</u>
<u n="300" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've already done that with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0046">no you have technically you have</u>
<u n="302" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I know <pause dur="short"/> he was like I'm glad we went <pause dur="short"/> I was like good <pause dur="short"/> I know we I know I got you lost cos I don't know how to get into St Ives but yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0041">have I told you about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> getting punched by that guy in Godzilla</u>
<u n="304" who="S0086">yeah of all people</u>
<u n="305" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were out taking the piss basically <pause dur="short"/> setting each other up for tune the person <pause dur="short"/> we were just really drunk by this point we were half a bottle whiskey down <pause dur="short"/> choose a person <pause dur="short"/> and I think  I think  the aim of the game was to get them to buy you a drink or to like pull them and get them to buy you a drink I don't remember <pause dur="short"/> but either way we were playing this game and he went for a girl that I'd chosen and he was talking to her <pause dur="short"/> her the girls boyfriend rocked up and he you know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like he wouldn't have said anything other than how's your night going? Em and the guy punched him in the stomach <pause dur="short"/> punched him</u>
<u n="306" who="S0086">he had a bruise the next day didn't he?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like fuck</u>
<u n="308" who="S0046">was that here?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was here</u>
<u n="310" who="S0086">that was after that Comedy Club night wasn't it?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0046">was it really?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0046">you never told me about that</u>
<u n="314" who="S0041">did I not <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> even in Barnsley and that is the roughest dive in the world ever <pause dur="short"/> if anybody ever says come with me for a night in Barnsley say fuck off cos honest to God it is bad it is so bad</u>
<u n="315" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I will I'll be like my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said fuck off I'm not going</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041">yeah it's so bad it's so so rough really like you've never seen anything like it <pause dur="short"/> there's not a place where you wouldn't stick to the floor <pause dur="short"/> or people would think it was okay to vomit in the club like</u>
<u n="317" who="S0046" trans="overlap">it's a bit like <anon type="place"/> really <pause dur="short"/> got to do it <pause dur="short"/> sorry ladies and gentlemen I've got to take it off and have a look</u>
<u n="318" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">not on top  Not on top</u>
<u n="319" who="S0041">not on the top  Not on the top</u>
<u n="320" who="S0046">sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you're the only person who wouldn't care</u>
<u n="321" who="S0086">I didn't say anything actually <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> to fuck off <pause dur="short"/> so yeah fuck off</u>
<u n="322" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's just its cos he's twisted both ankles probably</u>
<u n="323" who="S0046">and this was does hurt</u>
<u n="324" who="S0086" trans="overlap">why don't you put ice on it?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0041">I don't want to see that if I'm honest <pause dur="short"/> can I have a fire?</u>
<u n="326" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">fire fire</u>
<u n="327" who="S0046">that looks normal don't it?</u>
<u n="328" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah bottom of my bag if you can't find one</u>
<u n="329" who="S0046">does that look normal <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't look overly normal but <pause dur="short"/> not to me anyway <pause dur="short"/> I know my own feet</u>
<u n="330" who="S0041">that looks a bit fat on the outside</u>
<u n="331" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">it's a bit dodgy there</u>
<u n="332" who="S0041">that looks a bit fat on this outside</u>
<u n="333" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0086">you need to compare it to the other one <pause dur="short"/> cos we don't know what they normally look that</u>
<u n="335" who="S0046">no that definitely doesn't look overly normal</u>
<u n="336" who="S0041">yeah on the outside it looks a bit fat</u>
<u n="337" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">whoo <pause dur="short"/> put that one back on</u>
<u n="338" who="S0046">in all fairness my right foot looks worse than my left</u>
<u n="339" who="S0086">the right one looks bigger</u>
<u n="340" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no the left one <pause dur="short"/> the left one's slightly bigger <pause dur="short"/> but they do stink a little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0046">yeah I know</u>
<u n="342" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm going to have to step off a little bit now</u>
<u n="343" who="S0086">Stilton</u>
<u n="344" who="S0046">in all fairness that that's what worries me that bump there</u>
<u n="345" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is it's the bump</u>
<u n="346" who="S0086">put some ice on it <pause dur="short"/> you won't be able to walk on it in the morning</u>
<u n="347" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">sit here put your  there shut the frigging door</u>
<u n="348" who="S0046">it is weird cos my left foot is veinier than my right foot <pause dur="short"/> it always has been the case <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> That was a yawn</u>
<u n="349" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Don't start yawning <pause dur="short"/> it's not even like early yet</u>
<u n="350" who="S0086">I've been awake since five AM</u>
<u n="351" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">alright I'll give you that <pause dur="short"/> oh oh I feel cardboard <pause dur="short"/> yeah I did</u>
<u n="352" who="S0046">that's normal <pause dur="short"/> if it's going to be anyway it's there <pause dur="short"/> that's where it hurts</u>
<u n="353" who="S0086">are you supposed to be working tomorrow?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0086">not heard from <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0046">he's weird <pause dur="short"/> apparently I'm supposed to be in  tomorrow</u>
<u n="357" who="S0086">where's that?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0046">which is just up the road</u>
<u n="359" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="360" who="S0046">and I'm supposed to be <unclear/> with him <pause dur="short"/> I was speaking to my mother and she tells me oh I've not long got off the like seeing Steve <pause dur="short"/> you're in Mumford tomorrow aren't you? What? No I'm not  <pause dur="short"/> as far as I know I'm biking to work this week</u>
<u n="361" who="S0086">oh right</u>
<u n="362" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0086">have you spoken to him?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0046">I've text Steve <pause dur="short"/> I says right</u>
<u n="365" who="S0086">am I cycling or am I waiting?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0046">well <trunc>what</trunc> what? I hear you tell me one thing mum tells me another <pause dur="short"/> and he text me going they are <pause dur="short"/> that helps <pause dur="short"/> that really helps and I text him going Rumford what time? And he hasn't text me back so <pause dur="short"/> I I've really got a feeling that tomorrow is just going to be a blow out <pause dur="short"/> because if it is Rumford tomorrow there's no point in me going because Rumford don't as far as I'm concerned</u>
<u n="367" who="S0086">oh it's where you've been already</u>
<u n="368" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's there's there's no work for me left there <pause dur="short"/> apart from clean up and there isn't that two people can do that <pause dur="short"/> there's no work left for me there <pause dur="short"/> but I'm cheaper than the other dude</u>
<u n="369" who="S0086">so did you hear back from the Premier Inn?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="371" who="S0086">that's weird that they would interview you <pause dur="short"/> cos normally if they at least if they interview you</u>
<u n="372" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what's this?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0086">girton</u>
<u n="374" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's one at <anon type="place"/> as well isn't there? Or is that Holiday Inn? Holiday Inn are a similar <unclear/> as well aren't they? Well <anon type="place"/> sorry</u>
<u n="375" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0046">that's so that's Premier Inn and Travelodge</u>
<u n="378" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you wouldn't have <unclear/> if it weren't for them</u>
<u n="379" who="S0046">I know but I made <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> spray them <pause dur="short"/> she's hot she's young</u>
<u n="380" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">she's got a boyfriend <pause dur="short"/> she and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> she's got a boyfriend</u>
<u n="381" who="S0046">really <vocal desc="laugh"/>oh dear <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> kids <pause dur="short"/> you can tell I did fall over can't you?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0086">you've got grass stains on your knees</u>
<u n="383" who="S0046">it's not from falling over on grass though funnily enough <pause dur="short"/> on here</u>
<u n="384" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">the slabs</u>
<u n="385" who="S0086">you fell over on the slabs?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> man alive</u>
<u n="388" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s out there like practicing <pause dur="short"/> as well as having a fag</u>
<u n="390" who="S0086">challenge you to a rematch</u>
<u n="391" who="S0046">can't see her <pause dur="short"/> it's good fun</u>
<u n="392" who="S0086">you can't really see oh there she is</u>
<u n="393" who="S0046">as immature as it may be it is good fun</u>
<u n="394" who="S0086">it is really fun</u>
<u n="395" who="S0046">it really is <pause dur="short"/> it really is <pause dur="short"/> it's very immature but it's great fun <pause dur="short"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0086">what was?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0046">basketball <pause dur="short"/> yeah it actually really did cheer me up <pause dur="short"/> it's a complete game you play when you're like thirteen <pause dur="short"/> but it was really funny</u>
<u n="398" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">but if you were wicket and cheating it you'll be more like working out</u>
<u n="399" who="S0041">I'm not sure I'll be really less painful cheating it if I'm honest</u>
<u n="400" who="S0046">being a wicket keeper is harder than actually chasing after the ball</u>
<u n="401" who="S0041">should have strapped a cushion to my chest then I could play <pause dur="short"/> please</u>
<u n="402" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that definitely would have gone in <pause dur="short"/> the impact</u>
<u n="403" who="S0046">next Sunday is on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0041">huh?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0046">next Sunday is on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">yes sir</u>
<u n="407" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">if I'm not a <unclear/> for it</u>
<u n="408" who="S0046">you'd better not be</u>
<u n="409" who="S0041">I have a proposition and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s already shot me down so let's just pretend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not listening <pause dur="short"/> is that I went to the garden centre with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday who's obviously redoing her whole garden and I thought it would be a really nice thing</u>
<u n="410" who="S0046">I haven't shot you down</u>
<u n="411" who="S0041">for us to do all together if we went to the garden centre and bought some compact and just choose some flowers and out them all out down the little side <pause dur="short"/> I'm not going to guarantee that they will survive</u>
<u n="412" who="S0086">none of us are going to look after them</u>
<u n="413" who="S0041">well no</u>
<u n="414" who="S0086">well what I was think was after</u>
<u n="415" who="S0041">we could just buy some bulbs and buy some compost and just a have a day in the garden</u>
<u n="416" who="S0086">if we could  If we could  <unclear/> what we get then it'll be cheap won't it? You've just gotta find roses</u>
<u n="417" who="S0041">of course <pause dur="short"/> just choose the cheapest ones <pause dur="short"/> we don't care what looks great <pause dur="short"/> we'll just choose the cheapest ones buy a load of compost and a shovel and just have a day in the garden</u>
<u n="418" who="S0046">you you see <trunc>m</trunc> my theory is the patio</u>
<u n="419" who="S0041">he's saying that he wants basically to ask Trudy to move these slabs basically like two feet this way so they go to the edge of the conservatory</u>
<u n="420" who="S0046" trans="overlap">patio to the left of the <trunc>con</trunc> conservatory</u>
<u n="421" who="S0086">why why?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0046">I want three cos there's four rows of slabs</u>
<u n="423" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0046">I want three of them</u>
<u n="425" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="426" who="S0046">one for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to get out if if she want to get out <pause dur="short"/> and the other three to lay by the conservatory so we've got somewhere to sit comfortably in the summer and bake</u>
<u n="427" who="S0086">and cook <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0041">we could have a garden day</u>
<u n="429" who="S0046">I think that's more sensible</u>
<u n="430" who="S0086">A garden day would be nice <pause dur="short"/> I'd quite like a little allotment <pause dur="short"/> was thinking we could <unclear/> maybe we could buy a little <unclear/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0046" trans="overlap">that's another one</u>
<u n="432" who="S0041">we could buy a little tray and put them</u>
<u n="433" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that can be left of the eh barrel</u>
<u n="434" who="S0086">that could be where the shed was <pause dur="short"/> you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0046" trans="overlap">it'd be better  It'd be better  that end where the toilet is</u>
<u n="437" who="S0086" trans="overlap">take <unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> get compost and plant them down there</u>
<u n="438" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah cos you can buy <pause dur="short"/> there's a little place in the garden centre <pause dur="short"/> you might already know this but I didn't know</u>
<u n="439" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">she's been checking this out look at her</u>
<u n="440" who="S0041">there's a little place in the garden centre made for children that has like runner beans and</u>
<u n="441" who="S0046">so is that?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0086">yeah I know it's like a little <trunc>tra</trunc> a trough like this isn't it?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0041">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0086">oh well I went when I was with mum a couple of weeks ago and it's amazing <pause dur="short"/> it's like a massive like yeah like a trough isn't it?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0041">easy things to grow for kids</u>
<u n="446" who="S0086">yeah that's what we need</u>
<u n="447" who="S0041">shove them in</u>
<u n="448" who="S0086">Cos that's our intelligence level</u>
<u n="449" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0046">how are your chillies going?</u>
<u n="451" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I'm afraid I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0046">you need to keep watering your chillies darling</u>
<u n="453" who="S0086">oh no that's well that's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> I don't I'm rubbish <pause dur="short"/> I only <unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no cos <unclear/> they survive</u>
<u n="455" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <unclear/> we played children games today</u>
<u n="456" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">you're like children <unclear/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0041">children <unclear/> yeah we could do that</u>
<u n="458" who="S0046" trans="overlap">we play children games today we're allowed to do it <pause dur="short"/> we used more imagination today</u>
<u n="459" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so yeah we could do that <pause dur="short"/> and that would be a nice thing to do one go out in the sun <pause dur="short"/> on the weekend</u>
<u n="460" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">adults burning off the alcohol</u>
<u n="461" who="S0046">no it was called childhood imagination</u>
<u n="462" who="S0041" trans="overlap">we'll take the eh take the lot to the garden centre choose easy shit and shove it in the garden</u>
<u n="463" who="S0086">we well I've also been keeping an eye out for like cheap garden furniture cos we don't have anything in the garden that's the thing and then</u>
<u n="464" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Don't get plastic chairs</u>
<u n="467" who="S0041">it might be the cost effective option I'm afraid</u>
<u n="468" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">A picnic bench</u>
<u n="469" who="S0086">I wonder if we can like liberate certain things</u>
<u n="470" who="S0041">liberate yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0046">I'm working <pause dur="short"/> I'm working on a picnic bench <pause dur="short"/> I've got my eyes on the haymakers</u>
<u n="472" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0086">where is it?</u>
<u n="474" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you you I've got to have a look when I <unclear/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0046">Portland Road</u>
<u n="476" who="S0041">the one that's closed?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0046">yes</u>
<u n="478" who="S0041">is there picnic benches in there</u>
<u n="479" who="S0046">they've got a beer garden</u>
<u n="480" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">but I'm looking at the bench on the way home <pause dur="short"/> don't look at me like that <pause dur="short"/> I'm from Chetham <pause dur="short"/> again</u>
<u n="481" who="S0046"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/>'s just as bad</u>
<u n="482" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'll give it a little <pause dur="short"/> if it's not secured down expect a funny call</u>
<u n="483" who="S0046">yeah do it</u>
<u n="484" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'll leave my bike it's fine</u>
<u n="485" who="S0046">do it <pause dur="short"/> I'll come and get it <pause dur="short"/> cos a picnic bench we need</u>
<u n="486" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">when you knock on the door and Charlie will be like</u>
<u n="487" who="S0046">how awesome would that be to have a picnic bench</u>
<u n="488" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">got a bench</u>
<u n="489" who="S0041">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> kicks and thrills</u>
<u n="490" who="S0046">it's a good thing to have innit a picnic bench?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0086">yeah it'd be really good to have some garden furniture</u>
<u n="492" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0086">especially if we're going to like if the weather's going to be nice now and then shit in the summer be good to get stuff now like</u>
<u n="495" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0046">twenty-eighth of April <pause dur="short"/> big barbecue</u>
<u n="497" who="S0041">it's barbecue time</u>
<u n="498" who="S0086">it's a Wednesday isn't it? Or are you going to do it at the weekend</u>
<u n="499" who="S0041">weekend after <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="500" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> twenty-eighth <pause dur="short"/> big barbecue <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday is on the twenty-seventh which is Friday <pause dur="short"/> twenty-eighth we're going go carting first hand or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to do it</u>
<u n="501" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he can crash it here with you and you can wake him up in the morning</u>
<u n="502" who="S0046">we?</u>
<u n="503" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<u n="504" who="S0046">I can drive</u>
<u n="505" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">otherwise he'll sleep till four</u>
<u n="506" who="S0046">well yeah this is true <pause dur="short"/> mark staying here on a Friday night</u>
<u n="507" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah he's like me he he can't sleep at night cos he's just awake and he can't sleep and it's like four in the morning and like <pause dur="short"/> he can't sleep just be sitting there like I can't sleep <pause dur="short"/> seriously especially with work now they've put me on days so they fucked up my sleeping pattern</u>
<u n="508" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">so I'll get home from the day shift and I'll go and <pause dur="short"/> I feel tired have my dinner and I'm like that bang <pause dur="short"/> that does it to you</u>
<u n="510" who="S0046" trans="overlap">the bowling alley does it to you completely</u>
<u n="511" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that awake <pause dur="short"/> I'm like shit what am I going to do now <pause dur="short"/> not <unclear/> I sleep right okay</u>
<u n="512" who="S0046">you see whereas I get home from work now and I just want to sleep</u>
<u n="513" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">you sleep</u>
<u n="514" who="S0046">I really do <pause dur="short"/> I'm up at five I get home two three four five o'clock and I I just want to die</u>
<u n="515" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm Friday night shift I'm going to do a moony</u>
<u n="516" who="S0046">what?</u>
<u n="517" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Cos I'm off Thursday <pause dur="short"/> I'm on Monday day Tuesday day Wednesday day</u>
<u n="518" who="S0046">Thursday off</u>
<u n="519" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">maybe go to  if not I'll go <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="520" who="S0046">why would you maybe go to</u>
<u n="521" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I might do it depends who's going</u>
<u n="522" who="S0046">Don't give up on</u>
<u n="523" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm not cos if there's four of you there you don't get a fifth <pause dur="short"/> and Shaw weren't there last week so it means I don't have to go this week</u>
<u n="524" who="S0046">okay</u>
<u n="525" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">so I'll go Sarah's get woken up at five by <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0041">I'm a bit concerned that they allow a crazy horse to look after children</u>
<u n="527" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you ain't see me kids</u>
<u n="528" who="S0046">he's he's good with kids he really is <pause dur="short"/> he really is <pause dur="short"/> he's too kiddish with kids he really is <pause dur="short"/> that's the bad thing</u>
<u n="529" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no you say that but Joseph my god son does not get his own way with me</u>
<u n="530" who="S0046">you're still too childish with him</u>
<u n="531" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I put my foot no I put my <pause dur="short"/> I'll be childish with him but I put my foot down he won't do it <pause dur="short"/> he can stand there and cry and front of me I'll be like have you finished yet <pause dur="short"/> I will <pause dur="short"/> I know it's harsh but I'll be like done yet? Right okay let's carry on now</u>
<u n="532" who="S0041">how old is he?</u>
<u n="533" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he he'll be he's he's two he'll be three in November <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0041">and they allow you to look after him?</u>
<u n="535" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he's my godson <pause dur="short"/> of course they will <pause dur="short"/> gets away with daddy mummy don't and I'm not like his dad <pause dur="short"/> daddy's too soft on him sometimes <pause dur="short"/> most times</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">take the towels out <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> take the towels out</u>
<u n="537" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">take the towels out <pause dur="short"/> put them on another spin quick</u>
<u n="538" who="S0041">yeah maybe one more spin</u>
<u n="539" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">one more spin</u>
<u n="540" who="S0086">have you already put them on a spin?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0041">yeah but they're still quite damp <pause dur="short"/> pretty pretty damp in there</u>
<u n="542" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">but no he don't  he don't  get his way with me <pause dur="short"/> I will  I will  sit there until he stops crying <pause dur="short"/> it's the way forward <pause dur="short"/> yeah he might cry but they're not real tears <pause dur="short"/> they're crocodile tears <pause dur="short"/> you can tell with them when they're real tears <pause dur="short"/> it's like alright are you done yet <pause dur="short"/> I know you don't understand but properly cry</u>
<u n="543" who="S0041">that's not guilty as try harder</u>
<u n="544" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm like are you being a good boy? No <pause dur="short"/> do you know what no means? No <pause dur="short"/> my point proven <pause dur="short"/> but no he's a good kid  good kid</u>
<u n="545" who="S0041">I'm a godmother</u>
<u n="546" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh yeah? He's pretty much the most family I've got at the moment <pause dur="short"/> my godson <pause dur="short"/> and I do my best to see him every week</u>
<u n="547" who="S0041">do you take him out place?</u>
<u n="548" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I <trunc>do</trunc> no I look after him</u>
<u n="549" who="S0041">let's take him lambing <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was really excited I get to go see the lambs next weekend <pause dur="short"/> baby lambs <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen a baby lamb before</u>
<u n="550" who="S0046">have you not</u>
<u n="551" who="S0041">I'm excited <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="552" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you like lambs</u>
<u n="553" who="S0041">baby anything really</u>
<u n="554" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">baby shark?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0041">but I thought <pause dur="short"/> seen a baby shark</u>
<u n="556" who="S0086">I can't imagine a baby shark</u>
<u n="557" who="S0041">they're not very big they look like fishes</u>
<u n="558" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">go and see <unclear/> down at Yarmouth <pause dur="short"/> go down Yarmouth you see loads of baby sharks</u>
<u n="559" who="S0086">maybe I will</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">maybe I'll go there now</u>
<u n="561" who="S0086">just for shits and giggles</u>
<u n="562" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no <unclear/> be alright down there the weekend</u>
<u n="563" who="S0041">I thought the eh baby lambs came out like what baby puppies like this big</u>
<u n="564" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="565" who="S0041">they come out with legs</u>
<u n="566" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like horses</u>
<u n="567" who="S0086">what do you mean they come out with legs <pause dur="short"/> obviously they come out with legs <pause dur="short"/> where would their legs be?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I mean like <pause dur="short"/> they're as big as the</u>
<u n="569" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">like horses yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I mean like <pause dur="short"/> as big as a  As big as a  cat they can walk after a few minutes</u>
<u n="571" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041">I didn't know that <pause dur="short"/> didn't know it <pause dur="short"/> going to see them going to see them <pause dur="short"/> and the guy that I can go and see the with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's the one the farmer he's the one that I kept saying he's gay  he's gay  and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said no he's not  no he's not  I've known him for years <pause dur="short"/> comes out this week he's gay <pause dur="short"/> it's like told you I knew  I knew</u>
<u n="573" who="S0086">was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> surprised?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">yeah he was surprised cos he spent the last couple of weeks defending him saying he wasn't gay <pause dur="short"/> I knew it</u>
<u n="575" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">keep rubbing it in <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0086">where are you going to see the lambs?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0041">somewhere near <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> some farm</u>
<u n="578" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you say <anon type="place"/> or Tottenham?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0041"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="582" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0041">I used to live in is it <anon type="place"/> here? <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="584" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0041">I used to live in <anon type="place"/> near <trunc>Lo</trunc></u>
<u n="586" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">where's <trunc>Co</trunc> where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0041"><anon type="place"/> is here Cottingham is near Hull <pause dur="short"/> I used to live there</u>
<u n="588" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">right okay <pause dur="short"/> I thought you said <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0041">so I moved from Cottingham to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0086">that's amazing</u>
<u n="591" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">cottingham it's <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> no <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I used to live in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0086">me too</u>
<u n="593" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">past <anon type="place"/> I'm on about <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">yeah I used to live there</u>
<u n="595" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">really? How long ago?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">last year <pause dur="short"/> just before I moved in here</u>
<u n="597" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh right nah I weren't there then</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">in the Barn</u>
<u n="599" who="S0046">you were there years ago mate</u>
<u n="600" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">years ago</u>
<u n="601" who="S0041">just near the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="602" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">five five six <pause dur="short"/> ah mate you're asking <pause dur="short"/> been here about five years now so yeah it'll be about five and a bit years now</u>
<u n="603" who="S0041">thirty-nine years ago <pause dur="short"/> thirty years ago <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying that em they're closing the <anon type="place"/> on a Sunday at eight kicking everyone out</u>
<u n="604" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0041">yeah they're not keeping it open cos they don't make enough money and I was like what are you going to do? Where's your social? Where's your social life gone now? He's like I know it's hard isn't it?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0086">so that's just going to be Saturday night?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0041">Friday night and Saturday night but Sunday night they're closing from eight</u>
<u n="608" who="S0086">from Eight PM</u>
<u n="609" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0086">oh so it's open during the day then? So it's only for like three hours</u>
<u n="612" who="S0041">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0046">but have you seen <unclear/> Open at lunch time close at three open again at six</u>
<u n="614" who="S0041">no they have the old boys sitting there all afternoon playing the racing</u>
<u n="615" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">why do you look at me when you say that?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0046">the old boys</u>
<u n="618" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">the old boys</u>
<u n="619" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="620" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah couldn't resist</u>
<u n="621" who="S0041">you must be older than me seeing as I'm twenty-two soon</u>
<u n="622" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes yes I am <pause dur="short"/> only by two years <pause dur="short"/> now you think now you'll think about that</u>
<u n="623" who="S0041">sod you sorry for you  sorry for you</u>
<u n="624" who="S0046">big two seven this year</u>
<u n="625" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Don't go far down there <pause dur="short"/> any time</u>
<u n="626" who="S0041">Penny Lane?</u>
<u n="627" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">maybe?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0041">Penny Row <pause dur="short"/> are you on about in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="629" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Don't go far <pause dur="short"/> don't go down too far <pause dur="short"/> I've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">that's the wrong end of the high street</u>
<u n="633" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you might <unclear/> to <anon type="place"/> Sunday</u>
<u n="634" who="S0041">it's what now?</u>
<u n="635" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/> Sunday</u>
<u n="636" who="S0041"><anon type="place"/> Sunday</u>
<u n="637" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you can't call them travellers they get offensive <pause dur="short"/> you can't call them pikeys <pause dur="short"/> so it's <anon type="place"/> Sunday</u>
<u n="638" who="S0046">they all drink <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0041">on Sunday's only</u>
<u n="640" who="S0046">and they will pay</u>
<u n="641" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">two sixty</u>
<u n="642" who="S0046">two sixty</u>
<u n="643" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">at the Bine for a can of Red bull</u>
<u n="644" who="S0046">when it's a pound in Tesco's</u>
<u n="645" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I did watch Big Fat Gypsy Wedding yesterday</u>
<u n="646" who="S0046">I watched Brian Chillers yesterday</u>
<u n="647" who="S0041">no it was this morning</u>
<u n="648" who="S0046">Brian Chillers yesterday <pause dur="short"/> and oh my God the women on there are fucking one one one one one <pause dur="short"/> if it ain't right</u>
<u n="649" who="S0041">who do you think has to deal with them organising the wedding?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0046">oh my good God</u>
<u n="651" who="S0041">me <pause dur="short"/> me <pause dur="short"/> vickers <pause dur="short"/> arrange weddings</u>
<u n="652" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I remember that <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> give the phone to Charlie now</u>
<u n="653" who="S0041">yeah there are bridezillas</u>
<u n="654" who="S0046">when when?</u>
<u n="655" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">be a long time coming <unclear/> I'll be like  I'll be like  forty-five</u>
<u n="656" who="S0041">Good good yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you just need d to not hold back mate <pause dur="short"/> you hold back too much that's your trouble I think</u>
<u n="658" who="S0041">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> don't get married before you're thirty ever ever</u>
<u n="659" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'll go with that</u>
<u n="660" who="S0046">I'll go with that and all <pause dur="short"/> no way he's getting married before he's thirty</u>
<u n="661" who="S0041">Don't do it</u>
<u n="662" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm getting toed we're getting towed tomorrow yeah <pause dur="short"/> see if I can get out for free off <unclear/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0046">is he really?</u>
<u n="664" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah for free</u>
<u n="665" who="S0046">seriously</u>
<u n="666" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he's he's done a couple of practice <pause dur="short"/> and his friends are free</u>
<u n="667" who="S0046">okay</u>
<u n="668" who="S0041">I'm his friend</u>
<u n="669" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you're my friend and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friend so that makes you a friend</u>
<u n="670" who="S0046"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will get him up <pause dur="short"/> he's got stuff yeah?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0041">Will you sort out this stores for me please?</u>
<u n="672" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he's got the stuff but <pause dur="short"/> let him do a couple more cos obviously I haven't seen them <pause dur="short"/> so then the <unclear/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0046">all I want him is to design grandma in an arch</u>
<u n="674" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he'll be able to do that</u>
<u n="675" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0041">I'm not talking about that shit I just want these tattoos going over in black please <pause dur="short"/> these stars both black</u>
<u n="677" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">standard <pause dur="short"/> I'll speak to him <trunc>to</trunc> yeah tomorrow</u>
<u n="678" who="S0041">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> do it</u>
<u n="679" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">be easy</u>
<u n="680" who="S0041">that's an easy one for him to do if he's only starting <pause dur="short"/> they're already there I just want him to go over them in black</u>
<u n="681" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah he'll do that <pause dur="short"/> what only inside?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fill them in</u>
<u n="683" who="S0046">just fill them in</u>
<u n="684" who="S0041">they're in colours now and I want them going over in black</u>
<u n="685" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">what about shading</u>
<u n="686" who="S0041">no the whole lot just completely black</u>
<u n="687" who="S0046" trans="overlap">no just filled</u>
<u n="688" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you don't want them like that? No</u>
<u n="689" who="S0041">no I mean they're already coloured <pause dur="short"/> I want them going over in black completely</u>
<u n="690" who="S0046">another word about my grandma arch <pause dur="short"/> I want old English writing</u>
<u n="691" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I said to him no offence but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s doing by half leaf</u>
<u n="692" who="S0041">yeah if you're going to do something serious you don't want him to do it but it's already there they're already  they're already  a perfect shape I just want them going on in black coloured in filled in black done</u>
<u n="693" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is rubbish <pause dur="short"/> he says to me let me know when you want it when you've got the money <pause dur="short"/> I said to him I had the money like weeks ago but you don't come</u>
<u n="694" who="S0046">how much does he charge? Does he charge by the hour?</u>
<u n="695" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">he he's <trunc>go</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> well yeah because it's mate's rates for all <unclear/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0041">do you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had one on his arm done at Tattoo Crazy <pause dur="short"/> is that what it's called?</u>
<u n="697" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm hm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0041">is that what it's called?</u>
<u n="699" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">where's that?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0046">Down the</u>
<u n="701" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0046">the Hobson Street <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> place</u>
<u n="703" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"></u>
<u n="704" who="S0046"><unclear/> place yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="705" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's where  That's where  Tatties is</u>
<u n="706" who="S0041">what <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's near there <pause dur="short"/> what he had done could have been so easily fucked up <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>re</trunc> like was looking at I really really precise <pause dur="short"/> really precise</u>
<u n="707" who="S0046">no <pause dur="short"/> they're shit for tattoos in there</u>
<u n="708" who="S0041">whoever did his is good and the girl that does it <pause dur="short"/> is her name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="709" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">think so <pause dur="short"/> no yeah yeah something like that</u>
<u n="710" who="S0041">she's really good <pause dur="short"/> she's better than they guy that did his ad I can't pick a flaw in his <pause dur="short"/> she's even better</u>
<u n="711" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">if the place to go in <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="712" who="S0041">are you going to say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="713" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've seen <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> not first <pause dur="short"/> but my mate now he's not in Huntington is eh Custom Ink <anon type="place"/> near me at work</u>
<u n="714" who="S0046">do you want?</u>
<u n="715" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'll have another one yeah I'll <unclear/> it <pause dur="short"/> or it'd be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s even though he charges too much</u>
<u n="716" who="S0041">yeah I was going to say <pause dur="short"/> the other thing about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is</u>
<u n="717" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">disgusting <pause dur="short"/> you book that you'll get it cheap</u>
<u n="718" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a bit full of hisself though isn't he? If it's not something he likes <trunc>tat</trunc> if it's not something he likes to tattoo</u>
<u n="719" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><trunc>Ye</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> my mate said three  My mate said three  hundred and sixty for half a sleeve <pause dur="short"/> it was like two three hour sessions I was like mate it's not going to be that <pause dur="short"/> he's like what do you mean? You do as much as you can in one session <pause dur="short"/> why's that? I don't really care if I'm kicking and screaming you can finish that you finish that in one</u>
<u n="720" who="S0041">do you know tattoos here are so much more expensive <pause dur="short"/> you know the one on my back that you've seen</u>
<u n="721" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0041">here <pause dur="short"/> cos I wanted the colours touching up <pause dur="short"/> here eh they wanted to charge me a hundred pound to touch up the yellow and the white cos obviously when I got on the sunbed everything gets faded <pause dur="short"/> but the guy that actually did it</u>
<u n="723" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">how big is that again?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0041">the guy that did it thirty quid <pause dur="short"/> I mean I knew him so it should have been forty-five</u>
<u n="725" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">okay and that was? Yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0041">but still to have it done here initially hundred quid straight off</u>
<u n="727" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's like this one <pause dur="short"/> that's meant to be a hundred</u>
<u n="728" who="S0041">and the same with piercings here as well</u>
<u n="729" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">and twenty</u>
<u n="730" who="S0041">like when I had that bit pierced <pause dur="short"/> I've taken it out now cos I had to for work <pause dur="short"/> but I had it done here again cos I let it heal up <pause dur="short"/> here she charged me thirty-five <pause dur="short"/> hull tenner</u>
<u n="731" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah <pause dur="short"/> that was meant to be a hundred and twenty I got it for sixty <pause dur="short"/> mates rates</u>
<u n="732" who="S0041">well that to me if normal like I think it's madness <pause dur="short"/> do you know there's a guy called Kamal in London and he's well he's in New York most of the time now cos he's really really good <pause dur="short"/> like his tattoos look like watercolours</u>
<u n="733" who="S0046" trans="overlap">I've heard of him</u>
<u n="734" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what's his name?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0041"></u>
<u n="736" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh right no</u>
<u n="737" who="S0041">I saw this guy <unclear/> about a year ago I was stood in H and M and I was looking at this guy's tattoo and it was like em <pause dur="short"/> it was like a landscape really <pause dur="short"/> nothing special as in I don't know why the fuck he chose that but looking at it I was proper staring at it and I couldn't make out if it was a real tattoo or not cos it was just flawless <pause dur="short"/> it looked like it had been painted <pause dur="short"/> there was no outline or anything it had just been <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't believe it</u>
<u n="738" who="S0046">what with <unclear/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="740" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">my mate  My mate  who done my ribs</u>
<u n="741" who="S0041">yeah and I was staring at it and in the end I said to him I said I'm really sorry do you mind me asking is that a real tattoo? And he was like yeah a guy called Kamal does it <pause dur="short"/> and so I looked him up and the waiting list to have a tattoo with him is I think it's eighteen months now cos he's out the country most of the the time</u>
<u n="742" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0041">but to go to London to have him <pause dur="short"/> the thing that the guy had done was two hundred pounds</u>
<u n="744" who="S0046">what's he London Ink or something or?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0041">I don't know  I don't know  what that is <pause dur="short"/> but still two hundred pounds but it was out of this world</u>
<u n="746" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">my mate who's done that his brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he <pause dur="short"/> they always go they always say come to America  come to America  He'll go straight out there <pause dur="short"/> he's minted now</u>
<u n="747" who="S0046">his brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother</u>
<u n="748" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother</u>
<u n="749" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I would love to get tattooed by <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> but he's just so hard to get hold of now <pause dur="short"/> he is  He is  living in America now</u>
<u n="751" who="S0046">didn't he get called up by Miami or something like that?</u>
<u n="752" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah Miami Ink <pause dur="short"/> he they rang him up</u>
<u n="753" who="S0046">this Kamal guy has got loads in Miami</u>
<u n="754" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Miami Ink rang my mate's brother up and said we want here come here <pause dur="short"/> he went that just like that <pause dur="short"/> I'll be there</u>
<u n="755" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> but it just shows you someone who's that at that height of the profession is going to charge two hundred quid and fucking Fabio's sat on <anon type="place"/> saying three sixty <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so</u>
<u n="756" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you have any tattoos?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="758" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah I thought not</u>
<u n="759" who="S0041" trans="overlap">she has sense</u>
<u n="760" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">she's like  She's like  uh difficult</u>
<u n="761" who="S0046">it's alright you're not left alone <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you're not <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got any</u>
<u n="762" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yet</u>
<u n="763" who="S0086">I don't feel alone <pause dur="short"/> I've thought about it for while for a long time when I got back from Cuba I was going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="764" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">make sure <pause dur="short"/> everyone says this make sure it's got meaning <pause dur="short"/> I I I agree make sure they've got meaning</u>
<u n="765" who="S0086">yeah absolutely otherwise you're going to regret it <pause dur="short"/> or I mean you know when you're young and impulsive</u>
<u n="766" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">that's why I'm getting half a sleeve so I can cover my little T J up</u>
<u n="767" who="S0041">I know a lot of people like I would never ever have a name tattooed on me ever <pause dur="short"/> never a lot</u>
<u n="768" who="S0086">no no</u>
<u n="769" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I have but it's my old nickname</u>
<u n="770" who="S0041">that's different <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just wouldn't do it <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I need this bad boy doing over</u>
<u n="771" who="S0046">I'd have my first born and my grandma tattooed on my back <pause dur="short"/> well I want grandma tattooed on the nape of my neck <pause dur="short"/> in an arch</u>
<u n="772" who="S0086">I would never do that I would never put a name on me</u>
<u n="773" who="S0046">I want grandma</u>
<u n="774" who="S0041">yeah your reasons are a bit different though <pause dur="short"/> I'd never put a name on me</u>
<u n="775" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">not even if you're married</u>
<u n="776" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="777" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">and they passed away so</u>
<u n="778" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="779" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="780" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">give you that</u>
<u n="781" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I would never do it</u>
<u n="782" who="S0046">no I wouldn't</u>
<u n="783" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">probably <pause dur="short"/> well obviously it's different for you <pause dur="short"/> that's why I've got my granddad's service number <pause dur="short"/> cos that means a lot more to me</u>
<u n="784" who="S0041">I see the  I see the  logic behind it but I just would never do <pause dur="short"/> I could never do it</u>
<u n="785" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">but if I thought about that more and didn't have it now I would have got that in two <unclear/>bags and I would have got the chain wrapped round my arm <pause dur="short"/> a couple of times <pause dur="short"/> but I can't now cos it's too straight</u>
<u n="786" who="S0086">you must have been there about that <unclear/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0046">it's too straight <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="788" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well it is <pause dur="short"/> you don't want a dog tag within a dog tag you know what I mean? You want it</u>
<u n="789" who="S0046">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not straight though</u>
<u n="790" who="S0041">after I've got this one sorted I want something doing down my spine <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what though</u>
<u n="791" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">it's straight enough <pause dur="short"/> it was free it was straight enough</u>
<u n="792" who="S0086">it's fine <pause dur="short"/> it's really difficult on a girl choose somewhere that's not too</u>
<u n="793" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">sluttish</u>
<u n="794" who="S0041">Findable</u>
<u n="795" who="S0086" trans="overlap">butch <pause dur="short"/> butch-like or sluttish <pause dur="short"/> like my friend got a a flower tattooed on her back and it was nice and after that she got like a panther on her arm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0046">no ooh</u>
<u n="797" who="S0041">panther?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0086">which is really butch butch lesbian</u>
<u n="799" who="S0046">is that the one you had round here that time?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0086">no she hasn't been here</u>
<u n="801" who="S0046" trans="overlap"><trunc>Whi</trunc>? No okay <pause dur="short"/> who was that crazy girl that you had round here that weren't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> the <unclear/> at UCT</u>
<u n="802" who="S0086">what at the party?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0041" trans="overlap">the crazy girl?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0046">no there was another girl</u>
<u n="805" who="S0086">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was here at the party it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with the short short blond hair</u>
<u n="806" who="S0041">I like her  I like her</u>
<u n="807" who="S0086">with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> they were the ones that were here till the end</u>
<u n="808" who="S0046">this this this wasn't party time <pause dur="short"/> this was random</u>
<u n="809" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ramping time</u>
<u n="810" who="S0046">I think I came knocking on your door</u>
<u n="811" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had come a knocking</u>
<u n="812" who="S0046">but she and she came across quite lesbian</u>
<u n="813" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">was he throwing stones at your window?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0041">think do you <trunc>s</trunc> so you think he's thinking of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she's got short hair? She doesn't come off very lesbian like though</u>
<u n="815" who="S0086">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0046">possibly</u>
<u n="817" who="S0086">was it a Christmas?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0046">yeah ish</u>
<u n="819" who="S0086">was she sat on my futon? In the corner</u>
<u n="820" who="S0046">she was on she was in your bed <pause dur="short"/> she was ill</u>
<u n="821" who="S0086">oh yeah it probably was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually</u>
<u n="822" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0086"><trunc>No</trunc> a blond hair? Quite skinny</u>
<u n="824" who="S0041">I haven't met her have I?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0086">you haven't met her she was only here for a few hours I don't think you were at home</u>
<u n="826" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah she was ill she was quite dark</u>
<u n="827" who="S0086">lesbian</u>
<u n="828" who="S0046">sorry <pause dur="short"/> no it was just <pause dur="short"/> you know you you get that kind of instant impression about people?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0086">what cos she was in my bed?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0046">yes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's cos you were <pause dur="short"/> you pufta</u>
<u n="831" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you you dirty <unclear/> I mean look at you?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0086">what are going to do</u>
<u n="833" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you greedy person</u>
<u n="834" who="S0046">no nothing like that  nothing like that  No she she just came across</u>
<u n="835" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">to be fair I really was sick by you</u>
<u n="836" who="S0046">why?</u>
<u n="837" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">people say it don't hurt no offence</u>
<u n="838" who="S0046">fucking find <unclear/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it doesn't hurt</u>
<u n="840" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no there's always pain <pause dur="short"/> to me that hurt there more than that <pause dur="short"/> that's one of the worst places <pause dur="short"/> that and the back is the worst</u>
<u n="841" who="S0041" trans="overlap">the one on the back didn't hurt <pause dur="short"/> but think at the bottom of your back I think it's fat there <pause dur="short"/> that didn't hurt me at all <pause dur="short"/> the one on my foot really hurt</u>
<u n="842" who="S0086" trans="overlap">it needs to be fleshy <pause dur="short"/> if it's on the bone it's going to kill you</u>
<u n="843" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah that there <pause dur="short"/> look look that's my rib look</u>
<u n="844" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that really hurt <pause dur="short"/> I want one on my ribs <pause dur="short"/> when I'm skinny</u>
<u n="845" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that there I done <unclear/> in the tattoo shop and he fucking tattoos people</u>
<u n="846" who="S0046">oh is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> busy now</u>
<u n="847" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? Yeah he's working</u>
<u n="848" who="S0046">is he?</u>
<u n="849" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah he's working now <pause dur="short"/> cos he's on tomorrow night</u>
<u n="850" who="S0046">I'd get it done now</u>
<u n="851" who="S0041">you tell him  You tell him  this</u>
<u n="852" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I will <pause dur="short"/> when he comes and I leave I'll go look I've got two people hooked up for you</u>
<u n="853" who="S0041">be an easy one for him to do</u>
<u n="854" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Cos he tattooed himself cos her wanted to see what's <unclear/> He's done he said a dot but it's more of a line</u>
<u n="855" who="S0046">just tell him I'll give him twenty quid</u>
<u n="856" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he goes <pause dur="short"/> he's like that he goes look I've done a dot I was like <pause dur="short"/> that's not really <pause dur="short"/> there's me going that like with my nails like <pause dur="short"/> okay maybe it is real</u>
<u n="857" who="S0041">thing is for a girl I think you've to to choose somewhere that you can hide it</u>
<u n="858" who="S0086">exactly <pause dur="short"/> not a butch lesbian tattoo on your arm <pause dur="short"/> imagine on your wedding day</u>
<u n="859" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> wedding dress</u>
<u n="860" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">if you hide it it's more I reckon it's more sexy if you hide it</u>
<u n="861" who="S0086">yeah cos then only certain people then get to see it</u>
<u n="862" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why I done my ribs <pause dur="short"/> cos I only take my top off if <pause dur="short"/> my birthday I'll do the full monty <pause dur="short"/> two years ago <pause dur="short"/> or I'm going to bed <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="864" who="S0046">I love <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s tattoo</u>
<u n="865" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Cos at work when I get changed in the toilet</u>
<u n="866" who="S0046"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s tattoo was awesome <pause dur="short"/> and it hooked up <pause dur="short"/> it started off at the back as a little little back piece at the bottom of the spine which everybody's got which is just</u>
<u n="867" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0041">stamp <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've been told that so many times</u>
<u n="870" who="S0046">but she's she's adapted it and it's all been moved and curved around and it goes up there <pause dur="short"/> now it's discreet because not everything shows it off <pause dur="short"/> and she wants to get the other side done as well <pause dur="short"/> it's not all her back that's covered <pause dur="short"/> it is literally stamp</u>
<u n="871" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">bring it round</u>
<u n="872" who="S0046">and then round <pause dur="short"/> and it looks stunning <pause dur="short"/> it looks absolutely amazing</u>
<u n="873" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'd quite like that actually <pause dur="short"/> I don't want it up my side I want it up the front to the top of my ribs just below the boob</u>
<u n="874" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">my friend who's who skinnier than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> have you seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0046">yeah you've seen her here haven't you?</u>
<u n="877" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">her first tattoo was I don't know some sort of flower I don't know what was pretty much whole of her back <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah you're not getting it down you're not getting it <pause dur="short"/> I would have put bets on that she won't get it done she got it done like that</u>
<u n="878" who="S0046">whizz's tattoos though</u>
<u n="879" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">all over and I was like <pause dur="short"/> that is fucking well fuck off <pause dur="short"/> she was like yeah it's</u>
<u n="880" who="S0046">are you on about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="881" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no it's one of mine and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends <pause dur="short"/> but that's not <unclear/> I was like that <pause dur="short"/> you can feel the line if you know <unclear/> you're like <pause dur="short"/> fuck <pause dur="short"/> I'll give you that</u>
<u n="882" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="883" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'll give you a <unclear/></u>
<u n="884" who="S0046"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s tattoos are pretty hot though aren't they?</u>
<u n="885" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has got dragons and everything</u>
<u n="886" who="S0046">she she's got so many tattoos it's unbelievable</u>
<u n="887" who="S0086">dragons?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0046">but it doesn't  it doesn't  come across slutty subtle</u>
<u n="889" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> just make sure your</u>
<u n="890" who="S0046">it doesn't come across as slutty at all <pause dur="short"/> it's it's it's weird <pause dur="short"/> she's she's got tattoos on the inside of her thighs on her outside and they they look amazing</u>
<u n="891" who="S0086">really? On the thighs?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0046" trans="overlap">they really really do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="893" who="S0041">see I thought this <pause dur="short"/> I'd <trunc>ha</trunc> I'd have on at the very top of my thigh here because then I could hide it <pause dur="short"/> I just think for girls there's always going to be a time where you're going to show that <pause dur="short"/> what happens if you're a granny?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0086">you see that's the issue <pause dur="short"/> when you're a mum</u>
<u n="895" who="S0041">when you've got wrinkly skin <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="896" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I thought that <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>pe</trunc> the old people today they've got tattoos down here random tattoos down here</u>
<u n="897" who="S0046" trans="overlap">but she's just popped out a kid</u>
<u n="898" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah she's young though <pause dur="short"/> no don't do it</u>
<u n="899" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm like what the fuck? Do you know what I mean <pause dur="short"/> why? Cos I'm like I don't respect my old man cos of what he done but he's got tattoos down here <pause dur="short"/> it's stupid <pause dur="short"/> I was like what the fuck <pause dur="short"/> I'm not getting any down here unless they really meant something like <pause dur="short"/> you you're you're on about names</u>
<u n="901" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'd have one on my  but it would stop before my collarbone</u>
<u n="902" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you're on about names <pause dur="short"/> I'll definitely get my kids names if I had to</u>
<u n="903" who="S0041">is this yours <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0046">yes</u>
<u n="905" who="S0041">I just took it off cos it's done <pause dur="short"/> put it on the stairs</u>
<u n="906" who="S0046">yes</u>
<u n="907" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">but I'll definitely get my kids names if anything</u>
<u n="908" who="S0046">yeah I would as well</u>
<u n="909" who="S0086">what about a spider web on your face?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0046">no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="911" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">funny you say that I know someone who's got that</u>
<u n="912" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0086">on their face?</u>
<u n="914" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he actually looked like a pit-bull <pause dur="short"/> the actual <unclear/> pit-bull</u>
<u n="915" who="S0046">oh no you're on yeah you're on about <unclear/> yeah pit-bull <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">his pretend real name <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0046" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his name was</u>
<u n="918" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yes</u>
<u n="919" who="S0046"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="920" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah I just picked my <unclear/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0046" trans="overlap">yeah he has <pause dur="short"/> it's not on his like full on on his face</u>
<u n="922" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no</u>
<u n="923" who="S0041">it's not really on his face <pause dur="short"/> you're not being serious</u>
<u n="924" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no it's not like bam <pause dur="short"/> I saw this guy in Tesco's yesterday with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> no joke <pause dur="short"/> imagine I had no hair and a bit of stubble you know less than that <pause dur="short"/> a pumpkin face here yeah? So like whatever <pause dur="short"/> and then on top you know the England football team they've got three lions around it <pause dur="short"/> he had that on top</u>
<u n="925" who="S0086">blimey <pause dur="short"/> he sounds like a winner</u>
<u n="926" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">and he was security or something</u>
<u n="927" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah it sounds like <unclear/></u>
<u n="928" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I was like I looked at it  I looked at it  like that and I was like and I thought best not <pause dur="short"/> I looked  I looked  again I was like no fucking way <pause dur="short"/> and he went like that he turned round I was like England on his head pumpkin on the back of your head I was like what the fuck</u>
<u n="929" who="S0086">he's got issues</u>
<u n="930" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I was like football hooligan definitely <pause dur="short"/> before he was security</u>
<u n="932" who="S0086">wasn't it illegal in this country to tattoo on your face?</u>
<u n="933" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">see security wise I thought everything above the neck and <trunc>belo</trunc> <trunc>be</trunc> below the wrist</u>
<u n="934" who="S0046">employment wise <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> experience wise no <pause dur="short"/> it all depends <pause dur="short"/> cos that they can quite easily grow their hair and shave it off during employment</u>
<u n="935" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0086">I thought it was on your face and on your throat you weren't allowed to get tattoos <pause dur="short"/> but obviously there were places that would do it but I thought it was actually illegal</u>
<u n="937" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you can get  you can get  friends friends that will do it <pause dur="short"/> you know and it's not like it's unsafe it's just advised against</u>
<u n="938" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the throat though</u>
<u n="939" who="S0046" trans="overlap">it's a bit like smoking though isn't it?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="941" who="S0046">you know I I I wanted  I wanted  one there <pause dur="short"/> but I think that would freak me out a little but too much as a first tattoo</u>
<u n="942" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's <trunc>y</trunc> that's your skull <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="943" who="S0046">pretty much isn't it <pause dur="short"/> although I have got a lot of</u>
<u n="944" who="S0086">you haven't got cartilage there I suppose have you?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0046">I got a lot  I got a lot  of give there on that bit</u>
<u n="946" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you've got like muscle and stuff</u>
<u n="947" who="S0046">you know I got  I got  muscle and I got flab <pause dur="short"/> but I I want want I really want an arch grandma over over my shoulders the nape of my next <pause dur="short"/> I just want it <pause dur="short"/> she saved my life so</u>
<u n="948" who="S0086">your gran?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I don't really <pause dur="short"/> she was dead and she stopped me from doing something very stupid</u>
<u n="950" who="S0086">oh really?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0046">so em <pause dur="short"/> grandma <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's a nice name</u>
<u n="953" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> her name was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> which is very weird</u>
<u n="954" who="S0086">very weird</u>
<u n="955" who="S0046">very very weird <pause dur="short"/> how do you get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> out of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="956" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">every time you say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think of Dot out of like Eastenders</u>
<u n="957" who="S0041">me too</u>
<u n="958" who="S0046" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0086">well it's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't it? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is short from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="960" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0086">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I got an aunt I got a great aunty called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="963" who="S0086">yeah my nanny <pause dur="short"/> my nanny was called</u>
<u n="964" who="S0046">she's an alcoholic</u>
<u n="965" who="S0086">fine <pause dur="short"/> all the best people are</u>
<u n="966" who="S0046">she's she's an alcoholic through and though <pause dur="short"/> never worked a day in her life and she's rich as anybody</u>
<u n="967" who="S0041">I'm beered out are we beered out?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0046">almost beered out</u>
<u n="969" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I don't know I think there's one left of mine</u>
<u n="970" who="S0086">I've got one if anyone wants one</u>
<u n="971" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hey <pause dur="short"/> if we go back to mine someone is definitely coming back with you</u>
<u n="972" who="S0046">I can't I'm injured now</u>
<u n="973" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">fuck off you're on a push bike</u>
<u n="974" who="S0046">I am still injured</u>
<event desc="begin overlap"/>
<u n="975" who="S0086">had you noticed I had my hair cut?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0041">yes I loved it <pause dur="short"/> I noticed <pause dur="short"/> did I not say it to you <pause dur="short"/> no I really like it <pause dur="short"/> I will touch it will touch it <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's like the way you you had it cut not long ago <pause dur="short"/> I love it like that <pause dur="short"/> it suits you face a lot <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s asking me loads of question about you you know</u>
<u n="977" who="S0086">about me <pause dur="short"/> why?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? She's fine <pause dur="short"/> what's she doing now? I said what you did for a living all this blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and then she told me how jealous she was of your face</u>
<u n="979" who="S0086"><unclear/> Of my face <unclear/></u>
<u n="980" who="S0041">she's jealous of your face <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to see her actually next weekend</u>
<u n="981" who="S0086">are you? I thought you were going <unclear/></u>
<u n="982" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="983" who="S0086"><unclear/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0041">I think it's the</u>
<u n="985" who="S0086">oh no <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing on Sunday?</u>
<u n="986" who="S0041">and she em didn't offer me a <unclear/> out and find out to make sure it's for Sunday <pause dur="short"/> but she's going erm to see a consultant about her Botox</u>
<u n="987" who="S0086">okay really</u>
<u n="988" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> so I'm going with her</u>
<u n="989" who="S0086">oh God <pause dur="short"/> is she going go through with it?</u>
<u n="990" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think she is  I think she is  I mean she's thought about it <pause dur="short"/> no really</u>
<u n="991" who="S0086" trans="overlap">she's taken the <unclear/></u>
<u n="992" who="S0041"><unclear/> She's <pause dur="short"/> it's the only thing she's self-conscious about <pause dur="short"/> she's self-confident but <unclear/> then she's good to go <pause dur="short"/> she says it's the only thing that I feel conscious about and everyone see it <pause dur="short"/> I don't feel like I'm at the age that I am <pause dur="short"/> I'd feel a lot better if they weren't there <pause dur="short"/> I was like well if that's it</u>
<u n="993" who="S0086">fair enough</u>
<u n="994" who="S0041">let's go see what they have to say <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<event desc="end overlap"/>
<u n="995" who="S0046">I had one <pause dur="short"/> have you had one?</u>
<u n="996" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah I've got one here</u>
<u n="997" who="S0046">you have one and I'll have one</u>
<u n="998" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> one <pause dur="short"/> I'll be alright</u>
<u n="999" who="S0046"><unclear/> got one?</u>
<u n="1000" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no I've got this one here look</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1003" who="S0046">oh</u>
<u n="1004" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I 'm not fussed</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0046">oh</u>
<u n="1006" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's that's <unclear/> I 'm not fussed <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1007" who="S0046">she's alright <pause dur="short"/> we're we're good to go <pause dur="short"/> at the end of the day none of these are moving out <pause dur="short"/> I'm not moving out <pause dur="short"/> it's family <pause dur="short"/> innit really so you might as well</u>
<u n="1008" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah but I'm not on Facebook or got a phone number</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0046">I'm not on Facebook</u>
<u n="1010" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you've got a phone number <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got nothing</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0046">if you look in that cupboard there's a bit of paper with a phone number on it</u>
<u n="1012" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">shall I take it?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0046" trans="overlap">you can take it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> on the bottom shelf <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit of paper with a <unclear/> phone number on it</u>
<u n="1014" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah who's is that? alright</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0046"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I see what you're doing <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1017" who="S0046">huh <pause dur="short"/> it wouldn't matter</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0046"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you want to hit the hard stuff?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0041">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="1020" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you want a push bike <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm not going by myself</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0046">what? You're just afraid of getting jumped</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0041">that's not surprising seeing as</u>
<u n="1023" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">no <pause dur="short"/> I mean you say that but twice in the last few days I've thought fuck it I went down the subway <pause dur="short"/> down the subway</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0046">get you you fucking rebel</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0086">I don't go down the subway <pause dur="short"/> I've been flashed before</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0046">Down the subway?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0086">yeah not here</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0046">really?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0086">in Plymouth</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0046">oh okay</u>
<u n="1031" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah no no the subway as in Grafton you went down and up</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'm going to pinch these if that's okay</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0086">yeah yeah yeah not in like Subway sandwich place</u>
<u n="1034" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no Subway Subway but <pause dur="short"/> oh gosh I've fucked up twice now</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'm okay to beer pinch</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0086">to what?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0041">beer pinch</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0086">oh help yourself love <pause dur="short"/> in the fridge</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0041">it'll be empty until Wednesday you are aware of that don't you? So if you need it tomorrow it'll be gone</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0086">no no no <trunc>mi</trunc> mid-week drinking <pause dur="short"/> it's what I say every week and then I drink every week but <pause dur="short"/> I'm really going to try this time</u>
<u n="1041" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0046">that's the trouble living in this house isn't it really?</u>
<u n="1043" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what drinking too much?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0046">it is only weekends that we usually drink</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0086">can you not see it? Did we drink them all <pause dur="short"/> it's lying down</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0041">I think we did <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>ly</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc> yeah it's lying down</u>
<u n="1047" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">there's a Guinness there</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0041">it's lying down</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0086">yeah you can have Guinness</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0041">it's from the cake</u>
<u n="1051" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">one of us would like Guinness</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0046">oh is that open Guinness is it?</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's what I mean about the cake</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0086">I <trunc>li</trunc> no no no have the Guinness if anyone wants it</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0086">I didn't think anyone liked it <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> drinks them so <pause dur="short"/> left them in the fridge</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0041">how's he doing by the way <pause dur="short"/> I'm so sorry for being such a miserable fucker this morning</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0086"><trunc>Men</trunc> he's mental <pause dur="short"/> no I genuinely thought that he'd woken everybody up up in the house</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0041">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought he'd woke me up as well I was like no I was just being a miserable fucker</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0046">Cos I was  I was  talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not not been contemplating that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would still be in bed cos it was like half eleven</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0086">well we went up</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0041">no I was up</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0086">I went for a shower at eleven and then I came <pause dur="short"/> and your door was open but ajar <pause dur="short"/> and when I came down it was closed and I thought you were probably awake so then when I was up and wasn't being quiet and then I thought</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0041">yeah I'd been awake for ages and ages <pause dur="short"/> I'd been awake since about eight o'clock</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0086">when I saw you face I thought must something wrong but em didn't have time to stop and check</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0046">well something was wrong but</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0041">no it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> I was just being a miserable fucker</u>
<u n="1069" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">just cos I didn't wake her up in the morning <pause dur="short"/> crazy horse</u>
<u n="1070" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1071" who="S0046">no she came home last night</u>
<u n="1072" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm going to come here on the barbecue <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to  I'm going to  try and get a horse costume</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0041">please do</u>
<u n="1074" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">just for you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1075" who="S0041">get a two person like pantomime horse</u>
<u n="1076" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">nah that would just be me and I'll just put like</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0086">dragging your arse behind</u>
<u n="1078" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you know you can get them like <pause dur="short"/> you can get <pause dur="short"/> I'll get a couple of wheels and like attach it to my waist and just walk in like that</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0046">neigh</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0041">like the <trunc>me</trunc> the the wooden pole with a horse on the front</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0086">that would be easier</u>
<u n="1082" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what was that?  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what was that?  The wooden what?</u>
<u n="1083" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1084" who="S0041">you know what I meant  You know what I meant</u>
<u n="1085" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> I mean like a last sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="1086" who="S0046">I actually thought you were calling <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a horse earlier</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0041">crazy horse</u>
<u n="1088" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not an actual horse you know</u>
<u n="1090" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Cos I'm <trunc>wa</trunc> cos I'm wild yeah?</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0041">well you're just a little bit nuts</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0046" trans="overlap">did you mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though?</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0041">just a little nuts</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0046">so you did actually technically call <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a crazy horse</u>
<u n="1097" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I'm a little wild yeah</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0041">maybe</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0046">so</u>
<u n="1100" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you were alright <pause dur="short"/> soon as I walked in I was like brr <pause dur="short"/> I so <unclear/> I'm being a horse don't worry <pause dur="short"/> and people are walking through</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> seemed really good today</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0086">mm?</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in here today and I'm not <pause dur="short"/> every time I've seen here the past like couple of weeks she's been really really off with me</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0086">yeah me too</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0041">and em these two came in making brr horse noises being really daft and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were sat in the garden <pause dur="short"/> I'd been there all afternoon and <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came down and like I was washing stuff</u>
<u n="1106" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah as I was walking through the door</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0041">and she was really laughing and I came in and she'd got a blue shirt on <pause dur="short"/> it really really suited here <pause dur="short"/> em and she was quite chatty and she was laughing I said oh I'm putting my towels in third time lucky <pause dur="short"/> she said oh I've seen them on here whoever that is <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's me putting my towels in and walking away and forgetting about them and <pause dur="short"/> she was really chatty actually so</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0046">oh news news</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0086">that's good</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0046">speaking of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and old people <pause dur="short"/> did you see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yesterday?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0086">I think that was her dad</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0041">ah I didn't see it</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0086">I think it I hope it was her dad cos she left with the suitcases so I figured it was her dad taking her home</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0046">oh really?</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hope so <pause dur="short"/> cos he was a real old man <pause dur="short"/> what the fuck is the matter with the Spanish girls and the old men</u>
<u n="1116" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1117" who="S0086">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> please be her dad <pause dur="short"/> but do you know what's hilarious <pause dur="short"/> cos I came in here making fairy cakes <pause dur="short"/> they're gabbling away in Spanish fine <pause dur="short"/> and then then it went a bit quiet <pause dur="short"/> and I went hi how's it going?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0046">quiet with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> around?</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0086">yeah but then then they stopped talking and then they started whispering <pause dur="short"/> in Spanish <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if you know I don't speak Spanish so you might as well just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1120" who="S0041">shout all you like</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0086">but the fact that you're now whispering tells me that you are taking about me <pause dur="short"/> so fuck off</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0041">no way</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why I was giggling I was <trunc>la</trunc> I laughed out loud I thought it was hilarious</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0041">no way</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0046" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0041">thing is they know  they know  that if they speak fast I can't understand <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I can understand <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a really really strong accent</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0086" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> talks so fast</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0041">but even though she <pause dur="short"/> even if she slows down her accent is really thick <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where the fucks she's from <pause dur="short"/> but she's got a really thick accent</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0046" trans="overlap">loud deep</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0086">country</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0041">and I've said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> before when you're talking</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0046">yeah I reckon she's inland isn't she?</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0041">I can understand what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s saying no matter how fast she speaks because that's what I'm good at the the listening bit <pause dur="short"/> all my listening marks at at degree were all firsts <pause dur="short"/> her I don't have a fucking clue <pause dur="short"/> but I've noticed sometimes if I'm in here they will both speak really fast <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm not daft <pause dur="short"/> I know how you usually speak <pause dur="short"/> are you not thinking I know exactly what you're doing</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0046">but maybe she's doing it because of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1137" who="S0041">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> no it's like I was was talking like this on purpose just so the other person can't understand</u>
<u n="1138" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what?</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0041">it's extreme</u>
<u n="1140" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I speak like this so the other person can't understand</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0046"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1142" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I think I'm going to toilet <pause dur="short"/> alright</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0041">honestly it's really really extreme</u>
<u n="1144" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I understand what she said</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0046">yeah I got it</u>
<u n="1146" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's like when I go <foreign lang="pol"></foreign></u>
<u n="1147" who="S0046">yeah something like that Polish bastard</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0041">that wasn't Polish</u>
<u n="1149" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you <unclear/> you don't know what I'm saying do you?</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0041">that wasn't Polish</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0046">yeah it was</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0041">say it again</u>
<u n="1153" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="pol"></foreign></u>
<u n="1154" who="S0041">Don't know what that was</u>
<u n="1155" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">get on your knees and please suck my dick</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0046"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1157" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's all the teach like I'm not being <unclear/> All they teach me is rude stuff apart from hello and bye and thank you and all that</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0086">all the need to knows</u>
<u n="1159" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">but that's all they teach me</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0041">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="1161" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">all that they need know a man needs to know</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0041">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0086">so when you're trying to order a taxi that's going to be out the window</u>
<u n="1164" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no I'll be like eh taxi to this place</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0041">say say thank you</u>
<u n="1166" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="pol"></foreign></u>
<u n="1167" who="S0041"><foreign lang="pol"></foreign> Say sorry</u>
<u n="1168" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no they haven't taught me that yet</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0041"><foreign lang="pol"></foreign></u>
<u n="1170" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no fuck that</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0041">say goodbye</u>
<u n="1172" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0041"><foreign lang="pol"></foreign></u>
<u n="1174" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Don't even know that</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0041">that is basically it</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0046">can you speak Polish as well?</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0041">no I used to work in a place where the people who worked in the kitchen and did the pot wash were Polish and I felt bad that I couldn't speak to them so I just learnt a few words</u>
<u n="1178" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="pol"></foreign> Do you know what <foreign lang="pol"></foreign> is?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> did I tell you about the fake model language test?</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0086">what?</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0041">so the <trunc>gir</trunc> the women that I saw at the navy she was saying she saw my thought process for the CT thing and she said that navy are the only force that don't have a</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0046" trans="overlap">sorry I'm not trying to touch you up</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0041">yeah he is  Yeah he is</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0046">I'm not  I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0041">she said <pause dur="short"/> me too me please  me too me please  She said the navy are the only force that don't have a</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0046">it isn't going to take you long to get the hard stiff is it?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0041">intelligence officer</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0046">Don't need two people</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0041">em the military have one the RAF have one and the Navy don't</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0086">okay</u>
<event desc="begin overlap"/>
<u n="1191" who="S0041">so they had em <pause dur="short"/> a communications systems CS basically <pause dur="short"/> they have a CS and and CT <pause dur="short"/> a CT is slightly higher but they do quite a similar job apart from a CT gets plopped between ships all the time and to the <trunc>Emira</trunc> to the army and to the Royal Marines and to the RAF <pause dur="short"/> they get pulled out all the time</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0086">wow that's really interesting</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0041">yeah so if I went in as a CT chances are I'd be in actually on a submarine <pause dur="short"/> they pop them out all the time whereas I wanted to be sitting on a ship cos that's what I like the whole team ship thing</u>
<event desc="end overlap"/>
<u n="1194" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you want to have a fag on the way?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0046">she didn't text me back by the way</u>
<u n="1196" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">who? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0046">which makes me don't want to go round there</u>
<u n="1198" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no <pause dur="short"/> well no you can wait by the alley</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0046">I need to bump into boobs and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> the other <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1200" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well we're going that way anyway</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0046">at some point <pause dur="short"/> they've been quiet recently to be fair</u>
<u n="1202" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">we can knock on the way if you like</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0046">no we'll get distracted</u>
<u n="1204" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah probably <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sneeze"/> Bless you</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0046"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is taken so</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0041">em but they don't have an officer in that division because they're quite mobile they just pop them anywhere <pause dur="short"/> and she said they're basically trying to melt down CTs to merge the CT and the CS which is slightly lower than what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does job as one job and bring in em an intelligence officer</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0086">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0041">so she said if you go as em a warfare officer then you could you know if you decide after a couple of years it's not what you enjoy <vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="1209" who="S0086">bless you</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0041">thank you <pause dur="short"/> you could merge over because that's the way it's going <vocal desc="sneeze"/> to be em as an intelligence officer <pause dur="short"/> and what they do is they they're the people that know all the languages <pause dur="short"/> all of the languages</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0086">all of those languages</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0041">and they said it doesn't matter how many languages you know because they give you an exam <pause dur="short"/> and they've had people go in with a masters that speak six languages and they can't pass the test</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0086">oh my God</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0041">yeah and I was like how? <vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="1215" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">bless you</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0041">that's me washing those things a million times</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0086">is it?</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0041">yeah I can smell it?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0086">allergies?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0041">em <pause dur="short"/> she said basically they'll they'll test your brain on how capable you are to learn a language <pause dur="short"/> she said cos if you're good at writing you're good at grammar you're good at remembering <pause dur="short"/> that's not what we need <pause dur="short"/> I said good cos that's not what I'm good at <pause dur="short"/> I don't know any of that shit I'm just good at ear wigging <pause dur="short"/> and she's like oh well what we do is we give you a fake model language test <pause dur="short"/> a fake watch now it's basically language that they've made up within the forces <pause dur="short"/> no one knows it and you can never learn it cos it's not real <pause dur="short"/> em and they give you a passage to listen to a passage to read and test you on it <pause dur="short"/> it's completely fabricated</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0086">A made up language</u>
<u n="1222" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah but as soon as you're in you you get the lingo like <pause dur="short"/> when the squaddies come into my work cos obviously I used to go to army bases when I was in cadets you catch onto the lingo and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1223" who="S0041">no but this is a fake thing</u>
<u n="1224" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">like a boot neck is a royal marine</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0041">but I'm not talking kind of slang <pause dur="short"/> I'm talking all three forces have sat down and created an entire language like they have a dictionary for it but it's fake <pause dur="short"/> none of its real <pause dur="short"/> none of it relates to either a Latin language or a Germanic language <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't have any root whatsoever</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0086" trans="overlap">slang <pause dur="short"/> but it's just in order to test your comprehension</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0041">yes so what they do is they work out whether your brain can latch on to how a language I structured basically <pause dur="short"/> so Latin language is structured differently to Germanics languages <pause dur="short"/> but I mean I know <unclear/> and I've never learnt it but just because I can see how it's made up <pause dur="short"/> and so they test you on it <pause dur="short"/> you've got no chance of revising because it's fake <pause dur="short"/> but it tests how your brain could latch on to it <pause dur="short"/> and she said I've had people come in that have masters and they can't get it <pause dur="short"/> they can't get it they fail it it's not a mark it's a pass or fail <pause dur="short"/> but the guy that they've got that just passed it at the moment is some guy some scouser <pause dur="short"/> left school after GSCE <pause dur="short"/> he speaks eleven languages seven fluently</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0086">shit <pause dur="short"/> how did he learn them all?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he just did it in his spare time cos his brain is made to that <pause dur="short"/> so she said you know  you know  after a couple of years <unclear/> will have moved over you can sit the test <pause dur="short"/> there's no raising but you could just fail it we don't know</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0086">so you do it when you're in there then?</u>
<u n="1231" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1232" who="S0086">you don't do it as</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0041">it's not that post hasn't been made yet <pause dur="short"/> it's going to take a couple of years for them to move the CTs over to the CSs and merge as one role</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0086">well that's good then <pause dur="short"/> so you go in as warfare but no you could be doing something that's a bit more useful for you languages <pause dur="short"/> well that's good</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0041">and she said you know if you fail it you fail it like it doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/> but yeah how weird is that</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0086">very weird</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0041">I was like fake language test <pause dur="short"/> I said I'm really excited I want to try it</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0086" trans="overlap">I had no idea <unclear/> a fake language</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0041">yeah I was like I really want to try it <pause dur="short"/> I said do you think I can get it online and pretend <pause dur="short"/> and she was like no</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0086">well that would sort of negate the test</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0086">I thought you meant like it was a fake test like they got it from school or something but actually like it's like a fake language</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how mental is that?</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0086">that's a lot of time and effort to go to isn't it? To create a fake language</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0041">yeah but to a language person <pause dur="short"/> like I told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he was like fuck I want to go <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah I really want to go too <pause dur="short"/> cos it would be really like exciting to see if your brain could do it cos you don't get a choice <pause dur="short"/> there's no way you can train your brain to do it <pause dur="short"/> it just either can or it can't</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0041">and I think  I think  I could do it and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> couldn't</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0086">Cos <unclear/> learner of language so one of you can do it</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0041" trans="overlap">the way you learn it</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos like when we moved to places abroad</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0041">I couldn't reply cos I couldn't I never studied properly but I could understand everything they is a <pause dur="short"/> so we used to stand there and I'd listen to everything <pause dur="short"/> I could say in English my name is in Italian my name is and the number two <pause dur="short"/> obviously really went to all my classes</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0086">totally did yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0041">all of them <pause dur="short"/> so we'd stand there and for three month I listened to everyone told him what they were saying in English and he replied in Italian cos he could study and remember it</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0086">that's weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because I know her because she came over the year before to our university in Hull as a teacher of languages <pause dur="short"/> she was a student but that's what you do do the exchange <pause dur="short"/> so we went back over to see her <pause dur="short"/> and she did say to me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> fuck like you're screwed <pause dur="short"/> you never came to any of my classes <pause dur="short"/> what are you going to do? But I stood there and understood everything and relayed it to him and then he's reply in Italian <pause dur="short"/> I'd no idea what the fuck he was saying couldn't work it out but</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0086">and that's the thing cos even when you they make you do your oral test all you basically do is learn a passage</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0041">mm hm</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0086">that's what we did for my German exam</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0041">that's all I did <pause dur="short"/> so all my written exams I did I'd written an essay spent years going through the dictionary <pause dur="short"/> I remembered it off my heart <pause dur="short"/> couldn't write in now</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0086">yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0041">at all</u>
<u n="1264" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you go to eh Tesco's in <anon type="place"/> Chesham</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0041">in my life?</u>
<u n="1266" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">now</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0046" trans="overlap">shut at eleven <pause dur="short"/> I think they shut at eleven</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0041">in my life I have been there</u>
<u n="1269" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what time they shut?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0041">no idea</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0046">I think they shut at eleven so it'll be ten on Sunday</u>
<u n="1272" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">we'll go Tesco's then</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0046">I'll see you in a bit</u>
<u n="1274" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">go pick up the hard stuff <pause dur="short"/> just for you alright? Just for you</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0041">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0046">see you in a bit</u>
<u n="1277" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">see you in a bit</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0041">see you soon</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0086">bye bye</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0041">yes that's quite exciting</u>
<u n="1281" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you a starling fan <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yes?</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1283" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've got something for you later</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0086">oh God</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0041">yes that's quite exciting</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0086">present in his pants</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0041">he's in is pants?</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0086">present in his pants <pause dur="short"/> that's what he's got for you</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> did not hear that did I?</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0086">no no that wasn't said it was implied</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0041">no no <pause dur="short"/> oh oh right okay <pause dur="short"/> I should be very excited then surely</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0086">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> look forward to that exposure later <pause dur="short"/> I just find him really tiring when I'm tried it just eh makes my head hurt</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0041">squash your face against the floor</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0086">yeah I might go to bed when they get back <pause dur="short"/> it makes me tired</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0041">I've definitely been drinking since about four o'clock this afternoon</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0086">that's definitely fine</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0041">it was required</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0086">I haven't even drunk that much this weekend cos I've been driving everywhere <pause dur="short"/> I drank a bit on Friday night which was nice but I really there was a point when I was like I don't want to go  I don't want to go I don't want to go I don't want to go I don't want to go</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0046">do you really want the hard stuff?</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0046">I can get another crate</u>
<u n="1302" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">if some if someone has a quid that's it</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0046">I can get another quid</u>
<u n="1304" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a quid <pause dur="short"/> beer or hard stuff?</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0046">beer <pause dur="short"/> beer or</u>
<u n="1307" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">beer</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0046">she's happy with either or <pause dur="short"/> I'm good with that</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0046">I'm good with either or</u>
<u n="1311" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well it's up to you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> there it is <pause dur="short"/> we'll take your bike yeah?</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0046">okay</u>
<u n="1313" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0046"><unclear/> bike</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0041">it's Craig having issues</u>
<u n="1316" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's like throwing coins on you when I'm sitting on the street innit <pause dur="short"/> I'll lock your bike up to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s car <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are you taking your car in the morning?</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1318" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh damn it <pause dur="short"/> what about you? Are you taking <unclear/></u>
<u n="1319" who="S0086">Don't touch my car</u>
<u n="1320" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I won't be touching it <unclear/> lock</u>
<event desc="m leaves"/>
<event desc="0046 leaves"/>
<u n="1321" who="S0041">did you just see that top turn on</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0041">that's nice</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0086">that's pretty normal</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0041">how did your mum enjoy her birthday time?</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0086">she had a really good time I think em <pause dur="short"/> thursday obviously was the ballet which was really nice <pause dur="short"/> start the celebrations <pause dur="short"/> so that was really pretty apart from the neck and the back ache which was destroying <pause dur="short"/> it was really nice <pause dur="short"/> friday did I come home? I think I came home and I went out <pause dur="short"/> em yeah I think I did  I think I did  come home <pause dur="short"/> oh I went to get my hair cut <pause dur="short"/> that's what I did <pause dur="short"/> went to get my hair cut <pause dur="short"/> then I came home had a bath picked my brother up <pause dur="short"/> in fact actually he came over got a taxi over <pause dur="short"/> but the taxi I was really like fidgety I was really I don't I don't want to go  I don't want to go I don't want to go I don't want to go  I don't know who's going to be there</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0086">yeah my mum had tied up the side room of the pub <pause dur="short"/> you know can where you have functions and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but it's all sort of open <pause dur="short"/> it's eh <unclear/> just keep walking round and round like it's like a restaurant in one side and a pub in the other and there's this room at the back <pause dur="short"/> and eh I knew we were late which was making me panicky anyway <pause dur="short"/> and I was like I don't  I don't  know who is going to be there I don't want I don't really want to go <pause dur="short"/> so I was just talking absolute shit to Richard I was just gabbling on cos I just thought if I talk then I don't have to worry <pause dur="short"/> got to the pub and my mum was was there and my sister was there <pause dur="short"/> she's got a really bad flu bless her she'd actually passed out <pause dur="short"/> did I tell you she died her hair green?</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0041">no no</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0086">she had to go to work with green hair <pause dur="short"/> love her <pause dur="short"/> so she's been throwing the like bright bright blonde and eh she'd tried to die it on the</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0041">Brown</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0086">Wednesday night yeah like a sort of dark blond brown but hadn't used  hadn't used  the one with red in it until it had gone green <pause dur="short"/> had to go to work with green hair <pause dur="short"/> luckily works in a shop so the lighting is pretty bad <pause dur="short"/> I she came to meet us at the cinema and I was like oh your hair's what what colour is your hair? And she was like don't talk to me about my hair <pause dur="short"/> I can't really talk about it yet <pause dur="short"/> mum was like it's gone green <pause dur="short"/> couldn't really tell in the light <pause dur="short"/> I was like it's funny colour <pause dur="short"/> she said yeah it's it's not not the colour it's supposed to be <pause dur="short"/> so then after the ballet which finished at half ten we bought three bottle of hair dye with the red in it</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0086">so a sort of mahogany colour and then went home and dyed her hair <pause dur="short"/> it's like your hair there's just masses of it <pause dur="short"/> every time you lift a bit up there's more <pause dur="short"/> half one until half one they were dying her hair and then she had to get up at seven to go to work <pause dur="short"/> bless her so she's really poorly <pause dur="short"/> so she managed to drag herself there on Friday with better hair so that was good <pause dur="short"/> em and then my mum's friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I used to work with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> they're like Turkish girls they're really nice <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen them for ages so actually it was quite a nice evening <pause dur="short"/> they'd bought my mu as a present like a notebook like a diary and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had written from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the front she'd written in like happy birthday <pause dur="short"/> hope all your dramas come true <pause dur="short"/> and everyone wrote her a little message in the book <pause dur="short"/> so it was really nice <pause dur="short"/> and then some more friends turned up a bit later and <pause dur="short"/> left about eleven eleven thirty something like that <pause dur="short"/> and Saturday made the cupcakes</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0041">the cupcakes</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0086">made the cupcakes got the flowers got the fizz went over sat in the garden all afternoon and then dropped my brother off about eight <pause dur="short"/> picked up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came here <pause dur="short"/> ate like three Pringles and fell asleep <pause dur="short"/> woke up and six again in the morning I was really tired <pause dur="short"/> and eh I thought God he must think I'm really boring in bed now like <pause dur="short"/> the first few weeks I was really excited and now I'm falling asleep at like half ten <pause dur="short"/> he must be like God you're really boring <pause dur="short"/> but he'd fallen asleep as well <pause dur="short"/> like the morning he was like I think we're both like a bit tried last night <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it was nice and then I dropped him off went over there to pick up my uncle and my sister from mum's and then drove them to my dad's had lunch with my dad and <pause dur="short"/> it's always quite hard work with hi sometimes like his memory is going a bit I think <pause dur="short"/> he forgets when he tells me things <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit shit <pause dur="short"/> and then it eh</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0041">it's hard to be patient isn't it?</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0086">it's hard to be patient and it makes me worried because his mum my nan had Alzheimer's so I'm really aware of it</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0041">yeah I remember you saying</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0086">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm always like really heightened to it <pause dur="short"/> then went over to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>' which is nice <pause dur="short"/> they cooked some like mushroom gnocchi thing which was quite nice <pause dur="short"/> had a little garble on with them talked about weddings <pause dur="short"/> I feel like I've got weddings coming out of my ears as I'm sure you appreciate</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I was going to say actually when em payday comes round I'll get eh get online at book hoteledge straight away</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0086">oh yeah we haven't done that <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> that's right when do you get paid <pause dur="short"/> wednesday?</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0041">twenty-eighth yeah <pause dur="short"/> wednesday</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0086"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0041">thank fuck</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0086">so are you going to go to Peterborough on Friday night again are you?</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0041">yeah I think so  Yeah I think so  I think <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s having a bit of a hard time of it with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think she's coming to the point of <pause dur="short"/> there's always been quite a gap between them intelligence wise and so far they've kind of dealt with it <pause dur="short"/> as in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't know <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said well actually I I like all the qualities that he has so I'm just ignoring that <pause dur="short"/> but she spent the last three to six months going through his divorce with him and basically doing his accounts <pause dur="short"/> and she's of and shit loads of money like thousands and thousands of pounds that his</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0086">oh my God</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0041">now ex-wife has been hiding <pause dur="short"/> and I think now she kind of feels that all the work that he's helped her with on the house you know <pause dur="short"/> tiling thing sand helping her raking up stuff in the garden and all that snazzer <pause dur="short"/> you know she's matched and more with what the help she's <trunc>in</trunc> like intellectually given him for the divorce</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0041">and she's like he's lovely <pause dur="short"/> and he is nice he is very nice <pause dur="short"/> he's very much like a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though you know <pause dur="short"/> he's a hoverer <pause dur="short"/> like she's doing things he's can I do this can I help with that <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0086">you need your won space sometimes don't you?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0041">yeah she's like he's getting too much he's around all the time and <pause dur="short"/> I want my weekends to spend doing my garden or spend doing my house and <pause dur="short"/> so she's finding it quite hard to force him to get his own life a <trunc>arou</trunc> apart from her <pause dur="short"/> cos he's just just doing everything for her <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit weird  It's a built weird  but she's right in what she's saying <pause dur="short"/> you know in the long run there must come a point where that's as far as their relationship can go <pause dur="short"/> cos they're not equally matched <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know she's a bit moshed <pause dur="short"/> and I think that's a little bit why she wants me to move back in there</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> bit of support here</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0041">yeah so</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0086">it would be nice for you as well <pause dur="short"/> but I see what you mean like you can't help but like it's a bit of a regressive step</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0086">my mum said to me like you know if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does get a place on the course of she does move to London or whatever she ends up doing they'll always be a place for you here and you know <pause dur="short"/> I understand if you don't want to move back but you know if it's useful and you know just always know that there's space for us <pause dur="short"/> I think she did feel really bad when I came back from Croatia and she was like yeah by the way you've got to move out</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0041">you've got to move out <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0086">see you later <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0041">I suppose she would but she didn't have a choice in the matter</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0086" trans="overlap">em <pause dur="short"/> it was how it was <pause dur="short"/> no that's it <pause dur="short"/> and ultimately I would never have stayed there <pause dur="short"/> I would never have made <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> find somewhere <pause dur="short"/> you know she was the one who needed it and I was working and you know I was the older sister so obviously going to but <pause dur="short"/> yeah depending what I want to do</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0041">you take that role even though</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0086">what the fuck is going on</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0041">what are you doing?</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0086">they're being dickheads</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0041">yeah I see what you mean though</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0046">I'm sorry we're children</u>
<u n="1369" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0041">mm hm</u>
<u n="1371" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm a crazy horse</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="1373" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">did that scare you</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0041">I little I thought it was burglars</u>
<u n="1375" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">really? We wouldn't let that happen <pause dur="short"/> after you sir <pause dur="short"/> you've got the beers <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0046">I'm also a cripple</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0041">yeah it's a bit of a random situation</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0041">but I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying you know <pause dur="short"/> I know it feels like you're taking a bit of a step backwards <pause dur="short"/> but sometimes you know you have to take a step backwards to move forwards <pause dur="short"/> and I was like yeah I get that I understand that at some point sometimes you know you just have to swallow your pride and get on with it because in the long run it's going to help you out <pause dur="short"/> I understand that <pause dur="short"/> hey</u>
<u n="1380" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hiya</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0046">would anyone like one?</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0086">no I'm fine thanks</u>
<u n="1383" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0041">em <pause dur="short"/> I said but I like having you here <pause dur="short"/> I like that no matter what craziness I'm dealing with that</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0086">sorry am I in your way?</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0041">like I like no matter what craziness I'm hit with</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0041">that there's someone I trust that I can run things by <pause dur="short"/> not that I don't trust <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but it's always going to be a very different opinion that I get <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0046">he must think we're right bad asses in the Co-op</u>
<u n="1392" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0046">he was like you bought twenty-four earlier</u>
<u n="1394" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I told him we were going to get the <unclear/> like that</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0041">yeah so I don't know what to do about that</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0086">just  You know there's no rush is there?</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I said that too I said really you know <pause dur="short"/> I've dealt with this ridiculous wage for longer than now <pause dur="short"/> but the the killer is like come birthday time or come Christmas time <pause dur="short"/> like she said to me</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0086">there's no extra cash</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0041">extra miles in the car <pause dur="short"/> yeah she said em I don't mean to be rude but do you want me to give you money for your birthday rather than a gift because I think that's probably going to help you right now <pause dur="short"/> and I was like yeah actually I would thanks <pause dur="short"/> she knows that I've got my car coming out and she knows that I need to replace <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and it's just it's not nice at twenty-five years old to have to rely on somebody else for a bit of cash cos I'm thinking actually as as digging my heels in as it sounds I've studied my arse off <pause dur="short"/> I'm actually quite capable</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0086">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0041">and the kick in the teeth was I went to meet her <pause dur="short"/> went to meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> after I saw the navy guy <pause dur="short"/> drove round to her office and she had a young lad with her <pause dur="short"/> and I thought he was like seventeen turns out he's twenty-one and I'm just a granny <pause dur="short"/> whatever</u>
<u n="1402" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you're not a granny you're twenty-two</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0046">twenty-two twenty-two</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0041">and he's helping her with the accounts and <unclear/> and just basically chasing people of them sorting out invoices <pause dur="short"/> and they're pay she I saw her with him and she's chasing it every single thing he does she's on his back because he's shit <pause dur="short"/> he's capable <pause dur="short"/> he's going back to uni to be a mature student at twenty-one <pause dur="short"/> but she has to flow every single phone call that he makes <pause dur="short"/> he's on seventeen and a half</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and she was like I'm sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I watch him and I know you and I can't understand how the hell that's that's equally weighted</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0086">it's because of the industries you work in isn't it</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0041">so that's what she's saying <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0086">I was shocked and appalled that actually like entry level jobs in my office are eighteen grand <pause dur="short"/> and that's just bit bit of filing bit of stapling few contracts</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0041">sit there and look like you know what you're doing</u>
<event desc="m enters"/>
<event desc="0046 enters"/>
<u n="1411" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">wish I was</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0046">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's done now</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0086" trans="overlap">like it's normally you're not really you know speaking to suppliers that often <pause dur="short"/> you might be sometimes but you're certainly not meeting them face to face</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0041">yeah send a few faxes and that</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0086" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1416" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0041">forward an email maybe</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0046">yes <pause dur="short"/> it hurts when you've been on twenty-two twenty-five and you have to drop down to scrimping wage you know?</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0086" trans="overlap">yeah if you think what Eve is on it's pretty shite considering everything that she's supposed to do but it's juts basic salary like <pause dur="short"/> if you think that you know if you're realistic about what's what's going to happen with the army recruitment</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0086">now is the time to be looking at jobs</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0086">just in case</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's what she was saying like start looking but look Peterborough way cos</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0086">well look everywhere</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0041">you can stay here</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0086">look up the guy in the marketing recruitment office again <pause dur="short"/> see if he's got anything</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0041">yeah back at Brand</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0046">that's a hot curry as well</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0041">it smells good whatever that was</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0086">smells amazing</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0046">smells of curry</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0041">it's really nice</u>
<u n="1436" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like I smell curry and then you two are talking away he's like <pause dur="short"/> that's a good curry <pause dur="short"/> she was like that <pause dur="short"/> my curry</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0046">that's a definitely take away curry right there</u>
<u n="1438" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you want to go out there <pause dur="short"/> all all of this <unclear/></u>
<u n="1439" who="S0046">you can smell the difference between a normal curry and a take away curry</u>
<u n="1440" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">let's all go up there and go</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0046"><unclear/> curry place</u>
<u n="1442" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what a bitch <pause dur="short"/> you shouldn't put it in my way then</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0046">I can't it's my size tens leave me alone</u>
<u n="1444" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you wouldn't have them shoes if it was me</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0041">I was thinking actually when my rebate comes through from the tax</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0086">there's a letter from the tax office did you see?</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0041">yeah I opened it <pause dur="short"/> do you know what it was to say</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0086">you're on the wrong tax code</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0041">thank you <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thank you for calling us we've made sure you're on the correct tax code for April <pause dur="short"/> looked at it it's wrong</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0086">still wrong?</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0041">so they've reassessed and put me on the correct tax code for April and they think I'm on eighty grand</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0086">Good</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0041">yeah cheers</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0086">Good</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0041">thanks for that yeah</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0086">but that's for this financial year then?</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0041">no that's for the next one <pause dur="short"/> they've set me up</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0086">from April <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0041">so they know they've fucked over me for the last eight months</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0041">and but it's okay cos from April I'm good <pause dur="short"/> eh lies</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0086">shit</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0041">I'm going to chase that fucker up</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0086">so you'll still be paying too much</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> I can change it though <pause dur="short"/> I have to take it to the accountant tomorrow</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0086">this is ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> you'll be owed such a rebate though</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0041">I don't think it's going to be massive cos they only juts gave me one didn't they not long ago? I think it's going to be about three hundred</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0046">I was I'm looking forward to one</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0086" trans="overlap">be nice though</u>
<u n="1470" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">still <pause dur="short"/> every little helps <pause dur="short"/> that's Tesco's</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0041">every little helps</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0086">you said have you paid your taxes yet?</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0046">I paid some but technically I haven't earned enough</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0086">Cos you haven't declared it</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0046">so I should get some</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0041">from the beginning of the year?</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0046">mm</u>
<u n="1479" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">there's you lot talking about eighty grand we're like <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1480" who="S0046">well from March I'm still getting paid in March when I got sacked from the bar I was still getting paid cos I don't technically get sacked until the first of April or something around there</u>
<u n="1481" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well yeah and then you've got your holiday cos it did it so late</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1483" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">whatever your earned</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0041">that reminds me <pause dur="short"/> I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> earlier <pause dur="short"/> and em you know I've said to her about moving firms before and he's just such a country bumpkin he thinks he can just stay there forever <pause dur="short"/> he got a pay rise and I was like of that's good</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0086">thirty is he on?</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0041">twenty</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0086">his?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0041">his basically salary <pause dur="short"/> he said and now it's hit the twenty figures</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0086" trans="overlap">okay he works on commission though doesn't he?</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0041">his commission is shit</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0086">is it?</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0041">so I said what is your commission? One per cent of everything over eighty-four thousand pounds per month</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0086">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're well in the wrong job</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0041">he's been in sales for fourteen years and he thinks that's acceptable to be on twenty</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0086">oh bless him <pause dur="short"/> but surely his rent must be quite a lot though isn't Cottenham quite expensive?</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no his his dad doesn't pay for a thing</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0086">is his dad <unclear/> got kids</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0046">yeah but he's on twenty plus how many benefits?</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0041" trans="overlap">he doesn't like mention his kid</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0086">oh really? Does he pay for his kid</u>
<u n="1501" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah it's all about benefits</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> she won't let him have anything to do with him <pause dur="short"/> can't even speak to him</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0046" trans="overlap">how many benefits is he on?</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0086">really? Why?</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0041">Cos she's a cracker</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0086">Cos she's a <pause dur="short"/> right yeah</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0041">she's a nutter yeah</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0086">even though he'd be a really good dad actually</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0041" trans="overlap">doesn't even know where she lives</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0086">Cos he's got quite a big heart hasn't he?</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> doesn't been know where they live <pause dur="short"/> can't even get in touch with them</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0086">he doesn't even know where his son is</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0086">fuck</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0041">can't even get in touch with them</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0086">she must really gate him then not to accept any money</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0041">she must be a douche <pause dur="short"/> yeah she won't take</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0046">hasn't he got kids that he sees though?</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0041">no no no <pause dur="short"/> he's got a son that he doesn't see <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="1520" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">she's gonna fucking go back on that though <pause dur="short"/> no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1521" who="S0046">she can</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and he can't  he can't  even get in touch with her anymore because she basically fucked off with him <pause dur="short"/> doesn't speak to her won't allow her family to speak to him and he can't even <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't even know where they live now <pause dur="short"/> yorkshire is as far as he knows <pause dur="short"/> if they've not moved</u>
<u n="1523" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah but she's probably going to fuck him over no offence</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0046">she could</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0086">yeah but he if he's meant to be if he's made the effort to get in touch with her and she's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1526" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">she's gonna say look he's not been in contact</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah the solicitors know</u>
<u n="1528" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah but he needs proof <pause dur="short"/> he needs proof</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0086">he will have proof</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0041">no yeah he's got it <pause dur="short"/> the solicitors know that he's tried</u>
<u n="1531" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> as long as he's got proof that's fine <pause dur="short"/> cos otherwise she can go well there's nothing there</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0086">you've you've never contacted me</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0046">he he didn't mention much about this <pause dur="short"/> I'm worried about this</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1536" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> don't worry about what I said</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0041">yeah the solicitors know he's tried</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> gutted <pause dur="short"/> so long as you've made the effort to try <pause dur="short"/> they can't  They can't  force you</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0041">yeah he sent loads of letters <pause dur="short"/> to the point where the solicitor said I'm really sorry we don't know where to send them anymore</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0086">fuck</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0086">Cos that's the ultimate that's his son isn't it? Killer</u>
<event desc="begin overlap"/>
<u n="1543" who="S0041">yeah but he <unclear/> and he's great</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0086">ah bless him</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0041">I mean twenty quid I said Al what you doing working now I said <pause dur="short"/> how long have you been in sales now <pause dur="short"/> he said fourteen years <pause dur="short"/> I said do you know Red gate are starting their their new starters not even graduates on twenty-two</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0041">yeah and he was like what? Well what type of sales is that? And I said well it's IT I said I don't really understand it cos it's not my forte at all but either way it's twenty-two <pause dur="short"/> and he was like well yeah but I'm in different sales <pause dur="short"/> I was I like a salesman can sell whatever <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't matter what the fuck he's selling <pause dur="short"/> I could sell a dead camera if you want me to and I've only done sales for six years <pause dur="short"/> he's like yeah well that's good isn't it? Twenty <pause dur="short"/> oh of fucks sake like</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0041">seriously</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0086">some people have different aspirations though <pause dur="short"/> for him if if he thinks hat twenty grand is acceptable</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0041">yeah no but I said to him have you ever thought about moving firm <pause dur="short"/> he was like well yeah cos our firm is nationwide so I thought about upping to Cornwall <pause dur="short"/> I said no no no</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0086">different company</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0041">not your firm <pause dur="short"/> change the company <pause dur="short"/> and he was like yeah but I'm not really financially stable enough to move anywhere <pause dur="short"/> no no no no <pause dur="short"/> stay in Cambridge <pause dur="short"/> stay living where you are <pause dur="short"/> just change the company name</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0086">and then you probably will be financially stable because they would actually pay you proper wage</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0041">but not many people are hiring now and I was like they're always hiring sales <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't matter how much money people have not got the only role they will always take on is sales</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0086">absolutely</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0041">and if you can give them fourteen year experience they'll snap you up</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0086">maybe he's shit</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0041">maybe he's shit</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0086">I mean he's very sweet but I mean I don't know I don't know if I'd buy double glazing from him or whatever it is that he's selling</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0041">tools something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0086">eighty-four grand's worth of tools</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0041">well he makes his quota every month</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0086">does he?</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0041">he makes his bonus <pause dur="short"/> eighty-four thousand pounds he's bringing to that company</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0086">does he? Wow <pause dur="short"/> well he must be  he must be  good then is he's not <pause dur="short"/> for him to get a pay rise even if it is only twenty grand he must be doing something right</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0041">two per cent yeah <pause dur="short"/> two per cent he got yeah</u>
<event desc="end overlap"/>
<u n="1567" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> spoke to me the other day by the way</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0046">who?</u>
<u n="1569" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1570" who="S0046"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has no  <unclear/> a little while ago</u>
<u n="1571" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay yeah</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0046">and she said you <unclear/> To time <unclear/></u>
<u n="1573" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's fine</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1575" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ooh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> scotty wrote on my wall</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0046">right</u>
<u n="1577" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> stag do <pause dur="short"/> you going?</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0046">who me?</u>
<u n="1579" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="1581" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what do you reckon? When do you get paid?</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0046">every week but <pause dur="short"/> next weekend's going to be boring <pause dur="short"/> are you able to transfer?</u>
<u n="1583" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">me?</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1585" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> hopefully</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0046">okay <pause dur="short"/> can I let you know on Thursday?</u>
<u n="1587" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">know on Thursday <pause dur="short"/> I'll <unclear/> Ain't go this number <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s number</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0046"><unclear/> by the way <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you've met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> the bird in here that you you saw <pause dur="short"/> she's not pregnant</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0041">I knew it</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0046">I knew it and all</u>
<u n="1591" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">fat bitch</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0046">to be fair <pause dur="short"/> she's not fat you know she's not fat <pause dur="short"/> you know everything <pause dur="short"/> no you never met you never met her</u>
<u n="1593" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah exactly I was just going to say</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0046">yeah she's not pregnant <pause dur="short"/> I told you I had my spies <pause dur="short"/> my spies came up trumps <pause dur="short"/> not pregnant <pause dur="short"/> walking around with a can of beer <pause dur="short"/> enough said</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0046">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1597" who="S0041">told you you pull the crazy ones</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0046">yeah but I like a little bit of diversity and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="1599" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">and a crazy horse</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0041">A little bit of crazy</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0046">A little bit of crazy is I like a little bit of that and</u>
<u n="1602" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">is that why I'm still here cos I'm a crazy horse?</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0041">I said to you about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though didn't I? At least you can look back no matter what goes on from now on <pause dur="short"/> at least you've got the peace of mind that you can look back and say you tried everything <pause dur="short"/> I think she's a crazy person but it's not my place to say</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0046">I have <pause dur="short"/> yeah no I've I've tried everything now and the rest is down to her you know <pause dur="short"/> if <trunc>sh</trunc> if she wants to live the life the way that she's living <pause dur="short"/> and I'm not saying it's a bad way of living life <pause dur="short"/> at all <pause dur="short"/> she's she's obviously got a direction that she wants to stick to <pause dur="short"/> I think personally she's making a big mistake <pause dur="short"/> cos she's not going to get anyone who loves those kids as much as what I do <pause dur="short"/> she's not going to get anyone that wants to be with her as much as what I do</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0041">do you know what'll happen that actually <pause dur="short"/> if this  If this  is the actual end I think what'll happen in the future is she'll get some guy that's a bit of a douche</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0041">bit of a douche <pause dur="short"/> love the kids and love her but is shit at life</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0041">but she'll take it cos that's what she's used to <pause dur="short"/> I've stolen your lighter <pause dur="short"/> oh no it's my one it's your one</u>
<u n="1610" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no you've stolen my lighter <pause dur="short"/> fuck you</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0046">no <pause dur="short"/> it's a a lighter</u>
<u n="1612" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what did I say to you when  in my bag <pause dur="short"/> what did I say? Tell me now? What are my <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0041">you take <pause dur="short"/> keep it <pause dur="short"/> no it's fine <pause dur="short"/> you're lucky it's a message <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm a crazy horse</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0046">so yeah she is</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so maybe they can cut this shit out tomorrow</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0086">do it <pause dur="short"/> get them to hack it out</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0041">hack it out</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0086">A bit of the A and E</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0046">I hope  I hope  so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> don't don't walk away unsatisfied</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0086">maybe it's your twin</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0041">my twin</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0086">maybe it's going to have hair and teeth</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0041">and fingernails</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0086">what what is it in my Big Fat Gypsy Wedding? Em em <pause dur="short"/> no Gypsy <pause dur="short"/> greek wedding <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0041">ooh yes</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0086">when she says em</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0041">what is it?</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0086"><trunc>Bi</trunc> <trunc>bi</trunc></u>
<u n="1629" who="S0041">bebedubdub</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0086"><trunc>Bi</trunc> <trunc>bi</trunc> bivdisi <pause dur="short"/> she's trying to say <trunc>biop</trunc> biopsy isn't she? Bibopsy</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0041">bibedy <pause dur="short"/> bibopsy</u>
<u n="1632" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1633" who="S0041">bibopsy <pause dur="short"/> bibopsy <pause dur="short"/> has she had the <trunc>bibi</trunc> babadap badaba badebopsy</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0086">bebebopsy <pause dur="short"/> that's my twin</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0041">I'm just going to say if you don't do it I'm gonna say okay you've got a choice now <pause dur="short"/> you either do this or I'm going to sit here and cut it open and then you're going to have to deal with it</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0086">or it's the fork</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0041">the fork will come out</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0046">you know what they'll do <pause dur="short"/> they'll stick you in that white padded room</u>
<u n="1639" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">unless you get her to it quick</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0046">they will stick you in that white padded room</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0041">I'm going to do it</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0046">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> I'd I'd do anything</u>
<u n="1643" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what time are you going to hospital <pause dur="short"/> three? Two?</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0046">I would do it <pause dur="short"/> I really want a curry now <pause dur="short"/> I hate you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I really do</u>
<u n="1645" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">we can go to chip shop <pause dur="short"/> oh I've got no money and they're shut now <pause dur="short"/> this week is so tight for me cos that fucking shitty two days I worked</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0046">no yeah shitty two days of holidays</u>
<u n="1647" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he screwed me over the lad at work <pause dur="short"/> I booked off four days holiday they put three and I had to work two days <pause dur="short"/> I worked what twelve hours <pause dur="short"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> fuck me that roofer</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0046">mm <pause dur="short"/> twelve hours and two days holiday <pause dur="short"/> but they do work holiday days <pause dur="short"/> so on an average of twelve weeks</u>
<u n="1649" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah I haven't done fuck all <pause dur="short"/> so this week I've just worked technically seven seven shifts which is seven days</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0046">yeah and</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> luckily things have been pretty good so I go in tomorrow and tell her bombshell she's going to be like holy fuck go</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0086">get to A and E with a fork</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0046" trans="overlap">I'm on your side</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0041">she'll probably give me the fork to go with</u>
<u n="1657" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you know what go with chopsticks</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0046" trans="overlap">you've got a fork</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0041">she probably <unclear/></u>
<u n="1660" who="S0046">no <pause dur="short"/> she don't want to <unclear/> with chopsticks <pause dur="short"/> you'll be there for hours</u>
<u n="1661" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">make sure they're metal ones</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0046">you want to go in there with a damn cut throat</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0086">please don't put ideas in her head</u>
<u n="1664" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">or go with out and say where say go with that and go where's the wine?</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0046">mm</u>
<u n="1666" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1667" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's just your luck cos you screwed up <pause dur="short"/> next hole</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0041">the thing is it's it's <pause dur="short"/> do you know what pisses me off is that it's not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that bad <pause dur="short"/> in the grand scheme of operations this is just a pouch of blood</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's simple</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0041">do you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s partner <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying he used to get the all the time on his ankles from playing football <pause dur="short"/> he used to get fucking whacked all the time they'd come up <pause dur="short"/> and it used to be standard procedure if you had one</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0046">you'd just suck them out</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0041">you'd go there <pause dur="short"/> the first time you turn up at A and E all they'd do is whack the syringe in pull it out you'd be good to go <pause dur="short"/> he said literally a well done <pause dur="short"/> he said I don't <pause dur="short"/> and he said I don't really understand why you've still got it like <pause dur="short"/> you go in with this he said okay it was like fifteen years ago <pause dur="short"/> but you'd go in syringe it done <pause dur="short"/> and he said and what comes out is not just blood it's basically it's plasma it's like yellow</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0041">Cos it's not just blood cos it's just stuck there</u>
<u n="1675" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">make sure you pull the sexist thing on her</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0041">and he said I I don't understand why you're still sat with it <pause dur="short"/> like people in the <trunc>f</trunc> in the football team used to go every week with it <pause dur="short"/> and it's quite standard go in pull it out whack it up they'd be playing football next weekend</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0086">it's bad is'nt it?</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0086">I guess it's because they don't want to do any em procedure</u>
<u n="1680" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">pull the sexism on them <pause dur="short"/> go you're sexist</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0041">he said what it is is they don't want to do it because if it gets infected you can sue them</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0086">well no cos you're the one at this point you're the one saying this is what I want <pause dur="short"/> they might make you sign something</u>
<u n="1683" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you you yeah you will sign something yeah to say you'll sign something</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I will say to them if you want me to sign it up I'll sign it up good <pause dur="short"/> but he said the only reason I can see</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0086">that's what you were saying to them wasn't it? On Wednesday</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1687" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">infected it is your own fault you know what I mean but as long as it's not there</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> he said the only reason I can see for them not doing it is because you could sue them if it gets infected <pause dur="short"/> but the standard procedure used to me</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0086" trans="overlap">well I think for ever procedure you have to sign a consent from don't you?</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0041">do you?</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0086">normally you'd have to sign a consent from <pause dur="short"/> before they're allowed to touch you</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0046">not maybe <pause dur="short"/> not well I never did</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0041" trans="overlap">sign it up <pause dur="short"/> I'll sign it up</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0046">well mind you I signed to be knocked out when I never did <pause dur="short"/> that pissed me off</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0041">I'm going to do it anyway I'll say</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0046">I was <unclear/> by mail for three days</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0041">make your own little from I'll sign it up now <pause dur="short"/> he said it he's never seen one this big</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> usually it's golf ball size <pause dur="short"/> he said and I've seen loads of them ever week I saw them <pause dur="short"/> they should have been golf ball size <pause dur="short"/> he said I can't believe they've seen something that big and not said pull it out</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0086" trans="overlap">shitting hell</u>
<u n="1701" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's cos it's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1702" who="S0086">it's worrying isn't it? And it's getting bigger <pause dur="short"/> so that might work in your favour</u>
<u n="1703" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1704" who="S0086">that given that you <pause dur="short"/> given you've done everything they said</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0041">it's still fucked</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0046">just drum in your head don't leave tomorrow unsatisfied</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0041">I'm not <pause dur="short"/> no way <pause dur="short"/> you might have to bring me some food rations and that shit but I'm staying there</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0046">as long as you're satisfied</u>
<u n="1709" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I finish at five you you text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I'll be there I'll bring some food</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0041">come on in <pause dur="short"/> I'm not moving</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0046" trans="overlap">as long as you as long as you're satisfied tomorrow when you leave I'll be happy <pause dur="short"/> regardless of the outcome</u>
<u n="1712" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I'll work in I'll be like that <pause dur="short"/> I'll be like you're not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you're definitely not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you alright Charlie how're you doing</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No I've thought about it there's too much riding on it <pause dur="short"/> there's no way I'm walking out that place</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's important</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0041">no way <pause dur="short"/> but we have to book you time in theatre <pause dur="short"/> great <pause dur="short"/> I'll be here <pause dur="short"/> put me on the consolation list <pause dur="short"/> see you then</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you haven't been anywhere</u>
<u n="1717" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">honestly I'd book you now</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0041">do it <pause dur="short"/> cos she thing is if they leave me there I cut it open ah top of the list <pause dur="short"/> I'll do it right now I'd fucking do it <pause dur="short"/> sounds crackers like what type of person would think they would stab their self in the leg</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0046" trans="overlap">it is a bit cracker but <pause dur="short"/> you're your life kind of depends on it in all fairness</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0041" trans="overlap">but right now <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's like my whole career now <pause dur="short"/> they don't I don't think  I don't think  they realise what they're  what they're  holding me against</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0086">what they're jeopardising</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0041">yeah when we were talking to that guy when we went in obviously I thought the worse thing they would do would be holding me back for months <pause dur="short"/> now they're not it's not an option there's no July there's no January intake</u>
<u n="1723" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">you know why they don't understand</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0086">it is literally one a year</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0041">it's literally now or nothing <pause dur="short"/> it's either officer or not officer is basically what they're deciding <pause dur="short"/> so if they were passed fifteen grand they were prepared to make the decision <pause dur="short"/> put it in writing though cos it's your choice</u>
<u n="1726" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1727" who="S0046" trans="overlap"><unclear/> or what?</u>
<u n="1728" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1729" who="S0046" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="1730" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">there are too many there at A and E <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1731" who="S0041">it's a  It's a It's a  big deal <pause dur="short"/> it's a big deal now and it wasn't as serious before</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0086">yeah yeah of course <pause dur="short"/> that's what you have to get them to understand</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0046">ask just ask <pause dur="short"/> yeah like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said ask someone who's served</u>
<u n="1734" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">ask someone who's served <pause dur="short"/> there's only a few in <anon type="place"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> ask say look I know you've not served <pause dur="short"/> give me someone who has</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0041">they won't though they're not allowed to tell me though are they?</u>
<u n="1736" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">tough shit</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0041">they're not allowed to legally tell me who has</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0046">not legally but just generally they're not allowed to <pause dur="short"/> there's not there's no legal yes or no they're not allowed to tell you</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0041">it's alright if they don't do it I'm going to cut it open in front fop their faces so it's their own choice</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0086">stop saying that</u>
<u n="1741" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">make them feel so small say look you ain't served look this is what we'll do if you don't</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0041">I'll just say do it or else I'll put a Bic to it <pause dur="short"/> do what you want</u>
<u n="1743" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">can I film it if you do</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0046">I will  I will  stab it with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1746" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'll YouTube it and we can sue <anon type="place"/>'s</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I will stab it with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1748" who="S0046" trans="overlap">I will stab it with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has not got a point on it</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0046">but I will stab it</u>
<u n="1751" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">we'll get some ketchup in there involved somewhere</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0046">job done</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0041">I mean the thing is it's so silly <pause dur="short"/> it's not even <pause dur="short"/> it's not somewhere that' easily infected <pause dur="short"/> it's not  It's not  life threatening it's not in my muscle it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's just stupid it's surface it's superficial <pause dur="short"/> for the sake of draining it for somebodies wage</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0046">but that's why they want to leave it</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0041">is so silly cos it's not even</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0046">that's why they want to leave it</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0041">well they can't now <pause dur="short"/> don't give a shit</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0046">at the end of the say you you you pay your taxes <pause dur="short"/> you know? You're you're entitled to the surgery that you want</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that what that's exactly what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said <pause dur="short"/> she said you paid your NHS you paid your national insurance if you want it doing it's your choice <pause dur="short"/> you paid for it <pause dur="short"/> she said so stick to your guns <pause dur="short"/> cos she didn't stick to her guns when she went in for the thyroid and they fucked her over and she had to go to hospital and she we like if there's one thing I've learnt in the past six months is that if you think you're entitled to it fight for it <pause dur="short"/> cos if you're not at the very end then somebody who's qualified like a surgeon will say no <pause dur="short"/> but if you don't fight and fight and fight you'll never know <pause dur="short"/> just do it</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> they'll just screw you over yeah</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0041">yeah she said just do it <pause dur="short"/> she was like I'll take the day off I'll come with you <pause dur="short"/> and I said to her don't don't fucking take the day off I can fight as much as you can fight if it comes to it <pause dur="short"/> I'm snookered I'll call you but otherwise</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0046">you know think of the people that get plastic surgery week in and week out because they feel uncomfortable in their bodies</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0041">and they're depressed yeah I know</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0046">you know that that that is superficial</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0046">this is medical</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0041">this is a fucking tumour</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0046">this is fucking medical</u>
<u n="1770" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">pretty much that is a fucking tumour though</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0046">this this this this is not  this is this is not  nothing is it? It's something <pause dur="short"/> whereas something going and complaining about an imperfection in their body and then getting it given to them just so they can feel better about themselves</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my sister was one of them</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0046">fuck you</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0041">my sister had a boob reduction <pause dur="short"/> I know sacrilege</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0046">and why?</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0041">Cos she had boobs the size of mine but she was a size ten <pause dur="short"/> she was tiny she looked ridiculous</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0046">mm Yeah</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0041">she did look ridiculous</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0086">you get really bad back ache and stuff</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I had one like that <pause dur="short"/> she was like about four foot tall and she had like double F</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0041">you saw the pictures in the fat book didn't you?</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0046">she had double Fs and she was like four foot two</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0041">yeah bad times</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0046">her name we <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1787" who="S0041">so okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm not coming home tomorrow till it's gone so we'll have to think <pause dur="short"/> one more day</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0046">well party at <anon type="place"/>'s tomorrow night <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1789" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0041">one more day for a party up at <anon type="place"/>'s I'll text you up and tomorrow evening I will see you there</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0086">I'll give you a ring when I finish</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we shall be there</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0041">I'll be there <pause dur="short"/> be there with bells on</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0086">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
</body>
</text>
