<text id="S8XE">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:33:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-13</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0509 S0510</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON &amp; ANON's home, Hastings</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Bike theft, Social Media, College, Food, Cycling</topics>
		<activity>Mother telling daughter about recovery of stolen bike</activity>
		<conv_type>dicsussing, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0509">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hastings</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0510">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Receptionist</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0509">so come on then the bike tell us what happened</u>
<u n="2" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so you you know I had to leave the house very quickly this morning?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0510">you know I got a call</u>
<u n="5" who="S0509">yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0510">and I said they think they've found my bike</u>
<u n="7" who="S0509">yeah I thought it was auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos</u>
<u n="8" who="S0510">did you?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0509"><unclear/> sounded <unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0510">well I was really shocked that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was ringing me at that time in the morning cos it was like twenty-five to eight in the morning and I thought oh gosh has something happened?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh blimey <pause dur="short"/> hope she's alright yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0510">and so oh hello darling how are you? and she said have you? have you read the post? and I said no what post? <trunc>we</trunc> they've posted on the Facebook page they think they've found your bike what? no no she said oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has been trying to get hold of you she's erm you know? messaged all of us saying can someone get hold of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? erm because this lady and they they want you to act quick has has seen it erm she's on a bus going through <anon type="place"/> and literally she's just posted that she's seen my bike against the <anon type="place"/> road sign</u>
<u n="15" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0510">erm now bearing in mind that it was stolen two days ago</u>
<u n="17" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0510">and that I posted on this old town traders group</u>
<u n="19" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0510">that that same day and it's had like about a hundred and sixteen shares so it's reached a lot of people</u>
<u n="21" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0510">and this lady who's on the bus had seen that post with the photo</u>
<u n="23" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0510">but the thing was the photo that I posted it was actually it was slightly different to my bike because it was Halfords photo</u>
<u n="25" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right oh I see yeah yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0510" trans="overlap">cos mine was modified slightly in that erm it didn't have the mud guards that this particular photo had and it had a bike rack at the back and also</u>
<u n="27" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0510">instead of the gel saddle it had a sprung saddle so</u>
<u n="29" who="S0509">mm hm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0510">in the description I've put these things and she's put I saw your post the other day I'm on the bust er I'm on the bus that goes past that road hurry before it goes again and then somebody else has posted have you seen this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0510">and then she's put it's definitely your bike because it's got a rack and a sprung saddle</u>
<u n="33" who="S0509">how did she know that from going past on a bus?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0510" trans="overlap">on a bus well I don't know</u>
<u n="35" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0510">I know I know you <trunc>ca</trunc> kind of get all these suspicions don't you?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah but then <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0510">but I really think it's it was <trunc>gen</trunc> she had genuinely just seen it</u>
<u n="39" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0510">cos you know what I was like as well when I was on the bus the next day I know it was my bike so it was personal to me</u>
<u n="41" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0510">but I was literally watching every bike</u>
<u n="43" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but you were looking at every bike yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0510">that went past and sometimes the story engages somebody doesn't it? you know?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0510">and so there's <unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0509" trans="overlap">was it like on the corner as well?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0510">it was right on the corner</u>
<u n="49" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it might have been like going round so she had a little moment to look</u>
<u n="50" who="S0510" trans="overlap">bit of time to exactly yes no you're you're spot on it was right on the corner of the road she was going down so she was probably viewing it as she was coming down</u>
<u n="51" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0510">she had a bit of time</u>
<u n="53" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0510">erm and so it but it was weird cos it was almost like it was advertising itself you know?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0510">so then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one of the school nurses saw this and she put she tagged me and then she tagged all these other ladies at work saying help someone get text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0510">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said I'm on it and and then she texted me but she followed it up with a phone call straight away and that was the phone call that you heard when just before I left</u>
<u n="59" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0510">so she said you know? they think they've found it erm what are you doing? I said ah I'm just about to run for the bus and she said look I'll give you five minutes to gather your thoughts but I think ought to go up there in the car I can give you a lift I'll call you back in five minutes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0509">my god</u>
<u n="62" who="S0510">so so I'd ran to the bus stop at the end of the road she called me and she was like you know? <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> it's been posted so you know? therefore other people are gonna see</u>
<u n="63" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0510">that it's there as well you <trunc>kno</trunc> <trunc>wh</trunc> <trunc>ha</trunc> <trunc>wh</trunc> what are you <trunc>do</trunc> where are you? okay I'll come and pick you up I'm in my pyjamas but I'll just jump in the car</u>
<u n="65" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0509">dedication man dedication</u>
<u n="67" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh my god it was such a mission so erm we're on the way up we're like erm you know? possibilities well <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="68" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0510">I was saying well she says she thinks it's my bike but I'm not so sure because she's put it's got a bike rack and a sprung saddle but she's mentioned nothing about the rust</u>
<u n="70" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah then we were like driving along and</u>
<u n="71" who="S0509">what if we need pliers or whatever?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah like oh it's like what if it's locked up? I was going well well we'll just call the police because I've reported it to the police</u>
<u n="73" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0510">it's got a crime number and erm and then it was like why would <trunc>w</trunc> why would somebody kind of go and leave it in a really prominent place</u>
<u n="75" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0510">after they've taken the trouble to steal it and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying well maybe it was just to get them from A to B maybe they just needed to get up there and I was going yeah but who would wanna cycle all the</u>
<u n="77" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>who would</unclear> steal a bike to do that</u>
<u n="78" who="S0510">to cycle all the way up that blooming hill and then I went oh maybe that's it they got up the hill got half way and thought sod this for a lark and leave it there</u>
<u n="79" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0510">you know what <unclear>gradient</unclear> that hill has and how long it goes on for</u>
<u n="81" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0510">maybe you know? but then actually that that doesn't quite work out cos whoever stole it would have had to have bolt cutters and so they would have specifically gone out for planned planned it you know?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah they would have planned</u>
<u n="84" who="S0510">erm because of the type of lock it was they would have had to have done and erm but then you see so we we're going up the road and like all these different scenarios what what could be happening? is it still there? will it be the one?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0510">we're coming along the road and I can just as we're about to turn into this road I can see the back of it and I said it's definitely mine it's definitely mine oh my gosh oh my gosh like this</u>
<u n="87" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0510">and like we don't know whether there's gonna be somebody there or or what you know?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> oh my gosh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0510">and er but we turn the corner and there's nobody there we're looking actually although we've gone through all this council estate the road that it's sort of parked on the end of you look at the houses it's actually quite a nice little area there in in that road</u>
<u n="91" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0510">and erm it's like somebody could just be popping into the house you know? erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like right okay you get out of the car grab the bike erm cos we could see that it wasn't locked or anything grab the bike I'll just turn around and we'll come back round I'll come back round and course we were thinking of putting it in the back of her car</u>
<u n="93" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0510">so I jumped out I'm like ah it it looks alright kind of thing she's pulled back round it's like we're not gonna get it in your car are we? it's just too small so she's going right she said er just just run it up and down the road make sure you can cycle it and then we'll just get out of here sort of thing? so I did I got on the bike and it was like it's fine the only thing that was different about it it the tyres were fine they were pumped up lovely well you had them pumped up for me <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I did yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0510">proper job erm <pause dur="short"/> was that on the front of the bike you know I had that really massive bell that was a bit of a statement bell it was huge wasn't it?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah and rusty</u>
<u n="98" who="S0510">and rusty and of course it it you know? it wasn't really functioning very well</u>
<u n="99" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and barely working any more</u>
<u n="100" who="S0510">erm that was gone and also my front light was gone so erm but anyway tested it I said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's fine oh my gosh you're amazing you're a star</u>
<u n="101" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0510">you know? gave her a big hug and everything and erm and she was going right well I'm off then you know? get yourself to work</u>
<u n="103" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0510">so yeah so I was like ah I'll try and I started trying to cycle it up the hill and I thought I'm not even going to bother I'm just going to cos it was just too too steep and then I got on the phone as well because auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> then rang me</u>
<u n="105" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0510">she was ringing me to see how I was and was there any news on my bike?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0509">wow</u>
<u n="108" who="S0510" trans="overlap">funny you should say that</u>
<u n="109" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0510">because it just so happens that <unclear/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0510">yeah so I literally walked all the way up from <pause dur="short"/> from there with the bike got to work just in time</u>
<u n="113" who="S0509">oh my god you got in on time?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0509">what? that was mental</u>
<u n="116" who="S0510" trans="overlap">how about that? cos I was thinking will I text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and just tell her I might be a little bit late but I got in and erm how amazing is that? so I I posted a message on the noticeboard because you know? erm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah they helped you find it they helped you get it back</u>
<u n="118" who="S0510" trans="overlap">they yeah and so and so many people had shared it that I'd posted this message last night to thank everybody for all their good you know</u>
<u n="119" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0510">for posting it and what great community spirit we've got here and shame about the few that just you know? carry out these activities really</u>
<u n="121" who="S0509" trans="overlap">just <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0510">and erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had posted before I'd had a chance cos obviously she'd got home before I kind of got to work</u>
<u n="123" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0510">a little <unclear>bike</unclear> symbol reunited well spotted and thank you to the lady <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was emotional</u>
<u n="125" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> it was emotional</u>
<u n="126" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0510">but it's just amazing I never thought I was going to get it back</u>
<u n="128" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well no blimey</u>
<u n="129" who="S0510">so you you think it was stolen on Wednesday sometime I found out at five o'clock didn't I? when I got back from work</u>
<u n="130" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0510">and then I posted it I think within an hour of it being stolen and then it has been shared literally hundreds of times between Wednesday at about six and Friday this morning at seven you know? seven thirty or whatever</u>
<u n="132" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> aha <pause dur="short"/> crazy</u>
<u n="133" who="S0510">the power of social media</u>
<u n="134" who="S0509">yeah it can do good things can't it?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it can do very good things</u>
<u n="136" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0509">so why do you think they took your light and bell off?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0510">well I think maybe and I only thought about this just an hour or so ago because it did seem a random thing to do</u>
<u n="139" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0510">although the bell I thought maybe it's such a statement bell</u>
<u n="141" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0510">it's another you know? thing to</u>
<u n="143" who="S0509">a clue</u>
<u n="144" who="S0510">clue but the light didn't make a lot of sense but then I thought well hold on my my erm lock it was one of those coil locks that you know?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0510">I say coil it was quite a thick one that <trunc>w</trunc>was long and you could wrap it round lots of things and I always wrapped it round my handlebars</u>
<u n="147" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0510">one of the things that I did as well as the frame was wrap it round my handlebars</u>
<u n="149" who="S0509" trans="overlap">handlebars</u>
<u n="150" who="S0510">and so maybe where they cut it <pause dur="short"/> it was by the handlebars</u>
<u n="151" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they'd broke the <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0510">and therefore they had some problems there and maybe you know? they got broken along the way so they took them off</u>
<u n="153" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0510">took the light off anyway the bell might have just got taken off because it was a statement bell</u>
<u n="155" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0510">but I mean thankfully you know the good thing about my bike is that it had quite unusual paint job on it</u>
<u n="157" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0510">cos you don't see many with that kind of colour <unclear/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's an <trunc>unus</trunc> I was going to say it's an unusual colour</u>
<u n="160" who="S0510">yeah it's like a metallic light blue and a silver</u>
<u n="161" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah it's kind of a funny old frame actually it's quite like it's really thick in places you know?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah cos it's well a lot of hybrid <trunc>bi</trunc> bikes have got have that kind of shape</u>
<u n="163" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right well <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0510">but you know? it's erm <pause dur="short"/> it is distinctive I think and so that's a good thing that's going for it</u>
<u n="165" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0510">and maybe you know? it just got too hot for the person that had it because it got shared so much</u>
<u n="167" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0510">that you know? on all these sort of community groups as well and bike groups</u>
<u n="169" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0510">that er I don't know maybe they just left it there but then you I wouldn't have thought they'd leave it in such an obvious place you know? if you're gonna dump a bike there's plenty of places</u>
<u n="171" who="S0509">maybe they felt guilty and they wanted it to go back to you</u>
<u n="172" who="S0510" trans="overlap">well and that was what I thought about the woman that posted it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0510">so just thought oh that's you know? you immediately think oh well that's wonderful and then you start thinking well that's funny</u>
<u n="175" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0510">you know? that it's it's in that place</u>
<u n="177" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0510">and that some you know? but I don't think so I think she genuinely she was just somebody on</u>
<u n="179" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0510">on the bus that saw it I've checked out her Facebook page see what kind of person she is</u>
<u n="181" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I was going to say yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0510">I mean she's been swimming with the dolphins for goodness sake so she <trunc>mu</trunc> she must be of good character</u>
<u n="183" who="S0509">probably not <unclear>likely</unclear></u>
<u n="184" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0509">ah I don't know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0510">yeah so crazy huh?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0510">and then I thanked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in clinic you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always does all this praying? she's really into her churchy things and erm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0510">she has some amazing stories to tell about you know? outcomes after she's prayed for something</u>
<u n="191" who="S0509">course</u>
<u n="192" who="S0510">and but I said to her anyway I thanked everybody that shared it socially and and that and I said oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> amazing news thank you for praying I've got it back she was going no really? is it okay? is it intact?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0509">is it ill? is it hurt?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0510">I said yeah it's intact well you know it's all the the bell and that's gone but that's okay it's probably been it's made an improvement</u>
<u n="195" who="S0509">it's time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0510">exactly she was going well as soon as you told me when I went out I said dear lord you know? please you know? let <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> get this back and let her get it back intact <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah bless her</u>
<u n="198" who="S0510">bless her</u>
<u n="199" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><trunc>ma</trunc> maybe the only reason they stole it mummy was because your bell was a crime against bells and they had to remove it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they had to they have to do something this cannot be yes not only is it you know? twenty times the normal size of a bell</u>
<u n="201" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0510">it is warped and rusted and has no functional use</u>
<u n="203" who="S0509">it's it's a disgrace to the society of bells</u>
<u n="204" who="S0510">yes quite <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah maybe they were oh god what do they call them? what are the bell-ringers called? there's a word isn't there? for a group of bell-ringers</u>
<u n="205" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> bell-<trunc>ring</trunc> ah a belfry I don't know</u>
<u n="206" who="S0510">no that's not it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I know I know I was just making up words with bell in them</u>
<u n="208" who="S0510">I want to a say <trunc>taxi</trunc> but it's not</u>
<u n="209" who="S0509" trans="overlap">a taxidermist <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0510">it's not a taxidermist but it's erm no no no</u>
<u n="211" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mum a taxidermist is</u>
<u n="212" who="S0510">but it oh gosh what is it?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0509">I don't know what it is</u>
<u n="214" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that's going to get me now old Bill Bailey would be able to tell us</u>
<u n="215" who="S0509">ah yeah probably</u>
<u n="216" who="S0510">as he is he is chief bell-ringer erm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0509">oh yeah course</u>
<u n="218" who="S0510">yeah cos er yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0510">so amazing stuff so I I'm so glad that I didn't rush to kind of get a replacement from</u>
<u n="221" who="S0509"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0510"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0510" trans="overlap">cos I <unclear>I just thought</unclear> I just thought I'd give it a little few days and just give me time to sort out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had erm had offered to give me her old bike</u>
<u n="225" who="S0509">aha</u>
<u n="226" who="S0510">did I tell you about that?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0509">I think you did yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0510">yeah erm so yeah amazing but now of course the dilemma is after you know? after what happened you probably remember I said to you even if I had the money I <trunc>wou</trunc> I'd wouldn't get a new bike now cos I'd just be too worried about it getting stolen</u>
<u n="229" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0510">erm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0509">and now the dilemma is how to protect it</u>
<u n="232" who="S0510">yeah so I was</u>
<u n="233" who="S0509">cos you had a really good lock</u>
<u n="234" who="S0510">yes although actually uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent me a message and he begged to differ that I had a good lock so you know?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0510">eh eh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0509">isn't there like a whole thing about no lock is a good lock though?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0510">I've not heard of that</u>
<u n="239" who="S0509">well it's just like basically all bike locks are useless</u>
<u n="240" who="S0510">oh right well if any if somebody want to enough</u>
<u n="241" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0510">campanology</u>
<u n="243" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0510">campanology</u>
<u n="245" who="S0509" trans="overlap">campanology the art of bell-ringing</u>
<u n="246" who="S0510">yes indeed yes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I was going to say isn't there? I <trunc>co</trunc> maybe there was someone in a bike shop who was telling us or maybe it was uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about like how like you can spray freeze stuff on it or something and then it breaks really easily I don't know</u>
<u n="248" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="249" who="S0509">someone was criticising that kind of bike lock</u>
<u n="250" who="S0510">oh okay oh really?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0509">I might have just been making up that up</u>
<u n="252" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0509">but</u>
<u n="254" who="S0510">but then I've heard a couple of things in the last couple of days about how you can one get erm like a tag almost like you can get for animals you know a little erm oh what do they call it?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah microchip type thing yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0510" trans="overlap">microchip thank you yeah for your bike so that you can locate it</u>
<u n="257" who="S0509">oh what? like a GPS thing?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0510">yeah yeah yeah so you can tag it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh do it man</u>
<u n="260" who="S0510">erm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0509">but then you've got to make sure that they don't remove the tag</u>
<u n="262" who="S0510">tag yes make sure well I guess</u>
<u n="263" who="S0509">like drill a tiny hole in like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0509">the metal bit and push it in</u>
<u n="266" who="S0510" trans="overlap">the frame yeah yeah that's it that's the thing I mean you could couldn't you? you could put it <pause dur="short"/> within the frame or within the handlebars or you know? they might not necessarily find it right away</u>
<u n="267" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah in the handlebars would be a good one actually</u>
<u n="268" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so there's that I don't know about the cost of that I'd have to check it out erm also insuring it</u>
<u n="269" who="S0509">mm hm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0510">I'd say I'd have to find out about insurance but it's like you know? is it?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0509">is it worth it?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0510">yeah I mean although my bike kind of all in with all the accessories was four fifty when I bought it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0509">it's gone downhill since then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's yeah you know for the last year and a half I've left it in town every day in all weathers uncovered so there's a bit of rust on there you know?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0509"><unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0510">erm but it's still a good bike but yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0510">erm <pause dur="short"/> so therefore that thing about getting an old wreck where it doesn't really matter and nobody would want it anyway if it's an old wreck comes into play however of course the key thing which I'd completely forgotten about until we were discussing getting my bike home</u>
<u n="279" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0510">because obviously it's not got lights on and I didn't want to cycle down that massive hill with no lights</u>
<u n="281" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0510">hence chatting to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0510">can we get it in your car?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0510">he said can you take the front wheel off? I said yeah it's got a I've never used it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0510">but it's a easy release front wheel</u>
<u n="289" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="290" who="S0510">so that's what I need to do just take the wheel with me to work <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="291" who="S0509">it's a miracle</u>
<u n="292" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0509">it's a miracle</u>
<u n="294" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> why had I never thought about that before? because I'd never thought about it getting stolen before really</u>
<u n="295" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0510">well you know not <unclear/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but then how long is it going to take you to take a wheel off every morning?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0510">no it's a quick release wheel literally it's got a lever it's just figuring out how to put it back on</u>
<u n="299" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0509">if you could get the art of that down?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you know? I mean I just need to get the manual out and have a look cos I've never done it before</u>
<u n="303" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0510">but it literally has a flick lever cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying his and cos when we got it to his boot he was going aw have we got to mess around with the brakes as well? and I was going no I think it just flicks off and you take it off so there's no worries about that</u>
<u n="305" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0510">it's literally an easy release one but it's just figuring out the erm how you put the bolts back in</u>
<u n="307" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0510">cos there's a spring and stuff I just need to find the diagram to show us show me that and</u>
<u n="309" who="S0509">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0510">job done and then I just take the bike on the <trunc>bu</trunc> ah the the wheel</u>
<u n="311" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0510">on the bus with me to work</u>
<u n="313" who="S0509">I mean you could still steal it if you were really determined but it'd be it'd probably be enough hassle to deter a thief especially if there's other bikes there</u>
<u n="314" who="S0510">well they're not going to make a quick getaway are they? with a bike with only one wheel</u>
<u n="315" who="S0509">oh yeah you can't cycle it</u>
<u n="316" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0509">I was thinking because they could still wheel it like on the back wheel and just like walking around but then it would be like why? <trunc>wh</trunc>why?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><trunc>we</trunc> it's a bit obvious yeah yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0509">yeah that's <trunc>brill</trunc> yeah yeah just do that you'd be you'd be fine</u>
<u n="320" who="S0510" trans="overlap">so I'll do that</u>
<u n="321" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0510">and maybe get the double lock cos uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying to me you know? he lent me his bike last night to come home</u>
<u n="323" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0510">and er <pause dur="short"/> I was saying I'll take it home you know? I wouldn't want to take it out and leave it erm and he said well just double lock it and I'm sure it'll be fine double lock his bike</u>
<u n="325" who="S0509" trans="overlap">double lock what? so put two locks on it?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0510">yeah so</u>
<u n="327" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="328" who="S0510">I've got to buy another lock anyway I don't need to now though you know? I don't need to double lock his now</u>
<u n="329" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0510">but I was going to have to buy another lock anyway</u>
<u n="331" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0510">erm so that would have been the other thing but I don't even need any of those things</u>
<u n="333" who="S0509">you don't even need a lock to be honest</u>
<u n="334" who="S0510">oh well I do need that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0509">I was I was kidding I was kidding</u>
<u n="336" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0509">oh wow</u>
<u n="338" who="S0510">so amazing eh? <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so much</u>
<u n="340" who="S0510">really crazy it's funny how the whole story erm swept round the office though</u>
<u n="341" who="S0509">ah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0510">it's the talk of the office and when it happened when it got stolen and now only half the office actually stayed cos most of them have Fridays off</u>
<u n="343" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0510">so erm yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0510">there'll probably be more on Monday</u>
<u n="347" who="S0509">ah they'll bring you in a bike shaped cake</u>
<u n="348" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0509">bike party</u>
<u n="350" who="S0510"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me cos I saw her just as I was going to she she was arriving she she was like wow that's that's brilliant she said all you need now is to get your coat back <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0509">oh yeah I forgot about that</u>
<u n="352" who="S0510">cos that was stolen last week wasn't it?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0510">I had my card returned well a new card you know? cos I was saying about things happen in threes</u>
<u n="355" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah yeah yeah your card the coat and your bike</u>
<u n="356" who="S0510" trans="overlap">bike so card new card has been issued</u>
<u n="357" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0510">er no money stolen obviously cos the card machine just decided to eat it</u>
<u n="359" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0510">before I'd even put a pin in <pause dur="short"/> the bike I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was saying well maybe somebody's going to come in the clinic then next week so <unclear/> just say oh we realised that we came home with an extra coat we wondered oh yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0509" trans="overlap">extra coat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0510">ah so happy days and you know? Friday the thirteenth <trunc>pah</trunc> what does it matter?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><trunc>pah</trunc> <trunc>pah</trunc></u>
<u n="366" who="S0510">what does that matter?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0509">ah you should you should like tweet that that would make a good tweet that would</u>
<u n="368" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0509">Friday the thirteenth unlucky? I just got my stolen bike back</u>
<u n="370" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah superb huh? did you tell your friends?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0509">I told them when you got it back yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0509">I hadn't mentioned that it it was stolen</u>
<u n="374" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that it'd been stolen</u>
<u n="375" who="S0509">and I was like my mum just got her bike back</u>
<u n="376" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0509">they were like ah great</u>
<u n="378" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0509">but they probably they didn't understand the trauma of the <trunc>origin</trunc></u>
<u n="380" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="381" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">what's that?</u>
<u n="382" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what time are you going out?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0510">oh about quarter past seven</u>
<u n="384" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh alright</u>
<u n="385" who="S0510">that alright?</u>
<u n="386" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="388" who="S0509">well</u>
<u n="389" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0509">there we go</u>
<u n="391" who="S0510">yeah so what have you been up to?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0509">I used my er refectory bursary money for the first time today</u>
<u n="393" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did you?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0510">and</u>
<u n="396" who="S0509">I been successful it's like a contactless thing so you just like put it there and it does it</u>
<u n="397" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="398" who="S0509">so yeah but I had a had a baguette</u>
<u n="399" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0509">with bacon and salady stuff in it</u>
<u n="401" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="402" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0510">lovely</u>
<u n="404" who="S0509">and I had a smoothie</u>
<u n="405" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0509">but the smoothies cost two pound fifty they're the naked ones so like they're nice ones</u>
<u n="407" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh are they oh I see</u>
<u n="408" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0510">they're the pre pre-packed ones</u>
<u n="410" who="S0509">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0510">no naked are good though aren't they?</u>
<u n="412" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0510">so what was in it?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0509">I don't know it was like one of these antioxidant type things</u>
<u n="415" who="S0510">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0509">there was there was two and one of them was blueberries so I got the other one</u>
<u n="417" who="S0510">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0509">it had apple in it and other things</u>
<u n="419" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0509">the baguette was big and it was nice but it was like quite hard so it was like gnawing on it with my teeth</u>
<u n="421" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah <unclear/> your braces</u>
<u n="422" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0510">mm mm</u>
<u n="424" who="S0509">but yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0509">so it was like two pound for the baguette two pound fifty for the smoothie</u>
<u n="427" who="S0510">and what? what is it? two fifty ten pound a week</u>
<u n="428" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0509">but I get five pound a day well like I I sorry ten pound a week but the maximum spend on a single day is five pounds</u>
<u n="431" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> got you got you</u>
<u n="432" who="S0509">I just yeah I said that completely wrong</u>
<u n="433" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah oh yeah well that makes sense doesn't it? so people don't go mad eating lots of junk</u>
<u n="434" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah crazy yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0510">yeah ah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0509"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0510">so you can do a couple of days a week then?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0509">yeah I could do like two days a week</u>
<u n="439" who="S0510">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to make lunch</u>
<u n="440" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0510">bacon as well that's a treat isn't it?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0509">yeah it's quite it's quite a nice baguette you know?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0509">they have wraps as well but they were more expensive</u>
<u n="445" who="S0510">right so could you not get a wrap and a baguette?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0509">well I wouldn't get a wrap and a baguette <vocal desc="laugh"/> a wrap and a smoothie</u>
<u n="447" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I'm sorry I beg your pardon a smoothie yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0509">I could probably just cos I think the wraps were two pound fifty so then it'd be five pound exactly</u>
<u n="449" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right right yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0510"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0509">and it's alright actually cos it's not the hot food bit and it the queues aren't as bad yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's a quick queue right that's what you want yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0510">aha</u>
<u n="456" who="S0509">yeah I'll have to peruse through their er range of sandwiches and and other savoury delights</u>
<u n="457" who="S0510" trans="overlap">their selection yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah indeed</u>
<u n="458" who="S0509">and that they were selling cakes today cos it was children in need so I had actual money with me which I I</u>
<u n="459" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0509">had some cake</u>
<u n="461" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right oh you did did you?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0510">I had cake I went out and bought a cake for us at lunchtime to celebrate</u>
<u n="464" who="S0509">ah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0510">the fact that the bike was back</u>
<u n="466" who="S0509">that's nice</u>
<u n="467" who="S0510">reunited</u>
<u n="468" who="S0509">reunited with its rightful owner</u>
<u n="469" who="S0510">yes indeed</u>
<u n="470" who="S0509">lovely</u>
<u n="471" who="S0510">so we had a rather nice carrot cake what cake did you have?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0509">er I had a flapjack and oh it was everything though had raisins in it it was really odd</u>
<u n="473" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0509">it was like a raisin pastry thing</u>
<u n="475" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> is there a raisin mountain somewhere in Europe or something? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah that's what <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm thinking maybe the cooking department just had bought like way too many</u>
<u n="477" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="478" who="S0509">like raisins like you know instead of a ten packet they bought a hundred or something</u>
<u n="479" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're like I know there are ways of getting rid of that surplus</u>
<u n="480" who="S0509" trans="overlap">just just put them all in <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0510">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> put them in with the chocolate cakes then with the lemon <trunc>ca</trunc> mind you lemon and raisin is quite a good combo lemon and raisin pancakes yes please sorry</u>
<u n="482" who="S0509">mm not sure about that</u>
<u n="483" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0509">yeah and I had I had drama <unclear/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0509">The Caucasian Chalk Circle is that how you say it? Caucasian Caucasian Caucasian</u>
<u n="489" who="S0510" trans="overlap">Caucasian yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0509">The Caucasian Chalk Circle</u>
<u n="491" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0509">which is good she's quite she was sort of auditioning us today so she was testing us out in lots of different roles and she's gonna have the parts for us next lesson</u>
<u n="493" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="494" who="S0509">and I've got to buy the script but obviously I can get that on my bursary so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0510">bursary a wonderful thing that's so good</u>
<u n="496" who="S0509">yeah it is</u>
<u n="497" who="S0510">got that so the script how much do you have to pay for the script?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0509">I don't know I think it's like</u>
<u n="499" who="S0510">a tenner?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0509">I think it's about that</u>
<u n="501" who="S0510">yeah it's a bit like the <unclear/> isn't it? cos there's are a tenner aren't they?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah they are</u>
<u n="503" who="S0510">for a book</u>
<u n="504" who="S0509">yes indeed</u>
<u n="505" who="S0510">yes</u>
<u n="506" who="S0509"><vocal desc="yawn"/> so I've got to get that and then I've just had study period and then I had lunch and then I just stayed and worked more and didn't get everything I wanted to get done done <unclear/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah that's a shame cos you've got quite a lot of essays to do at the moment haven't you?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah I didn't actually do I did one of the essays one of the short essays</u>
<u n="509" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="510" who="S0509">I wanted to do one of the long essays as well but that didn't happen</u>
<u n="511" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm ah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0509">yeah and I didn't get to annotate as much of a room with a view as I would have liked</u>
<u n="513" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="514" who="S0509">partly because ah well I underestimated the time that it would take me to do my psychology erm key words definitions worksheet</u>
<u n="515" who="S0510">oh really</u>
<u n="516" who="S0509">it took me an hour which was fun cos there were five pages of it</u>
<u n="517" who="S0510"><vocal desc="misc"/> wow</u>
<u n="518" who="S0509">yeah which was in interminably boring</u>
<u n="519" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="520" who="S0509">and er and then oh and then I had some trouble I still can't get it erm I was copying I transferred some er text from my Ipad to the computer</u>
<u n="521" who="S0510">aha</u>
<u n="522" who="S0509">and er the formatting had gone crazy and it's still crazy and I tried to fix that and it was</u>
<u n="523" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0509">then it was like there's so much of this I'm not going to fix it so</u>
<u n="525" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="526" who="S0509">I thought I'll just I'll just ask mummy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0510">okay yeah I'll check it out for you</u>
<u n="528" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0510">what do you want? transfer from your Ipad to that laptop? <unclear>would</unclear> it work?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no yeah no it's not that it's in the document so I can get it from online but erm it's just like</u>
<u n="531" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh okay oh is it a google doc?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0509">no it was I did it through Dropbox I don't know</u>
<u n="533" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="534" who="S0509">I copied and pasted it and it just went <vocal desc="misc"/> what are you doing?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0510">yeah okay</u>
<u n="536" who="S0509">and so it's all there it's just like</u>
<u n="537" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0509">two words next line two words next line <unclear/> it's really annoying</u>
<u n="539" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right okay mm mm okay well we can have a look at that yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0509">cool er and what else was I doing? I did a what did I do the essay on? <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh it was this advert it was a really horrible sexist advert but erm it works well for analysing graphology so you know?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0510">oh okay</u>
<u n="542" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0510">what's the advert?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0509">it's for beer</u>
<u n="545" who="S0510">oh okay</u>
<u n="546" who="S0509">it was for Cobra beer</u>
<u n="547" who="S0510">yeah that's an Indian beer</u>
<u n="548" who="S0509">and it <trunc>ha</trunc> ah it is and it had a it had this man on it and it was making this weird comparison with like by day the boss of Cobra makes beer but by night he makes bras and then they'd like changed the Cobra logo</u>
<u n="549" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0509">so it was bra co at the bottom and it had this weird like split comparison between cobra and this imaginary bra co and it was so strange</u>
<u n="551" who="S0510">bizarre what <trunc>ana</trunc>analogy? what <unclear>er</unclear>?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0509">well</u>
<u n="553" who="S0510" trans="overlap">how weird what was all that about?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0509">I don't know</u>
<u n="555" who="S0510">well you're going to have to show me</u>
<u n="556" who="S0509">I will</u>
<u n="557" who="S0510">to see if it makes any more sense visually but</u>
<u n="558" who="S0509"><unclear/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0509" trans="overlap">like such a ridiculous concept they did show us erm this really well I thought it was quite a clever advert it was for erm <pause dur="short"/> ah probably Clinique makeup or no it was Cover Girl mascara</u>
<u n="561" who="S0510">oh yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0509">and erm it had this picture of ah I'll have to show it to you later</u>
<u n="563" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0509"><unclear/> makes sense you've got to get it yourself</u>
<u n="565" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0509">when I looked at it and I was like what? and then I was like oh</u>
<u n="567" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="568" who="S0509">that's clever</u>
<u n="569" who="S0510">oh okay</u>
<u n="570" who="S0509">erm yeah it was quite good erm what else was I doing? oh I just remember printing lots of things out oh I was updating my drama notes which was</u>
<u n="571" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="572" who="S0509">which is always fun</u>
<u n="573" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0510">not</u>
<u n="575" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0509">and annotating a room with a view</u>
<u n="578" who="S0510">yeah so you didn't get as much done of that as you would have liked? a room with a view</u>
<u n="579" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my god no I just ran out of time</u>
<u n="580" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0509">and it got to three thirty and I was like oh I just finished a chapter I'm leaving</u>
<u n="582" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah time to go yeah probably gets really dark as well</u>
<u n="583" who="S0509">yeah and then it's like an hour before everyone else goes so I couldn't like I don't have to navigate through people or anything</u>
<u n="584" who="S0510">right yes</u>
<u n="585" who="S0509">which is nice</u>
<u n="586" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0509">and yeah yeah cos at one point this week I left college like quarter of an hour late</u>
<u n="588" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0509">and by the time I got to like the <anon type="place"/> cycle path bit I was like oh this is quite dark</u>
<u n="590" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0509">whereas if I leave it on time</u>
<u n="592" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0509">it's like just right</u>
<u n="594" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="595" who="S0509">and I can still see everything</u>
<u n="596" who="S0510" trans="overlap">that's good oh I've got some reflectors for you</u>
<u n="597" who="S0509">oh thanks</u>
<u n="598" who="S0510">yeah <trunc>w</trunc> that have got LED lights on them</u>
<u n="599" who="S0509">oh wait are they for like my arms? oh</u>
<u n="600" who="S0510">yeah yeah cos I I I'll grab them out for you</u>
<u n="601" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh cool</u>
<u n="602" who="S0510">they're erm they're for runners</u>
<u n="603" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="604" who="S0510">they advertise them for runners</u>
<u n="605" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0510">but erm you you <unclear/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0509">okay that's cool</u>
<u n="608" who="S0510">so there we go I bought these in my favourite shop you know?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0509">oh oh oh oh Aldi's</u>
<u n="610" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> money you know on things that I didn't know I needed</u>
<u n="611" who="S0509" trans="overlap">needed but now you do</u>
<u n="612" who="S0510">but now I do</u>
<u n="613" who="S0509">you really didn't need these I'm not going to lie</u>
<u n="614" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> special offer</u>
<u n="615" who="S0509">how much did they cost you?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0510">oh no look they were three ninety-nine I think I paid two pound forty-nine for them they were kind of</u>
<u n="617" who="S0509">wow that is bizarre</u>
<u n="618" who="S0510" trans="overlap">so they've got like erm <pause dur="short"/> batteries inbuilt I don't know how you oh here we go here's the on off button</u>
<u n="619" who="S0509" trans="overlap">how do you turn them on?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0510">look</u>
<u n="621" who="S0509">oh my gosh okay</u>
<u n="622" who="S0510">how cool is that? they flash as well</u>
<u n="623" who="S0509">I'm not sure cool is the word</u>
<u n="624" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> static</u>
<u n="625" who="S0509">hey</u>
<u n="626" who="S0510">static there you go</u>
<u n="627" who="S0509">oh dear that's strange</u>
<u n="628" who="S0510">so therefore yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0510">you can kind of adjust them with the Velcro</u>
<u n="631" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0510">yeah?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0509">that's that's cool yeah thank you</u>
<u n="634" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh you just said cool <unclear/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0509">oh well <unclear/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="637" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's not actually cool</u>
<u n="638" who="S0510">but I was thinking you know we were talking high-vis jackets as your you're cycling</u>
<u n="639" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0510">you know? <pause dur="short"/> a lot more from a a lot further now</u>
<u n="641" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0510">and in the dark</u>
<u n="643" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0510">they'll they'll be good</u>
<u n="645" who="S0509">yes they will <pause dur="short"/> well done</u>
<u n="646" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you know? if you wanted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you could always put one as a headband</u>
<u n="647" who="S0509">I knew you were gonna say that</u>
<u n="648" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0509">and I won't be doing that</u>
<u n="650" who="S0510" trans="overlap">so predictable sorry</u>
<u n="651" who="S0509">I could like weave one through the top of the helmet and all the weird gap bits</u>
<u n="652" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah well I was thinking for our illuminated bike rides from here to <anon type="place"/> they'd be quite fun won't they?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah that'll be good <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="654" who="S0510">cos you could do that kind of thing then you know?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0509">yeah you could crown of flashing lights that's really strange but I mean</u>
<u n="656" who="S0510">well that's what</u>
<u n="657" who="S0509">you're not wrong</u>
<u n="658" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> from pier to eternity normally is strange in fact they're talking about doing another bike ride for Christmas</u>
<u n="659" who="S0509">ah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0510">they did one I mean we've missed so many we're not really part of the crew anymore</u>
<u n="661" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I know no but</u>
<u n="662" who="S0510">it's huge now</u>
<u n="663" who="S0509">is it?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0510">yeah did I not tell you? the last cycle ride they had I think it was the Halloween one they had about sixty-sixty people</u>
<u n="665" who="S0509" trans="overlap">blimey ah it's just cos it was like oh we're not here in the summer and then it was oh I'm too tired and then it was oh it's too dark and wet and cold</u>
<u n="666" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think it was the tea time thing like when you get in of a Saturday</u>
<u n="667" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0510">you don't really</u>
<u n="669" who="S0509">want to go out again</u>
<u n="670" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> back out again actually they used to do them a lot on Friday didn't they?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0509" trans="overlap">Friday I was just thinking that yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>dinner</unclear></u>
<u n="674" who="S0509">oh coming</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
