<text id="S954">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-15</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0529 S0530</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers bedroom in university halls, Lancaster University</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>ANON and ANON are talking in the kitchen, ANON is cooking Toad in the Hole for herself, ANON is helping and advising her. Talk about food, cooking, ANON’s date.</topics>
		<activity>Two flatmates talking about friendships </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing., inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0529">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Falmouth</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cornish/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Falmouth</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0530">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cheshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Chester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0530">I planned to actually sleep through the night at that point because I was so tired</u>
<u n="2" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0530">but then I woke up again at ten so</u>
<u n="4" who="S0529">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah going to sleep at seven and then attempting to sleep all</u>
<u n="5" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0529">night is pretty <unclear/> tall order <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0530">it was a pretty ambitious thought but</u>
<u n="8" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0530">I that's how tired I was thinking I might be able to do it cos this is what my family does because they're weird like my mum can go to bed at like eight o'clock at night and sleep all night and I just don't understand how she does it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0530">but yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0529">our <unclear/> in a situation where I think that my family know about my blog and that's just <unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="14" who="S0529">the thing you don't wanna hear isn't it? you know what I mean? like</u>
<u n="15" who="S0530" trans="overlap">they know where your blog is or they know you have a blog?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I don't know cos what happened was</u>
<u n="17" who="S0530" trans="overlap">my family know I think</u>
<u n="18" who="S0529">do they know? oh how do you deal with it?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0530" trans="overlap">they know I have a blog but they don't know what my blog is</u>
<u n="20" who="S0529" trans="overlap">do they know what it is though? cos I'm worried that</u>
<u n="21" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no no no no</u>
<u n="22" who="S0529">I'm worried that they know what it is is the problem</u>
<u n="23" who="S0530">I tell them it's like a writers' blog</u>
<u n="24" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="25" who="S0530">because it's partly true <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0529">yeah well like no that is for you cos you do actually <unclear>do like</unclear> writing <unclear/> no but what happened was like my mum rang me up yesterday and she was like I think you've been on like this you've just been like writing talking to people like on the internet for too long and I was like how what? why would you say something like that? cos she never says stuff like that</u>
<u n="27" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0529">and I kind of was like oh shit do you like know something that you wanna tell me? and then erm we had a bit of a fight so I just like hung up on her</u>
<u n="29" who="S0530">oh my god</u>
<u n="30" who="S0529"><unclear>I know</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> but she didn't like say whether she like found it or not cos I didn't wanna like bring to her attention that I had a blog if she didn't know</u>
<u n="31" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm if she didn't know</u>
<u n="32" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and then just like just find out if she had been on it but she said something that kind of sounded like she might have an inkling and then I wrote that on my blog I wrote like I've gotta hope my mum didn't know about this blog I hope like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't told her and then my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just texted me this morning that I'm gonna be really honest with you me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like erm wrote a message to your auntie on Facebook like telling her like we're worried about you erm and I got like really angry at that because they know how much I don't like talking about it to my family and they like</u>
<u n="33" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0529">what I tell them in confidence I expect to be kind of kept in confidence</u>
<u n="35" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0529">and I was really quite angry <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0529">but I said like yeah I get what I get like kinda why you did it but you've just gotta like take this with a pinch of salt like I'm up here you know I'm writing all this stuff when I'm on my own and I do actually have people to talk to like I you know I've got you I've got the college I've got you know like I'm seeing counselling and stuff so they don't need to worry</u>
<u n="39" who="S0530">mm mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0529">and she was like okay that's fine and then and then my other friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though who's the one who actually wrote the message I'm trying to get in contact with her but she's not replying to me</u>
<u n="41" who="S0530">no</u>
<u n="42" who="S0529">so I don't actually know if she has <unclear/> like she could have done but also I don't think they told her like my address the blog address</u>
<u n="43" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0529">like I I would hope they didn't but</u>
<u n="45" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I'm sure they wouldn't of told her</u>
<u n="46" who="S0529">I know it just seems to be the no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> apparently said like she just said I have a blog like in the message but I mean my auntie kind of knew I had a blog cos I think I mentioned it but I don't know what they told her like it's really really scary <unclear/> er</u>
<u n="47" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I doubt they would have told her where you're at on your blog or what your URL is</u>
<u n="48" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know but even so it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0530" trans="overlap">but yeah it's not great</u>
<u n="50" who="S0529">it's really like pissed me off a lot I kind of get why they did it but also I don't get why they did it because they know me and they know that that's like</u>
<u n="51" who="S0530" trans="overlap">your <trunc>spa</trunc></u>
<u n="52" who="S0529"><unclear/> one hundred of things you should not do</u>
<u n="53" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0529">to piss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> off</u>
<u n="55" who="S0530">I mean if</u>
<u n="56" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0530">if they said I'm worried about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they could of just said like I just I rang her up and spoke to her and she's not very happy if they had to do it you know what I mean? rather than say er looked on her blog</u>
<u n="58" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0530">like I wouldn't yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0529" trans="overlap">like why didn't they just tell me?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0530">yeah mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0529" trans="overlap">like why didn't they just say to me like I'm worried about you? because they haven't done that they've just been like like routinely asking if I'm okay</u>
<u n="63" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="64" who="S0529">and then I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like to be fair would you rather I kind of like unloaded on you like I do on Tumblr every time?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0529">cos that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been doing about her situation and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like completely exhausted with it and I said to her like do you really want that? and she was like yeah fair enough like cos I don't mind that I understand that you know not everyone can take it at once and so that's why I kind of like keep my answers short when she's when she's asking me how I am</u>
<u n="67" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0529">cos she looks on my blog anyway and it's just like <vocal desc="sigh"/> that's really annoying me and now I wanna change my URL cos I don't want yeah cos I I mean the ideal situation would be if I could just like delete it completely but <unclear/> do that</u>
<u n="69" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no I don't think you should have to do that</u>
<u n="70" who="S0529">but I don't know if I can do that at the moment like I do think I mean I know it's like really toxic and I am like really dependent on it but <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> uh I don't know I think I have gotten better with it like last year it was way worse than this on Tumblr like I was literally just going on there all the time</u>
<u n="71" who="S0530">mm mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0529">but now I kind of only go on there to re-blog stuff and then if I get messages I'll answer them but I'm making a lot more like a lot less kind of actual like personal posts</u>
<u n="73" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0529">than I used to</u>
<u n="75" who="S0530">definitely</u>
<u n="76" who="S0529">which is kind of an improvement <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I don't think I can actually delete it yet and <unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0530">well you shouldn't you shouldn't feel like you have to like there's nothing wrong with it but</u>
<u n="78" who="S0529" trans="overlap">well no it is <unclear>you know</unclear></u>
<u n="79" who="S0530">there is a point like where maybe it can detract from your real life</u>
<u n="80" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="81" who="S0530">just for your own yeah I mean for me now like I go on it in the evening a little bit</u>
<u n="82" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0530">but I don't go on it during the day really</u>
<u n="84" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0530">which helps cos it's like routine maybe</u>
<u n="86" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0530">I dunno but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean sometimes the reality like <unclear>if you do</unclear> get addicted to this sort of thing like the lines between real life and Tumblr can kind of get blurred</u>
<u n="88" who="S0529">yeah <unclear/> and like <unclear/> that and</u>
<u n="89" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0529">but yeah like when you're feeling really low you do get wrapped up in it and it's difficult not to</u>
<u n="91" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah definitely cos it's an easy way of expressing yourself really</u>
<u n="92" who="S0529">well exactly that that's what like my argument is like I feel better talking like writing about it than I do actually like</u>
<u n="93" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0529">verbally speaking and <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> oh it's just <unclear/> problems when it's friends <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but she just she shows it to everyone like like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and that</u>
<u n="95" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0529">I get that she's scared and she's worried and stuff but she shows it to her boyfriend er she shows it to her friends and they all know about it and it's just <vocal desc="sigh"/> er like I know it's public but you have to find it like you have to have the name of it to know what what it is</u>
<u n="97" who="S0530">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and she just gives out the name of it and it's like <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's not that's not right to be honest</u>
<u n="100" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="101" who="S0530">I wouldn't ever give out anybody's Tumblr</u>
<u n="102" who="S0529">no I know like I <vocal desc="sigh"/> like I I erm I sympathise with her because no I empathise with her even like <unclear>cos</unclear> I get <unclear>that she kind of</unclear> doesn't know what to do and her and her boyfriend talk about it a lot but I just I don't really like what she <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0530">went behind your back and did it yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> well no I'm glad she told me today cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't fucking step up like she hasn't even replied to me and she hasn't gotta read more things so I bet she's read it and just isn't replying <vocal desc="sigh"/> cos I've sent her like five messages <pause dur="short"/> it's really annoying</u>
<u n="105" who="S0530">ah <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="106" who="S0529" trans="overlap">but enough of my stupid dramas</u>
<u n="107" who="S0530">it's not stupid dramas</u>
<u n="108" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0530">I get pissed off and anxious when people read my blog that I don't know</u>
<u n="110" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> like if my family have read it that is like a massive <vocal desc="laugh"/> like a massive drama</u>
<u n="111" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <trunc>li</trunc>literally I don't mind if my friends read it sometimes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0530">like some of my friends like</u>
<u n="114" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0530">people that it freaks me out a bit like people <unclear/> saying I know you in real life and I really like your blog</u>
<u n="116" who="S0529">oh god I know yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0530">it's like okay like are you real or are you just trying to create drama? I don't know but</u>
<u n="118" who="S0529">yeah like <pause dur="short"/> do you mean when they're on when they're on Anon? yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah they say like I know you in real life and I think you're really cool and stuff I'm like okay</u>
<u n="120" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's really weird</u>
<u n="121" who="S0530">it is strange but like I don't like the <trunc>i</trunc> cos my family just don't get it</u>
<u n="122" who="S0529">no</u>
<u n="123" who="S0530">like they don't get what my blog means and what I do on it and</u>
<u n="124" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="125" who="S0530">stuff and</u>
<u n="126" who="S0529">no I mean I hope my <vocal desc="laugh"/> my family don't but <pause dur="short"/> I'm just worried about my sister as well like</u>
<u n="127" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0529">if I said anything on there that's like really bad which I have done in the past</u>
<u n="129" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0529">which is you know I should stop doing but <vocal desc="laugh"/> she always like I dunno I'm just worried she's gonna like tell my mum everything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0529">oh just like</u>
<u n="133" who="S0530" trans="overlap">er I mean like</u>
<u n="134" who="S0529">that would be the worst nightmare in the world</u>
<u n="135" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0529">if they found my blog like if they were literally on my blog just imagine it <pause dur="short"/> ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I mean er is your mum the kind of person who would like she would read it secretly er she'd keep reading it?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah she's nosy she's nosy like that</u>
<u n="139" who="S0530" trans="overlap">my you see my parents are like that</u>
<u n="140" who="S0529" trans="overlap">she's like extremely nosy like she's like Aunt Petunia nosy</u>
<u n="141" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0529">like honestly my mum is Aunt Petunia there are so many similarities she's a neat freak she's nosy she cares about what the neighbours think</u>
<u n="143" who="S0530">oh my god</u>
<u n="144" who="S0529" trans="overlap">she's quite severe she's really tall</u>
<u n="145" who="S0530">does she have a lot of neck? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0529" trans="overlap">long neck long neck yep</u>
<u n="147" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0529">honestly they are like the same person <vocal desc="laugh"/> I had an epiphany about this a couple of months ago and I was like oh shit</u>
<u n="149" who="S0530">she's Aunt Petunia</u>
<u n="150" who="S0529" trans="overlap">she's Aunt Petunia</u>
<u n="151" who="S0530"><unclear>oh god</unclear></u>
<u n="152" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's amazing <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> no she would definitely be one to do that I can totally see her doing that I know she used to read my diary</u>
<u n="153" who="S0530">really?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and my sister's yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0530">oh</u>
<u n="156" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I left it lying around when she came to clean our rooms</u>
<u n="157" who="S0530">is she how did you find that out? did she tell you?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0529">no cos I found it in a different place</u>
<u n="159" who="S0530">oh</u>
<u n="160" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I do certain things that like so I'll know exactly where it is and so I know exactly when someone hasn't moved it and it would it had moved</u>
<u n="161" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0529"><unclear/> my sister and she was like no I would tell you and she would so it was my mum <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0530">yeah it does freak you out when parents like cos I don't I don't think like they really get it at all like why people do it they just think</u>
<u n="164" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no they really don't well it's just a different generation isn't it?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0530" trans="overlap">and I don't think yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0529">they don't get that we're kind of Tumblr-obsessed this these days and we have been warped a little bit by you know what's on that website cos it's not all good like some of it's absolutely bullshit and people just need to go outside</u>
<u n="167" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0529">but <vocal desc="laugh"/> but for the most part it's like you know you <unclear/> people your own age</u>
<u n="169" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0529">and you all have like of like common issues and interests and things like that</u>
<u n="171" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="172" who="S0529">but yeah like it's ironic really that I've stopped using a diary and started using Tumblr like</u>
<u n="173" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos it is almost a diary</u>
<u n="174" who="S0529" trans="overlap">because it it feels more private to me than the Tumblr it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0530" trans="overlap">than a diary <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0529">a worldwide thing that anybody can see if they know my <unclear>ID</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's quite ridiculous but it feels a lot more personal than a diary <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0530" trans="overlap">if you ever wanted to keep a diary like here would be like the best place ironically</u>
<u n="178" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know it would yeah <pause dur="short"/> it really would</u>
<u n="179" who="S0530">because like nobody's gonna come here in here and like steal it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah but typing's easier</u>
<u n="181" who="S0530">yeah it is</u>
<u n="182" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0530">it is like I've tried keeping diaries recently but if</u>
<u n="184" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0530">blogging is easier</u>
<u n="186" who="S0529">and people reply to you as well</u>
<u n="187" who="S0530">yeah and try and comfort you and be like you're okay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and it's like yeah yeah I know and like I <trunc>kn</trunc>I know that sometimes that's not very good either but it's just yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0530">the thing is though like people understand like like Tumblr is one of the only places left on the internet where you can like say shit without being judged</u>
<u n="190" who="S0529">yes exactly</u>
<u n="191" who="S0530" trans="overlap">like they only say like now like on Facebook and Twitter they threaten you with erm like they say what is it they say? like employers will look at it and</u>
<u n="192" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0530">not hire you and stuff</u>
<u n="194" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0530">and it's like I dunno like I I I wouldn't want to post the sort of thing I write on Tumblr anyway to people that I know like no way in hell but Tumblr is just different like it's</u>
<u n="196" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0530">almost hidden within the depths of</u>
<u n="198" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it is</u>
<u n="199" who="S0530">the world <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0529">yeah cos I <trunc>s</trunc> I forget sometimes like how many people like in my actual life like know about my blogs <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0530">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and it really worries me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0530" trans="overlap">me too</u>
<u n="204" who="S0529">like cos they sometimes like pick up on it and say like oh I saw that on your blog last week and I was like oh god you know about it too?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="206" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just it's really bad cos it just feels like this internet thing for only people you don't know</u>
<u n="207" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0529">to see it but then I think like some of the anons that I get must be people I know you know like this</u>
<u n="209" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0529">it must be</u>
<u n="211" who="S0530">well who else would like</u>
<u n="212" who="S0529" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="213" who="S0530">care <unclear>that much</unclear>?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0529" trans="overlap">who else would like be so invested? like it's just erm I don't know it's really <unclear/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0530">cos you do get a few dodgy questions like</u>
<u n="216" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I do I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0530">well not even dodgy just strangely interested in certain bits</u>
<u n="218" who="S0529">I know yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0530" trans="overlap">like some of them admit that they know me in real life and I'm like oh god who are <trunc>y</trunc> like I always wonder like if they are somebody that I know vaguely or somebody like my</u>
<u n="220" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0530">one of my best friends or something I'm like oh god cos like surely my</u>
<u n="222" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0530">my best friends can just talk to me about shit</u>
<u n="224" who="S0529" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="225" who="S0530">so it's not like</u>
<u n="226" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know I sometimes think that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing it like sometimes I think that she sends <unclear>me them</unclear> like cos she I know she keeps up with it all the time erm and she probably doesn't wanna like just say it on her own blog and stuff <unclear>and then</unclear></u>
<u n="227" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0529">but then sometimes like I get well not sometimes but a few a few times I've had people on Facebook like message me saying like oh I I know your blog like I've been like kind of following it a bit and I just wanted to say that I have a lot in common with you and shit and</u>
<u n="229" who="S0530" trans="overlap">wow okay</u>
<u n="230" who="S0529">this is too much now it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0529">a real life thing and this is not okay I can't deal with it I really can't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0530">it's like when people on <unclear/> let's be friends like I don't know who you are so we can't be friends</u>
<u n="234" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I know I put like oh you need to come off and on then and then but in reality I'm like no please don't I don't wanna ever know who you are like I'm too scared I don't I don't want it to be revealed I'd rather they stayed anonymous</u>
<u n="235" who="S0530">yeah I part of me really wants to know but then another part of me is like plus when they're on Anon you can't block them</u>
<u n="236" who="S0529">I know</u>
<u n="237" who="S0530">so it's like</u>
<u n="238" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0530">like the I wouldn't ever say I know you in real life on Anon cos I know it would freak somebody out like the only time you'd ever use Anon is like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know just send a secret nice comment like you look nice or something but I wouldn't ever do it on Anon because like I have Tumblr so</u>
<u n="240" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0530">you know?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no I probably would have I would do it on Anon I think I'm too shy for that</u>
<u n="243" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah if somebody had come across came across their blog or something and then I was just like but I wouldn't ever hint like I know who you are sort of thing you know</u>
<u n="244" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no no no like if you're not gonna reveal yourself which they never do then what's the point in saying it? like</u>
<u n="245" who="S0530">I know</u>
<u n="246" who="S0529">cos you know they say to you like oh I know who you are I wish we were friends blah blah blah and then you're like okay well come on Anon and then we can you know whatever but then they just never reply like</u>
<u n="247" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="248" who="S0529">ever again it's really frustrating but also you're kind glad about it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no it isn't it's</u>
<u n="250" who="S0529" trans="overlap">the solution is to turn off Anonymous but I don't want to do that because</u>
<u n="251" who="S0530">it's not worth it for the good anons you can get you know</u>
<u n="252" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah cos most of them like the majority of them which is really surprising cos I have a lot of problematic things on that blog that people could pick into and really have a go at me but mostly people are nice</u>
<u n="253" who="S0530">they are like</u>
<u n="254" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0530">I have a feeling on my blog like people that do <unclear/> they're like my friends that are quite close to you but like I can't we don't just start chatting crap to each other like</u>
<u n="256" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0530">you know sometimes some of them be like some sort of trigger like <trunc>s</trunc> I've got some friends that we just don't talk about like</u>
<u n="258" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0530">personal stuff until something like major happens</u>
<u n="260" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0530">whereas I've got other friends like they see my blog and say what's up are you okay?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0530">I saw your blog <trunc>wher</trunc>whereas others'd just be like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0529">so <unclear/>'ll know about your blog as well</u>
<u n="265" who="S0530">not all of them only a few</u>
<u n="266" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0530">yeah but I think others do though like cos <unclear>others are family</unclear> it's so weird and I'm just like oh god like</u>
<u n="268" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know that's the problem like when you have one friend who knows it just gets out and it's just horrible</u>
<u n="269" who="S0530" trans="overlap">like I had like I think it was three friends that knew at the beginning that was it and then there's like there's some people though my friends who are friends with them found it because they've started re-blogging some of my stuff and I was like</u>
<u n="270" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0530">oh god I didn't consider this</u>
<u n="272" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0530">and then some of the girls in my sister's year were following me</u>
<u n="274" who="S0529">oh no</u>
<u n="275" who="S0530">so I'm like oh god please I bet you feed back to my sister</u>
<u n="276" who="S0529" trans="overlap">shit</u>
<u n="277" who="S0530">about me and my life and I'm oh god but my sister like</u>
<u n="278" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh that's horrible</u>
<u n="279" who="S0530">my sister denies anything like she's just like your <trunc>sis</trunc> she's like I'm not interested in your life I'm not that sad</u>
<u n="280" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0530">but I'm like surely you are though because you're my sister</u>
<u n="282" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0530">like you know</u>
<u n="284" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0530">so it's quite strange <pause dur="short"/> but then again my sister's friend posts really depressing shit so I could just like</u>
<u n="286" who="S0529" trans="overlap">why do we get so much flak for it? like we everyone does it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0529">it's not that bad</u>
<u n="289" who="S0530">I might just make a little page on my thing like if you know me in real life click this and I'm like if you <trunc>sa</trunc> if what I'm <trunc>proba</trunc> if I'm probably fine</u>
<u n="290" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0530">so just don't feed back stuff I say to friends</u>
<u n="292" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know I've kinda done that I wrote that on my about me I said I don't have a filter so just like you know expect everything</u>
<u n="293" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0529">just <unclear>don't</unclear> like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0530">yeah yeah they should do that</u>
<u n="296" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and it has been <unclear/> in the past but I can't help what I'm writing cos you know in the moment you can't really <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="297" who="S0530" trans="overlap">exactly like it's just my outlet to express myself so</u>
<u n="298" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah which sounds totally like lame but it's true</u>
<u n="299" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it is it is like you can kind of release your mind onto it and not be feared of putting</u>
<u n="300" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> literally like people that like going out like parties and things and things going on in my town like people have come up to me and said like oh I know I know your blog and then she's like how does it get round? I don't I don't understand</u>
<u n="301" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0529">how it gets round <pause dur="short"/> it's really scary</u>
<u n="303" who="S0530">er I mean it's just <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how it happens</u>
<u n="304" who="S0529">mm I I really wanna change my URL I dunno what to change it to</u>
<u n="305" who="S0530">how about the opposite of what yours is so it could be</u>
<u n="306" who="S0529" trans="overlap">what like backwards? <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos <unclear>no one</unclear> would find it</u>
<u n="307" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no like used it use erm is it <trunc>na</trunc> is it a how do you pronounce it?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0529">oh like loud <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0530">loud and <pause dur="short"/> revealing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0529" trans="overlap">loud and revealing <vocal desc="laugh"/> that would be funny <pause dur="short"/> no it needs to be something that people won't guess cos I don't want them to find it you know?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0530">oh okay</u>
<u n="312" who="S0529">ah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0530">we need to think of something deep and meaningful</u>
<u n="314" who="S0529">exactly exactly cos the first one's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that is deep and meaningful we need to think of something even more deep and meaningful</u>
<u n="316" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0530">how about</u>
<u n="318" who="S0529">I made it when I was fourteen and I wasn't even like I was still fine at that point <vocal desc="laugh"/> which is funny</u>
<u n="319" who="S0530">mm okay</u>
<u n="320" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> all the good ones have gone anyway</u>
<u n="321" who="S0530">yeah we don't want you to have to be like you know filling it with numbers</u>
<u n="322" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was like a four three and</u>
<u n="323" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0529">it was really bad</u>
<u n="325" who="S0530">like fried chicken queen one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0529">oh <unclear>that's so funny</unclear></u>
<u n="327" who="S0530">it should be fried chicken queen that'll be amazing</u>
<u n="328" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0530">erm <pause dur="short"/> you could always do an English literature-savvy name</u>
<u n="330" who="S0529">yeah I was thinking that but I don't know what <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what literary characters I actually relate to <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0529">oh who cares I'm gonna make food</u>
<u n="333" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0530"><unclear/> need a drink I can't believe I did like I did like nothing yesterday when I came in I was just</u>
<u n="335" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah me too</u>
<u n="336" who="S0530">lying on my bed and I felt so shit for so long</u>
<u n="337" who="S0529">did you?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0530">yeah just so bored</u>
<u n="339" who="S0529">oh</u>
<u n="340" who="S0530">but I was too tired to go and talk to anyone cos I was too tired</u>
<u n="341" who="S0529">yeah same I felt really not like a <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0529">wake yourself up and <unclear/> fall asleep and it's really strange and everything feels weird <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/> and go to <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0530" trans="overlap">woo</u>
<u n="345" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0530">oh your bread I found out my milk goes off today and I cried</u>
<u n="347" who="S0529">oh no</u>
<u n="348" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0529">eleventh of bloody November for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="350" who="S0530" trans="overlap">what date is it today?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> past it's the fifteenth</u>
<u n="352" who="S0530">really?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0529">how is that possible? I was eating <unclear>it</unclear> after that date</u>
<u n="354" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is it mouldy?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0529">I dunno I bought it like after the eleventh <pause dur="short"/> it's just ridiculous not fair</u>
<u n="356" who="S0530">oh that's one thing I</u>
<u n="357" who="S0529" trans="overlap">unless it's mouldy like you can eat it can't you?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah of course</u>
<u n="359" who="S0529">it's not just like</u>
<u n="360" who="S0530">you can always toast it if you like toast</u>
<u n="361" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0530">it's just cos it's like a bit stale but</u>
<u n="363" who="S0529">no I don't it feels alright does that does that feel alright to you? it's like <unclear>fluffy</unclear> bread <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0530">that feels fine <pause dur="short"/> touch my bread <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0530" trans="overlap">touch my bread I'd love to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'd love to touch your bread <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh god I'm so excited to see my cat next weekend</u>
<u n="367" who="S0529">ah yay cat <pause dur="short"/> god I wish I could go home at the weekend it's really dreary isn't it?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0530">I mean <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="369" who="S0529" trans="overlap">especially when I stay cos I <unclear/> was like tipping it down</u>
<u n="370" who="S0530">yeah cos I think I think going home can help because</u>
<u n="371" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0530">it doesn't feel like you're stuck</u>
<u n="373" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0530">whereas with you I think it must feel a bit like</u>
<u n="375" who="S0529">oh god absolutely like I was <unclear/> it today that if I do actually like <pause dur="short"/> drop out then how am I gonna get my stuff home? like cos my mum would have to erm probably hire a car again</u>
<u n="376" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0529" trans="overlap">cos our car probably wouldn't make it up here and even if I like went from my dad's house that's still like five hours</u>
<u n="378" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0529">and it's just just a fucking nightmare really like <vocal desc="laugh"/> she would literally have to come and pick me up and that's just the worst thing I could possibly do for them</u>
<u n="380" who="S0530">no yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0529">like cos they don't need that that's such a hassle</u>
<u n="382" who="S0530">that's the thing like everything takes effort doesn't it? like</u>
<u n="383" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0530">dropping out takes effort</u>
<u n="385" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0530">staying here it requires a degree of effort as well</u>
<u n="387" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hate effort <pause dur="short"/> I wish we could just be slugs and just sort of like lie around <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0530" trans="overlap">slugs would be nice just being all slimy and stuff</u>
<u n="389" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> where is the spoon?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0530">plus our lifespan wouldn't be as long</u>
<u n="391" who="S0529">exactly <pause dur="short"/> good for everyone I'm just like using all of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s cutlery and she won't <unclear/> don't tell her</u>
<u n="392" who="S0530">she won't care</u>
<u n="393" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> as long as I wash it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0530">oh</u>
<u n="395" who="S0529">this is what they meant when it's just constant rain</u>
<u n="396" who="S0530">yeah this is this is the reality of our situation now we're just here</u>
<u n="397" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah we're <unclear/> if <unclear/> really erm <pause dur="short"/> for some reason cos there's a little bit warm down there I suppose but erm yeah my mum was like oh it's just constant rain up here and <unclear/> like for the first kind of like month I was like oh this isn't too bad it's kind of like nice weather</u>
<u n="398" who="S0530">it was really nice when we first came here</u>
<u n="399" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it was yeah it was such a nice day and it was kinda like that for another week and <pause dur="short"/> but now it's shit</u>
<u n="400" who="S0530">it really is <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>gue</trunc> this is what we're gonna have for</u>
<u n="401" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0530">it's a rot day today it's like</u>
<u n="405" who="S0529">it's the fifteenth</u>
<u n="406" who="S0530">so we've been here six weeks <pause dur="short"/> longer than six weeks</u>
<u n="407" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> longer than that</u>
<u n="408" who="S0530">six and a half</u>
<u n="409" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0530">it does feel longer than that so we've been here six <trunc>week</trunc> oh fucking hell like how how is that even?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0530">I don't know</u>
<u n="413" who="S0529">I can't believe it's the fifteenth of November already Jesus</u>
<u n="414" who="S0530">mm yep</u>
<u n="415" who="S0529">come up <unclear>here</unclear> so quickly</u>
<u n="416" who="S0530">but then again we have by the by the time we get to next weekend it'll be three weeks till Christmas I think which it doesn't sound long does it? at all like I think a month sounds quite a while but then</u>
<u n="417" who="S0529" trans="overlap">what until Christmas day or until we break up?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0530">break up</u>
<u n="419" who="S0529">ah damn</u>
<u n="420" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0530">don't get your expectations too high</u>
<u n="422" who="S0529" trans="overlap">is it three weeks this week?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0530">is it this week?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0529">I think so cos it was four weeks I remember saying it's four weeks till we break up <trunc>ne</trunc> last week</u>
<u n="425" who="S0530" trans="overlap">see what the date is today the date is the fifteenth</u>
<u n="426" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe it is then</u>
<u n="428" who="S0529">not it's no it's just under a month so it's not quite four weeks I think</u>
<u n="429" who="S0530">alright okay that's good though</u>
<u n="430" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0530">oh it's gonna be so good and we'll be at home for a month how good is that?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0530">a month at home</u>
<u n="434" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'll probably get sick of it though</u>
<u n="435" who="S0530">you probably will you'll have to tell me how <anon type="place"/> is going and whether you're like I miss <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> which probably won't happen</u>
<u n="436" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'll be <unclear/> my <unclear/> out</u>
<u n="437" who="S0530">no I think I think a month is a <trunc>ni</trunc> a nice amount of time to be at home but it might be a bit it might feel a bit too long but I bet you'll have a really good week when you first get back</u>
<u n="438" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0530">or first two weeks at least</u>
<u n="440" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0530">just yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0529">yeah I think Christmas'll be good</u>
<u n="443" who="S0530">cos Christmas is a nice time of year anyway like even if I it's kinda shit when you go home for the summer because there's not really that much to do but Christmas there's things going on</u>
<u n="444" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0530">like even probably where you live there's stuff going on</u>
<u n="446" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there's a little bit going on</u>
<u n="447" who="S0530">little bit going on <unclear>about</unclear> Christmas so yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0529">I dunno <unclear>it</unclear> can also be really awkward being at home cos then everyone'll be like oh</u>
<u n="449" who="S0530" trans="overlap">how is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0529">how's it going? and it's just like no not doing it</u>
<u n="451" who="S0530">if you can get through the first term and not hand in anything I would I'd get I'd take my hat off to you and you stay and that'll be amazing</u>
<u n="452" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that would be really like impressive</u>
<u n="453" who="S0530">it would be</u>
<u n="454" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0530">but that's not an <trunc>exam</trunc></u>
<u n="456" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it's not going to happen</u>
<u n="457" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's not going to happen but</u>
<u n="458" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0530">ah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0529">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0530">I've still not seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this weekend in our flat</u>
<u n="462" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I think I heard them coming out of their rooms though cos I</u>
<u n="463" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0529"><unclear/> studying all of your footsteps and I'm kind of getting an idea of who's who now</u>
<u n="465" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0529">by the way they walk</u>
<u n="467" who="S0530" trans="overlap">how do I walk?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0529">erm usually quite like I don't know tiptoey it's not very loud</u>
<u n="469" who="S0530">really? ah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0529">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like really quite fast I think</u>
<u n="471" who="S0530">is she?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0529">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0530" trans="overlap">does she dash for it?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0529">yeah a little bit and I think that's what the erm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0530">the boys are slower</u>
<u n="476" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really like</u>
<u n="477" who="S0530" trans="overlap">manly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0529">really <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0530" trans="overlap">manly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0529">just sort of like strolls past</u>
<u n="481" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0529">yeah and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s really quiet you can't hear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> door which is really weird</u>
<u n="483" who="S0530">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is quiet she always</u>
<u n="484" who="S0529" trans="overlap">she always makes me jump like seriously <vocal desc="laugh"/> so many times</u>
<u n="485" who="S0530">this is a really strange scenario but imagine if</u>
<u n="486" who="S0529" trans="overlap">scenario is it?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0530">scenario but imagine if by the end of the year we realise one of our flatmates was a ghost</u>
<u n="488" who="S0529">oh my god</u>
<u n="489" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like we only saw her a few times like and then we're like who is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? or like she's a ghost yeah okay</u>
<u n="490" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's been dead thirty years</u>
<u n="491" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0529">oh I don't <unclear/> date</u>
<u n="493" who="S0530">what your cheese?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0529">yeah look it's the date's peeled off but it says one there that's definitely a one and then that's another figure <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="495" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that looks like eighteen</u>
<u n="496" who="S0529">I know that's what I'm hoping but it could be twelve as well</u>
<u n="497" who="S0530">but it's got a little thingy there like a little inward thing</u>
<u n="498" who="S0529">are you really telling me that you can determine that's an eighteen?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0530" trans="overlap">a little bit</u>
<u n="500" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0530">no but like</u>
<u n="502" who="S0529" trans="overlap">instead of a twelve</u>
<u n="503" who="S0530">it <trunc>goe</trunc> it goes in slightly</u>
<u n="504" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> funny thing oh</u>
<u n="505" who="S0530">I'm sure like is it mouldy? cos it's</u>
<u n="506" who="S0529" trans="overlap">or it could be fifteenth which is today I mean it looks alright I mean</u>
<u n="507" who="S0530" trans="overlap">if there's no mould on it and it's green then it's fine</u>
<u n="508" who="S0529">it smells quite strong cos it's just strong cheese but I don't think it's</u>
<u n="509" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cheese is mould</u>
<u n="510" who="S0529">is it just mould that makes it like I'm so proud of my <unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0530">no honestly it will be fine</u>
<u n="512" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh my god</u>
<u n="513" who="S0530">try a bit of it and if it's disgusting like chuck it but</u>
<u n="514" who="S0529">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0530">probably won't kill you though like a lot of people just like</u>
<u n="516" who="S0529">oh it's alright</u>
<u n="517" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0529"><unclear>well done</unclear></u>
<u n="519" who="S0530">it's just if it starts growing stuff on it <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> like if you <vocal desc="laugh"/> I started <trunc>eat</trunc></u>
<u n="520" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0530">yeah I mean I've started eating <unclear/> once is like this is out of date this is fine then I looked at the bottom and it was just white I was like ah for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="522" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0529">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh that's horrible</u>
<u n="524" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> totally gross but <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> god</u>
<u n="525" who="S0529">so cheese wish I had some salad or something <unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0530">get some of your spinach <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0529">yeah my frozen</u>
<u n="528" who="S0530" trans="overlap">your frozen spinach</u>
<u n="529" who="S0529"><unclear/> of spinach <unclear/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0530">er <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="531" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh no I was gonna make pasta oh</u>
<u n="532" who="S0530">with what?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0529">so my sauce is going out everything is going out of date and I'm trying to eat it all</u>
<u n="534" who="S0530">you could make that in the evening</u>
<u n="535" who="S0529">yeah but I really won't want to eat all that <unclear/> ruining my appetite is like nothing</u>
<u n="536" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0529">oh thirtieth that's fine</u>
<u n="538" who="S0530">woo</u>
<u n="539" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0530">I hate the way food goes out of date it's so annoying</u>
<u n="541" who="S0529"><unclear/> it's so horrible like I understand my mum now and she's always nagging at me to like</u>
<u n="542" who="S0530">eat certain things</u>
<u n="543" who="S0529">yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/> is this out of date? probably <unclear/> no that's fine</u>
<u n="544" who="S0530">woo</u>
<u n="545" who="S0529" trans="overlap">there's so much sugar in it <unclear>probably</unclear></u>
<u n="546" who="S0530">let's see what's going out of date in here</u>
<u n="547" who="S0529">nothing <unclear/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0530">yeah it's so handy though like</u>
<u n="549" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0530"><trunc>ha</trunc> when do these go out of date?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0529">never</u>
<u n="552" who="S0530">erm <pause dur="short"/> I can't even tell these go out of date <pause dur="short"/> two thousand nineteen we've got a bit of time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/> probably the quickest</u>
<u n="555" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no that's when the incredible <unclear>truth</unclear> comes out even not <unclear/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0530">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> I think it's gotta have a date next November so cool</u>
<u n="557" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0530">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0529">I keep thinking it's sixteen now for some reason</u>
<u n="560" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no oh well I like it when it's an even number I don't know why I have some satisfaction with that</u>
<u n="561" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know yeah oh thirteen was just like the worst year ever</u>
<u n="562" who="S0530">yeah it was just like what the fuck is going on? <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> I hate the way milk goes out of date oh when does tofu go out of date? I bought some tofu</u>
<u n="563" who="S0529">tofu?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0529">uh no</u>
<u n="566" who="S0530">it's fried though it's marinated it's not just plain</u>
<u n="567" who="S0529">oh that makes it better</u>
<u n="568" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's really it's really nice though it's almost like <unclear/> but it's really</u>
<u n="569" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I don't know what I'm saying <unclear>I've never</unclear> had tofu I just know that I'll hate it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0530">some people hate it but this looks quite good it's like <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0530">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're just like not going <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>that</unclear> looks really tasty</u>
<u n="576" who="S0530">it's like cos I don't like just plain tofu it's boring if you have like stuff in it it's protein and it's nice</u>
<u n="577" who="S0529">so did you like have Quorn instead of meat or do you just have vegetables and stuff?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0530">I have Quorn beans try to buy tofu now vegetarian sausages occasionally erm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0530">what?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0529">what are they made of?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0530">they're like they can be Quorn they can be like nutty stuff they can be all sorts of stuff erm what else have I got? I usually buy spaghetti</u>
<u n="583" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> lifestyle and he <unclear/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0530">it is it is quite you do feel quite good being vegetarian</u>
<u n="585" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0530">but it depends what you have like sometimes I just have a mountain of cheese and it's like</u>
<u n="587" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just like yeah healthy vegetarian life <pause dur="short"/> and I just eat cereal a lot I think</u>
<u n="589" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0530">cos it's just quicker</u>
<u n="591" who="S0529">have you ever been <unclear>a vegan</unclear>?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0530">no well I don't think I could be</u>
<u n="593" who="S0529">no</u>
<u n="594" who="S0530">I feel like too much stuff I eat is based on like milk and</u>
<u n="595" who="S0529" trans="overlap">do you eat eggs?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0530">yes</u>
<u n="597" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0530">and like fish like</u>
<u n="599" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0530">salmon and oh my god I can't wait to go home at Christmas and have smoked salmon</u>
<u n="601" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0530">I'm so excited <pause dur="short"/> that'll be amazing</u>
<u n="603" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0530">yeah we have erm smoked salmon we have not on Christmas Day we have it on like for the you know when the like you know in the evenings on Christmas not on the actual day cos we don't usually have to on Christmas Day it's all still full</u>
<u n="605" who="S0529">do you not?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0530">well we have like crackers and shit but we don't have like a big meal <pause dur="short"/> we <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="607" who="S0529" trans="overlap">that's so unusual</u>
<u n="608" who="S0530">we have erm</u>
<u n="609" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> isn't it's just meat or</u>
<u n="610" who="S0530" trans="overlap">we have turkey sandwiches for anyone that's hungry but I'm usually just like cheese biscuits and shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0529">well my family eats like so much it's really <unclear>ridiculous</unclear> like we have Christmas Eve we'll have a meal in the evening like we'll have roast ham and stuff</u>
<u n="612" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's what we have</u>
<u n="613" who="S0529">and we'll have like snacks as well as that cos we usually have a little party with the family and then Christmas Day we'll have erm Christmas dinner like the whole thing probably second helpings <vocal desc="laugh"/> then in the evening we'll have like cake and whatever like yule log or something and then Boxing Day we'll have probably another roast</u>
<u n="614" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0529">in an different family's house and it's just <unclear/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="617" who="S0529">food it's too much <unclear/> when you're talking about three roasts in the space of three days <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's really awful ah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0530">wow that's cool</u>
<u n="619" who="S0529" trans="overlap">weird it's not cool</u>
<u n="620" who="S0530">yeah at Christmas there's an excuse to just be like go crazy</u>
<u n="621" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I know just feel so horrible after it like the days after it as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you do <pause dur="short"/> like literally I just I dunno cos it's all the food it's just so nice</u>
<u n="623" who="S0529">yeah I know</u>
<u n="624" who="S0530">and then it's like ah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0529">ah Christmas food is like the best after Italian food</u>
<u n="626" who="S0530">Christmas is like the like Christmas Day we have our Christmas dinner cos it tooks takes ages to cook we have like like last year we had it like four in the afternoon</u>
<u n="627" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0530">that's how bad it got</u>
<u n="629" who="S0529">my mum's like really clinical like she gets up at like seven AM so she can put the turkey in for ten AM and</u>
<u n="630" who="S0530" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0529">so that's all ready by like one <unclear/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0530" trans="overlap">god wow yeah my family are always just late for everything so it's just like</u>
<u n="633" who="S0529">yeah I dunno what I'm gonna do if my husband can't cook cos like</u>
<u n="634" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0529">I'm not gonna be able to cook Christmas dinner like I can't do the timing</u>
<u n="636" who="S0530">no</u>
<u n="637" who="S0529" trans="overlap">but I would be able to cook it all just not so that it's all ready at the same time that's the problem</u>
<u n="638" who="S0530" trans="overlap">ready at the same time yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0529">maths betraying me again</u>
<u n="640" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you might have to get like frozen everything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh yeah cos</u>
<u n="642" who="S0530" trans="overlap">frozen everything</u>
<u n="643" who="S0529">that'll be nice</u>
<u n="644" who="S0530">oh</u>
<u n="645" who="S0529">no it <unclear/> spoil my sandwich uh</u>
<u n="646" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/> nice</u>
<u n="647" who="S0529">disgusting</u>
<u n="648" who="S0530">oh god <pause dur="short"/> you know when your friends just message you like really upset and you're like oh my god?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0529">yeah what's happened?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0530">one of my friends has had an anxiety attack</u>
<u n="651" who="S0529">oh shit</u>
<u n="652" who="S0530">yeah and she thinks <unclear>that</unclear> she can't do uni anymore</u>
<u n="653" who="S0529">oh fucking hell everyone's saying that</u>
<u n="654" who="S0530"><unclear/> see it's not just us it's not just you</u>
<u n="655" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know I told my mum last night I was like everyone in my flat is like freaking the fuck out honestly <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> it's not just me <pause dur="short"/> has she replied yet? no course not fuck's sake mummy <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna be like can you please reply to this? it's important <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0530">ah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0529">oh that thing they did about Paris on here like when Simon Cowell was like oh we're praying for Paris it's like no you're not you're just making sure you like do all the right stuff for</u>
<u n="658" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="659" who="S0529">having a TV show like so that you don't get fucking <unclear/> by OFCOM</u>
<u n="660" who="S0530" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="661" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was so fake I hated it uh</u>
<u n="662" who="S0530">I know</u>
<u n="663" who="S0529">horrible man</u>
<u n="664" who="S0530">they try and be all like correct and it's just no</u>
<u n="665" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s texting me good <pause dur="short"/> bloody hell</u>
<u n="666" who="S0530">what did she say?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0529">I don't know I'm really scared</u>
<u n="668" who="S0530">what did you ask her?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0529">mm?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0530">what did you ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? did was this</u>
<u n="671" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I didn't ask her anything she just said hi</u>
<u n="672" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="673" who="S0529">I was really worried she was gonna go off on something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no no don't worry <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0529">what was that word game we had?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0530">Word Up</u>
<u n="677" who="S0529">ah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0530">are you gonna install it again? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0529">on my Ipod cos it's got more storage</u>
<u n="680" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> my Iphone keeps like bringing up a message saying like your storage is almost full and I'm really scared <unclear/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0530" trans="overlap">uh oh</u>
<u n="683" who="S0529"><unclear>dial</unclear> me or something</u>
<u n="684" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no just say you'll have to delete stuff</u>
<u n="685" who="S0529">I've deleted everything I possibly can like I don't know what else I can like physically delete like <pause dur="short"/> you do that thing where you like put it you plug it into your phone and then you put it all on Icloud but I don't remember how to do that <pause dur="long"/> what other games are good?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0530">Club Penguin</u>
<u n="687" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0530">you should so get it</u>
<u n="689" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'm not getting Club Penguin</u>
<u n="690" who="S0530"><unclear/> hotel <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0529">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0530">erm <pause dur="short"/> there's an app that's like it's like a brain training app which I used to like I can't remember what it's called I'll have a look in a second erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0529">uh just like the amount of passwords you have to remember for things in life just makes me <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0530">oh I didn't notice all like the emoticon updates on my phone</u>
<u n="695" who="S0529">did you not?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0530">like I didn't notice the extent of how many new ones there are they've even got a turkey wow</u>
<u n="697" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0530">and a scorpion</u>
<u n="699" who="S0529">they've got a unicorn now</u>
<u n="700" who="S0530">they have</u>
<u n="701" who="S0529">and they've got like really cool little erm faces like different ones</u>
<u n="702" who="S0530">and a hurricane and</u>
<u n="703" who="S0529">and they've got loads of flags now</u>
<u n="704" who="S0530">oh have they?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0530">that's cool and they've got erm oh they've not got an avocado what a shame</u>
<u n="707" who="S0529">they still don't have a giraffe I'm really angry</u>
<u n="708" who="S0530">or a lion why haven't they got anything like that?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0529" trans="overlap">they have got a lion haven't they?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0530">no they've got a tiger but they don't have</u>
<u n="711" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh yeah they've got a tiger that's right maybe they thought like tiger was enough to</u>
<u n="712" who="S0530">well it isn't</u>
<u n="713" who="S0529" trans="overlap">well it isn't exactly <unclear/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it is not</u>
<u n="715" who="S0529">animals really <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean why not a giraffe though like? that would be so applicable to everything in my life <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0530">I know</u>
<u n="717" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh bloody hell here we go <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s replied <pause dur="long"/> oh for fuck's sake <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="718" who="S0530">er da da da <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> do the avocado guacamole <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0529">I think this map's like fairly useless</u>
<u n="720" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0529">cos it's like an old style map</u>
<u n="722" who="S0530">it is actually it's very pretty it's very <trunc>ni</trunc></u>
<u n="723" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know it's nice to look at but it's not really that helpful with geography</u>
<u n="724" who="S0530">I mean</u>
<u n="725" who="S0529">I can hardly see anything <pause dur="long"/> like I really <unclear/> problem cos I'm so shit at it</u>
<u n="726" who="S0530"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0529">right what's your explanation then?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0530">here we go <pause dur="long"/> mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0529">oh man <unclear>no</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> this is my problem cos I never get angry at my friends</u>
<u n="730" who="S0530">yeah and you need <unclear>her</unclear> really</u>
<u n="731" who="S0529">and I feel like I'm entitled to now cos I'm just gonna go for it</u>
<u n="732" who="S0530">scream your head off do what you want <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> do the avocado <shift new="normal"/> sorry I'm not helping with this</u>
<u n="733" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="734" who="S0530">I'm not helping with your anger</u>
<u n="735" who="S0529">you're not you're you're supposed to</u>
<u n="736" who="S0530">I'm sorry</u>
<u n="737" who="S0529" trans="overlap">maintain the anger and</u>
<u n="738" who="S0530">fucking fucking hell</u>
<u n="739" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> make me feel like less angry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0530">are you letting rip?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0529">I really am I'm in caps right now</u>
<u n="742" who="S0530">oh god</u>
<u n="743" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know it's that bad</u>
<u n="744" who="S0530" trans="overlap">wow okay</u>
<u n="745" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I never get the chance to do this okay?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you've reached that stage of the argument</u>
<u n="747" who="S0529"><unclear/> angry I'm really angry fucking hell</u>
<u n="748" who="S0530">still we have passed to the evil full stop we are going straight for caps are we?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yes oh yes</u>
<u n="750" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="751" who="S0529">absolutely no subtlety here <pause dur="long"/> fucking she's just goes okay I won't</u>
<u n="752" who="S0530">she won't what?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0529">she I said to her that I don't feel comfortable with you talking to my auntie about anything full stop and then she says okay I won't <pause dur="short"/> but she already has</u>
<u n="754" who="S0530" trans="overlap">but she's already done it</u>
<u n="755" who="S0529">and she already does every time she sees my auntie</u>
<u n="756" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="757" who="S0529">and she has done for probably about two years now oh my god <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0530">mm maybe say <pause dur="long"/> did you explain that you were able to reach out to people here when you need help and all that? yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I was <unclear/> saying like take it with a pinch of salt I'm reaching out to people here blah blah blah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0530">you can maybe also say that when you get angry and upset and struggle on Tumblr that is very much in the moment like you are gonna look back on that in hindsight like an hour later</u>
<u n="761" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="762" who="S0530">and be like I feel less bad</u>
<u n="763" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> thought of that</u>
<u n="764" who="S0530">yeah so it's it's not an accurate representation of like the whole time like when you post I know when I post something on Tumblr I'm I'm usually like I hate everything</u>
<u n="765" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0530" trans="overlap">and I do I might feel like that for the whole night but in the morning I feel a little bit better at least you know?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0530">even if it is only a tiny bit better <pause dur="long"/> you know all the flags for the profile pictures people are doing on Facebook now?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0530">of somebody I know has got a cat as their profile picture instead of changing it they just put the cat on a flag</u>
<u n="771" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh that's so cute</u>
<u n="772" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0529">yeah that's what you do isn't it? it's like a Facebook thing</u>
<u n="774" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0529">I was gonna do it but then I thought like it's not just France that's having this problem like I don't really wanna just</u>
<u n="776" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's what yeah cos I've done it but now I've been just looking at it and it's like these other countries that have actually</u>
<u n="777" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="778" who="S0530">and there's countries that experience this</u>
<u n="779" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the first the the like rich countries I feel like the ones that are kind of in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0530" trans="overlap">the important Western yeah <pause dur="short"/> but now it's like I look like a heartless bitch if I change it back</u>
<u n="781" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0530">can you imagine?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0529"><unclear/> okay with that now</u>
<u n="786" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god that is that is so me as well that picture <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="788" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0529">oh Miss Trunchbull every time</u>
<u n="790" who="S0530">yeah Miss Trunchbull <pause dur="short"/> I tested myself this morning on a quiz on Facebook erm what vision do you have? and apparently I have ninety-five percent better than any of the population</u>
<u n="791" who="S0529">wow</u>
<u n="792" who="S0530">yeah I was I know it's a Facebook quiz but I was quite proud of that even though that is hereditary it's not anything to do with me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0530">it's like yes do you have a pilot's vision? yes you do</u>
<u n="795" who="S0529" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="796" who="S0530">so I could be a well I couldn't be a pilot if I wanted to because there's other stuff involved but</u>
<u n="797" who="S0529" trans="overlap">you could you could be anything you want to be</u>
<u n="798" who="S0530">oh you inspirational you</u>
<u n="799" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I have really shit eyesight <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think I should have glasses full time really but I just wanna go to the eye doctors</u>
<u n="800" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's just effort isn't it? like</u>
<u n="801" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know everything comes back to that</u>
<u n="802" who="S0530" trans="overlap">getting everything sorted <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you can guarantee when any girl uploads a selfie to Facebook I'm completely for selfies but all the captions like when it really upsets me when people are really apologetic about it do you know what I mean? like</u>
<u n="803" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0530">they're like sorry for the selfie it's like no don't ever apologise for your selfieing ah <pause dur="short"/> or they'll say something like miss my long hair and then an emoticon it's like you look damn hot like a <vocal desc="laugh"/> I should totally post that but not in that voice <vocal desc="laugh"/> and actually if you could like voice comment I bet you'll be able to do that soon</u>
<u n="805" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="806" who="S0530">like you'll be able to speak and be like</u>
<u n="807" who="S0529" trans="overlap">you can do that on Whatsapp like my mum sent me a birthday like she sang happy birthday to me <unclear/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0530" trans="overlap">ah that's so cute</u>
<u n="809" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's so awful you can do it on mail on on texting as well you can send people like little soundbytes</u>
<u n="810" who="S0530">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0529">might do it to you when I'm in <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0530">you will you should do it be like</u>
<u n="813" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="814" who="S0530">yes I will do I'll make a proper film over Christmas</u>
<u n="815" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'll send you one of the sea lapping against the land</u>
<u n="816" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="817" who="S0529">that'll be nice</u>
<u n="818" who="S0530" trans="overlap">do lots of cool Insta videos like</u>
<u n="819" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm I will don't you worry</u>
<u n="820" who="S0530">and loads of crazy hipster photography</u>
<u n="821" who="S0529" trans="overlap">lots of time-lapse <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="822" who="S0530" trans="overlap">and take pictures of the interesting people that are in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0529">cos the thing is my <trunc>tum</trunc> my Instagram's gone way downhill since being up here cos it's just not as pretty</u>
<u n="824" who="S0530">I mean you can always take pictures of a bin or <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="826" who="S0530">or er a lovely view of whatever is out there</u>
<u n="827" who="S0529">exactly</u>
<u n="828" who="S0530">the mist the fog you see if we could just get easily in the country it would be rather nice like if</u>
<u n="829" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="830" who="S0530">we could go for a country walk but there's a fricking motorway in the way I'm just like like literally I looked out of my window before when I tried to walk all the way down I <unclear/> like go for a walk in the fields and be all like Julie Andrews <vocal desc="laugh"/> and and then I went down the road and there was a frigging motorway <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I was like</u>
<u n="831" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0530">like <shift new="singing"/> the hills are alive with the sound of vehicles <shift new="normal"/> and shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0529" trans="overlap">god</u>
<u n="834" who="S0530">yeah cars basically</u>
<u n="835" who="S0529">no vehicles fits better with the syllable</u>
<u n="836" who="S0530">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> lorries</u>
<u n="837" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> like an essay that should be enough</u>
<u n="838" who="S0530">that should be enough</u>
<u n="839" who="S0529">think that's long enough <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0530">see if you could do an essay on this sort of thing you'd be grand</u>
<u n="841" who="S0529">I would wouldn't I?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0530">you could just be like</u>
<u n="843" who="S0529">I know when I text I just get really like uh</u>
<u n="844" who="S0530">we need to set you some practice essays including why are you angry at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0530" trans="overlap">should just write an essay on that introduction conclusion</u>
<u n="847" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="848" who="S0530">just practise how your skills</u>
<u n="849" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0530">and yeah <pause dur="long"/> I am I'm so jealous of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right now</u>
<u n="851" who="S0529">what being in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="853" who="S0529">but to be honest I'd be quite scared to be in <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh right now yeah I forgot about that</u>
<u n="855" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> major terrorist threat <vocal desc="laugh"/> but yeah I get what you mean in terms of like being somewhere else</u>
<u n="856" who="S0530" trans="overlap">in terms of <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I bet she must it must be really hard for her to come back each time though</u>
<u n="857" who="S0529">I know I dunno how she stands it here? not I really <unclear/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I get really crazy cos I think the only</u>
<u n="859" who="S0529">I suppose it's cos she gets to go home so often</u>
<u n="860" who="S0530">mm <pause dur="long"/> I mean I know yeah I know she's kind of made out that like her parents want her to come back but I think she might have said to her parents like she can't deal with being here possibly</u>
<u n="861" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="862" who="S0530">which is completely natural I'd be the same to be honest</u>
<u n="863" who="S0529">yeah me too</u>
<u n="864" who="S0530">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it must be so hard like I think cos where I live is quite small this is sort of like <pause dur="short"/> almost an echo of where I live but it's actually you can get into the town quite easily from where I am like I can walk into town</u>
<u n="865" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="866" who="S0530">and here you can't</u>
<u n="867" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no I hate having to get the bus I can walk into town as well it takes like three minutes to get to town</u>
<u n="868" who="S0530">yeah well mine takes like ten minutes but yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> when I'm there</u>
<u n="870" who="S0530">yeah and you can get to where you want <pause dur="short"/> okay that's what you have to do at Christmas go for a pasty when you get home</u>
<u n="871" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="872" who="S0530">you'll fly so you'll be</u>
<u n="873" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>buy them</unclear> frozen and then take them up with you</u>
<u n="874" who="S0530">really?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0530">oh that's lovely</u>
<u n="877" who="S0529">so I might do that</u>
<u n="878" who="S0530">you'll have to buy what else? you'll have to get you should go totally be like a tourist and get all the shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I'm really am gonna like <vocal desc="laugh"/> buying myself like a <anon type="place"/> jumper or something</u>
<u n="880" who="S0530">hike I live in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0529">no cos the only tourist shop we have like proper like merchandise kind of tourists erm it is so expensive</u>
<u n="882" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah I can imagine like people willing to spend money when they come here</u>
<u n="883" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it's fair enough really cos I would probably exploit it like that as well but <vocal desc="laugh"/> so expensive <pause dur="short"/> anyway what happened with sleeping arrangements?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0530">oh god right okay he said <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="885" who="S0529" trans="overlap">has he not sent it?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0530">he said he said this morning no sorry he said on Friday you remember he said I'm in India the banks shut on Monday</u>
<u n="887" who="S0529" trans="overlap">until Monday that was right yeah I thought that was Sunday but that seems to have gone now</u>
<u n="888" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0529">cos Sunday <vocal desc="laugh"/> was even worse than Saturday for <unclear/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="891" who="S0529">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="892" who="S0530">yeah Monday he said Monday at any <trunc>b</trunc> I said you able to do it via Paypal? and he said I don't know what that is and I don't even see my bank my guys do it after I give instructions so sorry I don't know about these <trunc>presume</trunc>presumably online arrangements and I said Monday is fine thank you again he said sure so</u>
<u n="893" who="S0529" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0530">he we'll be doing it on Monday but I'm really excited</u>
<u n="895" who="S0529">I am for you</u>
<u n="896" who="S0530">the <trunc>m</trunc> you'll know when it happens because I will run into your room in the morning and just be like Christmas Santa's been yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0529">it will be like Christmas</u>
<u n="900" who="S0530">it will be</u>
<u n="901" who="S0529">what about grandad? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0530">that fucking twat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0529">he sent you thirty quid</u>
<u n="904" who="S0530">to be fair if it had been like a random person from around here I'd be so grateful just</u>
<u n="905" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0530">like it's like you have fucking like thirty thousand pounds like just no even more than that three hundred thousand pounds how'd they get so rich? cos half these men are so horrible</u>
<u n="907" who="S0529">I know</u>
<u n="908" who="S0530">who gives them this money?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0529">and the thing about him like my men'll do it sounds kinda like Mafia</u>
<u n="910" who="S0530">it does <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah and he doesn't sound like someone that's trying to get into my bank account</u>
<u n="911" who="S0529" trans="overlap">sounds <unclear/> henchmen <unclear/></u>
<u n="912" who="S0530">like what do how do you transfer money? like what information do you give? you give your sort code</u>
<u n="913" who="S0529">yeah and your account number</u>
<u n="914" who="S0530">which is the account number? that's on the back isn't it?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0529">no it's it's the big long one on the on the front yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0530" trans="overlap">on the front? <pause dur="short"/> oh is it? okay</u>
<u n="917" who="S0529">I'm pretty sure</u>
<u n="918" who="S0530">what's the one on the back then?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0529">that's your sort code</u>
<u n="920" who="S0530">is it?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0530">is is sort code the</u>
<u n="923" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh wait no it isn't no that's your security <unclear/> sorry</u>
<u n="924" who="S0530" trans="overlap">sort code is six digits</u>
<u n="925" who="S0529">yeah sort code's the little one on the front no I'm wrong no the back is security code</u>
<u n="926" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="927" who="S0529">that's for when you're logging in like you need that to prove like who you are and shit</u>
<u n="928" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah but they won't be able to like access my bank account then?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0529">no no not at all like what happens is like when they go on their bank account they just fill in like who you wanna send the money to they'll fill in your name your account number have you given him your name like that's on your card?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0530">I will do</u>
<u n="931" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos <unclear/> given me the details to my real name</u>
<u n="933" who="S0529">oh</u>
<u n="934" who="S0530">my name my account number well only my bank name my <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="935" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah you need the name that's on your card like the specific one that's on your card that you're <unclear/> to</u>
<u n="936" who="S0530" trans="overlap">do I give them <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? like as in to them</u>
<u n="937" who="S0529" trans="overlap">if it says it on your card then put <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0529">but if it doesn't then just don't worry</u>
<u n="940" who="S0530" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="941" who="S0529">yeah but I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would make a difference really just need your name and <unclear/> his</u>
<u n="942" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="943" who="S0529">erm and then your account number your sort code and that's it and then it just sends and he has no like he has no other access to it that's it like just send the money and then it's done</u>
<u n="944" who="S0530" trans="overlap">great great awesome well thank you for your help because I'm clueless about those sort of things I always do Paypal</u>
<u n="945" who="S0529" trans="overlap">but if you're sending it through Paypal I don't know how it works cos I've never <unclear/></u>
<u n="946" who="S0530" trans="overlap">Paypal's pretty easy but he can't do it that way cos he doesn't have it which</u>
<u n="947" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="948" who="S0530">I can imagine if you're rich you wouldn't need Paypal to send money</u>
<u n="949" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no <pause dur="short"/> paypal is wank I hate Paypal but I used to <trunc>us</trunc> it when I when I had my like Ebay business going this year cos I've been selling like loads of stuff on Ebay</u>
<u n="950" who="S0530">oh wow okay</u>
<u n="951" who="S0529" trans="overlap">making quite a bit of money to be honest</u>
<u n="952" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's really good</u>
<u n="953" who="S0529">that was kind of how I supported myself without a job but <unclear/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0530" trans="overlap">what did you sell?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0529">sell now so I can't do it anymore <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0530">how much did you sell shit for?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I sold all my old clothes <pause dur="short"/> like up to fifty quid</u>
<u n="958" who="S0530">wow</u>
<u n="959" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yes yeah cos I had this like I had this erm Kurt Geiger coat thing that I found at a car boot</u>
<u n="960" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0529">and that's like really expensive</u>
<u n="962" who="S0530">wow</u>
<u n="963" who="S0529">to buy so I made that like <unclear/></u>
<u n="964" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's really cool</u>
<u n="965" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="966" who="S0530">I could yeah to be honest I could sell I could sell some of my old clothes</u>
<u n="967" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0530">cos I've got so many old stuff at home that's still in good condition like I got one of my old prom dresses</u>
<u n="969" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="970" who="S0530">that I wore once and I could sell that for about forty quid</u>
<u n="971" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no it's all about how you like stage it like cos I always used to put them on a hanger on a white wall and it just made it look like really clean and you could just see what it was</u>
<u n="972" who="S0530">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="973" who="S0529">yeah people would just</u>
<u n="974" who="S0530">wow</u>
<u n="975" who="S0529">and erm I was like really ruthless about it cos I was like I'm usually really attached to my clothes but I just felt like no I I never wear this I'm selling it</u>
<u n="976" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you can buy new ones if you did that yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and and ever since I haven't thought about all the old clothes I've sold like I'd never have though about like wearing them</u>
<u n="978" who="S0530" trans="overlap">missing it</u>
<u n="979" who="S0529">no so it's really</u>
<u n="980" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="981" who="S0529">yeah it's fine</u>
<u n="982" who="S0530">that's really good</u>
<u n="983" who="S0529">mm <pause dur="short"/> I need to stop talking with my mouth open <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos I'm eating</u>
<u n="984" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0529">so disgusting</u>
<u n="986" who="S0530">you're <unclear>allowed</unclear> to be a pig</u>
<u n="987" who="S0529">mm thanks</u>
<u n="988" who="S0530">you are you are you're entitled</u>
<u n="989" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> to be fair but that's okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="990" who="S0530">you're entitled to eat with your mouth open</u>
<u n="991" who="S0529">she hasn't replied to this essay that I wrote</u>
<u n="992" who="S0530">that is insulting</u>
<u n="993" who="S0529">I know</u>
<u n="994" who="S0530">has she read it?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0529">it doesn't say she hasn't got <unclear/> more</u>
<u n="996" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="997" who="S0529">I know it's so infuriating it just says delivered but she's obviously read it</u>
<u n="998" who="S0530">just be like hello <vocal desc="laugh"/> hello hello <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <shift new="singing"/> mm mm mm <shift new="normal"/> I wonder what time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be back tonight from <anon type="place"/>? <pause dur="short"/> she'll probably be back at like ten o'clock</u>
<u n="999" who="S0529" trans="overlap">probably this evening yeah probably quite late cos of the train</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos she she could</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0530">can't believe she can get from <anon type="place"/> to here so quickly</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0529">I know</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0530">it's crazy <pause dur="short"/> well that's like half the time it takes me to get home if it takes two hours like that's mad <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of mobile phone"/>
<u n="1005" who="S0529">oh here we go <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0530">message</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0529" trans="overlap">she actually needed me to say hello with loads of question marks</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0530">what's she said? <pause dur="long"/> ah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's like yes okay I won't go I won't talk to your auntie and I won't go on your blog <vocal desc="laugh"/> blah blah blah think she's a bit scared of me</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0530">oh no or no <trunc>bu</trunc></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it's cos I never get angry like this with my friends ever I'm always the calm one</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0530" trans="overlap">she like this is she must think like this is some serious shit</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0529">yeah well it is serious shit I'm very angry about this</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0530">I would be to be honest like</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0529" trans="overlap">like this is one of my insecurities as well like my family knowing all this shit that I tell me friends like it's not okay with me</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0530">cos family is just too personal isn't it? like</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0529" trans="overlap">exactly and the fact that she's like really buddy with my auntie and it's really fucking annoying like it's just like</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0530">what do they get on really well then?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah and then she talks about her to me like as if they're friends and it's like you're not friends you're she <trunc>f</trunc> she is my auntie and I don't want you talking about me to her like fine you can talk to her about yourself and whatever you want but just not about me cos I don't think that's okay and I</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no I wouldn't</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0529">you know if I've said I don't want her to talk to her about me then she shouldn't do that</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0530">no exactly like she should respect your wishes</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and she's done it so many times I know I know</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0530">I mean it's your auntie</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0529">not I really don't mind that she's friends with her just not fucking talking about me all the time</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0530">I know</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0529">uh it makes me mad it makes me so mad <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it's over now calm again</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0530">it's over now</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0529" trans="overlap">feeling calmer forgiven them</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0530">you've forgiven them that quickly?</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0530">well well that's good that is good</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I'd forgiven <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> first cos she was honest with me in the first place like she said to me she just told me everything and</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0529">she was you know</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0530" trans="overlap">well they'll get the message now like they probably won't</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I hope so <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I just hope they'll learn from my example here because I've forgiven them and so in future if they ever <pause dur="short"/> if I ever piss them off then</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0530">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> have this to look at</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0530">and it's like invading your personal space so like</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it really does feel like that</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0529">mm <pause dur="short"/> bloody nightmare it is</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0530">nightmare <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I hate Sundays so much</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0529">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0530">it's the worst day of the week</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0529">it's just horrible because you start dreading the Monday again it's like <vocal desc="misc"/> no I'm not happy about</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
