<text id="S95D">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:05:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-07</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0146</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Clothes, food and cooking, travelling, health and illness, exercise classes</topics>
		<activity>Friends preparing and eating dinner while chatting.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0146">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Journalist / editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Punjubi -- Advanced; French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">so how much were your bargain buy shoes?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0146">my bargain buy eh twenty-five eh great British pounds</u>
<u n="3" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0146">em I don't know whether they'll be water resistant but you know what it doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/> they eh they do the job and they'll they'll be fine for work <pause dur="short"/> for as long as they last</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">they've lovely <pause dur="short"/> you look</u>
<u n="6" who="S0146">I went  I went  to em</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">very smart in black <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0146">I went to these em I went to loads of shops I just cos I'd been at work since like quarter to eight and then em my computer completely and utterly screwed up and eh and I just thought you know what I'm here I can't actually do anything and the team in Birmingham actually are struggling so let me  let me  go up there <pause dur="short"/> and then it started raining and then my shoes actually started falling apart on my feet eh</u>
<u n="9" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0146">and then I had a look around <pause dur="short"/> I went to the Topshop flagship store and like you know the whole thing about like you know disposable fashion and you know it's really cool and buy it it's in and then you know buy something else doesn't seem to work because actually it's really expensive <pause dur="short"/> like the prices are</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">totally <pause dur="short"/> and it's still a bad quality</u>
<u n="12" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like bad quality and really expensive</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0146"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I just couldn't understand</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">go figure</u>
<u n="16" who="S0146">so then I went to like you know cos they have the big department stores isn't there like Debenhams House of Fraser and stuff so I walked through all those and I thought if I can find a really nice solid pair of shoes like the brown ones I'd worn for the you know the ballet pumps that I wear <pause dur="short"/> there you know to the point that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't really notice my fashion know knows exactly what shoes I'm talking about whenever I mention oh your brown ones? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos when I got them I wore them I think for a year and a half nonstop</u>
<u n="17" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0146">and then I thought if I can find something like that and then I did but they were like a hundred pounds and I thought you know what that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">one hundred pounds</u>
<u n="20" who="S0146">for little ballet pumps?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">and did they look like they were going to last?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean they were all like Bertie Pied de Terre and all of that kind of stuff so they were they're pretty solid but <pause dur="short"/> if you wore them you would that's exactly what you would say <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't pay a hundred pounds for those <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">do you want some soup?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0146">no <pause dur="short"/> thank you I think this is gonna be quite a heavy protein carb fulfilment <pause dur="short"/> but get a glass and have some wine <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna go and find the can I go?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0146">I'm just gonna go and find the em the Tupperware thing and bring it down</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">no probs <pause dur="short"/> and were you  were you  supposed to come back tonight?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0146">yeah em I'm going back again tomorrow actually</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">so you came  you came  back from London tonight and you're going to London again tomorrow?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the em the thing I have to be in is for three hours and that's in the afternoon two till five <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just gonna work from Birmingham in the morning <pause dur="short"/> and also em the whole meeting on Thursday was unexpected and so I didn't really actually have a change of clothes and you know all of that <pause dur="short"/> so so I just I wanted to come home and have a good rest</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">Good idea</u>
<u n="32" who="S0146">Good idea</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">alright so what do you think of the top <pause dur="short"/> this top <pause dur="short"/> I bought it in out Urban Outfitters and it just doesn't</u>
<u n="34" who="S0146">wow that's lovely</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">it doesn't suit me at all because it suited me when I had a suntan but now I'm really pale</u>
<u n="36" who="S0146">well you might get a suntan in the summer and it has a nice holiday top as well</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I'll never get a suntan as much as I had when it suited me <pause dur="short"/> so I was just thinking</u>
<u n="38" who="S0146">but it's also a nice holiday top isn't it? To wear abroad</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">but</u>
<u n="40" who="S0146">if you did get that colour back</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">if you</u>
<u n="42" who="S0146">I like it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">if you  like it if you'd wear it <pause dur="short"/> the thing is I tried to wear it for work as well with a black</u>
<u n="44" who="S0146">exactly <pause dur="short"/> with a cardigan</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">cardigan but on me it just looks like it's a pyjama top or something <pause dur="short"/> and it's because I</u>
<u n="46" who="S0146">what about with em jeans with like light blue jeans?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the problem is the the colouring  the colouring  isn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0146">the face</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">the colouring of the face or <pause dur="short"/> no but I mean if you'd wear it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0146">I'd can I  can I</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">I'm happy for you to have it</u>
<u n="52" who="S0146">try it on after?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018">yeah sure</u>
<u n="54" who="S0146">but I think it's lovely</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> I want you to try it on while you're washing up</u>
<u n="56" who="S0146">while you're washing up and then while you're eating</u>
<u n="57" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0018">come on multitask woman <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0146">should we go in the lounge? It will be a bit it might be a bit warmer to eat</u>
<u n="60" who="S0018">yeah wherever you want</u>
<u n="61" who="S0146">I think it might be <pause dur="short"/> I was just cleaning this pan out because when the climbing boys come back they might want to use it</u>
<u n="62" who="S0018">bon appétit</u>
<u n="63" who="S0146">abso-blinking-lutely</u>
<u n="64" who="S0018">so what's in this? There is <pause dur="short"/> em okay I boiled the water</u>
<u n="65" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0018">then put potatoes carrots parsnips onion sweet potato and something else <pause dur="short"/> celery</u>
<u n="67" who="S0146">wow</u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> and now there's chickpeas in there</u>
<u n="69" who="S0146">I was going to say and then yeah then did you add them afterwards?</u>
<event desc="sound of television"/>
<u n="70" who="S0018">Will that be okay with the <pause dur="short"/> for the sound?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0146">oh put it  put it  alright down <pause dur="short"/> how about that?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0018">and then blended it all up</u>
<u n="73" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">and ta da</u>
<u n="75" who="S0146">and then you added the chickpeas afterwards?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">yeah I just put chickpeas in now because I needed some something heavy</u>
<u n="77" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">do you want to try some?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018">like it?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0146">mm <pause dur="short"/> what gives it the sweetness?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">I guess it's the parsnip and the carrot <pause dur="short"/> cos there's nothing</u>
<u n="83" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">there's nothing else in it at all</u>
<u n="85" who="S0146">God that is so gorgeous</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0146">try a bit of this this is em this is just curried tuna almost</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">how did you do this?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0146">with a god don't don't humour me</u>
<u n="90" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">go on tell me</u>
<u n="92" who="S0146">very very basic <pause dur="short"/> onion and garlic cumin sautéed <pause dur="short"/> this is so pathetic I mean I feel embarrassed to tell you</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">it's not pathetic</u>
<u n="94" who="S0146">I then everything is whacked in peppers tomatoes em masala salt black pepper eh sweetcorn tuna</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0146">mixed and mixed together</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">no it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> it's really flavoursome <pause dur="short"/> did you put tomatoes in it?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">fresh tomatoes or chopped?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0146">four</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0146">yeah I did</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">is that what keeps it a bit moist?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0146">yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> but then em I don't wait for it to dry out either so while they're all still a bit runny that's when I add the tuna and then just whack it together</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018">mm hm and is that wholemeal pasta?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0146">mm hm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018">I don't think I've ever tried wholemeal pasta before <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice</u>
<u n="108" who="S0146">when you mix it up it doesn't taste bad at all <pause dur="short"/> and once you get used to it you prefer it almost</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's more eh more eh  more eh  I don't know</u>
<u n="110" who="S0146">it's like brown bread white bread isn't it?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018">I do like brown bread especially with seeds in it like that</u>
<u n="112" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">Warburton's stuff but sometimes white</u>
<u n="114" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">bread and loads of butter is the best <pause dur="short"/> no but that's it's like wholemeal pasta it's like it's more meaty <pause dur="short"/> like it's more</u>
<u n="116" who="S0146">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">I'll have to get me some of that</u>
<u n="118" who="S0146"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0018">then again whenever I do pasta it's so unhealthy <pause dur="short"/> I'm not thinking</u>
<u n="120" who="S0146">why what do you do?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">just because I about every <pause dur="short"/> I usually do some kind of tuna pasta</u>
<u n="122" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">with red pepper onions umm a can of tomatoes a bit of garlic</u>
<u n="124" who="S0146">so <trunc>al</trunc> almost identical <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just without all the spices and</u>
<u n="126" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018">without the sweetcorn</u>
<u n="128" who="S0146">this is curried up isn't it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> and mine ends up being more like a bolognaise sauce</u>
<u n="130" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018">but the problem then is that I add so much Parmesan cheese</u>
<u n="132" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">I think I only eat it</u>
<u n="134" who="S0146">really?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0018">so that I can put cheese on it</u>
<u n="136" who="S0146">I find that if I eat it late and cos like when we have pasta Fezel always wants to put you know grated mozzarella or grated any cheese whatever cheese there is he wants to pop it on the top <pause dur="short"/> and I find it makes it quite heavy then</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0146">especially late at night <pause dur="short"/> I mean Parmesan's fine but you know but like full on grated mozzarella then blanketed over <vocal desc="laugh"/> melted</u>
<u n="139" who="S0018">I know my Parmesan is never light <pause dur="short"/> there's always at least an inch thick <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I get those little packets you can get from Sainsbury's and they're already grated</u>
<u n="140" who="S0146">exactly</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018">and just stick it all over and then when it melts and goes all stringy hmm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0146">so what's going on with your work stuff now then? What's cos you took a break didn't you?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">I'm waiting to hear for a few job applications and and then I'll take it from there</u>
<u n="144" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0018">but</u>
<u n="146" who="S0146">and so everything you will do just until September and then you'll start it again?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018"><trunc>N</trunc> oh the course no if I start the course again I'll start it in January <pause dur="short"/> because I've already done September to January</u>
<u n="148" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018">so I don't have to do that bit again <pause dur="short"/> I would do</u>
<u n="150" who="S0146">so you got a good big breathing space haven't you?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="152" who="S0146">do you think it would be okay to pick up from there then so you can just pick up and then</u>
<u n="153" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it will be fine <pause dur="short"/> it will be easier to pick up from</u>
<u n="154" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">that point</u>
<u n="156" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018">than it was complete exhaustion <pause dur="short"/> I've already done the first five months</u>
<u n="158" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and em at least I know how much work will be involved so</u>
<u n="160" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">I'll be able to try I'll try and do some before <pause dur="short"/> I'll do</u>
<u n="162" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">I'll try and do a lot of it the academic work before</u>
<u n="164" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018">January so at least I have the</u>
<u n="166" who="S0146">A bit of a head start</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> we'll see what happens <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0146">do you miss Spain or are you getting used to it a bit now?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018">em I miss <trunc>s</trunc> spring time</u>
<u n="170" who="S0146">there's no spring here <pause dur="short"/> it's like bloody winter</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah no I don't mind winter because there's winter in Spain too it's just</u>
<u n="172" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">my body tells me that now this is the time where you start wearing sandals <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0146">relaxing a bit <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's slightly long <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Next week is em British Summer Time</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018">no?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0146">it is <pause dur="short"/> next Sunday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0018">yeah but the words British and summer time never go well in a sentence together do they? Have you got any holidays planned?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0146">no <pause dur="short"/> nothing at the moment</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">have you got any holiday time still to take?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I've got about five days and I'm gonna try and carry it over <pause dur="short"/> cos I've got no reason to take it actually <pause dur="short"/> cos I wanted to go to India <pause dur="short"/> cos you know my mum is and dad they both work for British Airways</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">mm no I didn't know that</u>
<u n="182" who="S0146">they do <pause dur="short"/> my dad was an engineer and my mum worked for a British Airways catering</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0146">and they worked for a <trunc>lo</trunc> a long time actually</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0146">and em so we always had like up to the age of twenty-four we'd have a really good staff discount</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">brilliant</u>
<u n="188" who="S0146">and eh I mean the the flip side of it was the fact that you were always on a standby list</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0146">but the good side of it was that as the years accrued and experience em pardon me and seniority like you know you get up the list a bit <pause dur="short"/> so you know it wasn't I mean I've had some disastrous occasions where like I remember one school summer holiday and me my mum and my brother went to India and we spent two weeks going to Delhi like we were staying in Delhi at my auntie's house spent two weeks going to the airport British Airways flight no it's full <pause dur="short"/> that flight no it's full <pause dur="short"/> that flight no it's full <pause dur="short"/> staying there from like the afternoon to two in the morning</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0146">coming back doing the same thing again doing the same thing again I remember doing the same thing in Toronto for a week I mean the the the Delhi one was the worst <pause dur="short"/> my dad had to then fly because obviously with him flying we got a bit more seniority</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0146">Cos obviously there's a difference isn't there? And em he then had to fly that weekend because obviously school was starting again there I was think I was going to like my fifth fifth form or something <pause dur="short"/> and then he had to fly em and with his weight you know we got at least five hundred and two of us got a seat and the other two don't really matter that much and they just waited another few days <pause dur="short"/> and it was just because it was crunch time you know end of school holidays</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0146">em and the same thing happened in Canada I remember and it's so soul destroying going there everyday and then like to run into happy passengers</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="198" who="S0146">boarding and you're standing on the side cos you have to go and check in first as well</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">and you just wanna go home</u>
<u n="200" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then you watch everyone check in at the end of the holiday and then they wait and wait and in Canada they were really bad <pause dur="short"/> they would take you right up to the gate and at the gate they would tell you <pause dur="short"/> so then you would have to ring someone to come and collect you at midnight and go home</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> and where were you staying then? Wasn't that a problem with your accommodation?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0146">with em family and friends and whoever anyone <pause dur="short"/> it's been so random from like close family to absolute randomness <pause dur="short"/> and there was one time actually in Delhi when I I did  I did  get stuck and and because it was quite a sure safe seat and then what happened was there was fog and you know loads of flights were delayed and whatever <pause dur="short"/> what happened in this instance was that I'd come from the Punjab I'd travelled down for five hours and friends not even my family friends of the family these like they had said oh you know they took me out for like nice dinner and they said you know cos it looked it was quite a clear flight and they said oh you know fine bye bye whatever <pause dur="short"/> and then dropped me off at the airport and then about an hour later this like horrible mist started developing and then all the flights were grounded <pause dur="short"/> they were grounded for five hours and all I could ring was my dad up in the Punjab and let him know what was going on and I kept I didn't  I didn't  you know really want to ring these people cos it's like you know coming up to midnight and I thought I don't want them to come all the way you know forty minutes in to come and collect me and stuff</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0146">and I didn't know when I'd be sort of flying <pause dur="short"/> anyway I was there till like two three in the morning <pause dur="short"/> and then like my dad had to like properly coach me and he was like okay so em you know em <pause dur="short"/> what you have to do is you have to say you know on <trunc>p</trunc> proper BBC voice you have to em you know act really official don't try and be nice <pause dur="short"/> be really you know and he was like really coaching me and it absolutely worked cos in the end they were like okay madam you know <pause dur="short"/> come and stay you know we've got a hotel for these occasions you know so they put me up and they really took good care all of a sudden</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">how <pause dur="short"/> go on give me an impression of how you did it</u>
<u n="206" who="S0146">so I was just like em hi yes I'm <trunc>fly</trunc> eh yes so I'm a BBC journalist and I'm flying back to London you know my flight's been delayed <pause dur="short"/> I don't have family nearby em you know can you put me up <pause dur="short"/> please <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="207" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0018">do it</u>
<u n="209" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018">that happened to me in Sri Lanka once <pause dur="short"/> we em we were flying from Trivandrum to Sri Lanka from Sri Lanka to Heathrow</u>
<u n="211" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0018">and we were getting on the plane to come back to Heathrow from Sri Lanka</u>
<u n="213" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018">and they were all they were all these loads of <trunc>or</trunc> loads of men in orange like Guantanamo overalls crawling all over the plane on on the <trunc>ou</trunc> on the exterior of the plane</u>
<u n="215" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0018">and everyone was like that's a bit strange what's going on here?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0018">and then as soon as we had all sat down they were like sorry there's been a delay everybody off and they put us in this tiny waiting room and the men the orange men we could see them they were still crawling all over the plane <pause dur="short"/> and this was like mm I'd have to say happening for about five hours and wouldn't let us out or to go to the toilet or to get water or anything and there was nothing in there <pause dur="short"/> and so there was this huge mutiny <vocal desc="laugh"/> Everyone was like you must let us out we have to go to the toilet you must provide us with water at least and em <pause dur="short"/> to be able to go and get some food and they were just weren't giving us any information about how long the delay would be or when they would be able to let us out to go to the toilet <pause dur="short"/> and I think in the end they let us out and they gave us some free food but then by then it was like we'd been waiting for twenty hours <vocal desc="laugh"/> They cancelled the flight but it was only because we made a a huge stink about it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0018">but they said okay alright we we'll book a hotel for everybody</u>
<u n="221" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">but had we not said anything</u>
<u n="223" who="S0146">they would've  they would've  have been fine</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0146">Cos that was the other daunting prospect <pause dur="short"/> I mean leaving the hotel at sorry leaving the airport cos they said oh come back tomorrow you know just it's not safe to fly now <pause dur="short"/> and that was the other thing like leaving where the hell would I go and I wouldn't trust a taxi driver with all my luggage and just me at two in the morning to take me to the right place</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="227" who="S0146">alive <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0018">so what was em what were you going to say that you were thinking of going to India but could you fly?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0018">with these special priced seats then?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0146">yes so basically my mum and dad get like a couple of free tickets a year <pause dur="short"/> so like you know because they're both retired and stuff and that's sort of what happens <pause dur="short"/> and em <pause dur="short"/> and so like my dad can have one fellow passenger and my mum can have one fellow passenger <pause dur="short"/> and because you know politically because my sister is married and there's three of them so then my dad picked my brother and then my mum picked me and my mum and dad are going to India so basically I would have flown with them and obviously because of the years of experience that we always get upgraded to at least business class</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0146">it's just absolutely great you know flying with  flying with  them now is not have we got a seat it's are we in club?</u>
<u n="234" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0146">it's the <pause dur="short"/> it's like you know if you don't get that flight and then the disappointment no we're in world traveller plus <pause dur="short"/> aw</u>
<u n="236" who="S0018">mm so <pause dur="short"/> can the if if they get free? So if your parents can invite somebody to accompany them? Is that still like a standby seat?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0146">no <pause dur="short"/> well actually it's a standby seat but it's so high in the priority it's so <pause dur="short"/> so what happens is this is a whole big long thing right so basically like with anything they overbook so they you know seven hundred seats they will book for eight hundred and fifty knowing full well there'll be cancellations people won't get there in time people will lose their passports</u>
<u n="238" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0146">all that kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> so there's always seats but as it gets to your em like crunch holiday time so Christmas holidays Easter holidays and stuff <pause dur="short"/> sometimes and they're you know it some it used to happen quite a lot in the past but now there's like a big you know mushrooming of budget airlines and stuff there's so many airlines <pause dur="short"/> but before when they were the standard carriers what would happen is you know where airlines would make a mistake where there's like an overbooking actually when people are desperate to get back and then they did say and then they get stuck you know in the nineties they started these alliances</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0146">so you just pass them on so you know British Airways you know pass their passengers over to Qantas and say you know I'm sorry would you mind flying with we'll upgrade you to first class or business class or something and</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0146">you know circumvent it that way <pause dur="short"/> so there's a little bit of that going on but then normally they em they don't fill the seats so that's when you have you're you can have sometimes like fifty standby passengers actually <pause dur="short"/> I mean this was back in the day you know</u>
<u n="244" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0146">there were like they were the standard carriers now there's</u>
<u n="246" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0146">you know air travel is cheap and all of that and so the everything's slightly different <pause dur="short"/> but most times you could have you know up to fifty passengers so actually then it comes to priority <pause dur="short"/> and the more you know the more experienced you are like my dad had like eighteen years of experience at British Airways</u>
<u n="248" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0146">so he over the years accrued you know priority and we got pushed up the chain so actually you know retired people almost I think out of due obligation and certainly this was honoured in the past would you know experienced retired people would obviously be the first sort of you know you travel like normal passengers they wouldn't even really need to go into a standby list</u>
<u n="250" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="251" who="S0146">and that's the same with us really <pause dur="short"/> so we now I mean the last time I flew I suppose with them was in two thousand and nine and that was em to Calgary and it was peak time <pause dur="short"/> it was peak of the summer holidays and em it was you know in terminal five British Airways <pause dur="short"/> we got there and literally what we did we checked in I treated them to Carluccios we have this really great lunch which I'll come back which is funny and then we went back and they said yes and then they gave us four club class seats and we just walked straight through and went to the you know executive lounge chilled out and then went straight through</u>
<u n="252" who="S0018">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> I'm surprised they still do free flights nowadays <pause dur="short"/> cos British Airways were cutting loads of</u>
<u n="253" who="S0146">well they had a you know the year that my dad was made retired which was two and a half years ago that's when they introduced look <pause dur="short"/> either we're going to make further cuts or for three months we want eight hundred staff to work without pay what do you prefer?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0018">what? For three months? It's crazy</u>
<u n="255" who="S0146">I mean this was a a proposal</u>
<u n="256" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0146">I think  I think  it was rejected by the unions</u>
<u n="258" who="S0018">not surprised <pause dur="short"/> not surprising <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0146">it was almost a case of if you want your job if you want to keep your job you have to work you know for nothing or absolute minimum you know for a little while until we get over this <pause dur="short"/> em and I think it was rejected and you know my dad poor thing you know he had a year to go to retiring and you know he was first in the line wasn't he? He took it quite badly cos he actually expected to stay for another year <pause dur="short"/> so it was quite hard actually</u>
<u n="260" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="261" who="S0146">still getting over it</u>
<u n="262" who="S0018">what so he had to retire a year earlier?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0146">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0018">did that affect his pension?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0146">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't know much about his</u>
<u n="266" who="S0018">but eh why did it affect him? Just because he wasn't ready to stop working?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0146">yeah emotionally it affected him completely and utterly because suddenly you know you have to mentally prepare for such a transition in your life</u>
<u n="268" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> true</u>
<u n="269" who="S0146">and to like have spent your whole life doing something and then all of a sudden told you've got three months <pause dur="short"/> it's a bitter pill to swallow</u>
<u n="270" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0146">and then what the hell do you do with the rest of your life <pause dur="short"/> you haven't like got yourself geared up for that</u>
<u n="272" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we'll probably be em we won't have any memories when we retire we'll be like eighty and shuffling around with walking sticks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0146">we hope</u>
<u n="274" who="S0018">so what happened at Carluccios?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0146">so we sat there on this little table <pause dur="short"/> a really small little table me my mum my dad and my brother and then em like there was quite a long table next to us <pause dur="short"/> and then there was like this guy looked like a a guru like a priest you know almost like you know if he was bare you know bare chested he would have looked like Gandhi kind of thing you know like really really old and blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but he was in like mass like negotiations let's say he obviously had his business team all around him <pause dur="short"/> they were like oh you know and they were talking like high level marketing and they were talking about like high level economics to the point that I couldn't really understand you know but I knew it was so</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018">were you eavesdropping? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0146">so they were they sat as close as you were I suppose</u>
<u n="278" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="279" who="S0146">but on a a longer table <pause dur="short"/> and but they were like really and he was like especially like you know with his team they were like really hammering something but they they were all sort of leaning forwards they were like blah blah blah strategy structure something something like really going for it <pause dur="short"/> and then em and then all of a sudden I so we just carried on we're just like eating eating you know but kept looking over like eating eating and thinking who the hell is this guy he must be someone quite famous right? But none of us recognised him off the telly so we carried on eating <pause dur="short"/> and then all of a sudden like this one of his  one of his  cronies went and brought this little old lady over and so she walked over and then she came up and we just heard her she's like oh guruji I I'm so glad I've met you <pause dur="short"/> I've come all this way and I wanted to catch you before you left England <pause dur="short"/> and then all of a sudden the whole team were like completely like in this Zen like aura and he was just like oh my god <pause dur="short"/> yes thank you <pause dur="short"/> I just have a simple glass of milk <pause dur="short"/> Like he bloody ate a steak a minute ago</u>
<u n="280" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">and what?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0146">and he was like and then she was like oh thank you I want to <pause dur="short"/> so obviously they're doing that like classes and where like you know this practice and that practice and whatever and he's like and he was like all of sudden he's like <pause dur="short"/> you know really really <pause dur="short"/> we were like you little phony</u>
<u n="283" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">what kind of guru was he?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0146">God knows little he was too busy talking about what money he was making rather than what he was bloody preaching</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0146">the poor little granny god knows how she got to terminal five</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="289" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">it wouldn't surprise me if he was some kind of yoga guru</u>
<u n="291" who="S0146"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Exactly going back to India</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">the one the Ashtanga one <pause dur="short"/> em what's his name? Betabi Joy <pause dur="short"/> he's been really slated by a lot of fellow yogis in India for pushing the marketing side and America and</u>
<u n="293" who="S0146">well it is a money</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">making a profit</u>
<u n="295" who="S0146">you know</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0146">if you can't spin the money you know if you need to you can't get to be Madonna's yoga teacher <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's it isn't it?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">it's not something personally I'd aspire to</u>
<u n="299" who="S0146">no</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Being Madonna's yoga teacher</u>
<u n="301" who="S0146">no</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">yes making lots of money but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0146">no but that's it isn't it? That's where you know <pause dur="short"/> he works with you know Hollywood stars <pause dur="short"/> they're all nuts <pause dur="short"/> this Madhuri yesterday she's so like a you could tell that she was a bit of a prima donna</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">oh the famous girl?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">is she art is she an actress?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0146">she she dominated Bollywood in the nineties</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">oh yeah yeah yeah you said</u>
<u n="309" who="S0146">she was absolutely massive in the nineties <pause dur="short"/> she was on that</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">and now she's reclusive</u>
<u n="311" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well not reclusive what she did was she moved out of Bombay and she moved over to America <pause dur="short"/> she met a guy a surgeon which her brother had like fixed them up on a blind date and actually he had never even watched any sort of Bollywood film <pause dur="short"/> so you know he didn't really play into that sort of hype actually and what was really lovely was then you know what she wanted to do was settle down and have kids and all of that kind of stuff and she did it in Denver with him <pause dur="short"/> and it's now that she's looking to make a bit more of a comeback I suppose <pause dur="short"/> and so they're now living between you know Denver and Bombay <pause dur="short"/> but you could tell you know <trunc>y</trunc> like basically in the nineties the whole sort of romantic era all those love stories of Bollywood she was like the main <pause dur="short"/> she always had like a bit of Whitney Houston type like innocence sweet</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0146">pretty features you know like really good clean wholesome lovely girl</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0146">kind of thing and em</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">so is she going to make a comeback to films now?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0146">she made it about three years ago and then she denied it was a comeback <pause dur="short"/> she just said look I have been in the industry <pause dur="short"/> but it was so funny so like this new presenter <unclear/> not new presenter but the presenter hadn't really done this sort of thing before and she had like a little sugar plum fairy more overdressed than the poor little Bollywood actress you know like really went for it <pause dur="short"/> and like there was one point when like the <trunc>produc</trunc> like my colleague held up a white card to say you know we can't hear <pause dur="short"/> something was wrong with the earpiece thing</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="319" who="S0146">so they had to take their earpieces out there was interference or something and so she kept holding the card like you know behind the actress to say take you know take you earpiece out something <pause dur="short"/> take your earpiece out <pause dur="short"/> and em and she and then so but she just kept going</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0146">and then in the end Madhuri turned around and she said I think that white piece of paper there's an instruction should we just stop and see what what it's says</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018">oh she hadn't realised it was?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0146">so then the girl ran on the stage and she's said I'm really really sorry can you just take your earpiece out  can you just take your earpiece out? So they took their earpieces out and then the girl said to her who'd run on the stage oh if you want you know can you take your earring off please? Right <pause dur="short"/> so she said could you it's fine you can leave your other earring <pause dur="short"/> Yeah but from that camera I'll have one earring on <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="324" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0018">darling</u>
<u n="326" who="S0146">darling</u>
<u n="327" who="S0018">can't be done I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I find it quite funny the way that all the women on TV like on the you know the national lottery shows and the Dancing With the Stars and all that</u>
<u n="328" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0018">they're all dressed up beautifully but you can see that they've got this big they look like the hunch back in Notre Dame</u>
<u n="330" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0018">because they've got the big</u>
<u n="332" who="S0146">cable</u>
<u n="333" who="S0018">big box underneath their dress</u>
<u n="334" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0018">what is it? Is it for the mic? Yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> they've probably got one of those <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0146">it's kind of similar like a radio mic so the whole sort of em earpiece thing <pause dur="short"/> they've got a little bit in their ear as well but it with their big hear hair it's sort of kinda very discreetly comes over and you can't see it cos their hair is down</u>
<u n="337" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="338" who="S0146">so you can't see it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to tell my dad <pause dur="short"/> he's to start wearing a hearing aid <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to tell him that he should grow out his hair</u>
<u n="340" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0146">but you can get really discreet hearing aids that just that don't get over the ear that go right in there right?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's got quite a discreet one <pause dur="short"/> actually he doesn't care at all what</u>
<u n="343" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">what he looks like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0146">well I I was going to say I bet he doesn't really mind?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">he doesn't <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't particularly like wearing it but it's not because it</u>
<u n="347" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">it doesn't look aesthetic</u>
<u n="349" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">when he was having em the radiotherapy for the skin cancer on his face the he had to have radiotherapy for like</u>
<u n="351" who="S0146">when was that?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">eh last month</u>
<u n="353" who="S0146">you didn't say anything</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">eh it's all preventative it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's nothing it's not  it's not  treatment for something that's still there cos they cut it out and the radiotherapy was just as a precaution to make sure that they got it all</u>
<u n="355" who="S0146">and zapped it up</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0146">when where was it though?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">right here on the cheek bone</u>
<u n="359" who="S0146">okay so away from the eye</u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">yeah just like but right under it <pause dur="short"/> but em so they made an incision and snipped out what they could</u>
<u n="361" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">what probably more than they thought that they needed to but just as a precaution they wanted to give him some treatments <pause dur="short"/> anyway when he was having the treatment he had to have it for consecutive days over a week's period <pause dur="short"/> and so the the surgeon drew on with em permanent ink like this big box <vocal desc="laugh"/> on his face <pause dur="short"/> he was like it's permanent do you mind keeping it on for the seven days so we don't have to keep drawing it every day and dad was like no no problem <pause dur="short"/> and my mum was like you will not go out of the house with a big black box drawn on your cheek bone <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> So my dad doesn't care he's like yeah whatever</u>
<u n="363" who="S0146">has it all being cleared up?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">em he'll have to wait and see but you know because it was</u>
<u n="365" who="S0146">you didn't mention anything <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">aw well he was quite chilled about it <pause dur="short"/> it's it was a I can't remember what the name is? Basal cell carcinoma which is not at all very aggressive</u>
<u n="367" who="S0146">what does that mean? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0018">it's a very it's one of the least aggressive forms of skin cancer</u>
<u n="369" who="S0146">okay so very benign</u>
<u n="370" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so and very treatable <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing nowadays cancer <pause dur="short"/> obviously it's still got that those feelings of attached to the word cancer hasn't it? But a lot of cancers are treatable nowadays I don't think it needs to be so scary</u>
<u n="371" who="S0146">we'll I've lost em my mum's sister <pause dur="short"/> one of my mum's sisters died from cancer <pause dur="short"/> the other sister has just gone through a second you know she had cancer fifteen years ago and it's just reoccurred and so actually you know it's been quite traumatic and cos it's spread to she's had a kidney removed and it's been quite she's a single parent it's quite traumatic</u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="373" who="S0146">em and eh my auntie has just em had cancer near her thyroid so you know</u>
<u n="374" who="S0018">Dodgy</u>
<u n="375" who="S0146">and that was a couple of weekends ago so I need to see her next weekend but that's <pause dur="short"/> so I don't take it lightly actually and my em family side we were very close to em em you know how it happens you know like my one of my dad's best friends his you know we and his wife my mum and dad were very good friends with them and it just so happened that when we were growing up we'd spend like every sort of Friday night we'd go round for dinner you know the kids would all play board games and stuff like that and and I was very attached to their mum actually <pause dur="short"/> I just you know even to the point that when I was little I used to say you know in Punjabi terms if I ever had a you know if I had anyone close to her as my mother-in-law I'd be the happiest person in the world <pause dur="short"/> she is like the perfect mum</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="377" who="S0146">you know and and she died from cancer and so it came back and em</u>
<u n="378" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="379" who="S0146">so I sort of <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="380" who="S0018">how how old was she?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0146">we're both scared of it <pause dur="short"/> she was about fifty-six</u>
<u n="382" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> very young</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018">and what kind of cancer did she have?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0146">breast cancer again</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> poor thing</u>
<u n="387" who="S0146">whereas my auntie who died my mum's sister you know hers like properly spread all over you know and that was  that was  a really long drawn-out affair because it started I can't remember where it started in kidneys or the stomach or something but it spread to the back and you know <pause dur="short"/> every time you checked up on it like every week it would be in a different you know</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="389" who="S0146">spreading all over and they flew her everywhere <pause dur="short"/> I mean they flew her to America to Germany to you know everywhere they had any miniscule hope of you know curing it <pause dur="short"/> and it's costly as well</u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">yeah it must have  it must have  cost a lot of energy concentration health money <pause dur="short"/> aw <pause dur="short"/> how long did that go on for?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0146">A couple of years cos they thought it had cleared up or at least stabilised and then it kept going</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="393" who="S0146">and the kid and the kids wouldn't accept no for an answer in particular her young son <pause dur="short"/> he wouldn't give up <pause dur="short"/> so it destroyed the whole family because you know they were very very you know they separated they haven't spoken to the eldest son since but the whole family just sort of fell apart</u>
<u n="394" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="395" who="S0146">the dad was so in love with his wife that he just he was quite reclusive he just like lost the will to have any sort of family relationship now</u>
<u n="396" who="S0018">what a shame <pause dur="short"/> are you still in touch with them?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0146">I am with the youngest with my cousin and his sister they both sort of live em like they live quite close to my parents' house but I don't see them often maybe every sort of couple of years <pause dur="short"/> em and they've rebuilt their lives you know they sort of have now <pause dur="short"/> but the eldest son we haven't spoken to since em you know my auntie's funeral because he's sort of flipped out said a lot of things and everyone disowned him <pause dur="short"/> and it was all sort of verging to that because you couldn't handle or you know they all couldn't handle it <pause dur="short"/> and those sort of pressure times just bring out the the monster in people don't they?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0146">and then em</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">that's the thing people either support each other and come closer together or</u>
<u n="401" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0018">cope in different ways that kind of  kind of  grate against each other</u>
<u n="403" who="S0146">and my  And my  uncle who was very much in love with auntie like very you know other other couples they you know they've been together for forty years so they get on with it</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0146">they were really really in love and he was just completely and utterly in love and I think they have like a house in Goa and he <pause dur="short"/> either he stays there or I don't know where he is <pause dur="short"/> I've not seen him since my auntie's funeral and that was a good ten twelve years ago which is really sad</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0146">he just doesn't want any he's just disengaged</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018">oh well if he's happier like that it's his decision I guess <pause dur="short"/> then again if he's just depressed maybe maybe it's not the best thing for him <pause dur="short"/> aw what a sad story I'm sorry about that <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so are you looking forward to open mic night tomorrow?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0146">I am actually <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to be performing a poem but I've got to find it first</u>
<u n="410" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It does help</u>
<u n="411" who="S0146">and I thought about that when I was cooking oh bloody hell I haven't got a poem</u>
<u n="412" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0018">do you know which one what you're gonna be reading? What? You've written a couple?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0146">I haven't written anything <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna find it off the internet <pause dur="short"/> oh god I'd better write something right?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">wait <pause dur="short"/> wait there wait there wait there <pause dur="short"/> you're reciting a poem someone else has written or you want to recite a poem that you've written?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0146">I wanted to recite a poem I've written</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">eh huh</u>
<u n="418" who="S0146">but I haven't had the chance to write it</u>
<u n="419" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0018">how long is the train journey from Birmingham to London tomorrow? What are you going to write it about?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0146">women you are great we should celebrate <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0018">oh there you go <pause dur="short"/> oh of course cos it's for the women's whatnot <pause dur="short"/> what's it called?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0146">international Women's Day</u>
<u n="424" who="S0018">that's it</u>
<u n="425" who="S0146">women we are great we should celebrate <pause dur="short"/> here's a poem for you and you and you and you</u>
<u n="426" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">but not you cos you're a man</u>
<u n="428" who="S0146">but not you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0018">but not if you can <pause dur="short"/> cos we can multitask</u>
<u n="430" who="S0146">oh talking about bloody man <pause dur="short"/> so I went in in Oxford circus there's like this shop I don't even know it's called  or something like that <pause dur="short"/> and it's like just basically is glass fronted all the way round but it looks like it's just like an open door thing <pause dur="short"/> they just sell like you know like vest tops for phones you know something like that <pause dur="short"/> so I went to pick up a couple and em and I went to pay and then the lady that was selling it she was we had this really long chat it's like oh and I want to finish work and yeah that would look great on you and yeah that would look really great and blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and all I could see was like this big hair you know big bouncy kind of thing quite a tall person whatever and then <pause dur="short"/> he she turned around and I actually flinched like it was like a man with like full front you know like a transvestite</u>
<u n="431" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0146">but because they were in like such a conversation they were ooh I think that would suit you something something I was like thinking it was actually a really big lady <pause dur="short"/> and then it was just a guy wearing lipstick and wearing a wig and women's clothes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then I thought that's really wrong to flinch because how must he feel being so disdainful?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0018">yeah oh no and that happened to me as well coming out of yoga class did I tell you?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0146">no</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018">the woman with her hand <pause dur="short"/> I didn't tell you? Well cos it's it they do it at the Buddhist Centre and you know they have they sell things like books and jewellery and incense and anyway <pause dur="short"/> I was in the changing room and there was this woman standing in front of me having a conversation with someone standing in front of her <pause dur="short"/> and she had her back to me but her arms crossed</u>
<u n="436" who="S0146">you're going to scare me I know</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">and all I could see was this hand that looked like a mannequin's hand em but I I was you know just when you walk out of yoga you're a bit</u>
<u n="438" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> spaghetti legs</u>
<u n="439" who="S0018" trans="overlap">your head's all over the place <pause dur="short"/> totally <pause dur="short"/> and you're a bit spaced <pause dur="short"/> and I was looking at her hand and then all of a sudden she like <pause dur="short"/> what I thought I saw was a hand she just started waving it in the air but eh with her other hand</u>
<u n="440" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0018">so I thought okay maybe it's a a like a plastic hand but they're used to display jewellery on or something <pause dur="short"/> anyway it gave me such a complete start cos I thought it was like actually her hand until she grabbed it off and started waving it over her head <pause dur="short"/> that I actually said oh my gosh what a shock I thought that was your hand <pause dur="short"/> and then she turned around and I saw her stump arm and she said yeah it is my hand <pause dur="short"/> and I was so embarrassed not aagh not because I put my foot in it but because I made her have to say so ah I just felt so <pause dur="short"/> but I felt so bad but I felt so shocked that I couldn't actually say anything I was just like</u>
<u n="442" who="S0146">I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/>  I know what you mean  I actually  I actually</u>
<u n="443" who="S0018">speechless</u>
<u n="444" who="S0146">speech <pause dur="short"/> and then that person turned around like how have you just had this ladies conversation and you're a man?</u>
<u n="445" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0146">why did she take it off?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0018">because it was chafing underneath and had I listened to the conversation I probably would have understood the context of the situation but I was</u>
<u n="448" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0018">completely spaced out</u>
<u n="450" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0018">just came out of the yoga class and you know you're just like because you do the last ten minutes lying on the floor</u>
<u n="452" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0018">with your eyes closed so I was half asleep</u>
<u n="454" who="S0146" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I love it <pause dur="short"/> that's the only thing I I find about <trunc>ha</trunc> about yoga right? So you know I really really looked forward to em you know that last what's it called? Em when you lie down <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sh</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> whatever</u>
<u n="455" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> there's a name of the posture</u>
<u n="456" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0018"><trunc>Sha</trunc> Shairn Sapora? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0146">basically a <trunc>lit</trunc> the whole thing about the class and in any class I look forward to the the relaxation bit at the end <pause dur="short"/> and em in this class in particular like the other like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s class like you know they put the lights off and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> and then like you know but with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I hope she gives you a good five minutes on the clock lie still and after three and a half or four minutes she says em okay you know in your own time roll to your side you know put your hands over your eyes you know protect your hands from the light open your eyes slowly as you she really really drags it out and I love that</u>
<u n="459" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0146">with his class he's such a bloody you know and then  and then  you know you lie down oh yeah great and actually the most relaxed I've felt is after hot yoga because actually you really appreciate it you know</u>
<u n="461" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0146">and I <trunc>y</trunc> you lie there and then they're like okay get up in your own time and go you think and then all these people start getting up cos we're queuing for like one shower</u>
<u n="463" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="464" who="S0146">it's like seventy people queuing for a shower</u>
<u n="465" who="S0018">everyone's like vrmmm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you actually and I think that's like the best time isn't it?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0146">surely to like come to one with your thoughts and actually feel that sense of accomplishment and absolute where you want to be</u>
<u n="469" who="S0018">can't they just hose everybody down while they're still in?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0146">I don't understand and then people start</u>
<u n="471" who="S0018">sarangasana is it sarangasana? I don't know</u>
<u n="472" who="S0146">I don't know I can't remember</u>
<u n="473" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it begins with an S</u>
<u n="474" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">I can't remember the name of it <pause dur="short"/> anyway yeah I was definitely cos today I can do all of the class</u>
<u n="477" who="S0146">why? Oh the in inverted</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">because I can't</u>
<u n="479" who="S0146">oh yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">yeah cos of my neck <pause dur="short"/> I did I got to relax at the end and I was just like I don't need to relax <pause dur="short"/> I haven't done enough <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0146">I'm fine <pause dur="short"/> I'm fine <pause dur="short"/> what what does anyone want to talk about?</u>
<u n="482" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0018">oh that was so annoying in my class yesterday <pause dur="short"/> there were some of us that he had everyone up in shoulders stand around but the ones who weren't ready for shoulder stand or who have got neck problems like me <pause dur="short"/> we were just kind of lying</u>
<u n="484" who="S0146">sitting on the side</u>
<u n="485" who="S0018">against the wall with our feet up and a bolster under our bum</u>
<u n="486" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0018">and so he was kinda talking shoulder stand through to the other ones</u>
<u n="488" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0018">while we were just like relaxing <pause dur="short"/> and there were these two bloody washer women going ni ni ni ni ni ni ni ni <pause dur="short"/> she had a real Brummie accent as well and I could hear them <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> down the pub and du lu lu lu down the pub and he said this and I said</u>
<u n="490" who="S0146">during the class?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0018">during the class while he was still trying to give instructions to everybody else <pause dur="short"/> and I saw his face a couple of times but he's such a Zen man</u>
<u n="492" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0018">I don't think he would have actually said</u>
<u n="494" who="S0146">but it is rude isn't it?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0018">I thought it was bloody weird</u>
<u n="496" who="S0146">lack of etiquette</u>
<u n="497" who="S0018">everybody else is there relaxing or they're there trying to hear his instructions and they were just blah blah blah blah blah chat chat chat chat chat <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to  I wanted to  say shhhh <vocal desc="laugh"/> You know  You know  like in the cinema <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't <pause dur="short"/> that would have been rude <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0146">I'm quite happy to do that in the cinema <pause dur="short"/> excuse me would you mind keeping your voice down? Excuse me if there's if you continue to talk I think we'll have to call the steward</u>
<u n="499" who="S0018">but that's better than the passive aggressive evil stares that most people do</u>
<u n="500" who="S0146">I do that first but when I get mad then I I'm quite happy to</u>
<u n="501" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So are you going to hot yoga this week?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0146">Friday <pause dur="short"/> candlelit class wanna come?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0018">oh well Friday is Ashtanga and I can't go on Sunday cos I'm having lunch with my mum so</u>
<u n="504" who="S0146">only thing I would say about the hot yoga class cos I I'm on my ten day pass and that's my last day</u>
<u n="505" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="506" who="S0146">the only I would say is if you are gonna come to get a ten day pass cos that's fifteen pounds and then you can even if you have three classes that's five pounds cos otherwise it's</u>
<u n="507" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0146">it's a bit more isn't it?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0018">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying that she's got some passes for the gym on <anon type="place"/> Street</u>
<u n="510" who="S0146">oh in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0018">that's the one yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0146">if that's the case then</u>
<u n="513" who="S0018">some two week passes I think <pause dur="short"/> so maybe while I'm around these parts <pause dur="short"/> I might em</u>
<u n="514" who="S0146">if if that's the case may I recommend the best yoga class in the world?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0018">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still teach here?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0146"><trunc>W</trunc> we can check online <pause dur="short"/> but if she let's we can check now <pause dur="short"/> but if she does that's the one <pause dur="short"/> ten thirty</u>
<u n="517" who="S0018">where's?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0146">ten o'clock to eleven thirty sorry</u>
<u n="519" who="S0018">oh the one the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to go to?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0146"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to all her classes</u>
<u n="521" who="S0018">really? Ah so she knows <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> too?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0146">it was actually you know Swedish <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="526" who="S0146">it was Swedish <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that actually introduced me to em you know the class</u>
<u n="527" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="528" who="S0146">that's the only one that I ever went to but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to her Wednesday class her Friday class</u>
<u n="529" who="S0018">eh I'd definitely go <pause dur="short"/> she's if she's as good teacher as she is a practitioner <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ga</trunc> sometimes I watch her getting from one em posture to another and it's just like wait there <pause dur="short"/> how did she A get into that posture and then how did she B get into that other posture in a blink of an eye <pause dur="short"/> it's like</u>
<u n="530" who="S0146">that's obviously cos she's doing it all the time isn't she?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lucky <pause dur="short"/> what a nice life <pause dur="short"/> if you can make make a living out of being a yoga teacher or something?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0146">I think she is the  I think she is the  best in not that I've been to any or many but I do you know it's the rapport that you get isn't it?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0146">that you get and I think she's absolutely the best that I've ever encountered</u>
<u n="535" who="S0018">but was just that cos you like the standard or the dynamic yoga?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0146">I loved it  I loved it  but I love her teaching method as well <pause dur="short"/> like the hatha yoga class I don't really love it as much you know by any stretch of the imagination as much as the dynamic yoga</u>
<u n="537" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0146">but I go because I you know I enjoy her class</u>
<u n="539" who="S0018">nice <pause dur="short"/> how many different types of classes does she do?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0146">so she does from what I remember of <pause dur="short"/> actually I can just check on her own website rather than all of this <pause dur="short"/> em she does from what I remember she does one in <anon type="place"/> which is another dynamic class <pause dur="short"/> em well no she's been cut quite a bit actually</u>
<u n="541" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> what a shame</u>
<u n="542" who="S0146"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's her</u>
<u n="543" who="S0018">are there other yoga classes that other people teach at <anon type="place"/> or is it just her?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0146">I've moved away from <anon type="place"/> and now I'm on just her yoga schedule twenty twelve</u>
<u n="545" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="546" who="S0146">so Monday six thirty to eight is <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you know where that is?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0018">the thing is I'm so unlikely to go somewhere that I have to catch</u>
<u n="548" who="S0146">any more buses</u>
<u n="549" who="S0018">more than two buses to</u>
<u n="550" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0018">I think at the moment I want to take advantage of being</u>
<u n="552" who="S0146">here</u>
<u n="553" who="S0018">close</u>
<u n="554" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0018">Cos I can walk to <anon type="place"/> you see</u>
<u n="556" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="557" who="S0018">and I can walk down to the Buddhist Centre and it's just nice to be able to</u>
<u n="558" who="S0146">okay <pause dur="short"/> so Monday she does this power yoga which is a seven week course started in February</u>
<u n="559" who="S0018">at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0146"><trunc>Sel</trunc> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="562" who="S0146">Tuesday she does eh twelve to one fifteen Hatha yoga at <anon type="place"/> health club em</u>
<u n="563" who="S0018">in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0146">that's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="566" who="S0146">Wednesday is the Hub in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="567" who="S0018">oh the one in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0146">Thursday is gentle Hatha yoga which is in <anon type="place"/> and Friday is ten thirty to eleven thirty power yoga</u>
<u n="569" who="S0018">where? Where is that?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0146">every that's the one I used to go to ten but it was</u>
<u n="571" who="S0018">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0018">okay so she only does the one class there?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0018">what a shame</u>
<u n="576" who="S0146">if you do decide to go I would go with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thingy and then if you do decide to go em</u>
<u n="577" who="S0018">oh no I was thinking of going to use the free pass <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so use <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s free pass and then if you do decide to go after that I'd struck a deal with <anon type="place"/> where I just paid them for like five pounds a class</u>
<u n="579" who="S0018">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you didn't have to pay for any signing up fee or anything?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0146">no <pause dur="short"/> I just you know I well I negotiated it all with them I said look you know I'm not a gym person I don't really like the gym I'm very interested in this class <pause dur="short"/> this is the only place <pause dur="short"/> this is where I live this is what suits me you know <pause dur="short"/> I want to come in and can I pay for five classes? And I paid like twenty-five quid or something like that and then and you know they've never ever checked it though cos they <trunc>ne</trunc> you know unlike this eh hot yoga which is a start date end date</u>
<u n="581" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0146">and it's all computerised they take it and check it all on the computer <pause dur="short"/> they never checked it <pause dur="short"/> so I it's a bit fraudulent but I went for a good eight months</u>
<u n="583" who="S0018">for twenty-five quid</u>
<u n="584" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0018">you cheeky woman</u>
<u n="586" who="S0146">I'm very cheeky well I've used the <anon type="place"/> gym for on and off for about two years like that</u>
<u n="587" who="S0018">in the hotel?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because I you remember I use to finish work at eight o'clock?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="590" who="S0146">and I know that I've used you know I <pause dur="short"/> I know that their staff leave at eight o'clock and I had to push quarter to eight but actually the gym was open until ten <pause dur="short"/> so they have a sign to say sorry there's no support staff so there's no treatments no nothing</u>
<u n="591" who="S0018">ah okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0146">so you know and I finished work at eight o'clock <pause dur="short"/> by the time I'm there it's eight fifteen straight to the changing rooms that's it <pause dur="short"/> have a good two hours gym steam room spa</u>
<u n="593" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No</u>
<u n="594" who="S0146">sauna</u>
<u n="595" who="S0018">you should have eh set up your own little business there</u>
<u n="596" who="S0146">get changed go to the relaxation room <pause dur="short"/> amazing read like Jimmy Choo catalogues and things <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> what the hell is this?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0018">did they have a swimming pool there?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0146">price on request</u>
<u n="599" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">yeah that means too expensive for you</u>
<u n="601" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0146">em they have a spa a steam room and a sauna <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="603" who="S0018">and what do they have at <anon type="place"/>? I can't imagine</u>
<u n="604" who="S0146">well they have a a little pool em <pause dur="short"/> but the what's good about <anon type="place"/> is em cos they've got this like massive gym which is em upstairs and it's very em testosterone filled em <pause dur="short"/> but the have a quite small pool but the best thing about <anon type="place"/> is the fact they have so many classes on</u>
<u n="605" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0146">and then like really good classes like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wife goes to <pause dur="short"/> she like lives at <anon type="place"/> basically <pause dur="short"/> she like goes to Saturday classes Wednesday classes this yoga class you know evening classes aqua aerobics <pause dur="short"/> she just hangs out there all the time</u>
<u n="607" who="S0018">no wonder she looks like she's thirty</u>
<u n="608" who="S0146">amazing <pause dur="short"/> better than us</u>
<u n="609" who="S0018">Cos she's fifty no?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's gonna be fifty-one this year</u>
<u n="611" who="S0018">blimey <pause dur="short"/> mm well that's testament to eh keeping fit</u>
<u n="612" who="S0146">and Mauritian skin</u>
<u n="613" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0018">oh she's from Mauritius?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0018">oh I didn't know that</u>
<u n="618" who="S0146">she's em her parents were from Mauritius and but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looks great too doesn't he?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know he he looks very young <pause dur="short"/> he was fifty as well no recently?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0146">exactly</u>
<u n="621" who="S0018">they both do <pause dur="short"/> where's he's Pakistani?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0146">he's from Pakistan yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0018">is that Pakistani skin or is that just cos he's been living the life of a reggae man?</u>
<u n="624" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0018">he's so chilled out though <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="626" who="S0146">he is</u>
<u n="627" who="S0018">that's probably why he looks so young too <pause dur="short"/> he just doesn't let anything stress him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0146">the two of them are very good together</u>
<u n="629" who="S0018">they are <pause dur="short"/> I haven't met their sons yet</u>
<u n="630" who="S0146">they don't meet them very often I it's been a good year since I met them <pause dur="short"/> em and one is a bit more like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> one's a bit more like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0146">like one's <pause dur="short"/> the younger one's quite artistic and <trunc>consi</trunc> you know very artistic and creative in that respect and the older one's a bit more like yeah you know I'm at Manchester gonna live a little now <pause dur="short"/> but still into like <trunc>pitt</trunc> you know they've got their parents' genes you know</u>
<u n="633" who="S0018">they're politically minded</u>
<u n="634" who="S0146" trans="overlap">politically inclined you know active conscious</u>
<u n="635" who="S0018">how old are they?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0146">so one's in just finishing his first year of university this year</u>
<u n="637" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="638" who="S0146">he'll finish in June <pause dur="short"/> yeah and the other one is younger <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how much maybe sixteen something like that</u>
<u n="639" who="S0018">and what was he studying at uni?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0146">I don't know actually <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I ever asked</u>
<u n="641" who="S0018">well I think I'll definitely try out <anon type="place"/> especially if they've got loads of classes</u>
<u n="642" who="S0146">use the  use the  pass and see which classes you like</u>
<u n="643" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0146">so if there's one you absolutely love you know like I'm saying</u>
<u n="645" who="S0018">yeah no but I</u>
<u n="646" who="S0146">ooh I hope you're not going to recording all my fraudulence</u>
<u n="647" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="648" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0018">you knew that I hadn't pressed stop <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't worry</u>
<u n="650" who="S0146">you don't know who</u>
<u n="651" who="S0018">no one's gonna take take it to <anon type="place"/> and say look this girl right</u>
<u n="652" who="S0146">God this is all <unclear/> identification</u>
<u n="653" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Don't worry</u>
<u n="654" who="S0146">so can you edit some of this?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0018">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> If I knew how to edit I would <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0146">oh god</u>
<u n="657" who="S0018">Don't worry</u>
<u n="658" who="S0146">that's the only bit they're gonna transcribe</u>
<u n="659" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">and send it straight to the police</u>
<u n="661" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0018">no I wasn't thinking of <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> you going to <anon type="place"/> using the pass to test out the facilities <pause dur="short"/> I was just thinking of using the pass to get in free and going to lots of keep fit classes <vocal desc="laugh"/> See the same mind set <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And I would have totally freeloaded <anon type="place"/>'s hotel gym if I had been you</u>
<u n="663" who="S0146">if you were there at eight o'clock exactly <pause dur="short"/> gyms are boring though</u>
<u n="664" who="S0018">they are</u>
<u n="665" who="S0146"><unclear/> really mundane</u>
<u n="666" who="S0018">well I just don't see the attraction of <pause dur="short"/> cos most of them are set up where the you know your tread mills and the spinning things opposite a mirror <pause dur="short"/> and so it kind of just encourages all that <pause dur="short"/> all that  All that  testosterone stuff that you were talking about oh look at me</u>
<u n="667" who="S0146">ooh ooh</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">aren't I ripped?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">ooh <pause dur="short"/> how many muscles have I got?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0018">I'm more muscley than you are</u>
<u n="673" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0018">and I just don't like like what I like about yoga classes is that everybody is in the same room yet they're all within themselves <pause dur="short"/> they're not comparing each other to they're not going to push each other</u>
<u n="675" who="S0146">actually I do find that sometimes yoga can be a little bit competitive?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like not competitive but like people look at the people you know like especially in like the hot yoga class <pause dur="short"/> like you could see like you could do the moves and such such a big room there's a good fifty people in there <pause dur="short"/> so you can see the people that can you know and at my first class I was just I just looked at them and I thought you know great <pause dur="short"/> but then I realised that they were ballet dancers</u>
<u n="678" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0146">so of course they're gonna be</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah they're gonna be <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> totally supple and flexible and well the good thing was going to Zumba class <pause dur="short"/> well that that wasn't good at all cos that was done in front of a mirror and I just</u>
<u n="681" who="S0146">which one did you go to the dance workshop one?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0018">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there as well</u>
<u n="683" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0018">em but it was awful cos you had to do it in front of a mirror which made me look <pause dur="short"/> I was looking at myself and I was thinking oh no you look so stupid but then I'd started looking at everybody else like yeah they look stupid too <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0146">the only person that</u>
<u n="686" who="S0018">even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gorgeous blond girl looks stupid doing Zumba <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0146">I was going to say the only person that probably doesn't look stupid is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she was a ballroom dancer <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="688" who="S0018">oh no no no she looked stupid too</u>
<u n="689" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0018">but hey <pause dur="short"/> you can't be a you can't be eh can't be beautiful when you're sweaty and exercising</u>
<u n="691" who="S0146" trans="overlap">I don't think that teacher like that teacher is <pause dur="short"/> like I think Zumba is brilliant I think the the whole thing's fun but that teacher like I think she enjoys the fact that everyone is out of sync all the time <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? She almost like sort of sadistic pleasure like</u>
<u n="692" who="S0018">she likes a little anarchy</u>
<u n="693" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0018">in her ballroom</u>
<u n="695" who="S0146">as soon as people like start to get it then she'd like changes it completely</u>
<u n="696" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="697" who="S0018">no I think you have to go a few times don't you to at least get the routines in your head <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't even get the steps you know steps that they repeat eight times</u>
<u n="698" who="S0146"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0018">I couldn't even get those</u>
<u n="700" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> left foot right foot</u>
<u n="701" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0018">and it's all done in such a</u>
<u n="703" who="S0146">Da di da di da di da di da <pause dur="short"/> and then you're like da da de</u>
<u n="704" who="S0018">where did my feet go? Help <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> anyway I think I was dangerous I nearly whacked this woman in the face cos I was like whacking my right hand out instead of my left and she was</u>
<u n="705" who="S0146">whoa whoa <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="706" who="S0018">Kickboxing</u>
<u n="707" who="S0146">yeah poof take that bitch</u>
<u n="708" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0018">I didn't mean it <pause dur="short"/> sorry I'm just trying to keep fit</u>
<u n="710" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0018">no it was a good exercise actually <pause dur="short"/> it was a good workout</u>
<u n="712" who="S0146">it's a proper workout actually it's</u>
<u n="713" who="S0018">even though I didn't do it properly it was still quite good but</u>
<u n="714" who="S0146">you still end up like sweating loads</u>
<u n="715" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="716" who="S0146">the only thing with em things like  and in particular my hot yoga is that I worry about weight loss like I say to you and em subsequently like I since my yoga classes I've been drinking like a litre and a half to two litres of water every day which is good considering I don't drink very much <pause dur="short"/> but yeah that's the only thing I'm worried about</u>
<u n="717" who="S0018">you then go and sweat it all off again</u>
<u n="718" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> well you have to go and see a nutritionist</u>
<u n="720" who="S0146">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0018">dietician</u>
<u n="722" who="S0146">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I might get the numbers off you actually</u>
<u n="723" who="S0018">yeah definitely give her a ring</u>
<u n="724" who="S0146">I'll try and arrange it for this weekend or something</u>
<u n="725" who="S0018">Good idea</u>
<u n="726" who="S0146">should we have a cigarette then?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> let's <pause dur="short"/> I think we've been far too healthy <pause dur="short"/> we've been talking about yoga for the past twenty minutes that's</u>
<u n="728" who="S0146">and breaking an entry</u>
<u n="729" who="S0018">too healthy</u>
</body>
</text>
