<text id="S97B">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house, Cambs</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>How we evaluate the work that we do in our jobs. </topics>
		<activity>Couple talking about job evaluation</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0261">erm yeah so I don't see erm relevance in ones like investigative journalism moral enterprise experiment statistics factory finance gain economics or a job interview erm because they fit erm it's like evaluations being trying it's being fitted into a particular setting or something erm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0262">a context?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0261">yeah a context I I would argue that something like evaluation as engineering that makes sense to me having been an engineer because erm er because engineering is is a a logical process where you go through something and you need to evaluate along way in some kind of experiment or observation so erm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0262">so would that would experiments not be part of your?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0261">well the the evaluation is an <trunc>ex</trunc> an experiment in its own right though you you you're actually you're looking at something and you're erm coming up with particular arguments for why something is like it is yeah? so you would have carried out the experiment before you evaluate something</u>
<u n="6" who="S0262">oh right in engineering?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">yeah let's just er let's simply say erm you've got erm a bike and you've got erm a hill and you've got the same person rides up erm two different hills yeah? and somebody's trying to work out whether I don't know they're more puffed at the top of one hill versus the other they they they they go the same distance it's just one's steeper than the other right? so that's the experiment and then after that you would evaluate that and you would ask a question like which hill did you find harder to ride your bike up? or which hill made you feel more exhausted? or which one was easier to ride your bike up?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0262">okay so you see that as two separate things?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0261">yeah yeah mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0262">wow okay</u>
<u n="11" who="S0261">it's just er and <trunc>s</trunc> a statement like evaluation is a factory well it's not a factory a <trunc>fa</trunc> a <trunc>factor</trunc> a factory carries out a certain purpose erm but well I suppose if you put it in a context of of how evaluation is carried out in the context of career erm a a career type erm exercise or something then you could say evaluation is a factory because the the the the answers that come out of it are kind of churned</u>
<u n="12" who="S0262">yeah that's exactly ideas are churned churned the word churning out</u>
<u n="13" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it's churned yeah so it comes down to how you interpret</u>
<u n="14" who="S0262" trans="overlap">they're churning out students with degrees that's what it all means it's connect to this one</u>
<u n="15" who="S0261" trans="overlap">churning yeah yeah okay</u>
<u n="16" who="S0262">production line</u>
<u n="17" who="S0261">so yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0262">it's very systematic</u>
<u n="19" who="S0261">and and and things like economics and</u>
<u n="20" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0261">and that kind of thing you could look at in the same way erm and I've got a lot of things in the middle erm but I think it's because they're more generic erm to the whole exercise and I think that's what I referred to as the chose that evaluation as a thread and everything</u>
<u n="22" who="S0262">okay so talk about the ones on the left then the three on the left</u>
<u n="23" who="S0261">okay so I've got evaluation as a court <trunc>tri</trunc> this is in the context of a previous er profession which was engineering so I've got evaluation as as a as a court trial er as geography and as engineering so em I associate all of thing together erm in the context of engineering so erm er to evaluate something <pause dur="short"/> well I might yeah in support of my previous argument I don't know that calling it saying it's a court trial helps <pause dur="long"/> well the context of why I put it there was erm that engineering are sometimes called into court to be expert witnesses et cetera and in order to do that they they have carried out some kind of evaluative work to to state their position or their opinion or something like that</u>
<u n="24" who="S0262">absolutely yeah I mean that's very that's a very clever association I think</u>
<u n="25" who="S0261">that's that's the way I see it</u>
<u n="26" who="S0262">what you've just said there</u>
<u n="27" who="S0261">oh okay erm geography is is erm again related to engineering but that's obvious er an obvious point</u>
<u n="28" who="S0262">but why for you in your words?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0261">erm well because engineering by nature is is is erm construction of something within a geography related to that kind of thing</u>
<u n="30" who="S0262">but what does geography mean to you?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0261">oh well in related er well the role I had was as a as a highways engineer so geography was intrinsic to that</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262">why? why? you're not saying why you're just telling eRm that it is but you're not saying why</u>
<u n="33" who="S0261">well er er <trunc>i</trunc> well it was intrinsic to it because when you build a highway you have to change the geography</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262">so how do you evaluate geography?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0261" trans="overlap">in order to build a construction</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262">how to <trunc>u</trunc>use geography to in your evaluation</u>
<u n="37" who="S0261">well erm it geography is one of the the kind of the foundations of of what might shape where you put a road to start with you know that that before er a design for a road is ever undertaken people look at the the natural geography and they er say will it go here or will it go there or what makes sense and what's easy and what's hard and all of that kind of thing</u>
<u n="38" who="S0262">and there's the human and the human geography as well</u>
<u n="39" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and they come up with and and human geography and all that kind of thing so <trunc>w</trunc> do we have to destroy houses to build a road?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262">move people</u>
<u n="41" who="S0261">move people go wreck communities change water <trunc>r</trunc> erm regimes rivers all that kind of stuff so erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0262">okay and then</u>
<u n="43" who="S0261">that's specifically related to my particular role in engineering which was highways</u>
<u n="44" who="S0262">yeah well I mean even if it wasn't it might be <unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0261">well you could say the same as rail or</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">oil gas</u>
<u n="47" who="S0261"><trunc>physic</trunc> yeah yeah a whole a whole bunch of those type of</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">so is that?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">civil engineering typically</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262">civil engineering yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0262">and what and then you have evaluation as engineering so what is engineering for evaluation?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="long"/> well that's in terms of erm <trunc>pa</trunc> evaluation as part of a process and engineering is that process so you you are trying to engineer something you are an evaluation sits within that box so that's why that rings true to me if I disassociate it I've disassociated it with the from the profession and I've looked at it in terms of its alternative meaning which is to engineer something to make something up</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262">okay but somebody said today I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was that he he saw evaluation as engineering as somebody has already decided and made a decision and he saw engineering as a process by which to justify the decision has already been made so the idea is that something has been engineered to suit a certain purpose</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261">oh well that's looking at it from a a different point of view</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262">but he saw it as erm I think you know cos he worked in the aviation industry is that justifying how much money to spend on engineering planes or whatever the decision is already taken and the engineer is working backwards</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">yeah so he's talking about a kind of reverse engineering scenario which happens sometimes that budgets are limited and hence the solution that's provided has to be engineered within that scope</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262">and is that not the case in engineering a lot of the time?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0261">yeah but I wouldn't look at it at that that point of view comes across as a negative point of view to me</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">erm rather than</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">and engineering in a positive way for you is process?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261">yes because er it is a process erm if you go back to the point about budgets et cetera erm my interpretation of of what you've put across is that erm there may not have been enough money to do something that one wanted to do and sometimes it's like that so a clever way of looking at engineering is saying well I've got these constraints what's the best I can get of out of what those constraints are?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261">and that might involve research and discovery and erm experiment and trying to erm evolve something that provides the best solution in that engineering sense</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">its creation <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">okay great you've already just mentioned three metaphors <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0261">okay <trunc>tha</trunc>that's fine did you write down creation? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">okay so the next ones then you've come up with a thread but then you've got all these overlaps</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261">research reflection risk argument learning architecture technology management critique and a map and I think they all kind of fit together pretty much there might be a couple of outliers but if you put them together in a in a in a network you'd say they all they all linked <trunc>t</trunc>together</u>
<u n="74" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay try putting them together into pairs</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261">into pairs?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0262">associative pairs or or you know whichever way but try and see if there is er paired connections for you maybe not with that one but</u>
<u n="77" who="S0261">no mm <pause dur="long"/> do they have to be pairs?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262">no okay just erm I I asked you to do it as pairs but just associative like relationships</u>
<u n="79" who="S0261">mm groups mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262">yeah <pause dur="long"/> alright so let me just take a photograph of that so what what did you running through your mind when you're thinking of those ones?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">well I well I you know I couldn't say that it's it's complete but erm it's just a thirty second view point of something erm so I think it kind of puts together some of the reasons behind why I picked some things</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0261">erm so say if we look at evaluation as research architecture and a map erm you could argue hat</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">do they run like on a</u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">yeah they run horizontally</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0261">so erm you could say that erm from my point of view architecture and map are pretty much the same thing</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262">why?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">because I see architecture as a as a structure of something the that that is the network of how things are joined together erm and a map is kind of er similar that it it it provides guidance it shows the way erm so you can say if something's got a structure you understand how it might work</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262">sort of like a blueprint or something?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">yeah you could say erm a a blueprint or a or a foundation a erm a a skeleton that kind of thing erm and so when I say evaluation is research erm that is as it suggests that erm it is a part of research it is there's a research process and evaluation is just a part of that erm that is linked to an architecture which is some kind of structure and context of that research and the map shows the way so you know once you've got a structure how to work through that and out of that you might get erm this these bits that are at the bottom which is that erm you've got reflection critique and learning so you look at something you've carried out an experiment I know there was one in there that was experiment and I didn't pick it out but erm you reflect on what comes out of it erm there's a critique of of some elements erm and you and of course evaluation and out of that erm er the result is learning</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261">erm so what's left there is there is one which is management which is kind of left on its own erm but I see it as erm er the pure form of management in the context of its its erm working through process erm and and er leading leading define <pause dur="long"/> erm <trunc>take</trunc>taking control of how it all fits together I suppose it's an overarching thing cos I'm thinking in terms of experiment and erm <pause dur="short"/> that kind of thing</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262">you are being very you're you see this is this is this is interesting it's like that guy who did the er how how to be more creative yeah?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">erm you have come up with I mean I know the other guys are at work and constraints of being at work but you know you've come up with quite a awesome thing</u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">I have I haven't looked at that one yet</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">okay but I'm just saying but look how many metaphors you've come up with</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261">mm thanks discovery evolution blueprint constraint thread creation skeleton control mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">so you want to talk about the last one?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">yeah last one so that's got evaluation as a risk as technology and as an argument and they're all on a er a horizontal line erm so technology me quite often relates to erm things that have been created technology by by I suppose by definition is something that has come out of a process that has been quite risky</u>
<u n="102" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261">yeah? so to so to so to push boundaries and come up with new thing and that is what technology relates to erm that er that part of that process is going through a huge amount of risk erm experiment discovery evaluation erm learning so on and so on erm and I've got beside that evaluation as a argument and erm not too sure why I've associated them together but kind of just felt from the gut to be something that should fit together</u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">it could be because you might have thought of it as a defence</u>
<u n="105" who="S0261" trans="overlap">erm erm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0262">you defend you know when you've taken a risk you've processed it you've created it</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes it was it was how it was it was how argument argument was associated with risk</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yes yes</u>
<u n="109" who="S0261">so it might better go erm I didn't know which way round to put these but it might better go risk argument technology that you take a risk at something you've defined an approach you take a certain direction erm there'll be people erm and results that come out of taking such a <trunc>dir</trunc> a direction in relation to technology that can be blind alleyways or they might be erm er challenging points of view from other people et cetera and so you have to you have to erm defend your argument you have to define why you've you are doing this thing and erm present to people erm good a good basis for why they should believe in it to influence people convince them erm and then beyond that erm I'm putting this in the context of technology so erm technology is risky and you have to go through quite a few difficult paths to produce anything that's related to technology</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262">mm absolutely</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261">that's to create tools that are technology I suppose once you've created the tool that makes things easier quite often</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
