<text id="S99Z">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:40:20</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0223 S0224 S0225</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>France</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Money laundering, banking, kids, careers, fines, criminal activity</topics>
		<activity>Chatting with a family friend about work</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Inquiring, Advising, Requesting, Anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0223">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Business owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0224">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>no info</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0225">
				<exactage>49</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Carcassone</hab_city>
				<hab_country>France</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0223"><unclear/> er part of er computing which I've been in for many many years and if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> could get involved in it you know at this time I think he could have quite a good career so</u>
<u n="2" who="S0202">yeah cos that's one of the like that's the sort of trade that you need to learn isn't it really? so</u>
<u n="3" who="S0223">yeah at the moment in the in the city the biggest things are about anti money laundering</u>
<u n="4" who="S0224">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0223">erm know your client where's the money coming from?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0202">yeah I know <trunc>fin</trunc> I know that yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0223" trans="overlap">preventing the financing of terrorism it's huge and <anon type="place"/> the French bank got fined by the Americans billions of dollars recently for breaching erm sanction rules and you know the regulators are watching what the banks are up to the banks aren't actually that bothered about where the money's coming from as long as they're making profits so more and more the pressure's being put on them to question where the money's coming from</u>
<u n="8" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0223">and there's huge careers in that whole area of compliance and</u>
<u n="10" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0223">regulatory</u>
<u n="12" who="S0225">are you still eating prawns cat?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0223">you know I mean it's it can be probably a boring but also quite an exciting place to be at the moment</u>
<u n="14" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0223">and I I recognised this two or three years ago and I actually joked about you could get your son a compliance manual and he's got a career for life</u>
<u n="16" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0223">you know there's a lot a lot in that it's the biggest growing department in every financial company is their compliance team</u>
<u n="18" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0223">so <pause dur="short"/> and they're all trying to keep up with erm those people that are trying to break the rules</u>
<u n="20" who="S0224" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0202">the</u>
<u n="22" who="S0224" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">cos the fines are enormous</u>
<u n="23" who="S0223">oh the fines are</u>
<u n="24" who="S0224" whoConfidence="low">completely</u>
<u n="25" who="S0223" trans="overlap">astronomical</u>
<u n="26" who="S0224" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">outweigh the costs yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0202">yeah but that's the point it's just trying to</u>
<u n="28" who="S0223" trans="overlap">there's</u>
<u n="29" who="S0202">deter it happening again</u>
<u n="30" who="S0224" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0223">there's like a trillion they've worked out there's trillions of dollars of fraud <pause dur="short"/> fraudulent money going through the banking system every year</u>
<u n="32" who="S0224" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0223" trans="overlap">it's absolutely huge</u>
<u n="34" who="S0202" trans="overlap">where does this <pause dur="short"/> so these fines where does that money go? I've always wondered that like if a bank is fined where does that money go? like does it go into the government pocket?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0223" trans="overlap">it goes to the regulator and the regulator uses it to fund their more investigators for more banks or to change the rules or to tighten up the rules or to prosecute so it's a fine</u>
<u n="36" who="S0224" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0223">that kind of goes back to the central governing body</u>
<u n="38" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0223">so that they can then make themselves better and they are and they're buying software like my company's got so they're gonna be more advanced than the actual financial companies themselves to be able to go and do those sort of analysis projects and things like that so you know it's it's a bit of a race against time at the moment but what we've found is with anti money laundering is that erm those that are involved they'll set up a shell company</u>
<u n="40" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0223" trans="overlap">erm Geneva or the Cayman Islands or <unclear>you know</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> portugal anywhere but they won't do anything they won't trade in it for years three years four years maybe and then they start putting transactions through and they're laundering money through it and there's lots of steps in the transaction</u>
<u n="42" who="S0202" trans="overlap">cleaning the money</u>
<u n="43" who="S0223">and what we're trying to do is we're trying to identify patterns in those steps so if a trade starts in Switzerland goes to a Swiss bank and ends in Switzerland it's probably safe <pause dur="short"/> but if the trade starts in Switzerland goes to the Cayman Islands and then goes back to <pause dur="short"/> I dunno Colombia then that should start ringing bells</u>
<u n="44" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0223">but not everybody looks at the whole the whole chain each bank looks at them and the next party who could be</u>
<u n="46" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0223" trans="overlap">another friendly bank that next <trunc>fr</trunc> bank has a friendly bank in another country they know each other they maybe get together once a year they're er they on first name terms that bank's on first name terms with another country and in <pause dur="short"/> as as individuals everything looks okay you know</u>
<u n="48" who="S0202">but if you look at it as a whole</u>
<u n="49" who="S0223">but if you look at the whole transaction you think mm that's why? why are they doing the transaction like that? so <pause dur="short"/> banks in all countries France Spain Portugal have relationships with another institution in another country and on the surface it looks fine and it probably is <pause dur="short"/> but you if you put all the pieces of the jigsaw together you start identifying what could be attempts to to move money around illegally</u>
<u n="50" who="S0202">so how did how did you get into that then? like that's a really specific <trunc>s</trunc> field to be in like</u>
<u n="51" who="S0223">because I've been in financial services for all my career and <pause dur="short"/> I was looking for a new job and erm one of my contacts said look I work for a company why don't you come and meet our head of sales?</u>
<u n="52" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">where's the sprayer? I am being absolutely plagued with those little bastards now</u>
<u n="53" who="S0223" trans="overlap">ah it's oh erm just by the drinks cabinet inside erm <pause dur="short"/> I got in <trunc>c</trunc> I've got have you ever heard of Linkedin?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0223">well I'm on Linkedin and er I've I've always used it and I've been a member of Linkedin for quite a few years</u>
<u n="56" who="S0202">it's how you network ain't it? and make</u>
<u n="57" who="S0223" trans="overlap">yeah it's really good for in in my industry and and probably in others but I <trunc>w</trunc>we use it a lot <pause dur="short"/> and a guy that I've met in the past said my company's <trunc>recr</trunc> looks as though we want another sales person and when I joined them I didn't really know what they were selling erm and it turns out that the most interesting project that we've got or product is this forensic analysis tool and it was developed in South Africa for er fraud prevention</u>
<u n="58" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0223">and now we've got ex coppers that work for us and we've got these data architect types and you know techie really techie people but also that understand erm investigations so I've</u>
<u n="60" who="S0202" trans="overlap">a real mix of people</u>
<u n="61" who="S0223" trans="overlap">I find it very exciting actually cos it's kind of it's not just financial services it can go and be used to analyse industrial espionage it can be used to analyse construction projects where people might be erm claiming to work on two projects the same time and putting timesheets in it picks up things like that it picks up where bids are being won <pause dur="short"/> erm constantly over maybe other <unclear>competitive</unclear> firms it might connect up the fact that somebody over here is married to somebody down there things that you don't see on a day to day basis</u>
<u n="62" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0223" trans="overlap">if you ingest all the data and start kinda shuffling everything around and throw it back it it starts making connections which is really exciting</u>
<u n="64" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0223">so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0202">cos there's a lot of that I bet that goes on in the <trunc>in</trunc> in er different industries like bribing and so and so's</u>
<u n="67" who="S0223" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0202" trans="overlap">married to so and so so we're gonna get this contract and</u>
<u n="69" who="S0223" trans="overlap">I mean one of the things was erm a company where the guy's a manager and he's signing off stationery I mean companies buy stationery all the time</u>
<event desc="begin overlap"/>
<u n="70" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you want to play with it</unclear>?</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no it's <unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<event desc="end overlap"/>
<u n="72" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0223">so he's always buying paper and pens and things like that but as it turns out he was getting his firm to pay for fictitious invoices and he was the owner of the stationery company <pause dur="short"/> so you wouldn't know that unless you said give me details of all the company directors on Companies House and compare them to my staff</u>
<u n="74" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0223">have a look at the emails of my staff so <pause dur="short"/> it's quite interesting</u>
<u n="76" who="S0202" trans="overlap">right yeah it is really interesting</u>
<u n="77" who="S0223" trans="overlap">we find a lot of unknowns and every time there's fraud or some insider dealing or some transactions that have erm that look a bit dodgy <pause dur="short"/> typically when it comes to they've found somebody that's done something wrong the evidence is already there it's always been there it's just kinda hidden in emails sort of text messages</u>
<u n="78" who="S0202">different places where not necessarily</u>
<u n="79" who="S0223" trans="overlap"><trunc>pla</trunc> not</u>
<u n="80" who="S0202">look at all at once</u>
<u n="81" who="S0223">absolutely</u>
<u n="82" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0223">you know and what we're trying to do is connect all the dots and I think it's a great so</u>
<u n="84" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah it sounds really interesting</u>
<u n="85" who="S0223">the big <trunc>pro</trunc> one of the big projects I'm working on is for the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0223" trans="overlap">they're looking for a new investigative system</u>
<u n="88" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="89" who="S0223">to help them with fraud across all aspects of fraud you know because the <anon type="place"/> being that it's got most of the financial</u>
<u n="90" who="S0202">sector in there</u>
<u n="91" who="S0223" trans="overlap">fraud they want to get it right and then they want to start shifting it out to other parts of the country so we're bidding we we haven't won a bid but we're in a process of bidding erm and I just think that's fantastic cos my mum used to work for <anon type="place"/> police she was a civilian in the office</u>
<u n="92" who="S0202" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="93" who="S0223">putting all the cases together for court <pause dur="short"/> bringing everything</u>
<u n="94" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I must have</u>
<u n="96" who="S0223">so I kind of feel a little bit of a connection there</u>
<u n="97" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">chillies on my fingers cos I've touched my face and my face is stinging even though</u>
<u n="98" who="S0223" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">since I've touched the chillies I've washed my hands twice</u>
<u n="100" who="S0223"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm now burning round my mouth</u>
<u n="102" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0223">well have some more drink</u>
<u n="104" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="105" who="S0223">don't rub your eyes</u>
<u n="106" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh yes</u>
<u n="107" who="S0224" whoConfidence="low">don't pick your nose</u>
<u n="108" who="S0223" trans="overlap">so yeah it's good you know there's a lot <trunc>go</trunc> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was sort of toing and froing about what does he want to do now that he's not done that well with his ASs and he's going maybe I should get an apprenticeship maybe I should do sixth form I'm thinking no in <anon type="place"/> it's rural it's low wage forget it so eventually with a bit of persuasion he's decided</u>
<u n="109" who="S0202">on his own yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0223" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0223">and he's gonna come and live in <anon type="place"/> with me</u>
<u n="113" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I need to go for a wee sorry</u>
<u n="115" who="S0202">see that'll be good cos you can keep an eye on him as well</u>
<u n="116" who="S0223">yeah I mean I'm not gonna</u>
<u n="117" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="118" who="S0223">sort of pussyfoot around him but</u>
<u n="119" who="S0202">no but like you know what he's you know what I mean</u>
<u n="120" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0223" trans="overlap">I think the if he</u>
<u n="122" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> I think</u>
<u n="123" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh okay</u>
<u n="124" who="S0223">but if he lives with me for six months then decides he wants to go and move in with some <trunc>f</trunc> some mates from work that he's met perfect you know job done</u>
<u n="125" who="S0202">mm mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0223">he's launched he's got a job he's on the career ladder and he's living in <anon type="place"/> what better position could we be in?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0223">you know so</u>
<u n="129" who="S0202">well I'm working on something at the moment which is similar in a way to what you do but not it is investigative but it's not fraud <pause dur="short"/> so I work for erm something called the British National Corpus and <trunc>ba</trunc>basically what they do is <pause dur="short"/> part of my degree is studying languages and <trunc>dia</trunc> different dialects in England</u>
<u n="130" who="S0223">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0202">so like you can tell I'm from the north and I can tell you're from the south it's just a way of speaking and the way</u>
<u n="132" who="S0223" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0202">that you use your tongue and pronounce things differently to how I do</u>
<u n="134" who="S0223">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0202">so like I'll erm drop Ts I'll drop words out of a sentence and stuff like that whereas people who are generally from the south don't normally do that they normally speak a proper sentence so to speak</u>
<event desc="begin overlap"/>
<u n="136" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you want another beer?</u>
<u n="137" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh no I'm fine thanks I've still got some left</u>
<event desc="end overlap"/>
<u n="138" who="S0202">erm and erm I I erm work for the British National Corpus collecting data erm and recording stuff with people talking so me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll have conversations and we'll record them and send them off to erm the person who's head of this project</u>
<u n="139" who="S0223">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and what they do is they put this erm recording through a piece of software that picks out words and picks out erm <pause dur="short"/> how dialects are different in different parts of the country and how things are pronounced</u>
<u n="141" who="S0223">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0202">so this British National Corpus is normally used for erm like language studies speech therapists erm all that like how language is used and what it's used for in what way</u>
<u n="143" who="S0223" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0202">stuff like that so that's sort of a similar thing and it's</u>
<u n="145" who="S0223" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0202">just collecting a lot of data and then finding out</u>
<u n="147" who="S0223">it's what you do with the data after you've collected it really is the key thing and you know people have now are catching on to the fact that there's so much information out there if you can harness it you know you can do so much and learn so much that you couldn't see before you know cos most people work in isolation companies even if you work for a big bank and I've worked for a big bank my last firm was <anon type="place"/> which is a big American bank they've got like twenty-eight thousand staff around the world <unclear>paperwork</unclear> in silos the banking industry's renowned for it you do your job in your department and you don't really know what's going on over there and over the years multiple computer systems have grown up because maybe they've acquired a company or they've developed something quickly and they end up with lots of databases of information no one ever gets the big picture and if they do it takes them months of management time</u>
<u n="148" who="S0202">yeah and a lot of organisation</u>
<u n="149" who="S0223" trans="overlap">a lot of staff pulling data out and sticking it into spreadsheets and things like that so nobody really has a view what's going on across the company and they might have clients in here and clients over there and they're not using</u>
<u n="150" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0223" trans="overlap">that information</u>
<u n="152" who="S0202">not using it <unclear/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0223" trans="overlap">so there's so much more we can do and I think every sort of five or six years something new comes up in technology which</u>
<u n="154" who="S0202" trans="overlap">that allows it</u>
<u n="155" who="S0223" trans="overlap">kind of blows everybody away and you know big data is the big thing at the moment it's a the buzzword</u>
<u n="156" who="S0202">it is er</u>
<u n="157" who="S0223" trans="overlap">it's quite interesting actually now that I've updated my er Linkedin profile where I talk about big data and smart data I get a lot more people enquiring on my <pause dur="short"/> my my Linkedin profile that</u>
<u n="158" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0223" trans="overlap">are not related to what I'm doing in my day to day job so I think that</u>
<u n="160" who="S0202" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0223">if you're out there in the industry and you're looking for people that have got experience in this latest technology you start searching around to see who has so I think it's <trunc>qu</trunc> it's quite good it's quite profile building actually at the minute</u>
<u n="162" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0223">what we're doing keep</u>
<u n="164" who="S0202" trans="overlap">see the</u>
<u n="165" who="S0223" trans="overlap">updating it</u>
<u n="166" who="S0202">yeah that's what I like about my degree <pause dur="short"/> because a lot of people think that er an English degree is like a Mickey Mouse degree they don't really understand <trunc>w</trunc> erm what's involved in it so they just assume oh it's English you're an English speaking person it's easy because they know nothing about it <pause dur="short"/> but a lot of what I do is erm or what I will be doing in my second year is collecting data and researching it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0223">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0202">analysing it and then breaking it down into an essay or into a research project stuff like that and I think</u>
<u n="169" who="S0223" trans="overlap">well a lot comes out of the universities a lot of what industry picks up comes out from research that the universities do and I think they do a a good job</u>
<u n="170" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0223">and sometimes some of the competitive products that are out there in the market have come from universities you know</u>
<u n="172" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0223">I mean <pause dur="short"/> what is it? MUMPS programming language <trunc>b</trunc> which was <trunc>b</trunc> used probably eighty er in the eighties and the nineties and there are still some systems based on MUMPS was Massachusetts University something Programming</u>
<u n="174" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0223">you know it was actually a university developed programme</u>
<u n="176" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0223">which is still used across the world you know as one of the underlying programming languages with things have moved on but a lot of it came out of the technology and the study that people do so</u>
<u n="178" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0223">it can really go places</u>
<u n="180" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I think the universities are fantastic</u>
<u n="181" who="S0223">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0202">like the the office they offer like erm <pause dur="short"/> especially like if you decide to go into a career in <trunc>aca</trunc>academia like that is basically your job you teach and you research like a lot of my tutors go off on erm sabbatical research sabbaticals they basically spend a year being paid to research and do things like that</u>
<u n="183" who="S0223">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0202">and it's it's really interesting stuff <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0223">are we gonna eat inside tonight do you think?</u>
<u n="186" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="187" who="S0223"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hello?</u>
<u n="188" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">who said that?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0223">is that you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's getting <trunc>dar</trunc> it's getting dark quite early now isn't it? bit of a shame really</u>
<u n="190" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">the trouble is yeah well also if we start late <unclear/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0202" trans="overlap">just go and get a jumper <pause dur="long"/> hello <unclear/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0223">oh goodness we put the cover on the pool when we came up earlier</u>
<u n="193" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm <unclear>yes thanks for doing</unclear> that</u>
<u n="194" who="S0223">to keep the heat in there <pause dur="short"/> so that's all sorted</u>
<u n="195" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">cool</u>
<u n="196" who="S0223">nothing to do down there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0202">oh it smells fantastic <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="198" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yep <unclear/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0223"><vocal desc="yawn"/> oh excuse me <pause dur="short"/> how's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> getting back from her babysitting?</u>
<u n="200" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I would assume <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will pick her up <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0223">I think I'll go and lay the table in the other room actually I'm getting a bit cold</u>
<u n="202" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah I think we'll eat inside <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0223">if we're gonna eat in there yeah? okey dokes take my various liquids</u>
<u n="204" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">have to see might be some stars out tonight</u>
<u n="205" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that would be good <unclear>well</unclear> there's not a bloody cloud in the sky</u>
<u n="206" who="S0223" trans="overlap">shall I erm lay out for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well is she back in time to eat?</u>
<u n="207" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I don't think she'll be back in time I think she'll be late</u>
<u n="208" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">so</u>
<u n="209" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">so she'll eat</u>
<u n="210" who="S0223">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is here isn't he? and erm</u>
<u n="211" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll eat with us I think I don't think we'll wait <pause dur="short"/> probably eat with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well knowing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0223">I'm gonna I'm gonna lay out the table in here cos we're gonna eat in here</u>
<u n="213" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes I think so is that alright?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0223">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="215" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0202">saw loads of <trunc>s</trunc> I'd never heard of erm I've heard er you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> speaking about <anon type="place"/> before but I'd never heard of it like in England or anything I saw loads in America they're absolutely everywhere aren't they?</u>
<u n="217" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0202">like I thought she er when she were talking about it she just meant like a bank in the city</u>
<u n="219" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0202" trans="overlap">if that makes sense like I didn't realise that that were it <trunc>ac</trunc> its actual name but it's huge like they're everywhere in America they're absolutely everywhere</u>
<u n="221" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="222" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh <unclear/> the box <pause dur="short"/> what I'll do is I'll actually marinade these prawns in the sauce in the next ten minutes</u>
<u n="223" who="S0224">I've got the boar marinading for tomorrow</u>
<u n="224" who="S0225">oh excellent</u>
<u n="225" who="S0202" trans="overlap">oh are we having boar?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0224">so I need to get up early and and do that</u>
<u n="227" who="S0202">I'm not here <pause dur="short"/> we're not here tomorrow night</u>
<u n="228" who="S0225" trans="overlap">oh no you're not here no</u>
<u n="229" who="S0202">can you save us some please?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0224">might be a little bit saved</u>
<u n="231" who="S0202">thank you</u>
<u n="232" who="S0224">little snack size pieces</u>
<u n="233" who="S0202">I love your boar stew it's amazing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0225">did you shoot it?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0224">erm I don't know</u>
<u n="236" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0224">is the answer</u>
<u n="238" who="S0225">okay</u>
<u n="239" who="S0224">I shot one whether this is part of that one I don't know</u>
<u n="240" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0225">so it's a bit like a World War Two fighter pilot <pause dur="short"/> everyone's claiming to have the kill?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0224">no no no no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0225">no?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0224">what it is is that what what we do when we go up there it's very democratic actually it's very good is we decide based on who's found traces of boar in woods where we all we each go out and check our own little area</u>
<u n="245" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0224">and that helps us decide where we should go shooting one in the morning and one in the afternoon usually erm <vocal desc="cough"/> and then depending on how many people there are we mark out posts around the area we're gonna be hunting so basically what happens is beaters go in with dogs flush the animals out and they come screaming out of somewhere and you shoot them as they go past sort of thing</u>
<u n="247" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0224">but what it means is that there's no favouritism as to who gets which slot and you know this is my post I'm here all the time sort of thing so you actually get to see a lot of the countryside and a lot of different things rather than just standing in one place every time you go out</u>
<u n="249" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0224">to a particular place <pause dur="short"/> and then if anything gets shot it gets butchered when we come back at lunchtime and then just left and when we come back in the evening anything else gets butchered and then it all gets shared out again er depending on how many people are there it gets put into so many bags so if there's twenty people</u>
<u n="251" who="S0223" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what did you do with the forks?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0224">with the what? I didn't do anything with them they're in the sink to be washed</u>
<u n="253" who="S0223">you know you put the forks somewhere earlier?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0224">I put them in the sink to be washed</u>
<u n="255" who="S0223">in the sink?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0224">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0223">okay</u>
<u n="258" who="S0224">but they I think they've been did you wash them?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0223">he said they're in the sink</u>
<u n="260" who="S0224"><unclear>cos</unclear></u>
<u n="261" who="S0202" trans="overlap">the sink? oh they're in the erm dishwasher</u>
<u n="262" who="S0224">oh right they went into the dishwasher I left them out cos we needed them for tea</u>
<u n="263" who="S0202">oh right sorry</u>
<u n="264" who="S0224"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0202">it's not on</u>
<u n="266" who="S0224">erm so if there's twenty people then what gets killed gets put into twenty bags</u>
<u n="267" who="S0225" trans="overlap">divided yeah okay</u>
<u n="268" who="S0224">and again lots are done so that whoever's butchered it doesn't get to say you know I'll keep the fillet steak this side sort of thing</u>
<u n="269" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0224">so you end up with a bag that could be one that you killed it could be one that someone else killed you know and depending on how many have been killed that day you might not get anything some days</u>
<u n="271" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0224">erm so genuinely you don't know I mean people know who killed it when it gets shot cos obviously the person who's pointing their gun at it when it falls over it's fairly obviously who shot it some cases it isn't when it's running across a field and everybody's shooting it and you don't know who actually shot it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0225">oh dear it doesn't stand a chance there</u>
<u n="274" who="S0224">well no they they do get away <pause dur="long"/> especially the bigger older ones I mean they <pause dur="short"/> they don't run down the paths if they know they're being hunted they don't follow the tracks cos they're</u>
<u n="275" who="S0223" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we can't find the forks <pause dur="long"/> I definitely saw you put them aside earlier</u>
<u n="276" who="S0224">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she put them in the dishwasher <pause dur="long"/> I don't need to go in <unclear>because all I'll do is</unclear> look in the dishwasher and</u>
<u n="277" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0224">and find them <pause dur="long"/> yeah she's found them</u>
<u n="279" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0224">and then when you get the meat you keep it in the freezer for three months <pause dur="short"/> because there is a parasite that boar can have <pause dur="short"/> that are not good for you</u>
<u n="281" who="S0225">oh right so it's it it takes three months to be absolutely sure this thing is er</u>
<u n="282" who="S0224" trans="overlap">yes is dead</u>
<u n="283" who="S0225">yeah okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0224">so the stuff we're eating is basically something that was shot <pause dur="short"/> during last season and has been in the freezer since you know October November December whatever</u>
<u n="285" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0224">the time we ran the things <pause dur="short"/> so what I do when I bring my meat home is I leave it in the fridge for a day <pause dur="short"/> and then I carve it off into lumps to make stews basically</u>
<u n="287" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0224">and one I'll start doing now is I will start carving more interesting pieces cos you don't just have to do stews cos although it's very good for slow cooked it can be a tough meat if you get a younger one a smaller one you know fifty kilos something like that it's it can be quite nice meat you could actually barbecue it or</u>
<u n="289" who="S0225" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0224" trans="overlap">do other things with it as well</u>
<u n="291" who="S0225">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0224">the trouble is that the stew is just so nice it's just like you almost don't wanna do anything else <pause dur="long"/> so if you marinade the meat overnight and then <pause dur="short"/> cover it in flour and <trunc>r</trunc> and just fry it off and then put it in the slow roasty thing for the rest of the day <pause dur="long"/> it's amazing there isn't a cloud in the sky now</u>
<u n="293" who="S0202">I know</u>
<u n="294" who="S0225" trans="overlap">yeah I mean you know who would have thought?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0224">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="296" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">when erm the rice is neaArly done I'll do the prawns</u>
<u n="297" who="S0223"><unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0223">is it?</u>
<u n="300" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="301" who="S0223" whoConfidence="low">shall we finish it off?</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="302" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">they're just on the</u>
<u n="303" who="S0223"><unclear/></u>
<u n="304" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah they're just there that's fine <unclear/> no room in the fridge <unclear/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="305" who="S0223">I won't have any</u>
<u n="306" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might <unclear/> some of the sauce</u>
<u n="307" who="S0223"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might <unclear/></u>
<u n="308" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I won't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't</u>
<u n="309" who="S0223">well I'll put some on the table just <unclear/> wants any</u>
<u n="310" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">if he wants any you're very welcome to put it out right how are we doing out here?</u>
<u n="311" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I don't know what that was</u>
<u n="312" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah</u>
<u n="313" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what won't I have and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might?</u>
<u n="314" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">bread with dinner</u>
<u n="315" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh right</u>
<u n="316" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh I'll probably have a bit of bread</u>
<u n="317" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm <pause dur="short"/> so what's this we're drinking now?</u>
<u n="318" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="319" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">have you had some of this?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0202">yeah I've got some now thank you</u>
<u n="321" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you like it?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0202">yeah it's nice yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="323" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm yes it's definitely sort of the autumn's picked up now hasn't it? you alright sweetie?</u>
<u n="324" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well if this is autumn I'll take this over our autumn any day</u>
<u n="326" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">well er this is when we feel autumn's coming in the nights are really starting to draw in</u>
<u n="329" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">very quickly now</u>
<u n="331" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it is actually dark earlier than I think it would be</u>
<u n="332" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm mm</u>
<u n="333" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">you know cos back home we'd still be <pause dur="short"/> it'd still be light</u>
<u n="334" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">this is where we notice it here is is either end of the <trunc>seas</trunc> of of the summer season when it's sort of dark earlier cos we think although we're an hour ahead it's</u>
<u n="337" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">we're also further south so it</u>
<u n="339" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">we've got that change <pause dur="short"/> but erm rice is on and as soon as the rice is almost ready I'm gonna do the prawns</u>
<u n="341" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">so we're not far off</u>
<u n="343" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">good good <pause dur="long"/> <foreign lang="fre">quelle heure est que <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> fini</foreign> <foreign lang="fre"/>?</u>
<u n="344" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">vers minuit</foreign></u>
<u n="345" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh <foreign lang="fre">vers minuit</foreign> okay</u>
<u n="346" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">elle a telephone</foreign>?</u>
<u n="347" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">oui</foreign></u>
<u n="348" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">oui</foreign> okay so about twenty minutes?</u>
<u n="349" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm?</u>
<u n="350" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">well do we wanna wait for her to come back?</u>
<u n="351" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he said near midnight</u>
<u n="352" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh near midnight</u>
<u n="353" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <event desc="unintelligible"/> <foreign lang="fre">vingt minutes</foreign></u>
<u n="354" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">vingt minutes</foreign> yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">vingt minutes oui</foreign></u>
<u n="356" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">pardon</foreign> <foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="358" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>oh bless her</unclear> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="360" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>suppose I ought</unclear> to read really <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="361" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/> so where shall we go tomorrow then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? any</u>
<u n="362" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">dunno erm <pause dur="short"/> mountains are good that's good to head uphill you know that would be a nice thing <pause dur="short"/> you know be able to see a distance</u>
<u n="363" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="364" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> towards the Pyrenees or something like that you know</u>
<u n="365" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">get a bit of a height <pause dur="short"/> mind you we go up a couple of thousand feet mind you that shouldn't be <trunc>t</trunc> er it should be okay tomorrow because I mean we lose what? two degrees per thousands if we go up to four thousand feet or whatever we're losing eight but we're looking at so it's probably still gonna be about twenty-two degrees high up</u>
<u n="367" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you know so <pause dur="long"/> dunno <pause dur="long"/> that erm that village that er mind you I suppose it's still tourist season so</u>
<u n="369" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no that village won't be anybody in that village</u>
<u n="370" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">in the Ravel? where you saw the snakes?</u>
<u n="371" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no I was thinking that other one that we drove past that time that erm erm is <trunc>li</trunc>like on a gorge or something you know you could only get across <pause dur="short"/> do you remember you had to pay to park and we decided not to park? <pause dur="short"/> mm I dunno if you remember</u>
<u n="372" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">trying to think where that was</u>
<u n="373" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">pretty amazing place mind you you know I can't remember which direction that was but erm erm you know we've been past there already anyway so</u>
<u n="374" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh we that was erm</u>
<u n="375" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">maybe we should just go another direction</u>
<u n="376" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah that was up erm Minerve wasn't it?</u>
<u n="377" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">where there's a river running down and there's a car park yeah that was Minerve</u>
<u n="379" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">that was it it was er pretty amazing</u>
<u n="380" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah that will be still busy</u>
<u n="381" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah let's not head that way then <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="382" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well we could go down to Lagrasse and go through the Corbières</u>
<u n="383" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm <pause dur="short"/> not that I know where that is but</u>
<u n="384" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="385" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm just humming yes</u>
<u n="386" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh you're just saying yes but it doesn't</u>
<u n="387" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it doesn't really matter well we'll we'll see in the morning <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="389" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="390" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er <foreign lang="fre"/> <foreign lang="fre">le weekend</foreign></u>
<u n="391" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="392" who="S0202"><foreign lang="fre">anglais s'il vous plaît</foreign> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="394" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="fre">oui</foreign> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0223">ah <pause dur="long"/> excuse me I was just looking for that</u>
<u n="396" who="S0202">oh sorry</u>
<u n="397" who="S0223">no no I I was looking for it upstairs</u>
<u n="398" who="S0202">I'm hiding it</u>
<u n="399" who="S0223">food's almost ready I just tried home again</u>
<u n="400" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0223">but I'm not getting a reply</u>
<u n="402" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">course not he's busy <pause dur="long"/> what's the upside in him answering the phone?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0223">say again?</u>
<u n="404" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what's the upside in him answering the phone?</u>
<u n="405" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he's no longer busy <unclear>I think</unclear></u>
<u n="406" who="S0223"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no no what I mean is for <trunc>h</trunc> for him why would he answer the phone? it's gonna be somebody wanting him to do something</u>
<u n="408" who="S0223" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it is yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0223" trans="overlap">it's been busy for the last hour and a half <pause dur="short"/> I suppose at that age you could be</u>
<u n="411" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0223"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes yeah don't go there</u>
<u n="414" who="S0223" trans="overlap">let's not go there</u>
<u n="415" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">don't go there</u>
<u n="416" who="S0223"><vocal desc="laugh"/> stop</u>
<u n="417" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0223">stop that vision erm <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit cool out here guys are you alright?</u>
<u n="419" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">no it's okay</u>
<u n="420" who="S0202">yeah fine</u>
<u n="421" who="S0223">I'm gonna go and sit in the living room <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0202">can't wait for this curry</u>
<u n="423" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="424" who="S0202">been waiting for it since December <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="425" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">the first stars are out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="426" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah there might be shooting stars tonight have to have a look later on</u>
<u n="427" who="S0202">oh shooting stars do you get them often over here then?</u>
<u n="428" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0202">oh I wonder where the <trunc>I</trunc>ISS is tonight</u>
<u n="430" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you'll have to look on the internet</u>
<u n="431" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">somewhere in northern Syria I think</u>
<u n="433" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0202">yeah I don't think it it didn't go over France yesterday it said eleven days until next time it comes over this part</u>
<u n="435" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh right oh well</u>
<u n="436" who="S0202">so but I don't know how accurate that were obviously</u>
<u n="437" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well it <unclear>won't</unclear> be accurate because that's that's their site so they're saying it's gonna come over <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="438" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">have you got any pictures of your <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">want to do a for sale sign and stick it on the noticeboard at the garden centre</u>
<u n="441" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you?</u>
<u n="442" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just stick it up might be some interest</u>
<u n="443" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah?</u>
<u n="444" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">given that you know people know I've got one so we do get you know people in coming to talk about it and stuff like that so <pause dur="long"/> stick it on the noticeboard</u>
<u n="445" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah might as well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0202">it's so loud that noise ain't it? like out here especially</u>
<u n="447" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>it's</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0202" trans="overlap">cos it's so quiet <pause dur="short"/> that's why you notice it more <pause dur="long"/> when are you coming back over to England then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0225">I don't know don't have any plans</u>
<u n="450" who="S0202">you're not going over to see your dad or anything?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0225">he's coming out in a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="452" who="S0202">oh is he?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0225">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0202">he was supposed to come over for your birthday weren't he?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0225">he did yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0202">oh did he come out? <pause dur="short"/> oh that's nice <pause dur="short"/> cos he's fluent in French ain't he?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0225">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0202">he used to be a French teacher</u>
<u n="459" who="S0225">yep <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="460" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay explain to me something cos I might just be really stupid here <pause dur="short"/> ryanair I need to have a password we dunno what the password is so I've asked for a new password it's given us a temporary password</u>
<u n="461" who="S0225">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">so you go in and have to put in a new password so I've given myself a new password then it <trunc>w</trunc> asks you a question what was the name of your first pet? so I put a name in click it and it goes doesn't correspond with what we've got but I've just asked for a new password so does it matter what I've put before?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0225">well no because it's just it's just proving that you are who you are</u>
<u n="464" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">well I don't know what I put before</u>
<u n="465" who="S0225" trans="overlap">cos that could be anybody asking for a new password</u>
<u n="466" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I don't know what I put before</u>
<u n="467" who="S0225" trans="overlap">try try <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> not necessarily you who've put that it might've been me first pet'll be <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="468" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah but if you need a new password does it matter what the? oh</u>
<u n="469" who="S0202">will it be a capital C?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0225" trans="overlap">because anybody could ask for a new password if you put in say my email is <anon type="email"/> send me a new password is it really you or is it just somebody who's just stolen your email?</u>
<u n="471" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay fair enough but if you don't know your new er we're never gonna be able to do it are we?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0225">I just told you it's <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="473" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you know it's <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/>?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0225">yeah cos it's my first pet</u>
<u n="475" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="476" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">what? you didn't have Hammy the hamster or?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0225">no I didn't have any of those things</u>
<u n="478" who="S0202">I had Goebbel the gerbil <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">you had your first pet was</u>
<u n="480" who="S0202" trans="overlap">did you? I had Delilah</u>
<u n="481" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">Muggins</u>
<u n="482" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">the er the hamster</u>
<u n="484" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">she weren't mine <unclear>she was</unclear> my mum's <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0202">mine bit me it were a right evil little thing still got a scar on my finger from him</u>
<u n="486" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I've put the prawns on</u>
<u n="487" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah mine was alright my sister's was pretty evil</u>
<u n="488" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">so I'm just gonna give I'm just gonna give</u>
<u n="489" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">she had a rabbit called erm</u>
<u n="490" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">things a chance to catch up the rice is done</u>
<u n="491" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">Taffy who was just vicious</u>
<u n="492" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">we might be able to watch shooting stars tonight cos have you seen the sky?</u>
<u n="493" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="494" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well I'm looking at <trunc>sk</trunc> erm stars up there at the moment</u>
<u n="495" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er but nothing's moving</u>
<u n="497" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">so we'll eat and we'll come out and look at shooting stars</u>
<u n="498" who="S0202">yes</u>
<u n="499" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">there are more and more coming out</u>
<u n="501" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw two satellites when I went down to get the ponies the other night I haven't</u>
<u n="502" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="503" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">put the ponies down the field tonight</u>
<u n="504" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">was that documented? did anyone witness that?</u>
<u n="505" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did</u>
<u n="506" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah sure</u>
<u n="507" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah sure</u>
<u n="509" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you alright petal?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0202">no I'm <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="511" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="512" who="S0202">from Yorkshire</u>
<u n="513" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">like him then</u>
<u n="514" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">southerners</u>
<u n="516" who="S0202">he don't sound like he's from Yorkshire he's not a proper Yorkshireman</u>
<u n="517" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh I dunno sometimes I hear Yorkshire coming out of your gob</u>
<u n="518" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm <pause dur="short"/> bloody southerners</u>
<u n="519" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">so what am I? born in Essex but I've got a Geordie mother and a Scottish dad so what does that make me?</u>
<u n="520" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh it's a that's a foreign country Essex</u>
<u n="521" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">am I a mudblood?</u>
<u n="523" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er?</u>
<u n="524" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm a mudblood</u>
<u n="525" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes very much yeah a mudblood</u>
<u n="526" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="527" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">a mudblood</u>
<u n="528" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">anybody asks me where I come from now I say north London</u>
<u n="530" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I had a hard time when I went to school they used to beat me up for being a Geordie and when I came home they used to beat me up for being a Londoner</u>
<u n="531" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh dear</u>
<u n="532" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">so you were in a no win situation weren't you?</u>
<u n="534" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was no win</u>
<u n="535" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0202">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <trunc>w</trunc> she didn't get her vote through did she? or she didn't think she did and she couldn't vote in France so she was like well which country do I belong to then? I can't vote in either like she was saying she was like no one wants me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="537" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I feel so unloved</u>
<u n="538" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but it turns out that her</u>
<u n="539" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0202">arsehole flatmates had not given her the letter hidden under loads of rubbish in the kitchen</u>
<u n="541" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh they were fuckwits</u>
<u n="542" who="S0202">so she belongs to England it's okay</u>
<u n="543" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">bless her <pause dur="short"/> I ought to let <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> know that you will you will actually go in</u>
<u n="544" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm I'll go there about quarter to nine</u>
<u n="545" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yep <pause dur="short"/> either with or without <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear>or me and me</unclear></u>
<u n="546" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yep I'll just take the Land Rover and the wheelie thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="547" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah <pause dur="short"/> my first satellite just disappearing over the house</u>
<u n="548" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well that doesn't count if it's just disappearing does it? cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="549" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">well I can see it going it's still going well that was my first one of the night <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="550" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="551" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">and if I sit here long enough it'll reappear</u>
<u n="552" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah I wouldn't actually plan on sitting there</u>
<u n="553" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">several hours later</u>
<u n="554" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I was gonna say I wouldn't actually plan on sitting there that long</u>
<u n="555" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no <pause dur="long"/> I have broken my duck</u>
<u n="556" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="557" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I mean it just amazes me seeing as the other night I couldn't see anything</u>
<u n="558" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="long"/> get a stiff neck looking up have to go down and sit on those sunloungers <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0202">oh no <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
