<text id="S9B9">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:09:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013 S0152</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Health, technology, tweeting, jobs, football</topics>
		<activity>Talking whilst having a cup of tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0152">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Birmingham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>w_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0013">something different to make there</u>
<u n="2" who="S0012">got a brand new suit</u>
<u n="3" who="S0152">no I need to go on a diet <pause dur="short"/> no I don't need to go on a diet</u>
<u n="4" who="S0013">I think you do</u>
<u n="5" who="S0152">I'm not eating that much so why I'm putting weight on I just don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm not as active I suppose cos I'm not walking about as much as I used to walk about</u>
<u n="6" who="S0013">well your let go of <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0152">ah <pause dur="short"/> I'm not as active but I have put some weight on</u>
<u n="8" who="S0013">how much do you weigh now?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0152">I don't know I've not weighed myself</u>
<u n="10" who="S0012">no you didn't want to do that do you? You don't want to do that</u>
<u n="11" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="12" who="S0012">nah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0152">I know when I've lost weight I've got trousers I can get into and what I can't</u>
<u n="14" who="S0013">when you used to go to the quacks just for a check-up they used to weigh you take your blood pressure and everything <pause dur="short"/> don't do anything anymore</u>
<u n="15" who="S0152">you have to ask dad</u>
<u n="16" who="S0013">I asked  I asked  eh I think that was <unclear/> can I weigh myself <pause dur="short"/> he said go and see the nurse if you want to weigh yourself</u>
<u n="17" who="S0012">no you can't <pause dur="short"/> they're only allowed well ten minutes</u>
<u n="18" who="S0013">he wanted to me walk across and stare down the thing and weigh yourself</u>
<u n="19" who="S0012">yeah but if you've gone for a particular reason then you ask if you</u>
<u n="20" who="S0013">well I asked the other doctors and then <trunc>whe</trunc> when I went up <unclear/> that was years ago</u>
<u n="21" who="S0152">well that was years ago <pause dur="short"/> things have changed</u>
<u n="22" who="S0013">and they were nice</u>
<u n="23" who="S0152">things have changed</u>
<u n="24" who="S0013">ooh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> fell in a ditch the other day</u>
<u n="25" who="S0152">what just walking?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0013">she fell in ditch over there and hung upside down by her foot</u>
<u n="27" who="S0012">who did?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="29" who="S0012">what?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0012">how did it happen there?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0013">well she was just walk walking across checking the hedgerows slid down the ditch and caught her foot in the  in the  railing at the top and hung upside down</u>
<u n="33" who="S0012">oh gosh</u>
<u n="34" who="S0013">she said luckily there wasn't any water in the ditch</u>
<u n="35" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> could have been awful</u>
<u n="36" who="S0013">nobody knows I said didn't you bring you didn't you have phone? She said no I never cart my phone about <pause dur="short"/> I said cor you could have <pause dur="short"/> she said but I struggled and struggled and struggled and finally my foot came out and I fell right into the ditch then <pause dur="short"/> and there was water in the bottom and she managed to crawl out <pause dur="short"/> had to go to the quacks about her leg</u>
<u n="37" who="S0012">dear now</u>
<u n="38" who="S0152">that's not a that's not good</u>
<u n="39" who="S0013">that ain't good</u>
<u n="40" who="S0012">what a thing to happen</u>
<u n="41" who="S0013">it was terrible</u>
<u n="42" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0013">she told me that when she bought the eggs round</u>
<u n="44" who="S0012">right</u>
<u n="45" who="S0013">well she just said eh <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said how how is your leg? And I said what have you done to your leg? And she said ooh didn't you hear the saga?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0152">but she must <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0012">I can't see how it would happen</u>
<u n="48" who="S0152">she must have just slipped on something or tripped over something</u>
<u n="49" who="S0013" trans="overlap">she slipped yeah yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0012">to catch your foot in the railings</u>
<u n="51" who="S0013">she caught her foot in the top and she just hung</u>
<u n="52" who="S0012">dear</u>
<u n="53" who="S0013">hung down in the ditch</u>
<u n="54" who="S0012">oh she was lucky wasn't she?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0013">she was lucky yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said if anything like that happen you just give us a phone <pause dur="short"/> I don't carry my phone she says <pause dur="short"/> well you should she said I tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> every time when he goes out on his tractor take your phone he said he always said <unclear/> don't worry I've got it <pause dur="short"/> when he's gone I look by his desk there's his phone</u>
<u n="56" who="S0152">he needs to <unclear/> But this is the thing now with mobile phones isn't it? What did you do twenty years ago?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0013">eh?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0152">what did you do twenty years ago if you hadn't if you had a</u>
<u n="59" who="S0013">your wife gets somebody to come past</u>
<u n="60" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0152">yeah?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0013">well there was that <unclear/> in Australia or in a cave in Australia <pause dur="short"/> and he couldn't get signal but suddenly he could get a text and the only people he text was the cold get through to was the coastguard in this country <pause dur="short"/> and he got through the coastguard in this country <pause dur="short"/> he phoned up the the people in Australia and they found him by his little GPS signal</u>
<u n="63" who="S0152">yeah? It's amazing</u>
<u n="64" who="S0013">but he couldn't get through to anyone Australia because I suppose that that won't <trunc>cala</trunc> calibrate for his for that only got one  I don't know how it works</u>
<u n="65" who="S0152">I think from any phone you can do as S O S</u>
<u n="66" who="S0013">can you? Oh right</u>
<u n="67" who="S0152">from any phone you can do an SOS so you don't have to have your network <pause dur="short"/> so if you're in an emergency</u>
<u n="68" who="S0013">yeah that's right <pause dur="short"/> he did this SOS and the only place that picked it up was somebody in Bilmouth <pause dur="short"/> in</u>
<u n="69" who="S0012">so how do you do an SOS? S O S?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0152">no you can do one one two <pause dur="short"/> is it one one two or nine nine nine? International call</u>
<u n="71" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="72" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> one one two is international isn't it?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0152">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="74" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="75" who="S0152">and it just and it picks up <pause dur="short"/> and every network allows you to do that</u>
<u n="76" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0152">even though you're not on the</u>
<u n="78" who="S0013">that's good innit?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0013">the trouble with these GPS walkers they use this GPS for the phone on the phone or whatever <pause dur="short"/> then go for a walk and the phone battery only lasts so long and then they're lost <pause dur="short"/> they don't take maps with them</u>
<u n="81" who="S0152">no they'd just die <pause dur="short"/> I mean the normal GPS run on normal batteries like Duracell batteries and things like that <pause dur="short"/> phones don't <pause dur="short"/> you've got to charge them so</u>
<u n="82" who="S0013">but then they've got this just a <unclear/> ones and I haven't been <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0152">you can also have them with solar cells that you can recharge them on the backpack and things like that <pause dur="short"/> so you've got a solar cell on your backpack which attaches to your phone and keeps it charged all the time</u>
<u n="84" who="S0013">but they do say that GPS uses the battery a lot</u>
<u n="85" who="S0152">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> things things like GPS Bluetooth Wi-Fi <pause dur="short"/> I switch all those off if I know that I'm not going to need them <pause dur="short"/> so if I go <pause dur="short"/> so like in the Yorkshire dales or moors or lakes I turn off my Wi-Fi cos I'm not going to use it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0013">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0152">I don't have my Bluetooth on <pause dur="short"/> unless it's in the car <pause dur="short"/> and then I can charge the charge it via the car</u>
<u n="88" who="S0013">so it can charge via the car?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0152">I can charge my phone by the car <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0013">you see that's <unclear/> A phone charger in the</u>
<u n="91" who="S0012">we've got one</u>
<u n="92" who="S0013">we haven't</u>
<u n="93" who="S0152">but you need a new phone really</u>
<u n="94" who="S0012">but I'm sure there was all those wires that were underneath the seat</u>
<u n="95" who="S0013">they're not the phone charger they're the <pause dur="short"/> because this our motor was too old for a phone to have a charger <pause dur="short"/> the next one that came out all had phone chargers in</u>
<u n="96" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0013">ours is too old for it</u>
<u n="98" who="S0012">it's got something <pause dur="short"/> something in it</u>
<u n="99" who="S0013">something for the phone charger to be linked up to but Vauxhall did the wrong phone charger you see</u>
<u n="100" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="101" who="S0013">and we haven't got one</u>
<u n="102" who="S0152">but you it's just a normal plug in your lighter</u>
<u n="103" who="S0013">there's a lighter one yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you can buy the new phone chargers through and plug in the <unclear/> like you do the GPS <pause dur="short"/> you can do that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0013">but we do need new phones</u>
<u n="106" who="S0152">you do need new phones and you're going away in two weeks' time</u>
<u n="107" who="S0013">one week</u>
<u n="108" who="S0152">one week <pause dur="short"/> one week on <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0012" trans="overlap">this Wednesday</u>
<u n="110" who="S0152">what this Wednesday?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0152">oh it's this Wednesday isn't it?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0013">oh while we're on it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said they'd come and do you know for the day they went we're not there they'll water our <unclear/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0012">yeah cos we were planning on coming on coming back for Sunday</u>
<u n="115" who="S0152">that's alright cos I can feed the cat on the  on the  Saturday when I go <pause dur="short"/> it's not a problem</u>
<u n="116" who="S0013">so it doesn't  it doesn't</u>
<u n="117" who="S0012">so he doesn't need feeding on the Saturday?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0152">no cos I feed it when we go</u>
<u n="119" who="S0012">Cos we'll be back on the Sunday</u>
<u n="120" who="S0013">Cos I was going to say we can get up there at six o'clock and feed the cat</u>
<u n="121" who="S0152">no I can feed all I can get all that sorted so you haven't got to worry about the Saturday</u>
<u n="122" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0152">that's alright</u>
<u n="125" who="S0013">you've still got to leave the back door open</u>
<u n="126" who="S0012">so Saturday night will be alright will it?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0152">Saturday will be fine it won't be a problem <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to close the</u>
<u n="129" who="S0012">well I mean for us to be Sunday night to feed the rabbits and</u>
<u n="130" who="S0152">yeah that's fine <pause dur="short"/> yeah the rabbits will be alright <pause dur="short"/> yeah the rabbits will be fine</u>
<u n="131" who="S0012">okay</u>
<u n="132" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos as I said it's no problem <unclear/> So now they'll be here this week for this week you see <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> that was unfortunate</u>
<u n="133" who="S0152">oh it's bad <pause dur="short"/> it's bad news</u>
<u n="134" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0013">that was unfortunate</u>
<u n="136" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0013"><unclear/> is better <unclear/> is better <pause dur="short"/> they went for a walk yesterday <pause dur="short"/> they did go for a walk all the way round <pause dur="short"/> and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's quite a long way isn't it?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that's round about what's it is it? It's about ten miles</u>
<u n="140" who="S0012">did they?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0013">Cos this is a mile walk round there</u>
<u n="142" who="S0012">I don't know where they went <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="143" who="S0013">yeah they did the railway walk <pause dur="short"/> cos they like the wildlife down there</u>
<u n="144" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0013">haven't seen any march hares this year</u>
<u n="146" who="S0152">no I haven't</u>
<u n="147" who="S0013">no there's usually a load of march hares <pause dur="short"/> we had some come in the garden about two or three years ago <pause dur="short"/> youngsters <pause dur="short"/> young'uns playing <pause dur="short"/> one of them gnawed through the <unclear/> of the gate there and got stuck and I found it dead the next morning</u>
<u n="148" who="S0152">the next morning</u>
<u n="149" who="S0012" trans="overlap">poor thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0152">I haven't seen any but I suppose I haven't been going past any fields as such</u>
<u n="151" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0012">you haven't either <pause dur="short"/> you haven't come past the <pause dur="short"/> cos we used to go up that way and see loads of hares didn't we and we haven't been</u>
<u n="153" who="S0152">no it's just on the way to North Orsham I didn't it's forest and <unclear/> no I didn't see any <pause dur="short"/> I saw a lens that I wanted to buy</u>
<u n="154" who="S0013">but you're not allowed to</u>
<u n="155" who="S0152">eight thousand eight hundred and ninety pound</u>
<u n="156" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0013">yes I'd like to buy that lens too</u>
<u n="158" who="S0012">so <unclear/> what you did buy?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0013">yeah what did you buy?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0152">I used my Jessops voucher yesterday</u>
<u n="161" who="S0013">yeah to what?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0012">to buy <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't just a paper</u>
<u n="163" who="S0013">I bought a Compaq flash card <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0012">that's allowed</u>
<u n="165" who="S0013">that's allowed</u>
<u n="166" who="S0152">I didn't have to pay for it cos I've got the vouchers <pause dur="short"/> but I've got a four gig Compaq flash for twenty-three pound</u>
<u n="167" who="S0013">that's good yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0152">when I paid thirty pound for a two gig last year at the shop for from</u>
<u n="169" who="S0012" trans="overlap">just last year <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0013">well that shop in <unclear/> was a bit of a</u>
<u n="171" who="S0152">he's a bit expensive</u>
<u n="172" who="S0013">he's a bit expensive isn't he?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0012">it's funny isn't it? Cos we've still got  we've still got  sixteen what is it?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0013">yeah we've got sixteen megabytes</u>
<u n="175" who="S0012">what is it megabytes?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0013">megabytes</u>
<u n="177" who="S0012">memory stick</u>
<u n="178" who="S0013">memory sticks right?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0012">it takes about two photographs</u>
<u n="180" who="S0013">when when we first bought the Sony</u>
<u n="181" who="S0012">we'd</u>
<u n="182" who="S0013">and that was a five megapixel</u>
<u n="183" who="S0012">yeah funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0013">and that take that took five on five and about eighteen on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0012">it took loads on the five megapixel didn't it?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0013" trans="overlap">but this one <pause dur="short"/> if you put that in that take one <pause dur="short"/> bonk</u>
<u n="187" who="S0152">it's amazing</u>
<u n="188" who="S0013">Cos these new ones</u>
<u n="189" who="S0012">that's right because I did use it the other day not thinking</u>
<u n="190" who="S0013">but that went on fine that was on</u>
<u n="191" who="S0012">yes well <pause dur="short"/> I think it was yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0013">I mean well you can't take when you got that that three gig</u>
<u n="193" who="S0012">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="194" who="S0013">three no it's how many megapixels can you take you take now? It can take</u>
<u n="195" who="S0012">well anyway <pause dur="short"/> I remember putting it in the camera and thinking ooh Sony</u>
<u n="196" who="S0152">it <trunc>de</trunc> it depends doesn't it? It depends</u>
<u n="197" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it depends what you want what you put your camera on <pause dur="short"/> cos you can take</u>
<u n="198" who="S0152">you can have it on flat</u>
<u n="199" who="S0013">you can even take  pictures can't you?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0152">yeah fine <pause dur="short"/> did see a nice camera yesterday <pause dur="short"/> a Cannon six hundred</u>
<u n="201" who="S0013">I'll tell you what the new Cannon's look brilliant <pause dur="short"/> they do they look lovely <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0152">but I'm not having one</u>
<u n="203" who="S0013">no no <pause dur="short"/> that's what we thought well a photo is a photo <pause dur="short"/> I'd like I would like a long lens <pause dur="short"/> a lens that will take one of the those</u>
<u n="204" who="S0152">but you've got a long lens</u>
<u n="205" who="S0013">well that's not a that's not</u>
<u n="206" who="S0012">it's quite good</u>
<u n="207" who="S0152">what what have you got? A three hundred?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0013">yeah yeah but</u>
<u n="209" who="S0012">he wants to take birds</u>
<u n="210" who="S0013">yeah but it's got <unclear/> around it</u>
<u n="211" who="S0012">can't take birds <pause dur="short"/> like birds</u>
<u n="212" who="S0013">I want to take birds <pause dur="short"/> no the smaller the goldfinches outside outside on the blossom and they look lovely <pause dur="short"/> and you just can't get <pause dur="short"/> I want a close up of a goldfinch or something sucking the nectar from this plant</u>
<u n="213" who="S0152">but the <trunc>pro</trunc> but the problem is if you have a big lens which is just a lens in the sense that it's a four hundred <pause dur="short"/> you can't do anything else with it</u>
<u n="214" who="S0013">no you can't no</u>
<u n="215" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="216" who="S0152">so that means you've got to swap and change</u>
<u n="217" who="S0013">well you have to actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it's annoying isn't it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I hadn't thought of it</u>
<u n="220" who="S0012">one <unclear/> with the long long lens like that</u>
<u n="221" who="S0152">long lens <pause dur="short"/> I hadn't thought of that <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="222" who="S0012">and then of course you want another one for the macro and another one midrange</u>
<u n="223" who="S0152">just midrange yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can only get like</u>
<u n="224" who="S0012">three cameras yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0013">that bloke who who lives in the  in the  Maasai</u>
<u n="226" who="S0152">yeah I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> the desert</u>
<u n="227" who="S0013">maasai desert Maasai</u>
<u n="228" who="S0152">the eh game park game reserve</u>
<u n="229" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he lived there right? Well he doesn't live there he travels around it <pause dur="short"/> and he's got a Range Rover <pause dur="short"/> and on every window of his Range Rover all through and everywhere he's got the <unclear/> thing <pause dur="short"/> he's got all these different cameras with all these different lenses on depending on which one he wants to use he's there all the time <pause dur="short"/> and he's wildlife photographer of the year and he's</u>
<u n="230" who="S0152">well he probably earns a fair little bit from the pictures that he actually takes</u>
<u n="231" who="S0013">he probably does yeah <pause dur="short"/> he does  He does  it for National Geo <trunc>geology</trunc> geographical geographic</u>
<u n="232" who="S0012">there you go</u>
<u n="233" who="S0152">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's bound to have good things</u>
<u n="234" who="S0013">but he's got he lot and you just see him and he  and he  spends <pause dur="short"/> he's a Frenchman I think and he spends about six months of the year in the desert or in the wherever it is Massai I can't think of it Maasai Mara or something?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0152">maasai Mara yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0013">he spends about six month a year in there and then he goes home to Paris and sorts all his pictures out and that will take him just as long to sort all his pictures out cos he's took thousands <pause dur="short"/> and he says he'll finish up with about a hundred</u>
<u n="237" who="S0152">that's the normal rule isn't it?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0013">and then he's got to work through the hundred and he finishes up with five or six</u>
<u n="239" who="S0152">you think what they used to say about a reel of thirty-six the old-fashioned film <pause dur="short"/> you'd have one picture on a reel of thirty-six which was good</u>
<u n="240" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0012">and that's if you're lucky really</u>
<u n="242" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0012">but we don't travel we don't see tigers and lions and giraffes and</u>
<u n="244" who="S0013">so therefore you don't need a big lens</u>
<u n="245" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> we don't go to these exotic places <pause dur="short"/> why do you need them?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0013">look I need <pause dur="short"/> I need a big lens to take my budgies</u>
<u n="247" who="S0152">okay then buy an attachment for your telescope that you can put your camera to</u>
<u n="248" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0013">oh yeah that that would be good wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0152">it's not really ours</u>
<u n="251" who="S0013">but that's not really a telescope is it? That's a <unclear/> you just lift it</u>
<u n="252" who="S0012">you're only looking <unclear/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0152">yeah but you can still get the adapter</u>
<u n="254" who="S0013">they left it here for</u>
<u n="255" who="S0012">yeah but it might cost too much</u>
<u n="256" who="S0013"><unclear/> how much are the adapters?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0152">I don't know how much they are</u>
<u n="258" who="S0013">I'd love to get one and just fix it on there</u>
<u n="259" who="S0152">they're not that much</u>
<u n="260" who="S0013">Cos I find it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0012">what your not much is</u>
<u n="262" who="S0152">pardon?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0012">is not what our not much is</u>
<u n="264" who="S0152">no my my not much in money terms is probably less that your not much now</u>
<u n="265" who="S0012">ooh I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="266" who="S0013">I'd love to get the adapter <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to look into it to see how much they are <pause dur="short"/> if they're very reasonable like a thousand pounds <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No no they got to be they've got to be fairly reasonable</u>
<u n="267" who="S0012">twenty</u>
<u n="268" who="S0013">I don't know how much well they <pause dur="short"/> I don't know suppose they cost much more than that do they? Much more than twenty thirty quid</u>
<u n="269" who="S0152">if you just get the right attachment for it <pause dur="short"/> for your camera <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="270" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0013">and then I'll take pictures of I mean the the birds out there this morning when I fed  I fed  them there was goldfinches chaffinches green finches blue tits grey tits house sparrows robins <pause dur="short"/> one robin he comes down and he has  he has  to get his feed before all the rest of them so he's brave enough to look through the window</u>
<u n="273" who="S0012">yeah he hops around waiting for us to go out</u>
<u n="274" who="S0013">he taps on the window with his beak <pause dur="short"/> he even came indoors didn't he?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0012">yes he did</u>
<u n="276" who="S0013">and flew round and off found the door</u>
<u n="277" who="S0012">into the</u>
<u n="278" who="S0013">working on the computer and that flew right past our earholes like saying come on come out and feed me</u>
<u n="279" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's very <pause dur="short"/> playing with them</u>
<u n="280" who="S0013">and he he comes out and he sits <pause dur="short"/> if he sees us through the window he'll come to this window then we walk through and he sees us through that window and he comes to that <pause dur="short"/> and he just waits for us and as you walk out he flies with you <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of bird sound"/> you know as the wing beats and he lands there and you walk a little further and he goes <event desc="sound of bird sound"/> Then he lands <pause dur="short"/> he'll just brush past your shoulder and you put the stuff down and he's from here to the cup away and you just put putting the stuff down from and you just sit there watching him he jumps down and eats and you put it all the way round but you can't touch him <pause dur="short"/> he won't let you touch him anymore <pause dur="short"/> he used to feed out of your hand at one point but now it's <pause dur="short"/> I reckon he got a nest somewhere so he he's too</u>
<u n="281" who="S0152">rise have got some good mill worm offers on at the moment</u>
<u n="282" who="S0013">really? Yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0152">big pot of mill worms which is like a third of the price that you normally pay</u>
<u n="284" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0152">I went into Rise last week cos I'm looking for a bench</u>
<u n="286" who="S0013">what do you want a bench for?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0152">to sit on in the garden <pause dur="short"/> cos the three that I've got all the wood's gone rotten</u>
<u n="288" who="S0013">yeah <unclear/> that's because we leave them outside and</u>
<u n="289" who="S0152">well no they're quite a few years old</u>
<u n="290" who="S0013">yeah ours are a few years old I've got them got to mend mend a couple out there haven't we?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0152">if I could get some wood some hard wood I'd repair them but it's getting the hard wood isn't it?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0013">yeah you <pause dur="short"/> that's just as bad now buying wood <pause dur="short"/> very expensive wood isn't it?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0152">yeah I might as well just go and buy a new bench and take the metal bits to be recycled and you know go to and get the money for the metal bits that might buy me <pause dur="short"/> cos it's Cat likes them</u>
<u n="294" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so has Cat stolen anyone's <unclear/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0012">yeah they've got one of those haven't they?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0013">yeah we've got one it's down the bottom of the field in the shed down there</u>
<u n="297" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="short"/> we did put a lot away this time <pause dur="short"/> took us a long time but</u>
<u n="298" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cleaned up all the rest <pause dur="short"/> this morning they were soaking wet</u>
<u n="299" who="S0012">were they?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0013">absolutely drenched they were <pause dur="short"/> it's a heavy duty outside</u>
<u n="301" who="S0152">I don't know cos I</u>
<u n="302" who="S0013">you didn't get up early enough to see it</u>
<u n="303" who="S0152">I didn't get up early enough to see it now <pause dur="short"/> went to bed late <pause dur="short"/> went to bed a two o'clock</u>
<u n="304" who="S0013">why?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0152">couldn't sleep</u>
<u n="306" who="S0013">you know what's good for sleep don't you? Slap on the head</u>
<u n="307" who="S0152">that's weird <pause dur="short"/> I've had some weird dreams this week <pause dur="short"/> some real weird dreams</u>
<u n="308" who="S0013">why? What have you been thinking about?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0152">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> friday night's dream was two mice which moved and another two mice appeared <pause dur="short"/> and then they moved and another two mice appeared and then again another two mice appeared and another two mice <pause dur="short"/> at the same time there were two white cats <pause dur="short"/> and at the back of the white cats they were infested with fleas</u>
<u n="310" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0013">what a weird dream</u>
<u n="312" who="S0152">so that was Friday nights <pause dur="short"/> and last night dream was even weirder <pause dur="short"/> it was like past and present all in one go</u>
<u n="313" who="S0013">was it yeah?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0152">it was head teacher that I used who used to be my boss a long time ago when I was at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> who died a couple of years ago but he was in it <pause dur="short"/> and we'd walked on to a <pause dur="short"/> we were on roller skates on top of a building</u>
<u n="315" who="S0012">oh gosh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0152">right <pause dur="short"/> and I remember him saying there shouldn't be a problem with the budget <pause dur="short"/> don't know what they've done and I got called out I got called <pause dur="short"/> I was having lunch with somebody at school and the school was And he called me over and went come here and we went on roller skates on to this roof where he said  where he said  there shouldn't be a problem with the budget <pause dur="short"/> there should be no issues with the budget cos it's all been paid off <pause dur="short"/> so what is going on in this place? And that was the dream <pause dur="short"/> but it related back to when I was at <anon type="place"/> and now at  with the thing <pause dur="short"/> is that not weird?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0152">that is very weird yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0012">and the mice</u>
<u n="320" who="S0013">which way is your mind working?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0152">and the mice</u>
<u n="322" who="S0013">you didn't go out in the sun yesterday did you?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> and the mice just don't know</u>
<u n="324" who="S0013">yeah the mice <pause dur="short"/> that's a weird one with the cats with fleas</u>
<u n="325" who="S0152"><trunc>Wh</trunc> and they were white cats</u>
<u n="326" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0152">and you know like you get a spider's abdomen the bit at the back <pause dur="short"/> how they carry their little spiders on the back of that <unclear/> That's how these cats were</u>
<u n="328" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0012">ooh right <pause dur="short"/> with a little nest of fleas</u>
<u n="330" who="S0152">nest of fleas</u>
<u n="331" who="S0012">nest of fleas <pause dur="short"/> sounds like you're out of control really</u>
<u n="332" who="S0013" trans="overlap">sounds like someone has <unclear/> You know how some of them <unclear/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="335" who="S0013">that's a very weird one that was blimey <pause dur="short"/> very weird dream</u>
<u n="336" who="S0152">in the city yesterday I bumped into lots of people</u>
<u n="337" who="S0013">such as?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0152">em <pause dur="short"/> I bumped into ex-students quite a few ex-students <pause dur="short"/> they all said hello and asked if I was alright</u>
<u n="339" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> pleased to see you <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0152">and then I bumped into two members of staff <pause dur="short"/> who went for coffee with them <pause dur="short"/> and then as we were as I was walking back to get meet up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> outside Jarrett's I bumped into another two members of staff who I've got no time for those two members of staff</u>
<u n="341" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="342" who="S0152">because they</u>
<u n="343" who="S0013">didn't go for coffee with them?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> because they they've become</u>
<u n="345" who="S0013">yes</u>
<u n="346" who="S0152">yes people basically</u>
<u n="347" who="S0013">well they're protecting their own  now aren't they?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0152">so and one of them is going to take over the DT department</u>
<u n="349" who="S0013">yeah?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0152">so eh</u>
<u n="351" who="S0013">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> you've got to put all that behind you now</u>
<u n="352" who="S0152">so that was  that was  interesting <pause dur="short"/> so I did have a <pause dur="short"/> I had to find something to do yesterday while the girls went off shopping</u>
<u n="353" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0152">so I went</u>
<u n="355" who="S0013">went to Jessops</u>
<u n="356" who="S0152">I went to Jessops and got the card and some paper <pause dur="short"/> then I went into that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> shop</u>
<u n="357" who="S0013">bit posh</u>
<u n="358" who="S0152">no its brilliant <pause dur="short"/> you need you'd love it in there <pause dur="short"/> you would absolutely love it in there <pause dur="short"/> it's two floors and it's got everything that you could want in there <pause dur="short"/> in the sense that it's got tools it's got camping stuff it's got nuts bolts computer bits and pieces wire household things</u>
<u n="359" who="S0013">whereabouts is this?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0152">where Borders used to be in Chapelfield</u>
<u n="361" who="S0013">it's in Chapelfield shops</u>
<u n="362" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> three floors <pause dur="short"/> and I bought a thirty-four piece Bosch drills</u>
<u n="363" who="S0013">drill bits yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0152">drill bits screw bits for nine pound</u>
<u n="365" who="S0013">well that was cheap</u>
<u n="366" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0152">nearly nothing</u>
<u n="368" who="S0013">yeah you nearly <unclear/> You can <unclear/> for ages in there</u>
<u n="369" who="S0152">so and I I spent probably forty minutes looking round in that shop at the stuff <pause dur="short"/> they do different <pause dur="short"/> light bulbs <pause dur="short"/> you know you were talking about light bulbs?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0152">and you can't get the coloured ones <pause dur="short"/> you can</u>
<u n="372" who="S0013">can you?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0152">you can get coloured light bulbs which light bulb shaped and inside there's a ray of LEDs</u>
<u n="374" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="376" who="S0152">and you plug them in and they give you your coloured lights like the lights outside</u>
<u n="377" who="S0013">yeah? Oh that's lovely</u>
<u n="378" who="S0152">they've got a whole range <pause dur="short"/> and they've got strips of lights which you can put under work surfaces quite cheap</u>
<u n="379" who="S0013">yeah?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0012">oh?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0152">run on LEDs</u>
<u n="382" who="S0013">yeah?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="384" who="S0013">that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to have a look next time we go</u>
<u n="385" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0152">make a <unclear/> Are you going to go?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we're going to go</u>
<u n="388" who="S0152">you'd need  You'd need  a chaperone if you went in there</u>
<u n="389" who="S0013">what to stop me buying stuff or?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0152">you would need a chaperone <pause dur="short"/> cos you would just drool you would salivate</u>
<u n="391" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0012">oh we're not going in then</u>
<u n="393" who="S0013">so it's that's all the way to Norwich</u>
<u n="394" who="S0152">yeah it's such a long way isn't it?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0012">it's Norwich</u>
<u n="396" who="S0152">it's such a long way</u>
<u n="397" who="S0013">yes but it's nice ad quiet here and there's all people <pause dur="short"/> you get people in Norwich</u>
<u n="398" who="S0012">we were talking about the</u>
<u n="399" who="S0013">with beaten miserable faces</u>
<u n="400" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> it was sunny yesterday people didn't have miserable faces</u>
<u n="401" who="S0013">they didn't have miserable <pause dur="short"/> and Norwich won</u>
<u n="402" who="S0152">and Norwich won yes <pause dur="short"/> good result <pause dur="short"/> you're safe</u>
<u n="403" who="S0013">and as for the other one</u>
<u n="404" who="S0152">no we lost <pause dur="short"/> again</u>
<u n="405" who="S0013">no you lost didn't you <pause dur="short"/> yes you did</u>
<u n="406" who="S0152">three nil</u>
<u n="407" who="S0013">you did yeah <pause dur="short"/> I watched it this morning</u>
<u n="408" who="S0152">three nil we lost again <pause dur="short"/> and our next two games <pause dur="short"/> we're going to lose those as well</u>
<u n="409" who="S0013">what Manchester United and Manchester City?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0152">we got no we got something like Chelsea Liverpool Man United Tottenham coming up</u>
<u n="411" who="S0013">are you? Oh god</u>
<u n="412" who="S0152">Norwich Bolton</u>
<u n="413" who="S0013">well you'll lose against Norwich</u>
<u n="414" who="S0152">I did two the other week that I said at the beginning of the season Villa will be putting Norwich down into the championship <pause dur="short"/> no no no <pause dur="short"/> it's going to be the other way round <pause dur="short"/> they'll be putting us down <pause dur="short"/> I did twig that</u>
<u n="415" who="S0013">but Grant Hull got chucked off last night</u>
<u n="416" who="S0152">oh just a bad tackle that's all</u>
<u n="417" who="S0013">yeah but he's <trunc>t</trunc> out for here weeks just when you need him</u>
<u n="418" who="S0152">three games <pause dur="short"/> they might look at that and resend it</u>
<u n="419" who="S0013">I doubt it</u>
<u n="420" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="421" who="S0013">doubt it <pause dur="short"/> he did go in didn't he?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0152">yeah he's bit of a donkey sometimes</u>
<u n="423" who="S0013">he is a bit of a donkey</u>
<u n="424" who="S0152">but he scored goals <pause dur="short"/> he scored goals</u>
<u n="425" who="S0013">he did</u>
<u n="426" who="S0152">he scored goals</u>
<u n="427" who="S0013">so now they'll go back to the scoreboard for Norwich <pause dur="short"/> see <pause dur="short"/> now I can't put Norwich into <unclear/> again</u>
<u n="428" who="S0152">I'm sure if you knew there was something at the end of it you'd go to Norwich</u>
<u n="429" who="S0013">what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might buy me something? Why don't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go and find it bring back a present for me? Like that used to be when I was a little boy <pause dur="short"/> bring me back something mummy</u>
<u n="430" who="S0012">I didn't look after you when you were a little boy</u>
<u n="431" who="S0152">she's doing that now</u>
<u n="432" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I do now</u>
<u n="433" who="S0152">they say it comes full circle don't they</u>
<u n="434" who="S0012">yeah yeah they do yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0012">can they get there</u>
<u n="437" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that's true that yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0152">I was asked this morning <pause dur="short"/> oh I tweeted some pictures yesterday</u>
<u n="439" who="S0013">yeah?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0152">and I had Yorkshire days it's when you tweet it to all their followers <pause dur="short"/> and they've run about four and a half thousand followers <pause dur="short"/> which says great photo</u>
<u n="441" who="S0013">yeah?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0012">so when do they want to buy it?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0152">and then I had somebody from Kirkby Moorside this morning tweeted me saying I've got a new blog page for Pickering em <pause dur="short"/> if you want to submit this was to me if you want to submit any pictures or write any articles at any point let us know</u>
<u n="444" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="445" who="S0013">oh <pause dur="short"/> he's getting quite famous isn't he? On his tweets</u>
<u n="446" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="448" who="S0012">Will they pay you for it?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0152">probably not no</u>
<u n="450" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="451" who="S0152">it's a community  It's a community  blog</u>
<u n="452" who="S0013">of course it is yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0012">yeah it's just a part of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0152">you get you pictures out</u>
<u n="455" who="S0012" trans="overlap">all for free now isn't it really?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0013">you get your pictures out there</u>
<u n="457" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0013">that's the thing about <trunc>se</trunc> <trunc>se</trunc> sending your pictures to the BBC or the ITV or any of them you have to agree that that picture becomes their property</u>
<u n="459" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0012">same with any photographic competition it's the same isn't it?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0012">you</u>
<u n="464" who="S0013">unless you're in</u>
<u n="465" who="S0012">if you don't win then they've got your photograph</u>
<u n="466" who="S0152">you get your photo <pause dur="short"/> so yeah so that was quite  that was quite  nice <unclear/> I've got seventy-seven followers now</u>
<u n="467" who="S0013">seventy-seven? Do you have to put your picture up?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="469" who="S0013">oh I thought you'd got seventy-seven photos</u>
<u n="470" who="S0152">I've got that picture up of me in a car <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether we can pick it up <pause dur="short"/> it depends on what the signal is like <pause dur="short"/> yorkshire days out <pause dur="short"/> let's receive</u>
<u n="471" who="S0013">what what can you you can pick it up here can you? What have you got a <trunc>sig</trunc> what that's doing?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0152">that's that's the G that's like the 3G signal that is <pause dur="short"/> that's your normal telephone signal and that's your 3G signal</u>
<u n="473" who="S0013">that's your <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="474" who="S0152">this is the  This is the  battery there which is green <pause dur="short"/> that's my alarm clock <pause dur="short"/> that's my Bluetooth <pause dur="short"/> it'll take a bit of time to refresh cos it's not in it's not a really good 3G area</u>
<u n="475" who="S0013">no but</u>
<u n="476" who="S0152">I don't know whether this one will be</u>
<u n="477" who="S0013">these posh phones</u>
<u n="478" who="S0152">the problem is that <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> I looked at one of those <pause dur="short"/> it's taken a bit of time to load but <pause dur="short"/> I saw a fantastic picture today of <pause dur="short"/> see that's my picture of me in my little sports car</u>
<u n="479" who="S0013">oh right <pause dur="short"/> what that you went out and tried the other day</u>
<u n="480" who="S0152">the one that I had in the Lakes</u>
<u n="481" who="S0013">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0152">so I tweeted that one <pause dur="short"/> see it picks cos we've got Wi-Fi it picks up a lot quicker <pause dur="short"/> or if you're out in a 3G area it picks it up <pause dur="short"/> this is not picking any of my past ones up</u>
<u n="483" who="S0013">oh I see</u>
<u n="484" who="S0152">em <pause dur="short"/> no that's signal has gone completely I can see that</u>
<u n="485" who="S0013">so you've got a T for tweet</u>
<u n="486" who="S0152">A T for tweet <pause dur="short"/> cos it's not  it's not  refreshing <pause dur="short"/> but you can get <pause dur="short"/> and then on a Friday you have an FF on a Friday</u>
<u n="487" who="S0013">A what?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0152">fF</u>
<u n="489" who="S0013">what's an FF?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0152">follow Friday</u>
<u n="491" who="S0013">oh Follow Friday</u>
<u n="492" who="S0152">and people recommend you to follow <pause dur="short"/> for people to follow <pause dur="short"/> and I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0013">that's all LinkedIn?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0152">yeah that's all LinkedIn</u>
<u n="495" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm on LinkedIn <pause dur="short"/> but <unclear/> I don't even go on it anymore <pause dur="short"/> bit old for all this social networking</u>
<u n="496" who="S0152">see I follow hunters of housing which is a <pause dur="short"/> see oh see these are this is up to date you see <pause dur="short"/> Chris Hoy <pause dur="short"/> yorkshire Days <pause dur="short"/> Ian Taylor</u>
<u n="497" who="S0012">why is that all coming in there?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0013">you can set it all can you?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0152">no it's on</u>
<u n="500" who="S0013">Norwich City</u>
<u n="501" who="S0152">Norwich City follow them <pause dur="short"/> fresher <pause dur="short"/> pair of shoes</u>
<u n="502" who="S0013">brace's shoes?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0013">where did you find Brace's shoes</u>
<u n="505" who="S0152"><unclear/> when he goes on <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>you</trunc> Northumberland</u>
<u n="506" who="S0012">doesn't that take up all your money and that</u>
<u n="507" who="S0152">no no</u>
<u n="508" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="509" who="S0152">oh this one has just started to follow me this <trunc>Ju</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> loves stew has started to follow me</u>
<u n="510" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> loves stews</u>
<u n="511" who="S0152">she started to follow me yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0013">you love stew</u>
<u n="513" who="S0152">I do like stew yeah <pause dur="short"/> bBC Sports <pause dur="short"/> cos the rains caused a problem there I believe <pause dur="short"/> yorkshire days out <pause dur="short"/> see and that they will all say do you <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether it will pick it up very quickly <pause dur="short"/> but I put links into the web and it will show you other things</u>
<u n="514" who="S0013">oh I see right</u>
<u n="515" who="S0152">so if you're somewhere it will pick it up quite quick</u>
<u n="516" who="S0013">but this is not wireless <pause dur="short"/> why does that keep flashing on and off that one?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0152">Cos it's bringing it in</u>
<u n="518" who="S0013">oh I see</u>
<u n="519" who="S0152">that's 3G that is</u>
<u n="520" who="S0013">that's 3G <pause dur="short"/> why haven't you got 4G?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0152">Cos there's no  there's no  4G in this country yet</u>
<u n="522" who="S0013">isn't there?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0152">no only well in London there's 4G</u>
<u n="524" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not out yet <pause dur="short"/> well we'll get 4G when</u>
<u n="525" who="S0012">it wioll break <unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0013">when I get a phone one day</u>
<u n="527" who="S0152">no it's taking a bit of time to come in</u>
<u n="528" who="S0012">oh I should have phoned up</u>
<u n="529" who="S0013">you should have phoned them up</u>
<u n="530" who="S0012">yeah oh dear <pause dur="short"/> I keep forgetting</u>
<u n="531" who="S0013">they don't answer the phone though what's the point in phoning them?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0012">YHA <pause dur="short"/> I was supposed to get in touch with someone so we can get access to</u>
<u n="533" who="S0013">oh access to where you've got to go</u>
<u n="534" who="S0012">we we at least need the code to get in</u>
<u n="535" who="S0013">we do don't we yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0012">we can get her to show us round <pause dur="short"/> no one has been in touch with us have they?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> why don't you get in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> </u>
<u n="538" who="S0012">no I just <unclear/> suppose they should answer the phone they're on reception they should answer it</u>
<u n="539" who="S0152">extra <unclear/> and you can do direct messaging via tweeter as well</u>
<u n="540" who="S0013">yeah?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can tweet somebody as a direct message rather than everybody seeing your conversation</u>
<u n="542" who="S0013">oh can you? Yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0012">ah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's loads on here</u>
<u n="545" who="S0013">have you still got the woman on there? I bet you have <pause dur="short"/> look at me and say no</u>
<u n="546" who="S0152">the woman  The woman  is still on this phone yes</u>
<u n="547" who="S0013">the old woman</u>
<u n="548" who="S0152">the old woman is still on this phone</u>
<u n="549" who="S0012">she's not old at all</u>
<u n="550" who="S0013">yeah but I said an old acquaintance</u>
<u n="551" who="S0152">it's an old one</u>
<u n="552" who="S0013">why have you got the old woman on there?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0012">I'll just go and look up this house now</u>
<u n="554" who="S0152">look at the house yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0012">see if it's for sale</u>
<u n="556" who="S0013">you can't the <unclear/> is on the computer</u>
<u n="557" who="S0012">no I'll put the other one on <pause dur="short"/> Hammonds you said?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0152">Hammonds Lee</u>
<u n="559" who="S0012">okay</u>
<u n="560" who="S0152">why have I got picture of the <trunc>o</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know really</u>
<u n="561" who="S0013">well every time you look at her that'll remind you so get rid of them</u>
<u n="562" who="S0152">I don't  I don't  know why I've got them <pause dur="short"/> but she's not there</u>
<u n="563" who="S0013">no she's not there</u>
<u n="564" who="S0152">and she's not in my when I do a search for people <pause dur="short"/> oh they oh see</u>
<u n="565" who="S0013">ooh you got a message <pause dur="short"/> that's probably from her</u>
<u n="566" who="S0152">that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's off <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="567" who="S0013">oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="568" who="S0152">I didn't realise that all my followers everybody that I follow come into my contacts list as well</u>
<u n="569" who="S0013">do they?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0013">crikey <pause dur="short"/> look at all that lot</u>
<u n="572" who="S0152">she's not in the Acers anymore</u>
<u n="573" who="S0013">oh okay the</u>
<u n="574" who="S0152">she's under X</u>
<u n="575" who="S0013">is she</u>
<u n="576" who="S0152">yeah she's under X <pause dur="short"/> this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> what's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got to say? What are you up to today? Love you missing you love <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss and lots more</u>
<u n="577" who="S0013">ah <pause dur="short"/> she's lovely isn't she?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0152">I had a really nice text off <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday</u>
<u n="579" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0013">and how's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0152">she's alright <pause dur="short"/> I can't read all of it cos it's a bit naughty but</u>
<u n="583" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0152">I can't read all of it and I can't let you read it either cos some of its naughty <pause dur="short"/> but it did say it's not just one thing with you <pause dur="short"/> it's just thinking of you in lots of way</u>
<u n="585" who="S0013">there you go</u>
<u n="586" who="S0152">the way you look</u>
<u n="587" who="S0013">that's a bit iffy</u>
<u n="588" who="S0152">how you are <pause dur="short"/> how you touch <pause dur="short"/> kiss <pause dur="short"/> and hold me <pause dur="short"/> how you make me laugh <pause dur="short"/> feel wanted <pause dur="short"/> feel sexy <pause dur="short"/> how you talk <pause dur="short"/> your laugh your voice <pause dur="short"/> how you sometimes get that far away look in your eyes that gives you vulnerability</u>
<u n="589" who="S0013">oh see she knows <pause dur="short"/> she knows you are vulnerable</u>
<u n="590" who="S0152">how you are with the girls <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> like the one with the cat <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="591" who="S0013">the cat <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0152">how you get up early for me <pause dur="short"/> how you get my madness and neither encourage it or discourage it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0013">she is a bit mad</u>
<u n="594" who="S0152">how you make me feel like I'm home when I'm with you <pause dur="short"/> the way you look at me <pause dur="short"/> I can't tell you what else</u>
<u n="595" who="S0013">okay then <pause dur="short"/> we'll censor that last bit <pause dur="short"/> look at you looking at that with all love in your eyes</u>
<u n="596" who="S0152">there's no love in my eyes</u>
<u n="597" who="S0013">yes there is</u>
<u n="598" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="599" who="S0013">well you look at your phone as though there's love in your eyes</u>
<u n="600" who="S0152">I'm looking at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="601" who="S0013">ah well there you go</u>
<u n="602" who="S0152">so there you go <pause dur="short"/> so that's what she wrote to me last night</u>
<u n="603" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0152">she's even said I've liked you since the twenty third of November two thousand and ten</u>
<u n="605" who="S0013">and you didn't know <pause dur="short"/> now wouldn't have that been better for you if you'd have known <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0152">well I did know</u>
<u n="607" who="S0013">well it would've been a lot better for you if you'd have gone with her rather than the other one</u>
<u n="608" who="S0152">no it wouldn't cos I wouldn't have gone at that point in time</u>
<u n="609" who="S0013">yes you would <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't have gone?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0152">no I wouldn't have gone in that point in time</u>
<u n="611" who="S0013">yeah because you were  you were  intoxicated</u>
<u n="612" who="S0152">no because</u>
<u n="613" who="S0013">we told you to get rid of her two years ago</u>
<u n="614" who="S0152">because at that point in time she smoked</u>
<u n="615" who="S0013">oh she oh right <pause dur="short"/> and she's given up? Right <pause dur="short"/> well done <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't realise <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah she cut you said there was a I remember you said there was one that fancied you and you and she was rather nice but she smokes</u>
<u n="616" who="S0152">gave up eleven months ago</u>
<u n="617" who="S0013">did she?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0152">well I did say to her you do realise that you wouldn't be here now if you still smoked <pause dur="short"/> she went all the good reason that I gave up then isn't it?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she doesn't stink then?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="621" who="S0013">brilliant</u>
<u n="622" who="S0152">see I wouldn't even have gone there</u>
<u n="623" who="S0013">no no I don't blame you <pause dur="short"/> neither would I <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> well done <pause dur="short"/> ruth not you Ruth</u>
<u n="624" who="S0152">but I've known  I've known  that she</u>
<u n="625" who="S0013">she fancied you</u>
<u n="626" who="S0152">liked me I wouldn't can't say fancied can you?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0013">no no no</u>
<u n="628" who="S0152">and I knew July two thousand and ten as well</u>
<u n="629" who="S0013">what she told someone?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0152">somebody told me that she liked me <pause dur="short"/> and at the last end of term do at Poorbrough golf club she was there and I was there with Ali and I could tell that she wasn't</u>
<u n="631" who="S0013">very happy <pause dur="short"/> well yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're better off with her than that one</u>
<u n="632" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> well from what I hear yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0013">it's getting bad again is it?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0152">from what I hear</u>
<u n="635" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="636" who="S0152">they're looking after the child from down the road on a regular basis</u>
<u n="637" who="S0013">oh yeah you said last week <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit naughty isn't it?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0152">and I'm aware that they went to <anon type="place"/>'s last night</u>
<u n="639" who="S0013">what with the kid?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="641" who="S0013">why are they looking after him?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0152">I think one of them one of the other children who is in hospital in London</u>
<u n="643" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="644" who="S0152">but it's not the nicest of families is it?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0152">and it kind of makes <pause dur="short"/> well no I shouldn't really wonder anymore <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't it just annoys me now <pause dur="short"/> it really makes me cross really</u>
<u n="647" who="S0013">yeah well it would do</u>
<u n="648" who="S0152">it makes me cross</u>
<u n="649" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well she she was a bit yeah <pause dur="short"/> wasn't she?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0152">she was alright at the beginning</u>
<u n="651" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but she wanted to change your life <pause dur="short"/> that was the problem</u>
<u n="652" who="S0152">but she weren't going to you knew well that wasn't going to happen was it so</u>
<u n="653" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="654" who="S0152">I stuck my ground didn't I? Whatever I had my values in the end of the day</u>
<u n="655" who="S0013">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I still can't understand why you put up with it for so long <pause dur="short"/> you put up with her all that long time until you had a row that night with the children <pause dur="short"/> well not a row but you you said what you thought and then she she kept slapping that back at you</u>
<u n="656" who="S0152">because it was just the feeling wasn't it?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0013">love is blind as they say</u>
<u n="658" who="S0152">yeah there was nothing I could do about it <pause dur="short"/> I I you know I I'd said after the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> issue with the kids <pause dur="short"/> that I wouldn't let the kids get in the way or something <pause dur="short"/> that I wouldn't let the kids get in the way <pause dur="short"/> and and know that's what I did with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you didn't really let the kids get in the way you let that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get in the way</u>
<u n="660" who="S0152">but school was difficult at that point in time <pause dur="short"/> if you consider what what has happened in the last six years</u>
<u n="661" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you've gone through hell and high water you have</u>
<u n="662" who="S0152">since since two thousand and five</u>
<u n="663" who="S0013">out of the frying pan in to the fire as they say</u>
<u n="664" who="S0152">you know it's it's it hasn't been the easiest of</u>
<u n="665" who="S0013">no no it hasn't</u>
<u n="666" who="S0152">with everything that  With everything that  went on at at school <pause dur="short"/> I mean getting moved from one school to another which was good cos it was a promotion and everything else <pause dur="short"/> which was  Which was  good <pause dur="short"/> and I enjoyed that time <pause dur="short"/> I learnt a lot</u>
<u n="667" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0152">but then having to deal with that child protection issue <pause dur="short"/> with that ex-deputy <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't  That wasn't  good <pause dur="short"/> having to deal with a school with special measures <pause dur="short"/> then when you think the things that are okay on the personal front you've literally got that is going okay</u>
<u n="669" who="S0013">and then you got <unclear/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0152">and then  And then  <trunc>sc</trunc> you get somebody there you know <pause dur="short"/> it just wasn't  It just wasn't  right <pause dur="short"/> it just wasn't <trunc>pr</trunc></u>
<u n="671" who="S0013">but then that's changed your whole attitude towards work as well that's the point <pause dur="short"/> you don't  You don't  feel like <trunc>d</trunc> going back into everything</u>
<u n="672" who="S0152">I was you know <pause dur="short"/> we've we've sat here before and we've gone through how not feeling valued</u>
<u n="673" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0152">that's that's the whole thing wasn't it? It was a whole  It was a whole  feeling valued <pause dur="short"/> so not just work but also in a relationship which you tried <pause dur="short"/> you know I feel that I worked hard</u>
<u n="675" who="S0013">in both</u>
<u n="676" who="S0152">in in both and got nothing for it</u>
<u n="677" who="S0013">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was difficult for you</u>
<u n="678" who="S0152">you know and even even going when I went in November that was fine because that was just like being on holiday November through to Christmas cos I was being  I was being  paid so it wasn't nice at the time and I know for a fact I was quite low</u>
<u n="679" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you were</u>
<u n="680" who="S0152">and it's not as bad as it used to be <pause dur="short"/> it comes and goes <pause dur="short"/> but the biggest  the biggest  change was actually going to North Orsham</u>
<u n="681" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0152">and actually realising that it wasn't me</u>
<u n="683" who="S0013">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's done you good hasn't it?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0152">you know it it wasn't me that had the problem <pause dur="short"/> cos if I can  if I can  walk in a school where I like two members of staff know me three members of staff know me and a couple have heard about me in the sense from confidences and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> and the kids have never heard of me <pause dur="short"/> but to be able to walk in and not <trunc>stru</trunc> and have and have that respect</u>
<u n="685" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0152">and prepared to are prepared to listen and take on board what you are saying in short period of time</u>
<u n="687" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you did very well there <pause dur="short"/> pity that was only part time</u>
<u n="688" who="S0152">you know em</u>
<u n="689" who="S0013">well see you wouldn't have wanted it full time would you</u>
<u n="690" who="S0152">I couldn't have done <pause dur="short"/> I salary wise it just doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> but I'd like you know if I could if there's some if I was in the position where  if I was in the position where  that type of I could do that type of job because I didn't have to worry about what I've got to pay then I would do it</u>
<u n="691" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0152">because it was rewarding in another  in another  sense</u>
<u n="693" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0152">but I do want to be back in the classroom</u>
<u n="695" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0152">I do want to be back in the classroom</u>
<u n="697" who="S0013">you wouldn't want to be head then? You haven't heard anything from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="698" who="S0152">I've not heard anything from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I've not heard <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to make a phone call this week to a special school</u>
<u n="699" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you reckon someone would put the kibosh on that sort of thing?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0152">oh yeah somebody would count it</u>
<u n="701" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0152">somebody in county put the kibosh on it</u>
<u n="703" who="S0012">why?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0013">why because it all stems back into going into special measures</u>
<u n="705" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0013">oh I see</u>
<u n="707" who="S0152">and and</u>
<u n="708" who="S0013">well it wasn't anything to do with you was it?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0152">we supported the head</u>
<u n="710" who="S0013">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> you supported the head yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0152">we supported the head at that point in time to keep him in his job</u>
<u n="712" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0152">all the staff stood together the governors stood together <pause dur="short"/> lots of parents stood together</u>
<u n="714" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0152">alright? And then when we were going into the academy we stuck together on the right of we don't want to be part of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> we want a separate academy for <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and they didn't like that</u>
<u n="716" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0152">and I think certain things were said <pause dur="short"/> and I I <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got the proof but the head at North Orsham has kind of very much said the same</u>
<u n="718" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you don't reckon your chances of getting your head in North Orsham is any good?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="720" who="S0013">weird isn't it? Isn't it weird what the powers that be can do?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0012">not great is it?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0152">you know and then if you know if I put myself in the position of a head alright <pause dur="short"/> and you've got somebody applying for you from one of the so called exceptional academies now in Norfolk <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/> there aren't you going to be asking questions</u>
<u n="723" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0152">doesn't that go against</u>
<u n="725" who="S0013">no that's true</u>
<u n="726" who="S0152">go against  you <pause dur="short"/> I'm fortunate that I've been asked to go to city</u>
<u n="727" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="S0152">because they they've heard of me and they know me and yes I was there for a long period of time</u>
<u n="729" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="730" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well let's hope they see something different in you now there</u>
<u n="731" who="S0152">yeah so</u>
<u n="732" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0152">but that's that's all part of it isn't it? I suppose</u>
<u n="734" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0152">but being at North Horsham did make a difference</u>
<u n="736" who="S0013">Strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="738" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> did you find them?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0012">no it's not on there</u>
<u n="740" who="S0152">wonder when maybe</u>
<u n="741" who="S0012">must be relatively new then</u>
<u n="742" who="S0013">must have been put on yesterday or</u>
<u n="743" who="S0012">well I would have thought eh Sue would have been down</u>
<u n="744" who="S0152">did you check Rightmove?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0012">no I just went Hammond Lee</u>
<u n="746" who="S0152">try <trunc>ri</trunc> try Rightmove</u>
<u n="747" who="S0012">okay</u>
<u n="748" who="S0152">and put the <trunc>po</trunc> and put the postcode in</u>
<u n="749" who="S0012">yeah I'll do that</u>
<u n="750" who="S0152">and put it em a mile from here</u>
<u n="751" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0013">oh yeah you can do that can't you</u>
<u n="753" who="S0152">so so yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you know I'm</u>
<u n="754" who="S0013">anyway <pause dur="short"/> that's all behind you now so you've just got to look for the future <pause dur="short"/> it's no good  is there? That doesn't get you anywhere</u>
<u n="755" who="S0152">doesn't help</u>
<u n="756" who="S0013">doesn't help at all</u>
<u n="757" who="S0152">I mean yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't have as many bad days as I was having</u>
<u n="758" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> anyhow we enjoyed the meal the other day <pause dur="short"/> that was very nice</u>
<u n="759" who="S0152">it was good</u>
<u n="760" who="S0013">it was very nice very good <pause dur="short"/> very good</u>
<u n="761" who="S0152">my recipe book came in Friday</u>
<u n="762" who="S0013">did it?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="765" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> looked through it yesterday and said there's some good recipes in here <pause dur="short"/> we could try these <pause dur="short"/> and they're quite they're relatively simple</u>
<u n="766" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="768" who="S0013">which one was it that was?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0152">the one from the little Flaris</u>
<u n="770" who="S0013">from the little Flaris she's on  she's on  <unclear/> isn't she?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0152" trans="overlap">she's on tomorrow night  on tomorrow night</u>
<u n="772" who="S0013">we're going to record them <pause dur="short"/> which reminds us we've got to record everything for next week now and the week after <pause dur="short"/> we we won't miss it</u>
<u n="773" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> you'll soon catch up with stuff</u>
<u n="774" who="S0013">well you do yeah <pause dur="short"/> even with well <pause dur="short"/> we didn't watch Emmerdale or anything like that as you know but <pause dur="short"/> I mean you can miss a  miss a  few of those that sort of thing and just go on and on <pause dur="short"/> you watch Emmerdale don't you?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0152">I do yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I don't go back and watch what I've recorded</u>
<u n="776" who="S0013">Don't you?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0152">there's lots of stuff I record and don't go back and watch <pause dur="short"/> it's like</u>
<u n="778" who="S0013">you can get rid of them eventually</u>
<u n="779" who="S0152">yeah I mean like this morning I had a sift through Match of the Day <pause dur="short"/> I just wanted the <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't bother me now to watch Match of the Day in the sense of sit there for an hour and thirty minutes whatever it is <pause dur="short"/> cos they <trunc>ne</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> it's the <trunc>sa</trunc> it's the same in same out <pause dur="short"/> if Bolton and Blackburn yesterday hadn't have been such a high profile game because of what had happened they wouldn't have been put on first</u>
<u n="780" who="S0013">they wouldn't have been put on first no way <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> you know what games are going to be put on first</u>
<u n="782" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> manchester United Manchester City Chelsea and Arsenal</u>
<u n="783" who="S0152">yeah you know</u>
<u n="784" who="S0013">Tottenham and Arsenal</u>
<u n="785" who="S0152">see Arsenal were quite far down in the pecking order because they were <trunc>wi</trunc> against Villa and Villa well Arsenal got seven games on the run yesterday</u>
<u n="786" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0152">but <pause dur="short"/> no it's it's too heavy <pause dur="short"/> have you seen John Watson's interview with Brian Clough from about forty years ago?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0013">ooh that was a long while ago yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0152">yeah have a look at it <pause dur="short"/> it is really <trunc>int</trunc> it's really interesting with what he was saying <pause dur="short"/> he was saying down the lines of Match of the Day and this is like forty years ago <pause dur="short"/> he says you come in this is Match of the Day <pause dur="short"/> you pick a game that you're going to go and televise so it's Match of the Day <pause dur="short"/> it's a nil nil draw and you slate it <pause dur="short"/> why? Because you're saying it's Match of the Day? And it's interesting what it was saying it was saying there is too much football <pause dur="short"/> forty years ago there is too much football or there's too many people discussing about football that have no idea about it</u>
<u n="790" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="791" who="S0152">you know you can go forty years on this is still the same</u>
<u n="792" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember we used to  we used to  go cos they used to have Match of the Day and that used to just be division one and then <pause dur="short"/> and there'd be division two and there'd be</u>
<u n="793" who="S0152">I don't think there was any any division one</u>
<u n="794" who="S0013">was it? But we were</u>
<u n="795" who="S0152">FA cup games</u>
<u n="796" who="S0013">when we used to go there used to be a camera one camera at Norwich the <unclear/> and we used to say cor Match of the Day is here Match of the Day is here you know <pause dur="short"/> but they didn't have any facilities at all for the commentary box or anything <pause dur="short"/> they had no facilities at all <pause dur="short"/> and then when that used to come on cos you used to rush home and watch Match of the Day and know who'd won and things <pause dur="short"/> and if the wind had been blowing the <unclear/> had been going like this and the and all you could do was watch this sway about like you were on the sea <pause dur="short"/> and they used to come and take from a tent type thing</u>
<u n="797" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> amazing how it's moved</u>
<u n="798" who="S0013">now they have cameras all over the place and even cameras on individual players</u>
<u n="799" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0013">so that if they do foul anybody they can pick it up straight away and show you the leg <unclear/> sliding in</u>
<u n="801" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0013">pretty good innit?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the quality of the pictures now compared to what you used to get <pause dur="short"/> you used to think it was brilliant <pause dur="short"/> but the quality now</u>
<u n="804" who="S0013">it's fantastic yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's all all changed</u>
<u n="806" who="S0013">it has changed <pause dur="short"/> changed a lot hasn't it?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0152">well I <pause dur="short"/> you see with <pause dur="short"/> alright Sky  were the big changers in the way they do their sport and they do every which which is good which is what it needed <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> you you watch <pause dur="short"/> but you you Match of the Day always had the first  always had the first  division games <pause dur="short"/> and you had the one on a Sunday afternoon</u>
<u n="808" who="S0013">yeah that's right you did</u>
<u n="809" who="S0152">which was normally the same game that was on Saturday night</u>
<u n="810" who="S0013">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0152">because they shared the</u>
<u n="812" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0152">the rights</u>
<u n="814" who="S0013">they did <pause dur="short"/> and the BBC used to only have the FA cup fail didn't they? That went to BBC and ITV this year</u>
<u n="815" who="S0152">yeah but they put it on at the same time on both channels</u>
<u n="816" who="S0013">yeah yeah they did</u>
<u n="817" who="S0152">but now you it's either BBC and <trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="818" who="S0013">suddenly ITV got</u>
<u n="819" who="S0152">ITV have got the rights now and E P S EPSN <pause dur="short"/> ePSN <pause dur="short"/> at the moment</u>
<u n="820" who="S0013">and that one was encrypted and you can't get it on</u>
<u n="821" who="S0152">no you've got to buy it</u>
<u n="822" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's lucky ITV have got it</u>
<u n="823" who="S0152">yeah I think they've I think after that England game a few years ago where you couldn't get it unless you were  But it wasn't EPSN and it wasn't it was that strange channel that went bankrupt</u>
<u n="824" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was like something like Santander or something <pause dur="short"/> but that was</u>
<u n="825" who="S0152">it was yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0013">that was a sort of a weird</u>
<u n="827" who="S0152">sandana</u>
<u n="828" who="S0013">sandana <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0152">something like that</u>
<u n="830" who="S0013">something like that wasn't it? Yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0152">but you eh <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't get it and not everybody had that access to it</u>
<u n="832" who="S0013">no so <pause dur="short"/> and they they had to pay ten pound didn't they?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so the government said no <pause dur="short"/> english games have to be on certain channels <pause dur="short"/> the then you know the ones that are important have to be on at a certain time <pause dur="short"/> but see ESPN is owned by Disney</u>
<u n="834" who="S0013">is it? Oh right</u>
<u n="835" who="S0152">but they've got a big thing in America you see so</u>
<u n="836" who="S0013">once once when when we first got a television in there we could get EPSN <pause dur="short"/> although it's encrypted <pause dur="short"/> and that came on one day and I thought what?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0152">oh they do free days sometimes</u>
<u n="838" who="S0013">they do free days?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0152">and and that was</u>
<u n="840" who="S0013">it was a football match</u>
<u n="841" who="S0152">yeah they do <trunc>fo</trunc> every so often <pause dur="short"/> yeah every so often they'll do free weekends where you can watch it</u>
<u n="842" who="S0013">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh I didn't know that</u>
<u n="843" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0013">I thought oh look <pause dur="short"/> somehow we've got it without it being encrypted</u>
<u n="845" who="S0152">no you have a free weekend where they'll put things on</u>
<u n="846" who="S0013">plus you can get some of these cards from Europe nowadays that you can stick in your  in your  or you can have it updated and they're they're free <pause dur="short"/> because I some somewhere along the line these pubs can get it <unclear/> and they they're not quite free they pay pay a bit of money but then they didn't want Sky didn't want to allow it in this country did they?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> you you pull you pull the feed from another  from another  country somehow</u>
<u n="848" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0152">but they they they overruled that and these pubs can get whatever they like now can't they? Did you find it?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> I've asked them to let us know by email</u>
<u n="851" who="S0013">have you?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0152">what of any properties coming up</u>
<u n="854" who="S0012">any properties in this area</u>
<u n="855" who="S0013">he probably plans to put it up himself</u>
<u n="856" who="S0152">no they're proper boards</u>
<u n="857" who="S0013">are they?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0152">if they've only gone up over the weekend</u>
<u n="859" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="860" who="S0152">then it the details will be going on the web probably over the next few days</u>
<u n="861" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="862" who="S0013">well I suppose we get what for the for that lot about half a million pound and then retire <pause dur="short"/> cos he's made a lovely job of it</u>
<u n="863" who="S0012" trans="overlap">but this one I <trunc>lo</trunc> I looked up because it had just <trunc>ha</trunc> got the picture of the land and I thought oh no they might cut down you know half an acre</u>
<u n="864" who="S0013">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0012">but it wasn't  enough</u>
<u n="866" who="S0013">well they can't carry on down that eh <pause dur="short"/> well he's got to do his cows and stuff hasn't he? Or hasn't he got another <unclear/></u>
<u n="867" who="S0012">not necessarily <pause dur="short"/> don't <pause dur="short"/> pack it all up and</u>
<u n="868" who="S0013" trans="overlap">he's got all that stuff down there</u>
<u n="869" who="S0012">sell it as <unclear/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="short"/> we shall see</u>
<u n="872" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="873" who="S0013"><unclear/> If he sold that as the common <unclear/> we want the other two that live you know the other two places <pause dur="short"/> who would want it? With all that work going on and and the traffic going through his bit of land <pause dur="short"/> got to want all them tractors and everything</u>
<u n="874" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well he would just move out wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0013">he'll move out but who would want to live here while he's not using it?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="877" who="S0013">I wouldn't want to live there</u>
<u n="878" who="S0012">well but he he wouldn't be using it would he if he moves out?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0013">well who's going to use the bit of land then?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0152">the people who buy the</u>
<u n="881" who="S0012">the people who buy it</u>
<u n="882" who="S0013">yeah but he people in the middle of those cottages have still got to live there with all that <unclear/> still that might better</u>
<u n="883" who="S0012">it was for rent</u>
<u n="884" who="S0013">yeah it was for rent <pause dur="short"/> is he going to keep them? Or is he going to live in the one storey? Because they also foster a lot of children don't they?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0012">well you can't just guess can you?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0013">no you can't guess</u>
<u n="887" who="S0152">this stuff will be it'll be on there soon won't it so <pause dur="short"/> it will be on there soon</u>
<u n="888" who="S0012">quite interesting isn't it?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0013">we'll have to give everyone a phone <pause dur="short"/> see what's going on <pause dur="short"/> in the grapevine it'll be going round everybody will be going <unclear/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0152">see if you had twitter you could be tweeting it <pause dur="short"/> what's going on at</u>
<u n="893" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No I don't want to do that</u>
<u n="894" who="S0012">Don't want anyone to know we're interested</u>
<u n="895" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="896" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="898" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0152">right so</u>
<u n="900" who="S0012">would you like a bit of lunch with us?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0152">no I'm I'm going to go and get this sorted <pause dur="short"/> blitz his bedroom and get move some stuff around</u>
<u n="902" who="S0013">I'd hate to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s face when she goes back in there and all her stuff is gone</u>
<u n="903" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well you could take it <unclear/></u>
<u n="904" who="S0152">she no <pause dur="short"/> she said it's alright <pause dur="short"/> I said to her I said do you want me to get rid of this big <pause dur="short"/> there's that big pine Ottoman type thing in there <pause dur="short"/> I said do you want me to get rid of that she said yes please <pause dur="short"/> I said what about all the things inside it which is your dressing up costumes? Don't want them <pause dur="short"/> cos she can't get into them anymore so</u>
<u n="905" who="S0013">no that's true <pause dur="short"/> and you've got to give it away <pause dur="short"/> have you got one of those bags?</u>
<u n="906" who="S0152">no we've got a charity bag I can put all those in or whatever</u>
<u n="907" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they don't come an collect them very often do they? The charity bags</u>
<u n="908" who="S0152">if they if you put them out on the day they say</u>
<u n="909" who="S0013">it's the way they're <unclear/></u>
<u n="910" who="S0012">we did  We did  it once</u>
<u n="911" who="S0013">we did it once and it laid there for weeks</u>
<u n="912" who="S0012">got rained on and</u>
<u n="913" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I phoned up the council</u>
<u n="914" who="S0012">we had to put in the bin in the end</u>
<u n="915" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they wrecked my bin</u>
<u n="916" who="S0013">they broke your bin?</u>
<u n="917" who="S0152">they broke my black bin <pause dur="short"/> the dustman <pause dur="short"/> the other week</u>
<u n="918" who="S0013">did they?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0152">Brook <pause dur="short"/> shattered the lid in half</u>
<u n="920" who="S0013">did they?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0152">so why they didn't report they'd broke the lid themselves to get me a new bin <pause dur="short"/> so I phoned them up on Wednesday last week and said my lid my bin lid's been broken by people who are collecting the rubbish <pause dur="short"/> and usually they're quiet quick</u>
<u n="922" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0152">but they haven't come round yet so</u>
<u n="924" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> cos if you break the bin that's forty-five quid</u>
<u n="925" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="926" who="S0013">and they didn't report it they didn't?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="928" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="929" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="930" who="S0013">I just imagine those <pause dur="short"/> I mean plastic does deteriorate doesn't it?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0152">in sunlight it will</u>
<u n="932" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0152">and if it keeps fall if it gets blown over when it opens and closes and it</u>
<u n="934" who="S0013">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="935" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="936" who="S0013">well there we go</u>
<u n="937" who="S0152">so I'm going to do that <pause dur="short"/> and then eh <pause dur="short"/> I think it might take me a good three hours</u>
<u n="938" who="S0013">three hours to do it eh <pause dur="short"/> god <pause dur="short"/> that's a long time</u>
</body>
</text>
