<text id="S9E6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:12:40</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-03-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0380</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>computers, internet, university, exams, Japan, Tokyo, travel plans, plans for the future, restaurants</topics>
		<activity>Two friends catching up after quite a long time in a different friend’s apartment </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0380">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Jamaica</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Turkish</l2>
				<fls>Kurdish -- level unspecified; German -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0380">I'm not actually obsessed I just don't know like I think I'm just obsessive in general</u>
<u n="2" who="S0326">yeah but I it's like not I don't know if it's like healthy to like sit on the computer like to read like</u>
<u n="3" who="S0380">I don't sit on the computer all day</u>
<u n="4" who="S0326">I know but like looking at stuff like vicariously</u>
<u n="5" who="S0380">yeah I actually yeah I kind of do spend more time on the computer than I do reading actual books it just gets really fucking annoying like this feeling of just like having all these tabs and just like</u>
<u n="6" who="S0326">yeah and you know there's these studies that you can't erm receive or <trunc>proc</trunc> like retain information as well if it's on a screen as it is on paper</u>
<u n="7" who="S0380">yeah probably</u>
<u n="8" who="S0326">even like typing and writing is different</u>
<u n="9" who="S0380">I don't know if keeping information is my goal</u>
<u n="10" who="S0326">no but even sort of like processing it understanding it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0380">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="12" who="S0326">I can't like I can't really I can't remember like I don't I really think about <trunc>try</trunc> like learning things from Wikipedia and I don't think I do I just know it for like a second</u>
<u n="13" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0326">and I kind of think yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0380">I don't know I feel like I actually learn stuff from Wikipedia I don't know what but maybe it's cos I've never learnt anything before so like that's the only thing I've half-learned I don't know oh my god yesterday was so annoying</u>
<u n="16" who="S0326">why?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0380">cos I went to them and like they made me do this test on some fucking website like prospects dot AC dot UK or something</u>
<u n="18" who="S0326">like what you do in <anon type="place"/> on like the careers day?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0326">and it tells you to be a makeup artist</u>
<u n="21" who="S0380">yeah no it didn't say makeup artist</u>
<u n="22" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but it's that kind of stuff right?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0380">yeah and like it was all these questions and I answered them and stuff and then they're like the <pause dur="short"/> like outcome was like advertising or like magazine editor or like management consultant and shit like that</u>
<u n="24" who="S0326">yeah but what did you think it was going to say? poet?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0380">yeah I know I know but like I didn't yeah but yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0326">it was gonna say a real job</u>
<u n="27" who="S0380">yeah I'd rather it it also said like public affairs consultant I don't know what the fuck that is it's like a lobbyist I didn't know what that is either</u>
<u n="28" who="S0326">probably yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0380">I don't know what the fuck the things are like and then they just kept on telling me like to do that and like I don't know</u>
<u n="30" who="S0326">that's the thing I was talking about this article and I said you know like I've got this friend who's doing like babysitting stuff and she babysits these kids who go to a private school and they're in <trunc>yea</trunc> and they're in year two and they had a end of term like fun day like dress up day but you had to dress up as the job you wanted to be when you're older so you like dress up as like</u>
<u n="31" who="S0380">in year two? lol</u>
<u n="32" who="S0326">yeah you like dress up as a doctor or whatever but it's like really it's like teaching people to have these ambitions which are not really like</u>
<u n="33" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0326">and like people who don't have them feel anxious about them it's like</u>
<u n="35" who="S0380">I was always obsessed with being famous I like wanna be Shakira</u>
<u n="36" who="S0326">but I don't think you really would like cos otherwise you like would've like been like putting I guess you did put yourself on YouTube</u>
<u n="37" who="S0380">yeah but</u>
<u n="38" who="S0326">what was that stuff you had on YouTube?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0380">I had so much shit on YouTube</u>
<u n="40" who="S0326">yeah but I remember like I <trunc>so</trunc> showing that teacher in school Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0380">oh shit I remember that</u>
<u n="42" who="S0326">and I was like have you seen it? he's like yeah it's disgusting</u>
<u n="43" who="S0380">he said that? he's a fucking</u>
<u n="44" who="S0326">I know I was like what's wrong with you?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0380">he's disgusting himself though like some short little sweaty Italian man you seriously plus he used to perv on people like drop pencils underneath the tables just to look up girls' skirts and shit</u>
<u n="46" who="S0326">yeah obviously then he went out with Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0380">no</u>
<u n="48" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0380">oh that's so cute</u>
<u n="50" who="S0326">what's that?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0380">in like Austria or something</u>
<u n="52" who="S0326">looks cold</u>
<u n="53" who="S0380">it's cold here too</u>
<u n="54" who="S0326">yeah I know</u>
<u n="55" who="S0380">erm how was that yeah <unclear/> like I don't know when I think about it I would just rather even have like a stall in <anon type="place"/> market or something selling like <unclear/> I don't know</u>
<u n="56" who="S0326">have you got what does your what does your dad do again?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0380">he has a caff now?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0326">yeah why don't you like work in a caff</u>
<u n="59" who="S0380">no I would smell like oil bad I don't know but even that like I used to like look down on that now I'm just like okay maybe it's like a bit better than like being someone else's bitch</u>
<u n="60" who="S0326">yeah I think definitely</u>
<u n="61" who="S0380">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0326">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to Istanbul</u>
<u n="63" who="S0380">really? oh that's so cute</u>
<u n="64" who="S0326">for like two days</u>
<u n="65" who="S0380">why did she have her pictures did she?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0326">I don't know to follow on Instagram</u>
<u n="67" who="S0380">she would have like so many like good photo ops there especially with her like aesthetics</u>
<u n="68" who="S0326">I think she put like a few on Instagram</u>
<u n="69" who="S0380">let me find it Instagram <unclear/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0326">her <unclear>hand off the heart</unclear></u>
<u n="71" who="S0380">yeah I stalk everyone okay it's so depressing I always try to get it but I have no followers I'm just like fuck this I feel like</u>
<u n="72" who="S0326">yeah but you I don't have any followers</u>
<u n="73" who="S0380">yeah but your ratio is better than what my what other <trunc>peo</trunc></u>
<u n="74" who="S0326">it really doesn't matter</u>
<u n="75" who="S0380">I get really like cos it's like because I'm like I don't have any other like social media kind of thing and like I'm just new to it and like I'm just like really focused on the numbers itself and look it's just like</u>
<u n="76" who="S0326">well you can do it when it isn't even on the <unclear>see you</unclear> like if you're funny and you'll just get a random following you</u>
<u n="77" who="S0380">yeah I don't try to be funny though</u>
<u n="78" who="S0326">or interesting or you can take really nice photos of sunsets <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0380">she doesn't have any did you see the eclipse? you didn't right?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0326">no it was cloudy</u>
<u n="81" who="S0380">my friend saw it in Latvia</u>
<u n="82" who="S0326">yeah cos it wasn't cloudy in Latvia</u>
<u n="83" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I <unclear/> <anon type="place"/> Istanbul</u>
<u n="85" who="S0380">the <anon type="place"/> in Istanbul</u>
<u n="86" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/> yeah they put them everywhere</u>
<u n="87" who="S0380">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="88" who="S0326">she went to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lol</u>
<u n="89" who="S0380">lol oh my god you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that posh boy? he was like this really funny guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have you heard of him? I was like yeah my flatmate lived with him or something I don't know what he was saying</u>
<u n="90" who="S0326">embarrassing</u>
<u n="91" who="S0380">yeah I can't help but get worse than me because they don't <unclear/> awful yeah I think you should message <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> every day</u>
<u n="92" who="S0326">I am</u>
<u n="93" who="S0380">she said she's in she's on <trunc>cr</trunc> how do you say it in crutches</u>
<u n="94" who="S0326">on crutches</u>
<u n="95" who="S0380">cos I was like</u>
<u n="96" who="S0326">I think she's <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0380"><trunc>dis</trunc> you're going to be fucking on crutches as well be careful</u>
<u n="98" who="S0326">cos she always like dislocates herself but doesn't really</u>
<u n="99" who="S0380" trans="overlap">yeah she's not pretending dude</u>
<u n="100" who="S0326">I know but she used to</u>
<u n="101" who="S0380">no come on</u>
<u n="102" who="S0326">well I never I you <trunc>mu</trunc> you should have heard some of the stuff I've heard <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say</u>
<u n="103" who="S0380">she's a performance artist wait what?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0326">I can't even remember but at the time I was just like lol</u>
<u n="105" who="S0380">I remember like</u>
<u n="106" who="S0326">he's like <trunc>li</trunc> he's like she's telling me when she like lived used to live in Dubai and like</u>
<u n="107" who="S0380">ah I thought like the worst is like oh I'm going to go to New York next week and stuff like that she used to live in Dubai?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0326">no she <unclear/> successful she is really</u>
<u n="109" who="S0380">that's mean though</u>
<u n="110" who="S0326">it's not well it's not I'm not being mean</u>
<u n="111" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0326">but it's <trunc>sh</trunc> I it's weird though because she would tell that she <trunc>wo</trunc> I'm taking her to a party in <trunc>Gre</trunc> in Devon and like</u>
<u n="113" who="S0380">in where?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0326">Devon</u>
<u n="115" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0326">like a family party thing and like it's sort of totally fucked like you can say that stuff like to people who like you don't know and whatever but it's really awkward for me and I'm like sitting next to her and she's saying it do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0326">like what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0380">yeah you just have to go along with it I guess</u>
<u n="120" who="S0326">I know obviously I do yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0326">it makes you feel weird</u>
<u n="123" who="S0380">like some people just have that impulse I guess I think</u>
<u n="124" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah but it's quite yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0380">everyone's kind of well I used to be like that in primary school</u>
<u n="126" who="S0326">yeah everyone says that in primary school they're like</u>
<u n="127" who="S0380">yeah but</u>
<u n="128" who="S0326">this one time like yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0380">I yeah but I guess it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's like constant one-up one-upmanship but like you soon grow out of it</u>
<u n="131" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0326">or not you know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0380">yeah I think she's in her like first year of college now I think right? She was like do you want to go to a twenty-four hour library with me? I was like where? and she was like <anon type="place"/> or something near <anon type="place"/> and she just spelt it <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> funny erm yeah that's well scary though twenty-four hours in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0326">isn't your library twenty-four hours?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0380">no are you fucking <unclear/> nobody stays in the library like ever nobody does anything seriously it closes at like nine and it opens at like ten</u>
<u n="136" who="S0326">it's not bad</u>
<u n="137" who="S0380"><unclear/> twenty-four hours <unclear/> the closest I have is</u>
<u n="138" who="S0326"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0380">no the closest I have is <anon type="place"/> which is like open until eleven</u>
<u n="140" who="S0326">all the libraries all the college libraries are twenty-four hours there's like one where you can see it's like on the outside of the like public can see the windows and stuff it's like by the river like when you go over the bridge you can see the library you go over the bridge at like three AM it's just like full</u>
<u n="141" who="S0380">lol do you like it a bit more now?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="143" who="S0380">do you hate it a lot more?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0326">well I don't really I <trunc>ju</trunc> I don't really like I'm a bit ambivalent</u>
<u n="145" who="S0380">I remember you told me before you went that you could spend your third year in <anon type="place"/> or something?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0326">I could if I wanted to I know people who have done that but I can't</u>
<u n="147" who="S0380">why can't you?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0326">cos like to be honest I don't want to do that because</u>
<u n="149" who="S0380">you just want to finish it there</u>
<u n="150" who="S0326">yeah it's better I get better teachers and stuff and more attention</u>
<u n="151" who="S0380">yeah I wish I got more attention that's all I want</u>
<u n="152" who="S0326">but I don't go you once said that you went to coffee with your teachers and stuff</u>
<u n="153" who="S0380">yeah true</u>
<u n="154" who="S0326">I don't do that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0380">yeah are you jealous?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0326">no but like you must get quite a lot of attention cos there are only like sixty people on the course</u>
<u n="157" who="S0380" trans="overlap">yeah I do get attention yeah yeah but like yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="158" who="S0326">have you stayed the night here yet?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0380">no but I hang out here all the time even all my friends like yeah she's still nice she like if it wasn't for her I would have like failed last year because I couldn't find the exam hall and like she like came out like the exam had started already and she like ran out and like <trunc>four</trunc>found me cos it was this like place where city map basically led me to like underneath the bridge and this thing was like on top of the bridge I was like what the fuck? but yeah she's really nice</u>
<u n="160" who="S0326">do you have exams again?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0326">man I looked at my papers they're so hard</u>
<u n="163" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0326">it's like what?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0380">mm I think you sent me like a question that was like fucked up or something I feel like that must be fun like thinking of like how you're going to like fuck them up this year</u>
<u n="166" who="S0326">oh my days like classics paper's fine some of like the like ones there was like a practical criticism question on the English paper poem that had no words it was just punctuation</u>
<u n="167" who="S0380">no why? that's funny</u>
<u n="168" who="S0326">I know but it's like now write about that for an hour you like clever like smart-arses</u>
<u n="169" who="S0380">oh my god you can't do that for an actual exam maybe like a <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0326">they do that they do that in the exam</u>
<u n="171" who="S0380">how like?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0326">let's just do the best and that's like totally sort of arbitrary whether the examiner thinks like it's good or not</u>
<u n="173" who="S0380">I guess like if they studied something</u>
<u n="174" who="S0326">but that's the thing cos people were annoyed cos they didn't study it for it</u>
<u n="175" who="S0380">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0326">it is a kind of like you spend so long like revising and working and they do something</u>
<u n="177" who="S0380">yeah you can kind of link anything to anything though I think this year I'm going to have a question which is like just one word everyone gets that for like one of their things so it'll be like chance or something and you just have to go lol yeah well is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still doing art history?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0380">I was thinking maybe I'll do like an MFA in like actual art but it sounds fucking scary like you have to do like have a portfolio and shit</u>
<u n="180" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0380">don't know why probably go on Tumblr and like copy and paste shit onto a</u>
<u n="182" who="S0326">yeah it's not so easy though <unclear/> on businesses</u>
<u n="183" who="S0380">do you think so?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0326">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0380">but it it does sound quite competitive to cos like if you're coming from like</u>
<u n="186" who="S0326">well it depends where do you want to do it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0380">somewhere good if it's not somewhere good then I won't do it I don't know like <anon type="place"/> maybe <anon type="place"/> no erm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0326">but if you <unclear/> then you've got to be like technically good</u>
<u n="189" who="S0380">yeah I know I'm just like thinking</u>
<u n="190" who="S0326">just like start practising drawing</u>
<u n="191" who="S0380">yeah I don't think I could do that shit I don't know</u>
<u n="192" who="S0326">quite cool I think it would fun to go to do like art school thing afterwards but</u>
<u n="193" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0380">I think yeah it is a lot about like technical I don't know</u>
<u n="196" who="S0326">but I remember doing I'm like I can <unclear/> school in <anon type="place"/> like a bit of painting and stuff</u>
<u n="197" who="S0380">yeah yeah I remember that baby you made</u>
<u n="198" who="S0326">I still have that</u>
<u n="199" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0326">it's facing the wall in my bedroom</u>
<u n="201" who="S0380">lol what happened did you win like a Saatchi prize or something?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="204" who="S0326">it's on the Saatchi website</u>
<u n="205" who="S0380">lol yeah I feel like a lot of people will be doing like MFA</u>
<u n="206" who="S0326">I'll just put that in my thing</u>
<u n="207" who="S0380">yeah a lot of people who do these like who have these technical skills they like use them for like graphic design to like</u>
<u n="208" who="S0326">yeah they go and like work for Pixar and stuff</u>
<u n="209" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0326">which would be fun actually</u>
<u n="211" who="S0380">I used to want to do that when I was little too</u>
<u n="212" who="S0326">any lights?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0380">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I don't know where the toilet paper is</u>
<u n="214" who="S0326">you have to go buy some</u>
<u n="215" who="S0380">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> you want the fruit?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0326">yeah sure</u>
<u n="217" who="S0380">do you want apples or plums? or there's just some dusty apple</u>
<u n="218" who="S0326">did you put it in the bin?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0380">it was like old people's skin</u>
<u n="220" who="S0326">what's that plum?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0380">yeah but it's also wait this one's better kinda this is a better apple if you want she was telling me to like eat everything because it's all going to go bad</u>
<u n="222" who="S0326">this is a bit bad but it's alright what's that?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0380">I don't know if I can eat it</u>
<u n="224" who="S0326">why not?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0380"><vocal desc="cough"/> think she got it from Belgium or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0380">my throat's so bad ah can't even fucking go yoga today cos I'm so tired <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0326">can I eat the humus?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0380">yeah probably you can eat anything actually oh this is where it is piece of shit</u>
<u n="229" who="S0326">what's that?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0380">like <unclear/> throat things oh my god I was speaking about Whole Foods in one of my essays the question was you are what you eat</u>
<u n="231" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0380">er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0326">you still go to Whole Foods a lot</u>
<u n="234" who="S0380">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0380">I don't <unclear/> though I wish I did today though but yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0326">where's the one that's near here?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0380">erm <unclear/> Organic is right near here but the Whole Foods that's closest is <anon type="place"/> which is the one that I got arrested at lol</u>
<u n="238" who="S0326">didn't the guy say to you you're an immigrant like me?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0380">no he was like I put you down as one P because you're erm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0326">as one what?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0380">one P or something which is white male because erm I'm Bulgarian you're Turkish I'm not making any racial things or something I was like okay</u>
<u n="242" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0380">I didn't know what he was saying but you know</u>
<u n="244" who="S0326">that is weird</u>
<u n="245" who="S0380">yeah you don't know where to put it</u>
<u n="246" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="247" who="S0380">here you are let's keep it out erm yeah what are you doing tonight?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0326">erm I don't know might I'm going to meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually I haven't seen her for ages</u>
<u n="249" who="S0380">who?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0380"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0380">you haven't seen her in ages</u>
<u n="254" who="S0326">well no I have I have but I haven't seen her since like properly since two days ago</u>
<u n="255" who="S0380">yeah I think it's probably good where's that bread?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0326">I'll just eat it with a spoon</u>
<u n="257" who="S0380">ah lol</u>
<u n="258" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0380">what is that?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0326">what's what there?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0326">gherkin</u>
<u n="263" who="S0380">oh</u>
<u n="264" who="S0326">porridge I hate porridge <pause dur="long"/> raisins</u>
<u n="265" who="S0380">yeah where is the spoon kept? oh here it is</u>
<u n="266" who="S0326">Space N Space NK</u>
<u n="267" who="S0380">I thought you were going to say space cake is your phone charged?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0326">fifty</u>
<u n="269" who="S0380">let's out some more</u>
<u n="270" who="S0326">yeah so look at this phone it's bent</u>
<u n="271" who="S0380">did you did that on purpose?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0326">no I it's not even its <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s phone cos I had that other one remember</u>
<u n="273" who="S0380">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0326">I had a plastic one</u>
<u n="275" who="S0380">oh shit what happened to that?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0326">it's just it's like a bit crap and like it didn't tell the time anymore</u>
<u n="277" who="S0380">oh I actually thought that you were going to stick with that phone for a while</u>
<u n="278" who="S0326">everybody else had it</u>
<u n="279" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0326">it was the only it was the only Iphone five they make now like everyone like all my friends in <anon type="place"/> have got it</u>
<u n="281" who="S0380">so?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0326">it's too confusing man</u>
<u n="283" who="S0380">do you even have friends in <anon type="place"/>? what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0380">you do?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0326">that's not the real reason obviously lol but that's much better I'd much rather have a smashed up that one that tells the time</u>
<u n="287" who="S0380">cos then you don't have to be scared about smashing it up</u>
<u n="288" who="S0326">mm I might get it fixed as well you know?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0380">mm is this a new one then?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0326">I took it to the <anon type="place"/> and I was like can you fix it? he just laughed at me</u>
<u n="291" who="S0380">lol I'm sure one of them will</u>
<u n="292" who="S0326">nah he unlocked it for me and was like I can't fix that it's bent</u>
<u n="293" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="294" who="S0326">now from like two the guys are like oi where did you get your phone?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0380">lol let me see that? isn't bent like slang for gay or something?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0326">mm yeah kind of</u>
<u n="297" who="S0380"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0326">cos there's so people are like there's so many posters of Audrey Hepburn</u>
<u n="299" who="S0380">yeah I think this was the</u>
<u n="300" who="S0326" trans="overlap">like everyone everyone has one</u>
<u n="301" who="S0380">yeah I know there's like one that everyone like the exact one that everyone has like the one of the like cigarette thing whatever it's called <pause dur="short"/> wow I can't believe I forgot the name for that thing</u>
<u n="302" who="S0326">what? cigarette holder?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0380">oh okay I thought it had like a isn't there like a weird word for it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0326">maybe I don't know it though</u>
<u n="305" who="S0380">I'm so happy I'm a different person now</u>
<u n="306" who="S0326">happy birthday mate</u>
<u n="307" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="308" who="S0326">what did you do for your birthday?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0380">I went to some disgusting but expensive restaurant</u>
<u n="310" who="S0326">where?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0380">I'm not telling you</u>
<u n="312" who="S0326">not telling me tell me</u>
<u n="313" who="S0380">I can't remember what it was but like it was called like <anon type="place"/> or something and the website is really cute ha erm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows a lot about restaurants you should have asked which ones are good</u>
<u n="315" who="S0380">yeah I fucking love like going but yeah I love it but then I hate it too</u>
<u n="316" who="S0326">there's a good one sort of near or near here it's called the <anon type="place"/> or something on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0380">smoking</u>
<u n="318" who="S0326">it's nice not that expensive either</u>
<u n="319" who="S0380">yeah I feel like a lot of like expensive restaurants are not even that good</u>
<u n="320" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0380">because they just like they have to use like ingredients which are like kind of expensive like they just throw like truffle oil on everything and shit</u>
<u n="322" who="S0326">yeah like like</u>
<u n="323" who="S0380">which isn't even real truffle oil it's like probably has like meat <unclear/> or some shit</u>
<u n="324" who="S0326">that's what they do at like that <anon type="place"/> and stuff</u>
<u n="325" who="S0380">oh my god have you been there? lol</u>
<u n="326" who="S0326">no but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling me she went she has like this fan who's like Kuwait Kuwaiti like and really like rich and he's like <trunc>l</trunc> obsessed with her he's like really gay obviously</u>
<u n="327" who="S0380"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="328" who="S0326">and he took her there</u>
<u n="329" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="330" who="S0326">and but she had one of the most embarrassing dinners of her life cos like halfway through he started choking and he just kind of like vomited into his plate <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0380">what?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and like I met her afterwards and she had just had to get like totally <trunc>sh</trunc>shit hammered cos <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0380">that is so embarrassing especially with like the clientele there like you never know who is</u>
<u n="334" who="S0326">yeah she's like friends with the chef some guy apparently he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0380">okay</u>
<u n="336" who="S0326">and like so he was like sending out all this like really special stuff and the guy just like vomits it up on the plate <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0380">that's so embarrassing <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0326">yeah I know I think it was pretty bad</u>
<u n="339" who="S0380">so is he speaking to her still?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0326">I don't know</u>
<u n="341" who="S0380">I hate the way embarrassing stuff affects me so badly but yeah like cos <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> lol</u>
<u n="342" who="S0326">have you been there?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0380">no I don't know all those places are kinda like the same</u>
<u n="344" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0380">like but that's the like whole point I guess</u>
<u n="346" who="S0326">the restaurants we went to in Paris were like fancy</u>
<u n="347" who="S0380">really? were they good though?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0326">like they're not actually they weren't fancy they were just good you know? like there was one really funny one that's like</u>
<u n="349" who="S0380">you can't ever like finish everything though</u>
<u n="350" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0380">with French food cos</u>
<u n="352" who="S0326">well and also like erm whenever I go with this guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is always like tasting menus</u>
<u n="353" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0326">or whatever it's like twenty-eight courses it's like all the food on the whole menu</u>
<u n="355" who="S0380">there's a book that you should read it's written by like TJ Clark on like the like the weird <trunc>phenon</trunc>phenomenon or whatever it's it's called of being a food critic and like how it's just like the weirdest job in terms of like social class relations I don't know what the fuck he's the argument is but they have it I haven't read it</u>
<u n="356" who="S0326">I want to I actually I had loads of fun doing that</u>
<u n="357" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0326">I think like I might message like restaurants in Tokyo but I don't think they all know English</u>
<u n="359" who="S0326">they might it's worth trying</u>
<u n="360" who="S0380">yeah but like in Tokyo like</u>
<u n="361" who="S0326">didn't don't you have do you not have an email anymore for that?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0380">no she still she speaks to me so I could just get her again but yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0326">I have written like the most popular review I write I wrote I wrote the only review that was ever read on that site</u>
<u n="364" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0326">cos the guy shared it</u>
<u n="366" who="S0380">lol but I feel like with like Tokyo those people like would they even know if it's like popular or not? like they won't be able to tell</u>
<u n="367" who="S0326">no one knows like that's the thing</u>
<u n="368" who="S0380">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="369" who="S0326"><unclear/> sound like it is</u>
<u n="370" who="S0380">yeah it's just so dull yeah she keeps like it's sad because like she has no friends and like she keeps like trying to go out and stuff even though I don't have many friends either but</u>
<u n="371" who="S0326">she's trying to go out with you</u>
<u n="372" who="S0380">yeah and I'm just like I would go out but I just don't want to wear a suit</u>
<u n="373" who="S0326">you have to wear a suit</u>
<u n="374" who="S0380">to go to the <trunc>sa</trunc> like same kind of places</u>
<u n="375" who="S0326">you don't have to</u>
<u n="376" who="S0380">you do <pause dur="short"/> unless I wear like a sheikh costume <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0380">that's the only other alternative for me</u>
<u n="378" who="S0326">well yeah I guess but why why you could say oh well I'm not I don't mind going out with you but I'm not wearing a suit</u>
<u n="379" who="S0380">it's not up to her</u>
<u n="380" who="S0326">yeah I know but like just go somewhere else instead of like</u>
<u n="381" who="S0380">lol it's like everywhere that like is worth going for her is like that but yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0326">what even Café Rouge?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0380">no I didn't mean like that I mean like going out going out</u>
<u n="384" who="S0326">oh like clubs</u>
<u n="385" who="S0380">yeah that's what I mean yeah I know</u>
<u n="386" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no trainers</u>
<u n="387" who="S0380">yeah it's meant to be like I was on like fucking like websites looking for like suits and shit tailored for me so I could like get a real job and shit like I can't believe I was doing that it's such a like</u>
<u n="388" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0380">freedom for what you wear is important</u>
<u n="390" who="S0326">that was one of the fun things about fashion you could <unclear/> have a party at some places like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0380">oh yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0326">and it had normal people there too but like you were allowed to go in just like wearing whatever</u>
<u n="393" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0326">you could like be like in your like ripped jeans and dirty hair</u>
<u n="395" who="S0380">yeah lol</u>
<u n="396" who="S0326">everyone's like really shocked</u>
<u n="397" who="S0380">I'm still at uni man</u>
<u n="398" who="S0326">you're nearly done though</u>
<u n="399" who="S0380">yeah I know but it's just like ah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0326">you do a master's or?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0380">I don't know I don't I kinda of want to do it really I think I'm like can't be fagged not doing that</u>
<u n="402" who="S0326" trans="overlap">why don't you have a gap year?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0380">yeah exactly I was speaking to the fucking careers woman like I kinda want to like just take a year out like decide what I want to do kind of thing and she was like no like</u>
<u n="404" who="S0326">obviously that's not what you tell a careers woman</u>
<u n="405" who="S0380">but like they have no like</u>
<u n="406" who="S0326">their job is so you don't have to do that</u>
<u n="407" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0326">just join that army or something</u>
<u n="409" who="S0380">I would actually do that if I could I don't know <pause dur="long"/> I don't know why like everyone needs to have like amazing technical skills to do like fine art though but yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0326">no they don't honestly everyone knows that</u>
<u n="411" who="S0380">yeah even with like creative writing I don't know where is like good in England like <anon type="place"/> and stuff?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0326">there's isn't there isn't in England just don't do it in England</u>
<u n="413" who="S0380">that's why I'd be like I was just gonna like do my master's in art history and then just do whatever but I'm so fucking tired of art history</u>
<u n="414" who="S0326">what about philosophy man?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0380">yeah I was thinking of that too but like</u>
<u n="416" who="S0326">I think it's the only really worthwhile postgraduate study in a way</u>
<u n="417" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0326">if you're not doing it to like I don't know it's like really good stuff you'll like have that forever</u>
<u n="419" who="S0380">I really wish I did that before like cos I was like trying to just decide between art history and philosophy I was just like I'm gonna do art history just because of like the image of the <unclear/> and stuff and what I thought it was going to be like and blah blah blah it's just so fucking dumb but yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0380">but I think you actually need to be clever for philosophy</u>
<u n="422" who="S0326">yeah it's really hard that doesn't mean you can't do it</u>
<u n="423" who="S0380">I don't know also I don't know where I would do it like <anon type="place"/> I think you could do it if you have studied it before but yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0326">even like I don't know</u>
<u n="425" who="S0380">there's this cool like school of philosophy called the Kyoto School</u>
<u n="426" who="S0326">in Japan?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0380">it's like it's like merging like old Buddhist stuff with like modern philosophy it's like during the eighties or nineties or something <pause dur="long"/> what are you thinking?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0380">like postgrad-wise you said you went to like a Princeton like</u>
<u n="430" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0380">you went to like this thing where like they were like trying to make you</u>
<u n="432" who="S0326">no I just had to meet with my director of studies and she was like so like telling me to do like go to Princeton and stuff</u>
<u n="433" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0326">I don't know I'll probably take a gap year I'll definitely take a year out though</u>
<u n="435" who="S0380">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling me about like Eton clubs or something in Princeton lol</u>
<u n="436" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0380">she said they're really nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0380">okay oh my god your t-shirt what the fuck? you look like you're in a band I just realised</u>
<u n="439" who="S0326">I don't really have I don't really have any clean clothes it's my that's my <trunc>frie</trunc> like last week my <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his pizza restaurant makes t-shirts for them</u>
<u n="440" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="441" who="S0326">this is an old one his new ones are really good though</u>
<u n="442" who="S0380">so what he has a restaurant in <anon type="place"/> and where else?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0326">yeah their their Michelin star one is also in <anon type="place"/> actually which is like another reason why people talk about it</u>
<u n="444" who="S0380">cos it's in <anon type="place"/> and it has a Michelin star</u>
<u n="445" who="S0326">it's like a <anon type="place"/> a lot in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0380">lol what's his name?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0380"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like a <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0326">I don't know like that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I don't even think to be with him</u>
<u n="450" who="S0380">what do you mean think to be with him?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0326">no the oh yeah it must be images why is it? let me see that sorry mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0380">lol <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0326">maybe that's not his name</u>
<u n="454" who="S0380">maybe</u>
<u n="455" who="S0326">maybe it's not all those pictures that's it</u>
<u n="456" who="S0380">oh he looks cute oh</u>
<u n="457" who="S0326">he's got a really funny laugh as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0380">I like his hair I was like shall I get a perm? lol</u>
<u n="459" who="S0326">he's so generous and stuff</u>
<u n="460" who="S0380">he's so generous and stuff</u>
<u n="461" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0380">ah mm yeah keep <unclear/> all the shit like in Tokyo you could like go to a restaurant that's like in a station and looks like a shithole but it'll have like two Michelin stars</u>
<u n="463" who="S0326">you can apparently there's a restaurant in Tokyo where you like catch your own food and</u>
<u n="464" who="S0380">I don't want to catch shit by myself but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0326">what's with someone else I really that would be so fun man</u>
<u n="466" who="S0380">you should come and oh</u>
<u n="467" who="S0326">I can't cos I've got school and exams and stuff</u>
<u n="468" who="S0380">June</u>
<u n="469" who="S0326">yeah in June they don't end till like June the fifteenth or something</u>
<u n="470" who="S0380">and then till like you know</u>
<u n="471" who="S0326">then I'm going to Portugal</u>
<u n="472" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0326">I'm not free till July</u>
<u n="474" who="S0380">that's so fucking weird they don't end till June fifteenth I'm thinking of going like to Marseilles or something to revise it's so fucking cheap like Airbnb there</u>
<u n="475" who="S0326">yeah how cheap is it?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0380">like thirty pounds a night or something and it's like</u>
<u n="477" who="S0326">that's not even that cheap though you can get a hotel for that</u>
<u n="478" who="S0380">I'll share it though</u>
<u n="479" who="S0326">yeah you can get a hotel room for that though</u>
<u n="480" who="S0380">yeah but like it's really nice ones</u>
<u n="481" who="S0326">I don't like Airbnb</u>
<u n="482" who="S0380">why?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0326">I much prefer to stay in a hotel</u>
<u n="484" who="S0380">I like how you can like</u>
<u n="485" who="S0326">it's funny it's more fun</u>
<u n="486" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0326">do you know what I mean? like hotels are funny and fun they're weirder</u>
<u n="488" who="S0380">I know what you mean but like</u>
<u n="489" who="S0326"><unclear/> and like you know and it's also nice that they that you don't have to clean up</u>
<u n="490" who="S0380">I like the idea of like imagining that I live somewhere permanently</u>
<u n="491" who="S0326">I remember like I stayed in one Airbnb in Mexico City and it was just like the same price it was actually more expensive than a hotel and like so much worse</u>
<u n="492" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0326">so we went to a hotel afterwards and it was was much better</u>
<u n="494" who="S0380">cos the apartment I found for Tokyo is like so nice</u>
<u n="495" who="S0326">can I eat this apple?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0380">yeah yeah I showed you right?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0326">uh</u>
<u n="498" who="S0380">I just want to like pretend I live there</u>
<u n="499" who="S0326">how long?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0380">for like a month a month</u>
<u n="501" who="S0326">how long are you going for?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0380">a month they're giving me a discount too I think</u>
<u n="503" who="S0326">yeah if you get a long one <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="505" who="S0326">it looks cool yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0326">I want to come</u>
<u n="508" who="S0380">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh my god lol <pause dur="short"/> post <pause dur="long"/> what the fuck is a hipster club?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0326">I don't know it's so sad though man</u>
<u n="510" who="S0380">what is so sad?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0326">like the world you know?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0380">you can't think like that all the time though</u>
<u n="513" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0380">you can't like keep thinking like that</u>
<u n="515" who="S0326">yeah obviously but I don't really subscribe to any of that stuff that culture</u>
<u n="516" who="S0380">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0326">like being cool</u>
<u n="518" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0326">like I'm totally alienated by it I don't want any part in it and like I didn't want I <trunc>do</trunc> really don't really ever want to go to Berlin again cos I don't want to be any part of it I like feel embarrassed to say oh I like spent six months in Berlin</u>
<u n="520" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="521" who="S0326">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0380">kinda want to just go to like a really cheap city in like Japan like Osaka or something and live there</u>
<u n="523" who="S0326">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0380">plus is Berlin even that cheap though like?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0326">not really</u>
<u n="526" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0326">I want to go to like I think it'll be cool to live in like Athens and like Athens is cheap</u>
<u n="528" who="S0380">I was looking at like <unclear/> today and that thing you said about Shia like Shia LaBeouf or something Shaquille O'Neal was asked like what clubs have you been to? or like no what was that?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0326">yeah it was like</u>
<u n="530" who="S0380">have you been to the Parthenon?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0326"><unclear/> like erm a journalist asked Shaquille O'Neal when you were in Athens did you visit the Parthenon? he said no man I don't even remember what pubs we went to</u>
<u n="532" who="S0380">lol that bloke's so amazing</u>
<u n="533" who="S0326">and then going to Rome in a few weeks erm with some friends and they asked me if I like knew about stuff like cool stuff there like I guess they're thinking about classics and I was like oh I don't really know like about clubs and bars and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like okay Shaquille O'Neal</u>
<u n="534" who="S0380">lol ah yeah I bet it must be really cheap there now right? obviously</u>
<u n="535" who="S0326">yeah even in Paris because the euro's really weak</u>
<u n="536" who="S0380">yeah yeah true</u>
<u n="537" who="S0326">it's like used to be one euro twenty for a pound now it's one euro forty</u>
<u n="538" who="S0380">I don't know what that means</u>
<u n="539" who="S0326">it means that like it's <trunc>twe</trunc> like it's good</u>
<u n="540" who="S0380"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0326">yeah it's more like more than twenty percent</u>
<u n="542" who="S0380">yeah like everyone is saying like the yen is really weak or something too so</u>
<u n="543" who="S0326">well who cares about the yen?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0380">yeah I care but yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0326">where are you going <trunc>ba</trunc> Beijing?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0380">yen Tokyo</u>
<u n="547" who="S0326">oh they have yen in China too</u>
<u n="548" who="S0380">that's yuan</u>
<u n="549" who="S0326">no it isn't</u>
<u n="550" who="S0380">it is</u>
<u n="551" who="S0326">is it?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0380">it's the <unclear/> and then the yuan like the</u>
<u n="553" who="S0326">oh well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0380">white people</u>
<u n="555" who="S0326">yeah but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0380">I want to live in Norway just cos the passports are so cute</u>
<u n="557" who="S0326">why do you want? oh the passports</u>
<u n="558" who="S0380">yeah look at them</u>
<u n="559" who="S0326">they're good</u>
<u n="560" who="S0380">I can't believe I ever had LinkedIn</u>
<u n="561" who="S0326">LinkedIn</u>
<u n="562" who="S0380">it's the most fucking annoying thing ever please get it</u>
<u n="563" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="564" who="S0380">oh my god like</u>
<u n="565" who="S0326">actually that would be a funny social media to like reclaim and like</u>
<u n="566" who="S0380">as an art project</u>
<u n="567" who="S0326">no well probably someone would have that idea yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0380">yeah I think it's been done <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0326">a month is quite a long time</u>
<u n="570" who="S0380">yeah I know I'm scared that I'll get bored</u>
<u n="571" who="S0326">yeah you might be also like <trunc>re</trunc> like I'm a like you just read a lot of books</u>
<u n="572" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0326">like when I went I remember a bit in New York I didn't see a single person for a week</u>
<u n="574" who="S0380">how long were you there again?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0326">if you add it all up three months</u>
<u n="576" who="S0380">but there's gonna be people living with me which is good</u>
<u n="577" who="S0326">oh really?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0380">yeah and they're like really nice but</u>
<u n="579" who="S0326">er I didn't like talk or see anyone for a week</u>
<u n="580" who="S0380">yeah where were you living?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0326">I really liked it I had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s sister had an apartment in China tTown and she went away and like gave me the keys</u>
<u n="582" who="S0380">oh mm wait how long were you there again sorry?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0326">altogether in America like three months like two months in New York</u>
<u n="584" who="S0380">oh</u>
<u n="585" who="S0326">but I remember like when it was so cold and like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were staying in like such shitty places and I was like every time I woke up I was like can't believe I'm here for another three months <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0380">oh god were you like is it cos you booked your like return flight already?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0326">yeah and we like didn't have enough <trunc>mo</trunc> obviously didn't have enough money to get another one and then like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a massive fight and I was like on my own like</u>
<u n="588" who="S0380">why d'you have a fight?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0326">ah he <unclear/> saying I preferred <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to his other girlfriend</u>
<u n="590" who="S0380">oh <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> oh my god <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was fucking pissing me off like saying like and then she was like what's your passion? and stuff like that sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then she was like who is someone that like you look up to? like not even like just their job but like just like what they've done for themselves what kind of like life they've created for themselves and I was like er I don't know like even someone like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like she doesn't have to like kiss up to anyone like she has her own thing blah blah blah and like she has quite a bit of money probably and she was like yeah she's probably like I said and then it was like something about like <trunc>re</trunc> and it then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was just like sorry can't speak properly yeah she's probably rich for your friends or something I was like okay</u>
<u n="591" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0380">okay seriously I don't know but she is</u>
<u n="593" who="S0326">yeah but she's like yeah but and like but she earnt it man it's like</u>
<u n="594" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0326">you should say like you should say cos my friends have to earn that money</u>
<u n="596" who="S0380">yeah I don't know like I I like everyone and I want to be like peaceful and pacifist</u>
<u n="597" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0380">but</u>
<u n="599" who="S0326">sometimes I wish sometimes I wish that I could like <trunc>te</trunc> <trunc>we</trunc> <trunc>te</trunc> tell you things to say like you know when you were saying how</u>
<u n="600" who="S0380">I always like think of them afterwards it's just like ah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0326">when you're talking to your erm dad and your dad's like about you and your brother and like</u>
<u n="602" who="S0380">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0326">if your brother kills someone he's still my son if you kill someone you're still my son what about if I kill my brother?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0380">yeah yeah I'm just like okay</u>
<u n="605" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0380">he moved back in now it's like fine I guess for now</u>
<u n="607" who="S0326">now you have this place so</u>
<u n="608" who="S0380">yeah for a month</u>
<u n="609" who="S0326">yeah but</u>
<u n="610" who="S0380">yeah it's fine though like he didn't</u>
<u n="611" who="S0326">a month and it's like two months or one month until you go</u>
<u n="612" who="S0380">yeah I'm scared that I'm gonna go and then like he's going to take my room but yeah it's fine</u>
<u n="613" who="S0326">can't be too attached to anything but what about next year are you still going to stay there?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0380">I don't know probably unless I do a master's in <anon type="place"/> on Hegel or something</u>
<u n="615" who="S0326">yeah I didn't know how much I almost like I remember like last year I almost applied for this summer school cos I thought it was in <anon type="place"/> but it was it was in a different one in Germany with a really similar name like in the middle of nowhere</u>
<u n="616" who="S0380">oh my god that probably would have been way better for you</u>
<u n="617" who="S0326">but I thought it was good like loads of people who like teach you German and like sort of free like food and accommodation</u>
<u n="618" who="S0380">my best friend in the course right now is this German girl and she's fucking like amazing like she does every single reading and like she's fucking clever as</u>
<u n="619" who="S0326">all the reading list</u>
<u n="620" who="S0380">yeah she lives in like Kent or something and like she gets the train and oh yeah oh my god wait tell me about your like you thought of a way to make money or something like that was something</u>
<u n="621" who="S0326">oh just it's like there's this sale that you won't really know about for the <anon type="place"/> in their warehouses every time they drop a box of books or whatever they they can't <trunc>aff</trunc> afford to pay someone to check them for damage so there's like a every January a big sale where they sell all the books that have been dropped rather than check them but they sell them for three pounds for a paperback and seven pounds for a hardback but those <trunc>book</trunc> hardbacks cost like sixty-seventy quid</u>
<u n="622" who="S0380">wow</u>
<u n="623" who="S0326">so you get it for seven pounds and you sell it on Ebay</u>
<u n="624" who="S0380">does everyone do some? like nobody</u>
<u n="625" who="S0326">well I don't know like I haven't I missed it this year but I'll check it out next year</u>
<u n="626" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0326">you can only buy seven books a day</u>
<u n="628" who="S0380">I'll come yeah I wish there were like more things like that don't really know how I'm going to sustain myself lol it's getting to like tutoring or babysitting</u>
<u n="629" who="S0326">yeah babysitting <unclear/> fun to do</u>
<u n="630" who="S0380">babysitting yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0326">I'd quite like to be like a security guard</u>
<u n="632" who="S0380">I might get like a yoga teacher traineeship or whatever it's called</u>
<u n="633" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0380">but I think you don't make any money but yeah it would be nice to have anyway you'd quite like to be a security guard</u>
<u n="635" who="S0326">but not like you know someone who just like sits there like in like a office building all night you know</u>
<u n="636" who="S0380">you have to be black</u>
<u n="637" who="S0326">no you don't</u>
<u n="638" who="S0380">well</u>
<u n="639" who="S0326">and you just sit there you sit in like an office building all night and just read</u>
<u n="640" who="S0380">yeah oh my god my internship for like six weeks or something I wanted to fucking kill myself like just have to fucking sit in a desk all day and like I know like that's really obvious but like</u>
<u n="641" who="S0326">doing what?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0380">it was actually the people were nice and stuff the garage not the garage what's it called? <anon type="place"/> photos just like I didn't know like a publisher would be like oh I need like a picture of a girl standing by a lake she has to be in nineteen fifties costume and have to go through like a billion pictures finding that and stuff like that erm yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0326">how many internships have you done now? a lot?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0380">no like one I quit and one it was six weeks and I did that I used to wish that I'd done a lot and now I'm just like I'm never doing one again I was looking at this book in like east London stereotypes or something do you know what I'm talking about?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0326">yeah I've seen it it's so</u>
<u n="646" who="S0380">and then there's one like American grad school student and it was like she's done fifty internships and she'll stab you in the back for the fourth assistant curatorship or I don't know something like that</u>
<u n="647" who="S0326">I don't know if I saw that one</u>
<u n="648" who="S0380">work for free forever or something <pause dur="short"/> it's like I want to be a curator be like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he's so cute and he's a Bambi angel no more I don't know <pause dur="long"/> I think I'm attracted to things for the wrong reasons all the time</u>
<u n="649" who="S0326">I think I don't think any of those people were doing anything that's important</u>
<u n="650" who="S0380">who is?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0326">well no but like niche <unclear/> artists especially not who's like champion is like vision of youth and the future and it's like so backward</u>
<u n="652" who="S0380">oh yeah poetry will be made by all <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0326">I quite like that thing you sent me that was the guy who was in the Zurich poetry thing he was saying like</u>
<u n="654" who="S0380">oh I think that's that guy yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I don't want to be like well I don't know I feel like if you have like too much dignity then you'll just be stuck in your house forever maybe there's nothing wrong with that though I don't know</u>
<u n="655" who="S0326">well I think it takes a bit to like maintain your dignity you just have to be like brilliant</u>
<u n="656" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0326">you know like</u>
<u n="658" who="S0380">I don't know if I can afford that though</u>
<u n="659" who="S0326">no obviously like hardly anybody is like right like people who are just like fuck you to like everything</u>
<u n="660" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0326">and can't help that their work is like and people like still want a part of it</u>
<u n="662" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0326">like Oasis</u>
<u n="664" who="S0380">Oasis lol <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0326">you know what I mean? those guys were like just be like rude to everyone never compromise like</u>
<u n="666" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0326">if you don't like it go find somewhere else go listen to something else</u>
<u n="668" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0326">but you do like it <pause dur="short"/> are you gonna go back to <anon type="place"/> or are you going to stay here?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0380">I'm going to go back like later I think I'm gonna wait for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to finish and go go home</u>
<u n="671" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does yoga?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0326">does he do it when where does he do it? same place?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0380">same place but <unclear/> gym</u>
<u n="675" who="S0326">does he does does he go to university?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0326">what does he do?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0380">maths</u>
<u n="679" who="S0326">maths where?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0380"><anon type="place"/> er</u>
<u n="681" who="S0326">I don't know</u>
<u n="682" who="S0380">he does so much work <pause dur="short"/> it's so cute like he has so many friends and he loves them and they're all just like him they like play solitaire together and stuff</u>
<u n="683" who="S0326" trans="overlap">like you like you</u>
<u n="684" who="S0380">no</u>
<u n="685" who="S0326">all his friends are just like him I'm just one of his friends</u>
<u n="686" who="S0380">yeah well his maths friends <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0380">I don't know I think like yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0326">I got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the I need to think of something to write on a postcard</u>
<u n="690" who="S0380">what are you getting her for her birthday apart for Essex?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0326">that's what I'm getting her man</u>
<u n="692" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0326">like I got a hotel room and stuff</u>
<u n="694" who="S0380">oh really?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0326">I'm writing on that one</u>
<u n="696" who="S0380">how many did you get her?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0326">just one I mean <unclear/> but I don't like the <unclear/> and then the train tickets innit?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0380">oh</u>
<u n="699" who="S0326">like the kind of cases I'm taking lol</u>
<u n="700" who="S0380">oh</u>
<u n="701" who="S0326">I'm going to put them in the envelope but I still have to write something on this though something innit? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0380">I could be your manager</u>
<u n="703" who="S0326">I think she gets really sad about her birthday</u>
<u n="704" who="S0380">I think everyone does don't they?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0326">I guess but especially she's kind of talking about how like all her friends her age are kinda like married and stuff you know?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0326">and like and like</u>
<u n="708" who="S0380">that doesn't mean anything</u>
<u n="709" who="S0326">no but it does cos she feels a bit like I feel a bit lonely like where she doesn't really want any of that stuff that they want all they really want is like</u>
<u n="710" who="S0380">that's a good thing though</u>
<u n="711" who="S0326">yeah I know but it's you know she I think it's hard to understand like it's different from being like different when you're like <trunc>ni</trunc> seventeen</u>
<u n="712" who="S0380">yeah does she not want to get married ever?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0326">well she does like <trunc>do</trunc> definitely doesn't want to have any children</u>
<u n="714" who="S0380">really? how comes?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0326">cos they're annoying</u>
<u n="716" who="S0380">yeah but she like she puts them on that photo thing that cute little thing with the yellow coat</u>
<u n="717" who="S0326">yeah she likes her friends' children but she wouldn't want to like raise one</u>
<u n="718" who="S0380">yeah yeah that's what I feel I'm like ah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0326">yeah exactly so she like she likes hanging out with kids and like but she like does it vicariously through</u>
<u n="720" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0326">her friends</u>
<u n="722" who="S0380">my mum always like screams at me cos I like go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when he's sleeping and I like kiss him and cuddle him and she's like you only come close to him when he's like sleeping</u>
<u n="723" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> not there when he's like pissing all over the settee</u>
<u n="724" who="S0380">yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/> her friends don't like <unclear/> do they?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0326">no but like</u>
<u n="726" who="S0380">oh my god all my vocabulary is like so American don't judge me you're so mean like but like what sorry</u>
<u n="727" who="S0326">they don't judge you or they probably think like I mean I think her friends think it's funny that she has a boyfriend that's like twenty you know</u>
<u n="728" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0326">but I've met them before and they were all like that's the only thing I'm like I really felt like a mimbo</u>
<u n="730" who="S0380">mimbo? oh right</u>
<u n="731" who="S0326">male bimbo like I was <unclear/> like do you know I was like they were like really like checking me out like</u>
<u n="732" who="S0380">you're probably like more mature than their husbands</u>
<u n="733" who="S0326">yeah probably man I hear about them actually like it's funny cos she's got this one friend called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's quite funny like but really like bossy and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says that she like totally like bosses her fiancé around like and then she's talking about this guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I guess <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum was staying with them in their apartment and I thought that she lived with her friend who had a kid called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know the way she was talking about it</u>
<u n="734" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="735" who="S0326">she's like to don't your doesn't your mum like make funny <trunc>noi</trunc> like do you I thought she was like trying talking about her kid</u>
<u n="736" who="S0380">oh my god that's quite cool though I would like to be bossy</u>
<u n="737" who="S0326" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="738" who="S0380">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> no</u>
<u n="739" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're confused man <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0380">does she have lots of friends?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0380"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="743" who="S0326">does she have loads?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="745" who="S0326">well knows a lot of people but like doesn't have like just a few close ones</u>
<u n="746" who="S0380">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0326">I'm well confused with all this stuff man</u>
<u n="748" who="S0380">keep pressuring her about opening a space in Tokyo man</u>
<u n="749" who="S0326">it'll be so much work I don't think she can be bothered</u>
<u n="750" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0326">I saw something online with her about like this magazine or this article and I was just I was like laughing cos it's funny cos she's all dressed up and she's like but like she looks normal to like compared to all the other ones and she's like yeah but I'm the only one of those like six like young entrepreneurs I'm the only one of those that isn't a millionaire though</u>
<u n="752" who="S0380">lol <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="753" who="S0326">oh so confusing</u>
<u n="754" who="S0380">why do you have to put them all there?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0326">cos of like cos of railcards and stuff</u>
<u n="756" who="S0380">maybe you should get like those like paper clip things?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0326">maybe you should like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0380">oh stop it stop it</u>
<u n="759" who="S0326">please stop it I think that's alright yeah I'm like yeah I'm taking you somewhere really glamorous it says <anon type="place"/> on it</u>
<u n="760" who="S0380">lol <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="761" who="S0326">happy birthday <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0380">there's <unclear/> deal</u>
<u n="763" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0380"><unclear/> deal</u>
<u n="765" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0380">which also doubles as a gallery lol anything that doubles as a gallery</u>
<u n="767" who="S0326">coffee shop</u>
<u n="768" who="S0380"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0326">I think I'm gonna go in a minute</u>
<u n="770" who="S0380">really? what have you got?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0326">meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0380">are you working at the bakery this Sunday?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0326">I don't work there on Sundays</u>
<u n="774" who="S0380">when do you work there?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0326">I don't even do that like four <trunc>pa</trunc> like four weeks of the year they open in <trunc>Chris</trunc> like on a Wednesday</u>
<u n="776" who="S0380">oh</u>
<u n="777" who="S0326">I just did that it's not like part of the business like it's so busy there on a Sunday man</u>
<u n="778" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0326">I would yeah like working there must be stressful it's like five hundred people like queued up outside</u>
<u n="780" who="S0380">really? okay yeah yeah I would freak out she doesn't work work there on Sunday does she?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0326">no no no way <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0380">so what you're going to go to Portugal when again?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0326">twenty-second of June</u>
<u n="784" who="S0380">and then do you know what you're going to do after that no?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0326">no I think I might go to America</u>
<u n="786" who="S0380">yeah with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0326">yeah go to <anon type="place"/> cos like her family just want to go there and like open they might open a bar there or something</u>
<u n="788" who="S0380">that's going to be so F F photo</u>
<u n="789" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0380">like that is F F photo</u>
<u n="791" who="S0326">I forgot that you looked at F F F photo I don't really do it so much though</u>
<u n="792" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0326">did you see the ones in Paris?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0380">no wait</u>
<u n="795" who="S0326">well you wouldn't have they the</u>
<u n="796" who="S0380">they don't have like a location thing</u>
<u n="797" who="S0326">that's what I did with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday</u>
<u n="798" who="S0380">oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lol</u>
<u n="799" who="S0326">yeah sliding down a banister <pause dur="long"/> look boat in Paris I like that one</u>
<u n="800" who="S0380">oh that's cute <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0380">lol <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0326">it was fun to go back to Paris</u>
<u n="803" who="S0380">I just realised</u>
<u n="804" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0380">lol <pause dur="long"/> that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ah wait how did she meet him?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0326">in New York right before New Year</u>
<u n="807" who="S0380">oh yeah yeah sorry New York</u>
<u n="808" who="S0326">and they're like really kind of best friends</u>
<u n="809" who="S0380">ah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0326">they went to like Thailand together and to Australia and it's like just did a lot of lols</u>
<u n="811" who="S0380">is he gay? I can't tell</u>
<u n="812" who="S0326">no <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> weird</u>
<u n="813" who="S0380">yeah I can't oh</u>
<u n="814" who="S0326">he has that too he calls himself <trunc>p</trunc><trunc>p</trunc><trunc>p</trunc><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="816" who="S0326">did you see that? did I send you a picture of the Duchamp's grave?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0326">why did I <trunc>ke</trunc> that was like accidently all I keep seeing is like toilets on the street everywhere</u>
<u n="819" who="S0380">I keep thinking of Duchamp now cos it'd</u>
<u n="820" who="S0326">that's me on the stage in the club</u>
<u n="821" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="822" who="S0326">it's a super club our friend was <unclear/> I was like I'm just going to dance right next to him</u>
<u n="823" who="S0380"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that in Paris?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0380">I didn't even know they had like space for that</u>
<u n="826" who="S0326">it's called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="828" who="S0326">so bad went to such a crazy club it was like <trunc>s</trunc> trying so hard to be like post-net cool but it was like French</u>
<u n="829" who="S0380">that's so weird</u>
<u n="830" who="S0326">and like weird yeah so weird man</u>
<u n="831" who="S0380">I can't imagine that in Paris post-net lol</u>
<u n="832" who="S0326">it was like all this like it was all this like French boys and like it's so weird like sort of like Nike joggers and like Nike stuff with like a Burberry like little fisher hat you know like little bum fluff</u>
<u n="833" who="S0380">yeah oh my god</u>
<u n="834" who="S0326">it was like beautiful girls</u>
<u n="835" who="S0380">lol my dissertation supervisor was like you should look into post-internet</u>
<u n="836" who="S0326">yeah you know like TBT you should look it to post-internet</u>
<u n="837" who="S0380">no and that's not him thank god</u>
<u n="838" who="S0326">truth be told</u>
<u n="839" who="S0380">oh my god I forgot to tell my supervisor about how dumb that teacher is ah that's so embarrassing</u>
<u n="840" who="S0326">so funny</u>
<u n="841" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="842" who="S0326">right I'm going to get going to get going</u>
<u n="843" who="S0380">I want to see you soon again though</u>
<u n="844" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0380">never see you anymore</u>
<u n="846" who="S0326">I'm like well I'm I think I'm going to did I tell you why I'm going to Italy?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0380">you're going to Italy?</u>
<u n="848" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0380">what the hell man?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0326">and <trunc>Tu</trunc> and Tuscany I'm getting married</u>
<u n="851" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0380">wait for real?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0326">well like I'm going through the motions</u>
<u n="855" who="S0380">what?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0326">like there's this thing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing like some food convention in this beautiful villa in Tuscany and they also like</u>
<u n="857" who="S0380">food convention?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0326">I don't know what it is man some you know just like conference I don't know she's like doing the cakes for it and like it's a it's a big house but they sort of rent it out for weddings</u>
<u n="859" who="S0380">wait for real?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0326">yeah and I think they're like updating their brochure</u>
<u n="861" who="S0380">I'm like looking at the ring like</u>
<u n="862" who="S0326">they're like <trunc>upda</trunc>updating their brochure and stuff so they're like having so there's going to be like a lot of people there for this event and like at the end like a big party slash wedding which they're going to like <trunc>ph</trunc>photograph</u>
<u n="863" who="S0380">wedding for who?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0326">for me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="865" who="S0380">oh my god</u>
<u n="866" who="S0326">cos they're like when she met for the meeting they're like we're also doing this wedding thing we need like some like modals do you know any boys with like a London look?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0380">why are you just telling me this when you're going are you crazy? what the hell?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0326">so she's like do you know any boys with a London look? and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like I know exactly who like</u>
<u n="869" who="S0380">the boy lol</u>
<u n="870" who="S0326">and so like I think it's going to be really weird though cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes to meetings with them and she says that like they're really Italian and like they want to like they have this like weird ideas like she saw some dresses that were like dayglo</u>
<u n="871" who="S0380">oh my god</u>
<u n="872" who="S0326">and they and she's like and then they start talking about a wig a pink wig <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0380">oh my god wait so is it going to turn into a real one?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="875" who="S0380">okay</u>
<u n="876" who="S0326">it's just like but it'll be funny cos we'll have all these photo and I can like send my mum a picture and be like</u>
<u n="877" who="S0380">oh my god what's your mum doing now?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0326">my mum's like with some <trunc>boyf</trunc> got a <trunc>boyf</trunc> like moved in her boyfriend it's actually really annoying</u>
<u n="879" who="S0380">he's really annoying?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0326">he's kind of annoying yeah</u>
<u n="881" who="S0380">oh is she still writing her book?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="883" who="S0380">really?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0326">she's not doing everything man she like just like she's not really like happy like she's just with this guy now</u>
<u n="885" who="S0380">oh the painter guy?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0326">yeah but yeah so then I'm so I'm that's in Tuscany and I think I'm going to Rome like a week before like our friend's coming who can drive and we're going to like go round Italy</u>
<u n="887" who="S0380">oh mm wait when is that?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0326">thirteenth of April I think we're going it's not actually that it's quite soon</u>
<u n="889" who="S0380">wait thirteenth of April for how long?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0326">for like nine days or something</u>
<u n="891" who="S0380">ah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0326">going to be late for school again</u>
<u n="893" who="S0380">wait you have school still then?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0326">yeah we're meant to go back for stuff like lectures and stuff</u>
<u n="895" who="S0380">how the hell? like I have nothing now</u>
<u n="896" who="S0326">yeah it's a rip-off man</u>
<u n="897" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0326">that's like same with my brother like what are you <trunc>do</trunc> what are you like you're <trunc>ba</trunc> you're basically paying like nine thousand for two terms</u>
<u n="899" who="S0380">I pay seven thousand</u>
<u n="900" who="S0326">is that a <unclear/> price?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0380">no they like pay it they give me they take two thousand off my fees and give me one thousand to spend which makes it a bit better I guess but not really</u>
<u n="902" who="S0326">yeah they give me a thousand to spend as well which they take off my bill or my rent</u>
<u n="903" who="S0380">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is a rip off now</u>
<u n="904" who="S0326">especially at other uni some other universities man it's just like a racket</u>
<u n="905" who="S0380">yeah I think mine's a rip off but no it's like going to like</u>
<u n="906" who="S0326">University of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="907" who="S0380">well even that but like I don't know <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="908" who="S0326">no I think <anon type="place"/> it was probably better than most I think somewhere like <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="909" who="S0380">oh yeah true yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> but you have friends at uni though?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="911" who="S0380">you said you do</u>
<u n="912" who="S0326">what I don't I have people I like hang out with and like they're kind of friends yeah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0380">mm everyone I've met from like Oxford and Cambridge doing an MA at <anon type="place"/> they're like fucking super into like extracurricular shit and it's like what are you doing?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0326">yeah obviously</u>
<u n="915" who="S0380">yeah I know but it's just like you leave that behind like you're here for a reason</u>
<u n="916" who="S0326">it's like a whole <unclear/> village of like do-gooders and over-achievers</u>
<u n="917" who="S0380">yeah ah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0326">obviously it's not not everyone's like that but like everyone's really like they're talented and like</u>
<u n="919" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0326">do you think those people are actually talented?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0326">well they're good at like yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0380">they're good at what they do</u>
<u n="923" who="S0326">they're good at stuff like they've been like their parents made them learn the violin from the age of four and they're good at it</u>
<u n="924" who="S0380">yeah <pause dur="long"/> that's so cute</u>
<u n="925" who="S0326">what? feels cold outside is there no heating on here?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0380">erm I think she turned it off before oh can you fix these?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0326">yeah okay well I don't actually know</u>
<u n="928" who="S0380">yeah what the fuck is that stick thing?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0326">that's like the I think that might be to like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="930" who="S0380">seriously <pause dur="short"/> lol</u>
<u n="931" who="S0326">what happens if I can't do it either?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0380">oh no it's so like people can proper see me</u>
<u n="933" who="S0326">you need to like unstable those let me get a chair to stand on</u>
<u n="934" who="S0380">you're not that short</u>
<u n="935" who="S0326">yeah got to reach right to the top mate</u>
<u n="936" who="S0380"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="937" who="S0326">there's no chairs</u>
<u n="938" who="S0380">stand on the bed if you want</u>
<u n="939" who="S0326">I need to get up there</u>
<u n="940" who="S0380">stand on that but don't fall</u>
<u n="941" who="S0326">it's heavy this chair <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> oh my days er</u>
<u n="942" who="S0380">I'm scared</u>
<u n="943" who="S0326">I'm scared too man <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="944" who="S0380">don't fall out the window please</u>
<u n="945" who="S0326">that's what I'm scared of I don't know how to untangle it let me just do some experimenting oh that's easy man it's one of those</u>
<u n="946" who="S0380">thank god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0380">what am I going to tell my friend <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0326">tell her I'm suing her</u>
<u n="949" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="950" who="S0326">like if this it's a bit like you've got to like fiddle a bit so like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="951" who="S0380">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="952" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="953" who="S0380">yeah right that's it I think</u>
<u n="954" who="S0326">you've got to find the right combination of strings to pull and just like</u>
<u n="955" who="S0380">right combination of strings to pull I tried everything</u>
<u n="956" who="S0326">it's trial and error man</u>
<u n="957" who="S0380">oh my god how are you still into Words with Friends?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0326">it's fun</u>
<u n="959" who="S0380">it is fun yeah</u>
<u n="960" who="S0326">so why what do you mean?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0380">I don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0326">erm it's fun to do like when you're waiting for a bus or something</u>
<u n="963" who="S0380">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="964" who="S0326">you just have to spend a few minutes on each curtain if you get the right two strings you can kind of shimmy it down <pause dur="short"/> do you want me to do that one?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0380">no this one's faulty</u>
<u n="966" who="S0326">yeah you bet? you think so?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0380">lol</u>
<u n="968" who="S0326">what? oh</u>
<u n="969" who="S0380">what the fuck is this seriously?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know it's not easy I must admit <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you want it down or up?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0380">down</u>
<u n="972" who="S0326">alright let me try these two maybe this is the down string</u>
<u n="973" who="S0380">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0326">it's like I'm being a puppet</u>
<u n="975" who="S0380">yeah it's like a marionette <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0326">come on then I think these are the up strings though yeah man they're definitely up now how do you? <pause dur="long"/> I know oh fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="977" who="S0380">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0326">why don't you call your friend and like maybe actually I know what's probably happening change of combination</u>
<u n="979" who="S0380">who doesn't?</u>
<u n="980" who="S0326">I know if anybody's watching from the outside street they're laughing at us <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="981" who="S0380">I thought you'd be an expert on this though</u>
<u n="982" who="S0326">I thought so too man it's not my fault the blind's <unclear/></u>
<u n="983" who="S0380">you can't just pull them I tried</u>
<u n="984" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0380">you're making it worse</u>
<u n="986" who="S0326">wait that's good <pause dur="long"/> come on why didn't it do that before? <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's good</u>
<u n="987" who="S0380">it's a <unclear/> all the positions of your body</u>
<u n="988" who="S0326">I feel like I'm sailing</u>
<u n="989" who="S0380">what is that? you made like a zigzag thing</u>
<u n="990" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="991" who="S0380">are you down? wait why is it everywhere? oh my god</u>
<u n="992" who="S0326">I don't know I'm sorry I don't know why it's stuck either</u>
<u n="993" who="S0380">dude</u>
<u n="994" who="S0326">you have to get someone who's smarter than me</u>
<u n="995" who="S0380">where would I find that?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0326">get <trunc>l</trunc> get like <trunc>up</trunc></u>
<u n="997" who="S0380">wait I'll fold the thing</u>
<u n="998" who="S0326">I might have to <unclear/> and fucking go</u>
<u n="999" who="S0380">you fucking did this you have to finish it</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0380">okay fine are you getting on the thirty-eight? what the hell I guess it'll give me something to do</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wanna I wanna help I want to get it down to like a <trunc>re</trunc> a respectable amount you know?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0326"><unclear/> time</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0380">seriously never living in an old apartment like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0326">what is this man?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0380">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0326">have you looked on Google?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0380">what the fuck is it going to tell me to go pull the string? wait</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0326">it might just tell you how the system works like what is that about?</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0380"><unclear/> come on checking</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0326">then it gets like stuck you know I'm going to change string</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0380">oh my god</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0380">there's people on the bus that can fucking see us</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0326">I don't know what I don't really know what to say about this</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0380">that is fucking slow progress <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0326">I don't know if this is going to go up again you know oh my god</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0380">why don't you just leave it?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0326">I think I think we're going to have to maybe untangle it up there</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0380">yeah I'll do it</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0326">you sure?</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0326">I won't tie my shoelaces innit cos then I have to do that</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0326">I but I think Google might have some tips</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0380">I don't know what to Google</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0326">I mean what's the point in that plastic?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0380">I have no fucking idea like what is that like?</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0326">I swear I made it higher I think to untangle it you just probably yeah you're doing good</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0380"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will probably do it</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0380"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is probably good at this domestic stuff</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0326">yeah maybe not though</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0380">oh my god wait no</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0326">did you untangle it?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0380">I can't even tell what this thing is do you reckon the fucking</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0326">well I'm going to leave you to it</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0380">okay</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0326">so I'm sorry that erm I was quite hopeless</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0380">this is the one that was important though</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0326">yeah exactly I did the right thing</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0380">yeah thank you</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0326">alright then I'll see you later</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0380">yeah</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0326">bye bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
