<text id="S9EP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:22:59</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-01-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0281 S0355</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home, Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Scottish referendum, job interview, colleague, my daughter, present personal situation.</topics>
		<activity>Recent news, personal situation.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0355">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hove, Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hove, Sussex</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>64 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Business Owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">er what yeah what did that guy say about er the work you've done?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0355">he said I thank you for all you've done in my flat and it's a blast when you're there <pause dur="short"/> next up are the bathroom tiles whoopee send me a recording of your trumpet playing</u>
<u n="3" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0355">so here's here's my trombone playing <event desc="sound of trombone playing"/></u>
<u n="5" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0281">nobody sleeps when you're around do they?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0355">no bugger them</u>
<u n="8" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> er yeah <pause dur="short"/> I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this afternoon</u>
<u n="9" who="S0355">oh yeah how was she?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0281">she was fine yeah as er bubbly as ever</u>
<u n="11" who="S0355">did she ask after me?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0281">er no she asked erm er well I said I was staying with you and I said do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and she said oh yes yes erm er yeah we're I mean I haven't seen her for fifteen years nearly</u>
<u n="13" who="S0355">the last time I saw her is when I went up there to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0281">when was that?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0355">when I took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> out when I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh didn't I tell you that?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no you swine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0355">didn't I tell you I went out with your wife your wife?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when was that then?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0355">erm oh long after you'd thrown her aside like a dish dirty dishrag</u>
<u n="20" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0355">yeah she was in England living with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up er near the in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0281">where did you go?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0355">I can't remember now it was dark anyway</u>
<u n="24" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0355">and and very warm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0355">as I remember</u>
<u n="28" who="S0281">good good</u>
<u n="29" who="S0355">I think we both had to take our clothes off</u>
<u n="30" who="S0281">I just phoned her actually and er</u>
<u n="31" who="S0355" trans="overlap">who <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0355">oh well say hello</u>
<u n="34" who="S0281">well she she said oh I I'm I'm I'm trying to sleep cos I've got to get up at six o'clock in the morning so I said</u>
<u n="35" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0281">oh I'm sorry I'll phone you tomorrow so that was it but erm yeah I did quite a long conversation with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm and we about an hour nearly we had a coffee</u>
<u n="37" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="38" who="S0281">at <anon type="place"/> well near <anon type="place"/> and erm catching up on on life she she hadn't heard that I'd had a heart attack and big you know open <trunc>surg</trunc> open heart surgery hadn't heard about it I said didn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tell you? er no I don't think so I said well I'm really surprised anyway so we had a lot of catching up to do about who's doing what and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got his operation tomorrow up in <anon type="place"/> it's his other knee he's had one knee done already</u>
<u n="39" who="S0355">and was that particularly successful?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0281">well the first one I think was alright yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0355">good</u>
<u n="42" who="S0281">but erm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0355" trans="overlap">has he had an artificial joint put in?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0355">god amazing</u>
<u n="46" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it is isn't it? isn't it? you you think knees are really complicated I don't know I expect they are but erm he's had one done and he's having the other one done it's amazing and it's and at er <anon type="place"/> somewhere</u>
<u n="47" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0281">I asked her I said is is it <anon type="place"/> because that's where my father died? and er she said no I don't think so she said it's a new hospital</u>
<u n="49" who="S0355"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0281"><anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> that's where</u>
<u n="51" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that's where your father died?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0355">really?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0281">yeah he had a</u>
<u n="55" who="S0355" trans="overlap">is that?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0281">he had a brain operation he had</u>
<u n="57" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0281">yeah it's there was apparently no hope and it's it was cancer brain cancer and I think it spread everywhere there's no hope erm erm the last time I saw him he was lying in bed there with a bandaged head the last time</u>
<u n="59" who="S0355">oh I'm sorry</u>
<u n="60" who="S0281">yeah oh well but erm it's not the same hospital erm so yeah and catching up on er on everybody mm and erm I asked about erm you know that er DBS thing <trunc>w</trunc> with police and I said three times I've emailed the woman er about er you know expunging that record and I got no reply they're just ignoring me I don't and I don't know what</u>
<u n="61" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well they're probably not there to er she's a policewoman is she?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0281">I think so or she might be might just work in the office I don't know</u>
<u n="63" who="S0355">amazing</u>
<u n="64" who="S0281">but you'd think they'd reply I know she only came back from holiday last week but after a week you know?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0355">well some things never get expunged and that's it</u>
<u n="66" who="S0281">well okay but at least they had the would have the decency to reply</u>
<u n="67" who="S0355" trans="overlap">decency yeah well if they were decent people they wouldn't become policemen would they?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0355">let's be honest there's more corruption and <unclear/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to work in er work er in the police I mean she wasn't a policewoman</u>
<u n="71" who="S0355" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="72" who="S0281">but she she worked for them you know? erm and I said have you have you still got any contacts and she said well I have but I <trunc>d</trunc>don't know if you know but I'll sort of send him an email and find out and it's funny that just er as we were finishing our conversation and we were just about to go and just about saying goodbyes my phone rang and it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd finished talking with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and quickly said you know <event desc="sound of kissing"/> and bye bye er you know and nice to see you blah blah blah and and then I had to continue the conversation with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and er</u>
<u n="73" who="S0355" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0281">she said about er she said I should try and <trunc>fi</trunc> phone <anon type="place"/> cos you know it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that actually took my my form there to <anon type="place"/> to erm so erm she said oh I'll try and get the phone number and er and phone them up I said well er I can try so maybe tomorrow I'll try and track down <anon type="place"/> and police phone <anon type="place"/> phone number and try and track this woman down and try and get something done about it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0355">well good luck</u>
<u n="76" who="S0281">well thank you very much</u>
<u n="77" who="S0355">you're welcome</u>
<u n="78" who="S0281">yeah so <unclear/> phoning <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was that you know I was asking about it and she mentioned that the money is a bit tight and I said well doesn't she get the pension? I said cos when we got divorced er when I went down there we went to this er pension office because when when you're self-employed in France you have to pay erm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0355">a stamp?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0281">well yes the equivalent of a stamp and erm er well like National Insurance er for a pension but it's er erm and you have to all all the obligatory things that you have to pay er and it's all tied to your <trunc>tur</trunc> declared turnover</u>
<u n="81" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="82" who="S0281">so when I was last saw her when I was last in <anon type="place"/> when I went down there for the divorce erm we went together to this er place and I signed over my right to the pension for her</u>
<u n="83" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="84" who="S0281">because I mean I thought it's the least I could do <trunc>b</trunc> seeing that it was my fault that you know she's in the situation she was alone and as and I was earning good money you know at university? and I thought well that's the least I could do and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really surprised me when she said she hasn't received a penny or rather a euro</u>
<u n="85" who="S0355">so how old is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0281">well she must be about er <trunc>fif</trunc> what is it nineteen fifty-two she's or fifty-four it was fifty-four and she'll be sixty now won't she?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0355">so when do women in France get their pensions?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0281">I don't know I don't know I'd and I said well that's crazy because you know she should have been receiving quite good money because of all the years the eighteen years that we paid into this</u>
<u n="89" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah but if you haven't er</u>
<u n="90" who="S0281">well I haven't</u>
<u n="91" who="S0355" trans="overlap">reached retirement age there she won't get anything surely?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0281">but women always retire earlier don't they? I mean what is it sixty? is it <trunc>si</trunc><trunc>six</trunc>sixty?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah but here it's gone up</u>
<u n="94" who="S0281" trans="overlap">is it sixty?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0355">it may have gone up there</u>
<u n="96" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well maybe maybe but er I might and that's that's what I wanted to talk to her about you know <trunc>t</trunc>to find out why she hasn't received this and what what she's has done or hasn't done to try and get it erm but she's too tired so I'll I'll phone them tomorrow afternoon but er I might have to go down there er which will be a nice excuse to go to to go to <anon type="place"/> you know? cos I can get cheap</u>
<u n="97" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0281">well I can get cheap flights now erm I'm on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s erm <trunc>f</trunc> list you know for erm you know if you worked for I've starting doing it now have you noticed? saying you know you know? er she has been working for <anon type="place"/> for over twenty years and they have they're allowed to nominate two people <pause dur="short"/> for erm concessions they have a concession</u>
<u n="99" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="100" who="S0281">and you get standby flights and you get them really cheaply like when I came back from China</u>
<u n="101" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="102" who="S0281">sixty quid</u>
<u n="103" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="104" who="S0281">it cost me more to pay for my second bag</u>
<u n="105" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="106" who="S0281">than it did for the flight back</u>
<u n="107" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="108" who="S0281">so I I can</u>
<u n="109" who="S0355" trans="overlap">unbelievable</u>
<u n="110" who="S0281">I know isn't it? but erm I <trunc>c</trunc> I could so I could get a cheap flight down there and try and sort out this business about pensions <pause dur="short"/> so that's what I was just trying to phone her about but er so afterwards so after we finished chatting er I went to <anon type="place"/> to find out where this language school is so I I knew where it would be for my appointment at half past three</u>
<u n="111" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0281">and it was I I went through the arcade and when you get the outside the other <trunc>arc</trunc> er the the other end of the arcade right in front of me this huge poster language school and I thought okay right so then I came back here and got changed and went down there er for an interview a very friendly DoS</u>
<u n="113" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="114" who="S0281">erm lovely lady and er she's only been doing the job for a few weeks</u>
<u n="115" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="116" who="S0281">and cos I've done that job twice you know before director of studies and er she was er she was the one it is quite a small school but erm er she was all <unclear/> they do IELTS preparation down there and of course that's my speciality you know and er she said well now I've got the DoS's job responsibilities I I've had to er handover teaching IELTS to somebody else and she said you would be perfect for that you know? so erm we spoke for oh it must have been about forty minutes</u>
<u n="117" who="S0355">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0281">and basically er it's to start with and I I didn't really expect any more actually but er they they don't know from one week to another how many students they've got and she said she said I think I'm she does it on Thursday her schedule for the following week and she said is that alright and if I just phone you up and say well can you do this or can you do that? and I said yeah I said er because it would be good to get back into the swing of teaching again you know cos er I haven't taught for a few months and er to do something positive the the pay is pretty low but just to to get back into it would be good and obviously you know to to get out and meet people you know as well as you know teaching so unusual afternoon really</u>
<u n="119" who="S0355">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0281">and er quite positive in some ways <pause dur="short"/> yeah so er you had a nice relaxing afternoon didn't you?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0355">yeah I suppose so</u>
<u n="122" who="S0281">you mean you mean you didn't?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0355" trans="overlap">it's very tiring</u>
<u n="124" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh I know you were absolutely exhausted <pause dur="short"/> it must be accumulation that's been building up for some time and it's not just er from one day to the next there's a there's a</u>
<u n="125" who="S0355">possibly I don't know</u>
<u n="126" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I'm sure no I'm sure I mentioned to you last night you know and you seem really wound up like a spring you know all tension there but you see</u>
<u n="127" who="S0355" trans="overlap">was I?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0281">yeah lately and you seem much more relaxed today</u>
<u n="129" who="S0355">well it's probably diet that's what it is</u>
<u n="130" who="S0281" trans="overlap">do you reckon?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0355">yeah yeah sure yeah diet with with erm with er diabetics</u>
<u n="132" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well you only you only started it today will it take effect already?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0355">well look how quickly a drink takes effect but it's it's just stuff you put in your body isn't it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0281">or don't</u>
<u n="135" who="S0355">what?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0281">or don't put in your body</u>
<u n="137" who="S0355">or don't er put in your body that's it isn't it? I mean</u>
<u n="138" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0355">camomile tea was a good idea</u>
<u n="140" who="S0281" trans="overlap">here's here's to your your diet</u>
<u n="141" who="S0355">oh yes cheers</u>
<u n="142" who="S0281">cheers</u>
<u n="143" who="S0355"><pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0281">I think you're a very brave chap doing all three things that are more or less at the same time giving up smoking giving up drinking more <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll drink to that <vocal desc="laugh"/> well to to all intents and purposes</u>
<u n="145" who="S0355">yes thank you</u>
<u n="146" who="S0281">and erm and now your your diet but you're it's it's it's not only wise I mean it's more than wise it's absolutely necessary isn't it? especially the diet</u>
<u n="147" who="S0355">but I think one of the biggest things is stopping smoking</u>
<u n="148" who="S0281" trans="overlap">was it?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0355">and the next one is diet and the next one is drinking</u>
<u n="150" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="151" who="S0355" trans="overlap">those are the orders I'm I'm putting it in difficulty for me</u>
<u n="152" who="S0281">yeah you're you're into your third week now of giving up smoking</u>
<u n="153" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I quite liked smoking</u>
<u n="154" who="S0281">yeah I know but you haven't made a big deal of it</u>
<u n="155" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and it does choke me up and it makes me feel depressed and it makes me get stomach gives me erm indigestion and there's lots of things that smoking does that I really don't like</u>
<u n="156" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0355">so but it's the thing that I do enjoy smoking</u>
<u n="158" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0355">but erm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but you you don't</u>
<u n="161" who="S0355">but then again I don't and there's too many things that I when I smoke it depresses me it's depressing</u>
<u n="162" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah you you don't usually do things in half measures do you? you whatever you do you usually put everything into it and that includes the vices as well as work and and and</u>
<u n="163" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes you could say that</u>
<u n="164" who="S0281">virtues and everything really is er</u>
<u n="165" who="S0355">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0281">so you're not you weren't a chain smoker but sometimes not far off</u>
<u n="167" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that's true</u>
<u n="168" who="S0281">it was it was just one after another wasn't it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0355">it's true</u>
<u n="170" who="S0281">I mean look when I brought that carton back for you</u>
<u n="171" who="S0355">oh that's fatal but I'd be the same with a box of chocolates or a bottle of wine or</u>
<u n="172" who="S0281">I started so I'll finish <vocal desc="laugh"/> I I I feel I feel the same often with a bottle of wine</u>
<u n="173" who="S0355">it's called dipsomania <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0281">here's to intemperance oh no my glass is nearly empty</u>
<u n="175" who="S0355">oh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0281">well I like to er <pause dur="short"/> do you want some more?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0355">yeah go on twist my arm <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0281">I like to <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> a stress free day not have to get up early you know the alarm I used to hate that so wake up when your body tells you you've had enough sleep</u>
<u n="179" who="S0355">who this is your perfect morning?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0281">well it's my ideal type of day</u>
<u n="181" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="182" who="S0281">and I get up when I don't need any more sleep</u>
<u n="183" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="184" who="S0281">and then do something useful er if I can for most of the day I mean like today I was meeting somebody job interview coming back doing my CV you know?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="186" who="S0281">and I've only just stopped now right? so now I feel like well it's the end of the day I deserve a drink <pause dur="short"/> yeah? so <pause dur="short"/> it's er but I feel that to have a a reasonably a reasonable day I need to have a combination of work effort anyway and erm some kind of reward at the end of it to relax do you feel the same? do you feel you need to do something usually?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0355">mm erm no I think it's a dangerous thing really to think like that I think I believe that <pause dur="short"/> to <pause dur="short"/> because then you're dependent it creates a dependency</u>
<u n="188" who="S0281">well it doesn't have to I mean it's that's it's not it's only lately that er</u>
<u n="189" who="S0355">I'm saying no you asked me a question</u>
<u n="190" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0355"><unclear/> you thought about it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0281">yeah okay</u>
<u n="193" who="S0355">but it was your you'd earnt it or that you know or what <trunc>phra</trunc> what was the phrase you used not that you'd earnt it you deserved it or?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0281">yeah something like that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0355">so erm <pause dur="short"/> I have to look at stuff like that because I basically am an alcoholic</u>
<u n="196" who="S0281" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0355">and I have to and because I have er trouble with my liver and I've been warned that if I drink it would kill me if I went back to drinking because I'm quite on the edge of drinking and I still drink a bit but <pause dur="short"/> erm and that drinking has caused my diabetes the fatty liver has caused my diabetes as well erm <pause dur="short"/> and I'm well aware of sort of the internal voice that makes excuses for myself and allows me to do things that aren't good for me</u>
<u n="198" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0355">I'd much rather say oh well <trunc>f</trunc>fuck it you know I I know this is going to kill me I know it's not good for me but I'm gonna have it anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0355">and rather than to</u>
<u n="202" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0355">kick myself and say well I've earned this I justify this I don't you know I have to say this makes me this is this takes away some of my pain <vocal desc="laugh"/> or the pain of life and er but and you know it's bullshit <pause dur="short"/> continually we fool ourselves there's something in us that keeps us fooling ourselves and I'm well aware that <pause dur="short"/> that there's plenty within me that needs to be addressed as it were and needs needs to be worked on and yeah and that's fine I do it in my own way I think I do it in the quiet of my room thinking</u>
<u n="204" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you'll go blind</u>
<u n="205" who="S0355">well I'm just going to do it until I need glasses</u>
<u n="206" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that why you've got so many pairs?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0355">absolutely</u>
<u n="208" who="S0281">I've never known anybody with so many glasses as you've got <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're everywhere of all shapes and sizes</u>
<u n="209" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="210" who="S0281">and colours</u>
<u n="211" who="S0355">I know well my glasses</u>
<u n="212" who="S0281" trans="overlap">how <trunc>ma</trunc> have you ever counted them up?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0355">no well basically I use two strengths of glasses I use one point oh I use I think one point fives for work and if I need to look at something really close up in detail I need two point fives and then I have different eye glasses and hand glasses to to erm magnifying glasses to see what I'm doing at different levels if I need to really look at something really intricately erm so all my glasses are in doubles I've got a white pair of one point fives and a white pair of two point fives and because I buy them at the Pound Shop</u>
<u n="214" who="S0281">ah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0355">they only cost me a pound a pair and</u>
<u n="216" who="S0281" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0355">I so I use them also as fashion fashionable</u>
<u n="218" who="S0281" trans="overlap">fashion statements</u>
<u n="219" who="S0355">I like them fashion statements so I've got white ones I've got erm all different types of ones in both sizes then I've got the ones like like I'm holding in my hands these Big Al like ones that someone had that worked for me but er they had them at a dinner party and said er I like your glasses I'll swap you mine for yours and okay and and I've also got another pair of glasses that I bought for a pound or two pounds and they're Specsaver glasses and probably cost a hundred quid from the market for two quid that er are in my strength but what happens is with my type of work that I do I scratch damage break or lose quite a considerable amount of glasses</u>
<u n="220" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0355">and so the amount of glasses I'm probably looking at monetarily in terms probably if I said fifteen pounds it would probably be too much and probably probably you're looking at about ten pounds so it's ten pounds twelve quid</u>
<u n="222" who="S0281">I wouldn't have thought you'd have got through all that many pair pairs of glasses being a male escort?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0355">well it depends on what you're doing</u>
<u n="224" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0355">it depends what you're doing you know? I I don't have eyes in the back of my head but it <unclear/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so then you'd wear two pairs of glasses? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0355">if that's what you're thinking yeah so that that's it really <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0281">I'm gonna go to <anon type="place"/> tomorrow to see about</u>
<u n="229" who="S0355" trans="overlap">have you?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0281">erm</u>
<event desc="sound of trombone playing"/>
<u n="231" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> to see about this er charity thing</u>
<u n="232" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0281">charity shop business <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0355">well good luck just remember to get the save the good stuff for me</u>
<u n="235" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I'll give you</u>
<u n="236" who="S0355">and when I come in give it to me cheap</u>
<u n="237" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah I'll give you a call</u>
<u n="238" who="S0355">alright? I'm gonna find out when you're on the till and I'll come in there and you give me a you say oh that's a quid that's that much alright okay?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0355">well done</u>
<u n="241" who="S0281">charity begins at home</u>
<u n="242" who="S0355">mm that's why they should be called charity shops <pause dur="short"/> not for the two hundred and fifty thousand a year they pay their the guy who runs it yeah it'll be interesting to find out how much they do pay the bloke who runs it won't it?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0281">well the</u>
<u n="244" who="S0355" trans="overlap">interesting</u>
<u n="245" who="S0281">the little I've found out about this so far is that there's normally a manager or manageress gets paid</u>
<u n="246" who="S0355">oh yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0281">and the rest are volunteers</u>
<u n="248" who="S0355">right well the managers are paid quite well I believe</u>
<u n="249" who="S0281">are they?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0355">so I believe</u>
<u n="251" who="S0281">it's funny that cos I I went to the other one erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0355">oh yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0281">and I haven't heard anything from them</u>
<u n="254" who="S0355">yeah well that's strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0355">what did you leave? did you leave a er?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0281">well I just left a form but it wasn't so detailed as</u>
<u n="258" who="S0355" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="259" who="S0281">oh you're operating on your hand?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0355">yeah I'm cutting open my hand with a penknife to get a rather large wooden splinter out that has gone septic in my hand but they say that's the best thing you can do with wood to let it go septic and the pus forms around the wood and when you squeeze it just pops out which has just happened here it just has popped out oh my god that's a long one look I don't know how good your</u>
<u n="261" who="S0281">oh my eyes are useless</u>
<u n="262" who="S0355">really?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0355">god that's just come out of my hand here you are put that on and have a look</u>
<u n="265" who="S0281"><pause dur="long"/> it's just blur</u>
<u n="266" who="S0355">sorry?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281">it's just blur</u>
<u n="268" who="S0355">really?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0355">oh <pause dur="short"/> you can't see that?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0281">oh yeah with if I don't wear glasses up close it's fine it is big isn't it?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0355">mm that was in my finger</u>
<u n="273" who="S0281">almost a thorn rather than a splinter</u>
<u n="274" who="S0355">really yeah yeah no but it was yeah it looks like a thorn but it is a it is a splinter oh it was sort of paining me that was</u>
<u n="275" who="S0281">paining <unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0355" trans="overlap">so what are you going to do with your life?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0281">well I could define that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> try and get a job and somehow look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know what they say trust to the universe to sort everything out well that's what I'm doing at the moment I'm I'm trying to be positive and and not let the situation get me down and I think I'm getting better <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said today she said oh you sound very good today she said compared to you know what I was before</u>
<u n="278" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="279" who="S0281">mm I think I'm I'm moving in an upward direction of course it oscillates from day to day but generally it's it's getting better and er</u>
<u n="280" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0281">I finished my my last antidepressant last night and</u>
<u n="282" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="283" who="S0281">I'm due to go to the doctor on Thursday so</u>
<u n="284" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281">it'll be interesting to see if two days without them has any effect</u>
<u n="286" who="S0355">do you think they have helped you?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">I don't know because unless I go without them there won't be any way to compare if it's natural or not</u>
<u n="288" who="S0355">don't you remember what you were like before you started taking them?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0281">I certainly do but is that due to the pills or your help and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s help or a combination of both? and my or myself and and me helping myself and <trunc>i</trunc>it's I don't know</u>
<u n="290" who="S0355">I don't know right but they know there you go then</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281">er but I'll I'll certainly get some more</u>
<u n="292" who="S0355">will you?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0355">what even if you feel okay?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281">well if I don't get any more I I mean I can do an experiment right? er and go without them and see if there's any difference if there's no difference then I can do without them but</u>
<u n="296" who="S0355" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281">if I slip back into it again</u>
<u n="298" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281">I'll I'll need them on hand as it were</u>
<u n="300" who="S0355">I'm with you</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281">no but I that's not</u>
<u n="302" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well ask the doctor's advice is my if I can put it to you</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well I will yeah yeah but that's not why I'm going to see the doctor the doctor I'm going to see the doctor about my skin</u>
<u n="304" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281">cos I wanna see if if this have you seen noticed this thing on my the side of my face?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah I think it's er I don't think it's erm I I I've looked a lot at malignant tumours on the on the er er web or net web or net?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I'm I'm both no no <trunc>we</trunc> web is one particular site on the net</u>
<u n="308" who="S0355" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="309" who="S0281">the net is a general</u>
<u n="310" who="S0355">then I look at a lot on the net about skin cancers because I am particularly vulnerable to them</u>
<u n="311" who="S0281">are you?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0355">one I'm fair skinned two I've been working with chemicals and er erm er er light erm ultraviolet radiation I've been under <unclear/> causes that yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="314" who="S0355">so I have to be very careful about my skin</u>
<u n="315" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0355">cos er I I can you know you get skin cancer</u>
<u n="317" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0355">from my job and erm what you have on your visage is not in my humble opinion well it's just not a a a er it's not a a a a a bin er what do they call what's the opposite of benign?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0281">malignant</u>
<u n="320" who="S0355">I don't think it's malignant skin cancer I think it probably is a skin cancer but I don't think it is erm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0281" trans="overlap">malignant</u>
<u n="322" who="S0355">malignant I think it's er and there's a vast array of stuff you get them with flaps growing on your skin and stuff like this and <unclear/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and no I've had I've had this develop in the last week I'm <trunc>unzip</trunc> I'm unzipping my trousers no</u>
<u n="324" who="S0355">but that's called an erection <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="326" who="S0355">oh sorry no right my god are you kidding me? what the fuck is that?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0281">I don't know</u>
<u n="328" who="S0355">you haven't been to the doctor's with that?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="330" who="S0355">fucking why not? and does it itch?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0355">oh shit come over here</u>
<u n="333" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well it's just like a heat rash it's getting it's getting better</u>
<u n="334" who="S0355">is it?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0281">yeah it's not so itchy as it was <pause dur="long"/> there's a spot that's developed there</u>
<u n="336" who="S0355">yeah well I don't think it's scabies if that was scabies fucking hell I'd be running for the door</u>
<u n="337" who="S0281">scabies</u>
<u n="338" who="S0355">I had well I had scabies a couple of years ago and I literally washed every fucking thing and I ended up stripped off my <pause dur="short"/> what is that then?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0281">I think it's a heat rash</u>
<u n="340" who="S0355">are you hot?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0281">not now but I was when it developed and I think it just spread</u>
<u n="342" who="S0355">I'd get that looked at immediately I've never seen anything <trunc>l</trunc>like it</u>
<u n="343" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="344" who="S0355">fuck me man</u>
<u n="345" who="S0281">oh well I'm going to see the doctor on Thursday</u>
<u n="346" who="S0355">good god <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's scabies but I hope to fucking <trunc>g</trunc> it's not up your legs or anything?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0281">no no</u>
<u n="348" who="S0355">gee whiz</u>
<u n="349" who="S0281">maybe it's rabies or scabies</u>
<u n="350" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0355">my god that looks awful</u>
<u n="352" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0355">god</u>
<u n="354" who="S0281">there's always something isn't there? before Christmas it was a stomach virus and now skin thing</u>
<u n="355" who="S0355">sorry?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0281">before Christmas there was a stomach problem</u>
<u n="357" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0281">and now a skin thing</u>
<u n="359" who="S0355">good god is it? well the other thing is er <pause dur="short"/> change of er washing powder that can sometimes do that</u>
<u n="360" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0355">erm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0281">maybe it is</u>
<u n="363" who="S0355">have you did you ever wear any of those shirts that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got you directly against the skin without the?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0355"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0281">no no</u>
<u n="367" who="S0355">you always want to wash them first if you get <unclear/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no yeah well she did she did</u>
<u n="369" who="S0355">okay</u>
<u n="370" who="S0281">erm no I always er well in winter I wear er thermals yeah and I think maybe that's what did it cos at night it got too hot although I felt yeah I didn't feel hot when I went to sleep but <pause dur="short"/> anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I would get her get her opinion I mean</u>
<u n="372" who="S0281">well I will on</u>
<u n="373" who="S0355">god</u>
<u n="374" who="S0281">as I say it's getting better so it's not as itchy as some itchy as</u>
<u n="375" who="S0355">I tell you what it could be as well it could be er what's that nervous er complaint erm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0281">anorexia nervosa <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0355">what is it? shingles? it's not shingles is it?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0281">I don't know what shingles is</u>
<u n="379" who="S0355">shingles is quite painful it's a nervous complaint <unclear/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0281">no it's not painful oh talking about medical things or things medical erm remember I asked you about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and you you said he had er phlebitis?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0355">yes well</u>
<u n="382" who="S0281" trans="overlap">is is that spelt with a P H?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="384" who="S0281">that's what Nixon had wasn't it?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0355">president Nixon?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0355">oh was it?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0281">I think so that's er that just springs to my mind well and you said it's er a vein thing? it's erm it's it's was that it?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0355">well it is a possible phlebitis I mean I don't know he had a a phlebitis that I sort of looked at on the on the web was er on the net was erm I think it was caused by erm by infection I think so erm but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s one was er caused by I've forgotten what phlebitis was now I looked it up at the time if you remember erm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0281">is he alright now?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0355">he seemed alright when I saw him today yes</u>
<u n="392" who="S0281">was he at work?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0355">he was er no I saw I saw him yesterday at work</u>
<u n="394" who="S0281">oh he's back at work then so</u>
<u n="395" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0281">then he must be alright</u>
<u n="397" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0281">good <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0355">yeah he's back at work erm and</u>
<u n="400" who="S0281">I'm gonna put some water on</u>
<u n="401" who="S0355">you're going to put some water on?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0281">yeah I'm gonna have some pot noodles</u>
<u n="403" who="S0355">pot noodles are you?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0281">cos er I didn't have lunch today</u>
<u n="405" who="S0355">right so you're having your lunch now are you?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0281">well no I had my lunch before this is er supper</u>
<u n="407" who="S0355">right and are you still recording here?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0281">yep</u>
<u n="409" who="S0355">what do you think the quality of these recordings are? do people phone you up and say look what is this you've sent me?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0281">it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="411" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="412" who="S0281">I mean quality in terms of technical quality I mean can they hear it is there any background noise?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="414" who="S0281">or quality in terms of interesting conversation no well the latter apparently doesn't matter oh it rhymes erm from what I understand about it it's recording English as it's spoke</u>
<u n="415" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="416" who="S0281">today by</u>
<u n="417" who="S0355" trans="overlap">today's English</u>
<u n="418" who="S0281">by by British</u>
<u n="419" who="S0355">by yesterday's speaking</u>
<u n="420" who="S0281">yesterday's speaking and yes today's English but yesterday's speaking there you go and somebody is gonna be listening to us in the future and using it for their dissertation</u>
<u n="421" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="422" who="S0281">maybe I don't know</u>
<u n="423" who="S0355">right well then that's a very grave responsibility that I've got here in my</u>
<u n="424" who="S0281">not at all</u>
<u n="425" who="S0355">throat</u>
<u n="426" who="S0281">not at all ah so do you wanna stop and watch the TV?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0355">I'm easy</u>
<u n="428" who="S0281">Oh we know that but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0355">well not really I mean I just come in every night and you're always on that</u>
<u n="430" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="431" who="S0355">so I never have a conversation with you so this is about the closest thing I ever get to have a conversation with you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0281">sorry</u>
<u n="433" who="S0355">that's alright</u>
<u n="434" who="S0281">but I've got I've gotta get these er these things done</u>
<u n="435" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I know you have but you know you have to say for yourself is it is it working all day and all night is that because that's what effectively what you're doing is that good for you? I don't know it might be</u>
<u n="436" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well to a certain extent what would I be doing if I wasn't doing that?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0355">well we could have a chat like this</u>
<u n="438" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="439" who="S0355">hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how are you? look at that we could share a TV we could watch TV together well what do you think of that?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0281" trans="overlap">or could we we could play a game</u>
<u n="441" who="S0355">or we could play a game yes we could <unclear/> things</u>
<u n="442" who="S0281" trans="overlap">okay okay then I'll <trunc>tr</trunc> I'll try</u>
<u n="443" who="S0355" trans="overlap">so I'll come in every night and you're doing that and then I go oh fuck that yeah and I talk to you and oh look at that and you could go yeah well you don't even go yeah you go mm and I go well alright that's boring er</u>
<u n="444" who="S0281">sorry</u>
<u n="445" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it well look don't be sorry it's the way that it is it's the way that it is but I just think to myself is this good for him? is it good for him? is it good for me? you know</u>
<u n="446" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well it's something that it's it's something I need to get done right?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I understand that</u>
<u n="448" who="S0281">once it's done it's done</u>
<u n="449" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I understand that I understand that</u>
<u n="450" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and like today I was working on my CV I've got a list of schools that I've got to contact with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gave me</u>
<u n="451" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="452" who="S0281">right? erm and but I've got other things that are coming up that won't hopefully you know make my life so mundane and stuck at you know I need to do I need to do something and that's why I <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to do this charity shop thing but then I've got er some work coming up hopefully</u>
<u n="453" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0281">erm she also gave me a good lead about <anon type="place"/> you know I mentioned <anon type="place"/> that that company you know? you know? anyway er they're very big erm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="456" who="S0281">and they er <pause dur="short"/> as far as I can gather er are like a job agency they they market jobs er for different erm academic institutions</u>
<u n="457" who="S0355" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="458" who="S0281">so she suggested going she said out they're out by <anon type="place"/> er <anon type="place"/> University erm so I could go out there and she said you know very often she said they're very busy and she said erm I she said I know somebody who went there and er presented themselves you know like instead of just <trunc>ap</trunc>applying online and said well here I am I'm looking for a job blah blah blah and I think I'll do that as well so</u>
<u n="459" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well I think that's a marvellous thing to do</u>
<u n="460" who="S0281">so I'll I'll do that and today when I was walking er on my way to meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er I saw there's another school just up the road here called <anon type="place"/> er I don't remember</u>
<u n="461" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0281">erm so I'll pop in there since it's so close and er I've got lots of er CVs to to send to all these schools that I haven't sent to erm so and tomorrow so I've got to phone <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've got to erm go to the er meet go to er <anon type="place"/> erm I wanna go to the library check out and see if they've got a book I want erm Thursday the doctor so er and yeah try just try and keep myself busy</u>
<u n="463" who="S0355">yeah no you're doing well you are doing well <pause dur="short"/> you're doing well and and that and that's fantastic and you're looking better and and you're looking better your head's in a better space and erm and it's great and that's that's great you are you're looking er looking better your head's in a better space everything yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah no it's good <pause dur="short"/> it's good you know er but I know you hurt and I know that you've taken a few arrows and I'm sorry about that and er and always <unclear/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah those bloody Indians exterminate them</u>
<u n="465" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> your racism <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0281">it's like you remember it reminds me of that old joke do you remember there's the er Lone Ranger and Tonto?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0355">like what do you mean white man?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0281">that's right</u>
<event desc="sound of trombone playing"/>
<u n="469" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="sound of trombone playing"/>
<u n="470" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="472" who="S0281">more than three notes consecutive notes is a bit of a struggle at the moment but good start</u>
<u n="473" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well it it was saying on there there's one note there</u>
<event desc="sound of trombone playing"/>
<u n="474" who="S0355">oh that's a</u>
<event desc="sound of trombone playing"/>
<u n="475" who="S0355">oh I don't know I think it's because</u>
<u n="476" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but that's called that's called a slide trombone isn't it?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0355">it is</u>
<u n="478" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so how is that different from another trombone that's not slide? I thought all trombones <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0355"><vocal desc="cough"/> er there's a trombone which is just like that which is like a big bugle</u>
<u n="480" who="S0281">but they still call it a trombone?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0281">not a bugle?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0355">well it's like they don't call a a</u>
<u n="484" who="S0281" trans="overlap">a spade a spade</u>
<u n="485" who="S0355">bass cello a violin do they? <pause dur="short"/> because you can't get it under your chin <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0281" trans="overlap">okay here's your here's your <trunc>st</trunc> here's here's your musical <trunc>st</trunc></u>
<u n="487" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they look the same shape they're both with bows they've got the same amount of strings one's a little thing you can hold under your chin and play and then you get a viola which is a bigger violin don't you? then they go to a cello and then a bass</u>
<u n="488" who="S0281">okay is your is your</u>
<u n="489" who="S0355" trans="overlap">but they're all the same shape aren't they?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that's your musical starter for ten</u>
<u n="491" who="S0355">you get the piccolo go on then</u>
<u n="492" who="S0281">what's a glockenspiel?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0355">it's like a a a thing you hit with hammers and er like a like a</u>
<u n="494" who="S0281">a wife?</u>
<u n="495" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0355">yes like a wife what we call wife</u>
<u n="497" who="S0281" trans="overlap">a musical wife eh? you want some more?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0355">yes I want some more</u>
<u n="499" who="S0281">yeah there you go help yourself</u>
<u n="500" who="S0355">glockenspiel and it's like a thing you hit with hammers like er erm a little thing what what do they call them? er you know like er erm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0281">a dwarf?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0355">a dwarf you hit the hammers with dwarfs with hammers erm well what I mean it's like a kind of a glockenspiel</u>
<u n="503" who="S0281">xylophone?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0355">and it's like a bass or a or a or grown ups I forget what the the other one's called but you hit them with with things xylophone</u>
<u n="505" who="S0281">that's what I said</u>
<u n="506" who="S0355">it's like a big xylophone</u>
<u n="507" who="S0281" trans="overlap">xylophone</u>
<u n="508" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0281">because when I was watching that programme about Tubular Bells last night and the glockenspiel came</u>
<u n="510" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0281">and erm it's and it said glockenspiel <shift new="singing"/> da da da down down down da da da la down down down <shift new="normal"/> and I thought what instrument is that? did you? it's really interesting about the way he explained it why why? cos it's so repetitive at least side one is and do you know why it is although it's so repetitive that it still grabs our attention it holds our attention? apparently so I was listening to it last night as he explained that he wrote it that the there were seven notes to the bar followed by eight notes and then seven and then eight <shift new="singing"/> da da la down down down down <shift new="normal"/> seven <shift new="singing"/> da da la down down down down down down down <shift new="normal"/> eight and and that's why he wrote it like that so that it's it is repetitive there's there's this theme running through it on side one that er everything flows a crescendo sometimes</u>
<u n="512" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0281">which is great and er but there's <trunc>s</trunc>some other musician who apparently performed the work in two thousand and eleven erm explained it that erm it's it is repetitive but it takes us in different ways and different places but in the end like any good work of art erm music brings us back and therefore encapsulates the whole thing in a</u>
<u n="514" who="S0355">it's like a trip</u>
<u n="515" who="S0281">in a way yes it's a musical trip</u>
<u n="516" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0281">yes erm so and that's why he reckons it's a perennial classic apparently it's up to sixteen million copies have been sold so far I <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="518" who="S0355" trans="overlap">is that all? sixteen million is that all?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0355">well it's not a lot really when you think of the Bible how many copies of that have been sold?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0281">I don't know but that's been going a long time Tubular Bells was in seventy-three I remember the do you remember the first time you heard it? I remember I was</u>
<u n="522" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="523" who="S0281">I was in this grotty bedsit and just off erm god I know where it is and I can't remember the road but at that time we were I don't think we were sharing a girlfriend but we'd we do you <trunc>reme</trunc> I can't what's her name? she wasn't particularly attractive but erm oh</u>
<u n="524" who="S0355">who are you talking about you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0281">no you and I</u>
<u n="526" who="S0355">we were sharing a oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0281"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's right yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0355">you shagged my girlfriend?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0281">she wasn't your girlfriend at the time</u>
<u n="530" who="S0355" trans="overlap">you had a relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you bastard</u>
<u n="531" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but you knew very well I did</u>
<u n="532" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0281">but at that time it was about yes</u>
<u n="534" who="S0355" trans="overlap">no I didn't no I didn't</u>
<u n="535" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="536" who="S0355">you know very well I didn't</u>
<u n="537" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0355">it's alright</u>
<u n="539" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0355">you can <trunc>h</trunc>have it as a get me back for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0355">no my relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was purely sexual and I didn't love her at all alright?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0355">yeah I had no respect for her whatsoever</u>
<u n="545" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you know she she she told me erm well just shortly after we arrived in erm in er in <anon type="place"/> and I'd got I told you about the story about me getting <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> over and when he er first arrived he was sharing our our flat</u>
<u n="546" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="547" who="S0281">and I went up to er <anon type="place"/> which is er a holiday resort <unclear/> on the east coast up north and er for a conference and er while I when I came back it was just for the weekend and when I came back she said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tried to er seduce me and I was what?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0355" trans="overlap">who said this?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0281"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0355"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tried to seduce her?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well that's what she said that's what she said yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0355">well I'd probably believe her</u>
<u n="553" who="S0281">and I confronted <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with this</u>
<u n="554" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0281">when I saw him just before I left and he said</u>
<u n="556" who="S0355" trans="overlap">what what this time? what now?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well the last time the last time I saw him</u>
<u n="558" who="S0355">oh really?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0281">I I told him <unclear/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0355" trans="overlap">and he denied it?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0281">as you would</u>
<u n="564" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well there you go of course he would deny it just <unclear/> still here I'm just going to the loo <unclear/> you can listen to me peeing if you like</u>
<u n="565" who="S0281">can I?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0355">okay</u>
<u n="567" who="S0281">okay can I bring the recorder in to the loo?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0355">you can't watch though</u>
<u n="569" who="S0281">well it's not it's only er audio recording it's er not visual <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> oh listen to the rhythm of the pouring rain telling me just what I fool I've been I wish that I could away <unclear/> rain please tell me that <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/> come on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wherefore art thou <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> here we all are sitting in a rainbow cor blimey missus Jones here's your Bert's lumbago mustn't grumble doodly doo dum de do do <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0355">ah here I am</u>
<u n="571" who="S0281"><shift new="singing"/> stop me from grooving <unclear/> lazy Sunday afternoon <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0355">so are we still recording?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0281">we are we are indeed</u>
<u n="574" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="575" who="S0281">but not for much longer because I think we need to watch some some TV or something something interesting if anything is on that's interesting</u>
<u n="576" who="S0355">why?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0281">well okay well we don't we don't have to we can carry on</u>
<u n="578" who="S0355">well it's nice to talk I haven't talked to you for about ten days</u>
<u n="579" who="S0281" trans="overlap">okay let's you do exaggerate</u>
<u n="580" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well good <vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0355">bless you bless you</u>
<u n="582" who="S0281">oh</u>
<event desc="sound of trombone playing"/>
<u n="583" who="S0281">there we go</u>
<u n="584" who="S0355">it clears the sinuses and I have this Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0281">what's that?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0355">smokeable material</u>
<u n="587" who="S0281">what is it?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0355">it's Afghani</u>
<u n="589" who="S0281">oh really?</u>
<u n="590" who="S0355">no it's Lebanese</u>
<u n="591" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="592" who="S0355">none of your bloody English rubbish</u>
<u n="593" who="S0281">okay</u>
<u n="594" who="S0355">ah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0281">interesting the evening is getting interestinger and interestinger</u>
<u n="596" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="597" who="S0281">do you know why we say <trunc>m</trunc>more interesting rather than interestinger?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0355">because we're not American</u>
<u n="599" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0355">thank god thank god that we're not American thank god I get down on the ground every morning and suddenly think god I'm not American</u>
<u n="601" who="S0281">Allah Akbar thank god I'm not American</u>
<u n="602" who="S0355" trans="overlap">thank god I am not American <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0281">well somebody's got to be <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0355">oh yeah but what about why don't you just leave that job to the native Americans eh? if there's any left</u>
<u n="605" who="S0281">well it's a bit</u>
<u n="606" who="S0355" trans="overlap">let them get on with it</u>
<u n="607" who="S0281">it's a bit too late</u>
<u n="608" who="S0355">let them enjoy being American</u>
<u n="609" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that was that was a great line in that film last night do you remember?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0355">yeah what the ending of it?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0281">yeah do you remember what he said?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0355">yeah he said</u>
<u n="613" who="S0281">he said America's not a country it's a business</u>
<u n="614" who="S0355">it's not a community and it's not a country it's a corporation <vocal desc="laugh"/> now fucking pay me</u>
<u n="615" who="S0281">oh talking about movies as we just were <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she erm she met Mel Gibson when she went to <anon type="place"/> recently</u>
<u n="616" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh wonderful how amazing</u>
<u n="617" who="S0281">yeah apparently erm how is the what's the connection? erm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0355">where do you keep your tobacco?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0281">oh it's in my coat pocket</u>
<u n="620" who="S0355">where do you keep your coat?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0281">in your bedroom</u>
<u n="622" who="S0355">what colour coat is it?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0281">black</u>
<u n="624" who="S0355">black and did she speak to him for very long?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0281">I don't know I don't we didn't pursue that er that line <pause dur="long"/> I know what the connection is the her her her man her partner erm the one who's got the villa with the swimming pool</u>
<u n="626" who="S0355" trans="overlap">he's got the what?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0281">he's got a villa with a swimming pool</u>
<u n="628" who="S0355">oh I thought you said Godzilla</u>
<u n="629" who="S0281">well you are a little hard of hearing</u>
<u n="630" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="631" who="S0281">do you want do you want me to say that again? you are a bit hard of hearing</u>
<u n="632" who="S0355">thank you</u>
<u n="633" who="S0281">so yes he's her fellow she's living in luxury at the moment</u>
<u n="634" who="S0355">who's this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0281">no it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're not paying attention are you?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is</u>
<u n="637" who="S0281"><shift new="singing"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> baby is it you? <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah but I didn't know if it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saying it about someone or if it was er yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought er I thought erm she was a lot of fun <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0281">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was a way back</u>
<u n="640" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0281">she was</u>
<u n="642" who="S0355">yeah I I enjoyed her company</u>
<u n="643" who="S0281">yeah she was <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what she's doing if she's still alive?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh she's a very old lady she's she was ill she got ill she had erm she had an illness that sort of laid her up I think</u>
<u n="645" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well she would be an old lady if she's our age wouldn't she?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0355">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who I used to work with in the erm medieval jousting wild west shows</u>
<u n="647" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0355">they had a kid together and er they erm yeah they had a child together er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his name was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what a lovely name cos she was a bit</u>
<u n="649" who="S0281">don't tell me his family name was bear</u>
<u n="650" who="S0355">huh I think he's in <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> or somewhere now like that who'd wanna go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is</u>
<u n="652" who="S0355">well there you go but er yeah <pause dur="long"/> that smells very dangerous of chemicals that that you're drinking it says hazard <unclear/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0281" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0355">well that's the container that's just the container that it's in</u>
<u n="655" who="S0281" trans="overlap">chicken laksa</u>
<u n="656" who="S0355">oh god</u>
<u n="657" who="S0281">rice noodle</u>
<u n="658" who="S0355">god</u>
<u n="659" who="S0281">puff pot</u>
<u n="660" who="S0355" trans="overlap">it smells very dangerous</u>
<u n="661" who="S0281">rice and noodle pot</u>
<u n="662" who="S0355">it it smells like something that when a firework goes off</u>
<u n="663" who="S0281" trans="overlap">rice noodles</u>
<u n="664" who="S0355">that's what it smells like</u>
<u n="665" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><trunc>ri</trunc>rice noodles in a laksa style curry sauce</u>
<u n="666" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0281">in a laxative style with coconut milk powder chicken and spices</u>
<u n="668" who="S0355">who's this for is this for people trying to infiltrate our society by understanding what the fuck we talk about? we talk the same rubbish as as everybody else don't we? when we're</u>
<u n="669" who="S0281"><unclear/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0355"><unclear/> I mean how long are we supposed to maintain the sanity of of being people? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0281">what would you have us be other than people? cockroaches?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I don't want to have anyone be anything because I'm not a power crazed maniac who dictates other people's lives it's up to them providing they don't hurt me I'm okay if they wanna be idiots and <unclear/> that's up to them what they wanna do</u>
<u n="673" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0355">but all I say is er you know as far as I wanna do is just keep a grip on reality reality is yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0281">which is what?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0355">well the contradiction is it is reality is getting out of it sometimes that's the reality of things that it's good to get out of it that's that's what it's good to do <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0281">I suppose reality is</u>
<u n="678" who="S0355" trans="overlap">but but that's the that's for me that's just for me it's not er I'm not basing that on anyone else that you know I try not to anybody else I try you know I am pretty vindictive if someone hurts me I weigh it up and I think well yeah I'll either do something immediately or I'll wait for them to do it to themselves or I'll wait and then do it to them so I'm just like anyone else I think just more honest</u>
<u n="679" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well you are many things</u>
<u n="680" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0281">but like anybody else you are not</u>
<u n="682" who="S0355">well that's yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you're a you're a one off</u>
<u n="684" who="S0355">well er exactly like everybody else</u>
<u n="685" who="S0281">well no</u>
<u n="686" who="S0355">everybody else is a one off</u>
<u n="687" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> yeah you know we're all unique but</u>
<u n="688" who="S0355" trans="overlap">because life keeps on with its contradiction all the time continuously</u>
<u n="689" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="690" who="S0355">doesn't it? I don't know</u>
<u n="691" who="S0281">there are so many people that race a very similar <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> there's only one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0355" trans="overlap">there's only one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0281"><shift new="singing"/> one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there's only one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0355">well in this you know there may be many many <trunc>ma</trunc> they say there are infinite someone's come up with this there are infinite parallel universes so there are there's infinite <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="695" who="S0281">there was one apparently on that erm that programme I watched last night about Tubular Bells there was a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in that</u>
<u n="696" who="S0355">ah really? what was he doing?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0281">I don't know playing playing the bells <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0355">what was he doing?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0281">you know how that became part?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0355">I'm sorry?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0281">do you remember how the Tubular Bells became part of the the whole concept?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0355">concept of what?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0281">the album apparently you know they got this manor</u>
<u n="704" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="705" who="S0281">and this is where they recorded all the artists and erm as fate would have it it just threw some person and meeting another person and he he found himself there and he had managed to</u>
<u n="706" who="S0355" trans="overlap">do you need to blow your nose?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0281">yes I do thank you erm he managed to put down on a two track tape recorder</u>
<u n="708" who="S0355">who was this?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0281">Mike Oldfield</u>
<u n="710" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="711" who="S0281">the erm the basic concept of the album and he recorded it on two tracks and played it</u>
<u n="712" who="S0355">on two tracks</u>
<u n="713" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0355">wow amazing</u>
<u n="715" who="S0281">and played it to er I think one of the ultimate producers of the album</u>
<u n="716" who="S0355">who produced it?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0281">er two guys and they I don't know their names</u>
<u n="718" who="S0355">oh I thought he produced it</u>
<u n="719" who="S0281">no he</u>
<u n="720" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0281">he er</u>
<u n="722" who="S0355">how amazing</u>
<u n="723" who="S0281">well anyway they found themselves in the recording in the manor</u>
<u n="724" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0281">where they recorded the album <pause dur="short"/> and they said they thought it was a great idea I mean revolutionary I mean</u>
<u n="726" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0281">the idea that <pause dur="short"/> one album both sides can comprise of of one single track never been done before and they said go for it and Richard Branson was saying that er he thought it was a great idea but at that time the cash flow wasn't great and they were just struggling to survive and he said</u>
<u n="728" who="S0355" trans="overlap">who Virgin Records were?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and that er they but they thought it was such a <trunc>gr</trunc> an innovative concept and great potential although musically speaking I mean Branson's favourite song apparently was er I'm a Batchelor Boy by Cliff Richards you know? so that</u>
<u n="730" who="S0355" trans="overlap">jesus christ</u>
<u n="731" who="S0281">that that was yeah I know so he had no idea er about the the quality of the music but he realised and was told of its potential and he said well yeah go ahead and they said well what do you need? and then Mike Oldfield wrote down a whole long list of all these different instruments that he needed including the glockenspiel and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="732" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="733" who="S0281">and he played every instrument on the album himself</u>
<u n="734" who="S0355">does he?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0355">god almighty</u>
<u n="737" who="S0281">and he was saying er what was the name of the the artist? I can't remember</u>
<u n="738" who="S0355">Mike Oldfield?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0281">no the the artist that some guy had been recording I can't remember who it was now some guy had been recording there before him and they're clearing out the studio and <pause dur="short"/> as he's waiting for the the the studio to be emptied there were these tubular bells and</u>
<u n="740" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="741" who="S0281">and he said hold on a minute <vocal desc="laugh"/> he said can I have these? yes yeah sure so that's how it started that's how</u>
<u n="742" who="S0355" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="743" who="S0281">and then he got er</u>
<u n="744" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh that was the start of it?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0281">no that was at the end of it well about halfway they were on their way to record it right?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0281">and and and they got Vivienne</u>
<u n="748" who="S0355" trans="overlap">what was the name of the album?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0281">well it hadn't been formulated then</u>
<u n="750" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="751" who="S0281">then it came from that and it came from it because er they introduced er into er an artist who was gonna do produce the cover and you remember that the cover of the Tubular Bells is like that?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="753" who="S0281">and everybody was blown away er by the art of of it <pause dur="short"/> and er and that's how it came about to be called Tubular Bells</u>
<u n="754" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's fantastic</u>
<u n="755" who="S0281">I mean <trunc>wh</trunc>when he'd he'd written it at least side one erm <pause dur="short"/> it hadn't been titled you know it's er so erm and then they they put down the first side and he had to he had to write a side two which is I think you know much weaker but er still incredibly interesting <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0355">oh god <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0281">oh my goodness curried noodles <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> da da la down down down down down down da down down down down down <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0355">well put it on let's listen</u>
<u n="759" who="S0281">I haven't got it</u>
<u n="760" who="S0355">well it's on the computer</u>
<u n="761" who="S0281">I don't think so</u>
<u n="762" who="S0355">oh god you come from <anon type="place"/> don't you? you can get anything on that computer just google it</u>
<u n="763" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah but the oh I see</u>
<u n="764" who="S0355">and you just google it Mike Oldfield</u>
<u n="765" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="766" who="S0355">and it'll play it you've come from <anon type="place"/> you get your look anything you wanna find out about anything any tune you want is on there</u>
<u n="767" who="S0281">I know</u>
<u n="768" who="S0355">christ almighty</u>
<u n="769" who="S0281">you do it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0355"><unclear/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0281">thank you sir <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0355">anything you want you can see him playing it</u>
<u n="773" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="774" who="S0355">you can see him do which recording do you want? you've got ten different recordings of him doing it</u>
<u n="775" who="S0281">I'm sure you're right</u>
<u n="776" who="S0355">it's amazing you can see the original where they do it on stage</u>
<u n="777" who="S0281">that <trunc>fir</trunc> that he he was</u>
<u n="778" who="S0355" trans="overlap">you can see that now</u>
<u n="779" who="S0281">did you hear his comment</u>
<u n="780" who="S0355" trans="overlap">on the screen there</u>
<u n="781" who="S0281">did you hear his comments about it? he said he said when they burst into applause at the end and everybody was on their feet he couldn't believe it</u>
<u n="782" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0281">he he thought it was total crap and they the guitarists one of the guitarists on it was Mick Taylor you know went went along to become part of The Stones for a while</u>
<u n="784" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="785" who="S0281">and his guitar was flat and you could hear it hear it was flat and erm it <trunc>wa</trunc> I mean er he thought that er that it was terrible and he just couldn't believe at the end where everybody jumped to their feet and gave them a standing ovation</u>
<u n="786" who="S0355">yeah he was elated</u>
<u n="787" who="S0281">he was so elated well surprised</u>
<u n="788" who="S0355">you were just showing that elation and that's good you started showing that elation <pause dur="long"/> that's</u>
<u n="789" who="S0281" trans="overlap">every day and every way I'm getting better and better</u>
<u n="790" who="S0355">yeah you can think about it but you've got to practise it what you what you preach man you've got to get out there and practise it you've got to dance you've got to do things</u>
<u n="791" who="S0281">I'm getting there I'm getting there</u>
<u n="792" who="S0355">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's not a criticism I'm not judging you I'm judging you I'm sorry hang on</u>
<u n="793" who="S0281">oh here we go</u>
<u n="794" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="795" who="S0281">put your earplugs in</u>
<event desc="sound of trombone playing"/>
<u n="796" who="S0355">right that's better</u>
<u n="797" who="S0281">you feel better now then?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0355">yeah do you remember Jimmy Edwards?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0355">he used to play the trombone didn't he?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0281">oh yes professor Jimmy Edwards</u>
<u n="802" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="803" who="S0281">what was that guy's name the the schoolboy who wasn't a boy at all he was stunted do you remember? Jimmy was it? Jimmy?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0355">what Bunter?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0281">no there were two</u>
<u n="806" who="S0355" trans="overlap">Billy Bunter</u>
<u n="807" who="S0281">oh yeah there was Billy Bunter wasn't there?</u>
<u n="808" who="S0355">there was Billy Bunter and then there was that Scots one that came in in a schoolboy uniform</u>
<u n="809" who="S0281">I think probably Clive Dunn did it at some stage</u>
<u n="810" who="S0355">no he didn't he was the grandpa wasn't he?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0281">I can't remember</u>
<u n="812" who="S0355">who were the people that played schoolboys?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that was a long time that was fifty years ago right?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0355">god I can remember what people did fifty years ago can't you?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0355">fifty years god fifty years ago shit ah fifty years ago</u>
<u n="817" who="S0281">we'll be dead before we know it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0355">well there's a cheering thought hurrah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0281" trans="overlap">let's let's drink to that</u>
<u n="820" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="821" who="S0281">here's to death</u>
<u n="822" who="S0355">here's to death <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> bring it on no no no I was only joking oh god</u>
<u n="823" who="S0281" trans="overlap">one of the few things everybody's got in common</u>
<u n="824" who="S0355">death and taxes</u>
<u n="825" who="S0281">yeah that's right Franklin Roosevelt no not Franklin erm Benjamin Franklin he said that didn't he? one of America's founding fathers well no he wasn't a founding father</u>
<u n="826" who="S0355">was he a founding father?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0281">I don't know what the definition of founding <trunc>fa</trunc> was it the pilgrims that actually went there were they the founding fathers or was it the the first parliament after independence? I don't know anyway he was er one of the first</u>
<u n="828" who="S0355">they they were talking about Benjamin Franklin weren't they?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0281">who who's they?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0355" trans="overlap">in that that er gangster movie saying Benjamin Franklin he fucking robbed the declaration of independence he said and then he</u>
<u n="831" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="832" who="S0355">and then he then he then then he screwed this black slave he kept slaves <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no no that wasn't Benjamin Franklin that I was talking about</u>
<u n="834" who="S0355" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="835" who="S0281">Jefferson Thomas Jefferson</u>
<u n="836" who="S0355" trans="overlap">was it? Thomas Jefferson was it? yeah well there you go</u>
<u n="837" who="S0281">he he drafted he wrote the er the constitution I think <pause dur="short"/> and I'll bet he was useless at information <unclear/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0355">god it vibrates that doesn't it? that</u>
<u n="839" who="S0281" trans="overlap">the trombone?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0355">trombone vibrates <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0281">are you still shaking? I am</u>
<u n="842" who="S0355">I am <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0281">you were playing it</u>
<u n="844" who="S0355">are you still shaking listening to it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0281">it reminds me of a time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were in er in <anon type="place"/> at my first teaching post and we had a room and we shared a house with other teachers and we had a room and er I was lying on the bed there and I had my knees crossed and up like that and a book <trunc>prop</trunc>propped against it and I was reading er I think it must have been er Deepak Chopra's book and I was reading this and my knees started to go like this why am I doing this? and I looked up and I saw this light bulb bulbs I think it was an actual chandelier thing and it would be going like this and I'd think it's not me and it was a bloody earthquake</u>
<u n="846" who="S0355">can we switch that off now?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0281">yeah if you want</u>
<u n="848" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0281">it was an earthquake <pause dur="short"/> there we go eighty-two minutes night night oh how do I stop it? there we go</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
