<text id="S9ER">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:21:42</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-02</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0517 S0518</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Fradley, Staffs</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Death, cancer, health (mental and physical), family, children.</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about family, friends and health issues.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0517">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sutton Coldfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Self employed - marketing &amp; Proofing services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- working knowledge; German -- Working knowledge</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0518">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Staffordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services Team Leader</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0518">okay</u>
<u n="2" who="S0517">there we go have a have a Quality Street and I'll</u>
<u n="3" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="4" who="S0517">I'll tell you my depressing saga</u>
<u n="5" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0517">oh it is depressing</u>
<u n="7" who="S0518">thank you</u>
<u n="8" who="S0517">it's not what you think anyway what are you thinking?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0518">I was worried it was about your friend</u>
<u n="10" who="S0517">oh it is <pause dur="short"/> oh I thought you were gonna say about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum <pause dur="short"/> no it is you know my friend that had cancer?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0517">last year <pause dur="short"/> and she had got over it <pause dur="short"/> or she's had a scan <pause dur="short"/> and it hadn't erm <pause dur="short"/> come <trunc>b</trunc> it it was okay</u>
<u n="13" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0517">and she was fine but then <pause dur="short"/> through the summer <pause dur="short"/> when I was speaking to her she had this cough</u>
<u n="15" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh no</u>
<u n="16" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that she couldn't get rid off <pause dur="short"/> well exactly she kept saying oh it's a cough and they'd given her antibiotics then there'd been a break and then there'd been this</u>
<u n="17" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0517">but anyway just before half-term I spoke to her <pause dur="short"/> and erm she'd been rushed into hospital and diagnosed with pneumonia <pause dur="short"/> so I immediately think oh no <pause dur="short"/> cancer of the lung it's come back</u>
<u n="19" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0517">but they gave her antibiotics and they let her out <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and that was only the week before half-term so we're only talking two weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> and she'd had a scan <pause dur="short"/> and I think she was with the oncologist who said <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know why he's not qualified but he'd said I'm not qualified to look at this scan <pause dur="short"/> think it was the radiologist that had to look at it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0517">but he said I have looked at a few and it looks okay to me <pause dur="short"/> so you know so I was thinking oh well that's a relief it's still okay <pause dur="short"/> but she had she did have pneumonia <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking oh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0518">how strong is she?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0517">yeah and you know cos you just your immune system's low isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> anyway in half-term I came home one day <pause dur="short"/> from getting my nails done <pause dur="short"/> and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s phoned <pause dur="short"/> I said oh he says it's not good news I said oh what's the matter? <pause dur="short"/> he said apparently erm <pause dur="short"/> the proper person had read this scan <pause dur="short"/> and they'd said <pause dur="short"/> that the cancer's back</u>
<u n="25" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0517">it's in the lining of the liver</u>
<u n="27" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="28" who="S0517">and somewhere else and somewhere else <pause dur="short"/> and they're going to do chemotherapy but they said to her that erm <pause dur="short"/> she needs to know <pause dur="short"/> they're doing this not to cure it <pause dur="short"/> just to extend her life</u>
<u n="29" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="30" who="S0517">and she said <pause dur="short"/> she didn't want to know cos I've spoken to her since <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> how much <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows cos I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> back a few days later cos I thought oh god what what am I gonna say? I don't know what to say it was awful</u>
<u n="31" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0517">but when I phoned her back she said oh <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> she didn't want to know about life expectancy <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know whether she still knows or not but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that the the doctor had said to him <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> up to two years</u>
<u n="33" who="S0518">they could extend it for?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0517"><trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc> that's would be her life expectancy now</u>
<u n="35" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0517">up to two years but then you don't know what her quality of life'll be for those two years do you or it might not be two years so she probably won't make fifty</u>
<u n="37" who="S0518">does she want to spend those two years going constantly through chemotherapy radiotherapy?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="39" who="S0518">feeling like that?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0517">and her children are <pause dur="short"/> months younger than mine</u>
<u n="41" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="42" who="S0517">she got them years nine and <pause dur="short"/> not sure if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in year ten or eleven <pause dur="short"/> either way he's doing his GCSEs</u>
<u n="43" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0517">how awful</u>
<u n="45" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh that's terrible that is</u>
<u n="46" who="S0517" trans="overlap">awful</u>
<u n="47" who="S0518">that's awful</u>
<u n="48" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't know what to say I just thought oh my <pause dur="short"/> cos she said oh you know <pause dur="short"/> she'd been quite <pause dur="short"/> when she was diagnosed last year <pause dur="short"/> she was very positive</u>
<u n="49" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0517">you know I'm gonna beat this</u>
<u n="51" who="S0518">and she did</u>
<u n="52" who="S0517">and and she did</u>
<u n="53" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0517">and she said to me on the phone this week she said <pause dur="short"/> you know I always knew it would get me it would come back but she said I really genuinely believed that I would maybe have ten fifteen years before</u>
<u n="55" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0517">now <pause dur="short"/> she says you know <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>w</trunc> I won't even get the school <unclear>doubt if</unclear> I <trunc>may</trunc> might not</u>
<u n="57" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0517">how awful <pause dur="short"/> and then she was doing all this <pause dur="short"/> you will be there for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> after won't you? I thought oh</u>
<u n="59" who="S0518">mm god</u>
<u n="60" who="S0517">just awful</u>
<u n="61" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="62" who="S0517">oh it was really</u>
<u n="63" who="S0518">I thought about her the other day <pause dur="short"/> because I thought oh I haven't asked for <pause dur="short"/> I think it was when we had after we'd had coffee a couple of weeks ago and I thought I know what I'm meant to ask you and I didn't ask you</u>
<u n="64" who="S0517">yeah well I mean and I've only spoken to her sort of on and off cos obviously they're down in <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="65" who="S0518">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0517">and I really must go and <pause dur="short"/> go get down and see her now but</u>
<u n="67" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0517">it's so difficult <pause dur="short"/> cos all of our weekends are busy but I think I'm gonna have to just go on my own</u>
<u n="69" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0517">let <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you can do that can't you?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0517">yes but they always want us all to go cos <pause dur="short"/> her boys <pause dur="short"/> you know they're similar ages to my boys and we've had holidays with them we've been up to the Lakes together and we've been away and they</u>
<u n="73" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0517">you know they always ask after them <pause dur="short"/> but but I will go down</u>
<u n="75" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>you</unclear> might just have to have a weekend and say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we're not doing hockey and football</u>
<u n="76" who="S0517" trans="overlap">on we're not doing <pause dur="short"/> not doing everything</u>
<u n="77" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>just the</unclear> weekends <pause dur="short"/> yeah we're going away for a weekend it's important so</u>
<u n="78" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> but it's awful though <pause dur="short"/> I just thought to myself I cannot imagine <pause dur="short"/> what you would <pause dur="short"/> what you would do? what you would plan to do? what you would want to do?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but you can't even do it because your children are at school you can't even say <pause dur="short"/> oh I'll go</u>
<u n="81" who="S0518"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="82" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and see a bit of the world I <unclear>genuinely</unclear> can't you can't you can't can you? can't do anything</u>
<u n="83" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah well there is yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no there's a friend of ours in the <anon type="place"/> and he had bowel cancer but he did have ten years so <pause dur="short"/> you know they did <pause dur="short"/> and the daughters were grown up so they were able to travel and to do this and</u>
<u n="84" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0518">you know he erm <pause dur="short"/> bought a mobile caravan and put it somewhere so really nice so that <pause dur="short"/> he when he knew when he wasn't there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would have somewhere to go for holidays and stuff like that and he totally <pause dur="short"/> he got the house completely all made perfect so there wasn't anything for her to worry about</u>
<u n="86" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0518">and they just did everything that they'd wanted to do</u>
<u n="88" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0518">but they had ten years to do that</u>
<u n="90" who="S0517">had they sort of expected ten years though?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0517">or was it one of those where the doctor had said and then they'd <pause dur="short"/> you know defied the doctors and?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="94" who="S0517">lived long oh</u>
<u n="95" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="96" who="S0517">they did?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0518">because his I remember when he told us <pause dur="short"/> it was <pause dur="short"/> the end of a committee meeting <pause dur="short"/> any other business? yes</u>
<u n="98" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> ah oh no</u>
<u n="99" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I've got I've got bowel cancer <pause dur="short"/> but he said</u>
<u n="100" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="101" who="S0518">he knew <pause dur="short"/> because it it's what his mother had <pause dur="short"/> and when he started with his symptoms he just thought <trunc>he</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> here we go <pause dur="short"/> so he was not surprised when he got that diagnosis</u>
<u n="102" who="S0517" trans="overlap">really? <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="103" who="S0518">but <pause dur="short"/> it was <pause dur="short"/> basically they said we can operate we can do this we can do this we can do this <pause dur="short"/> and you know? <pause dur="short"/> erm it it probably will kill you in the end however <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> it you will have <pause dur="short"/> a <pause dur="short"/> you know a few more years left</u>
<u n="104" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="105" who="S0518">because I think in the end <pause dur="short"/> that did spread <pause dur="short"/> and that went to his lungs and various other places</u>
<u n="106" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0518"><trunc>o</trunc>other tumours <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>settled</unclear></u>
<u n="108" who="S0517" trans="overlap">see and that and that's <trunc>inme</trunc>immediately made me think oh god they're gonna say lung cancer</u>
<u n="109" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0517">cos she's been coughing all summer but</u>
<u n="111" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0517">and part of me still thinks <pause dur="short"/> oh let's hope they you know it hasn't spread there as well cos the</u>
<u n="113" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0517">the more it spreads the quicker it is I suppose isn't it?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> thing is if it's got into your lymphatic system isn't it? or</u>
<u n="116" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0518">and it just goes spreads round</u>
<u n="118" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but but you know the the the awful thing is as well that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I've known <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was at <pause dur="short"/> college with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> and they got together <pause dur="short"/> similar time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I got together so we've known them</u>
<u n="119" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0517">twenty-odd years now <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> her brother <pause dur="short"/> who I think was just a few years younger than her <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you know when we <pause dur="short"/> before children you know this before we had kids and everything I remember seeing them and meeting her brother and his girlfriend and they were lovely <pause dur="short"/> and they got married <pause dur="short"/> and his wife her brother's wife <pause dur="short"/> died of breast cancer when she was only thirty-seven</u>
<u n="121" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh god</u>
<u n="122" who="S0517">and she was diagnosed when she was expecting their second child so they couldn't even start the treatment until you know?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0517">and she I think the baby was two when she died <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought to myself that poor man they're not related you know no blood relations whatsoever <trunc>sp</trunc> so he will've lost his wife</u>
<u n="125" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0517">and now <pause dur="short"/> quite probably his sister</u>
<u n="127" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0517">and I just think you know by the in your in your mid-forties that's just awful isn't it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0518">it is</u>
<u n="130" who="S0517">awful</u>
<u n="131" who="S0518">it is</u>
<u n="132" who="S0517">anyway let's let's not talk about depressing things anymore <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it's terrible <pause dur="short"/> no okay</u>
<u n="134" who="S0517">that's all we talk about <pause dur="short"/> on a completely frivolous note are you doing that hockey bonfire this Saturday have you heard?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="136" who="S0517">you're not?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0518">because <pause dur="short"/> we might you know we might've done but erm we are going to my best friend from university they live in <anon type="place"/> and when we were at college they <pause dur="short"/> they always used to have a bonfire party at their house <pause dur="short"/> and erm when they we left and they got married they always used to every year every year and then they haven't done it for a bit <pause dur="short"/> and then this year they've decided</u>
<u n="138" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh they've decided to</u>
<u n="139" who="S0518">let's</u>
<u n="140" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0518"><trunc>re</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> invent it invent it? <trunc>re</trunc></u>
<u n="142" who="S0517" trans="overlap">reignite it whatever</u>
<u n="143" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0518">erm <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> er we're going</u>
<u n="146" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="147" who="S0518" trans="overlap">to that yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0517">cos I <trunc>d</trunc> had the email as you know we get hundreds of emails from hockey day then I just said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today</u>
<u n="149" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0517">excuse me I said oh <pause dur="short"/> perhaps we should go we never support the hockey club things</u>
<u n="151" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0517">and it looked quite a reasonable price way</u>
<u n="153" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0517">cheaper than the rugby club actually</u>
<u n="155" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0517">but he said is there anybody else going that we know?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0518">well we've done the rugby club one before</u>
<u n="158" who="S0517">yeah we have</u>
<u n="159" who="S0518">erm which the boys liked because it had loads of funfair rides and stuff</u>
<u n="160" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I <trunc>w</trunc> I wouldn't yeah I wouldn't rush back to it though</u>
<u n="161" who="S0518">no not</u>
<u n="162" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I thought it was really <trunc>over</trunc>overpriced for what it was to be honest</u>
<u n="163" who="S0518">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I mean <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>l</trunc> I dunno what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought actually I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> quite liked it because it has a <trunc>l</trunc> funfair rides and stuff like that</u>
<u n="164" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and he likes going on all of that <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> you didn't have the mess of the bonfire in your own gardens</u>
<u n="166" who="S0517">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0518"><unclear>and there's loads</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0517">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0518">but erm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0517">it was just a suggestion that I put to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today and he said well is there <trunc>anyw</trunc>? <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean we're at the <trunc>e</trunc> stage now the the boys probably <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably won't even want to come with us</u>
<u n="171" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0517">you know</u>
<u n="173" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0517">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't unless he's got some friends going but we'll see <pause dur="short"/> I just felt we never support the hockey club in anything you know we always do doing</u>
<u n="175" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I would <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0517">other stuff</u>
<u n="177" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0517">so perhaps</u>
<u n="179" who="S0518">I would've said <trunc>t</trunc> I would've said yes then we'll go</u>
<u n="180" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0518">with you</u>
<u n="182" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0518">but <pause dur="short"/> we can't</u>
<u n="184" who="S0517">is he doing the hockey on Sunday cos they've got a football match again this Sunday haven't they?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0517">but it's</u>
<u n="187" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah we've said yes</u>
<u n="188" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="189" who="S0518">erm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0517">we haven't replied yet we were one of the names in blue</u>
<u n="191" who="S0518">well we were <pause dur="short"/> but last night I head <trunc>c</trunc> because or <trunc>u</trunc> you know we just <pause dur="short"/> have other things to think about really</u>
<u n="192" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well yes yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0518">and erm <pause dur="short"/> just not knowing <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> last week <pause dur="short"/> there were so many things that I wanted to do we couldn't plan anything</u>
<u n="194" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="195" who="S0518">couldn't plan anything</u>
<u n="196" who="S0517" trans="overlap">just waiting for the phone</u>
<u n="197" who="S0518">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah because I didn't know <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> one <trunc>t</trunc> I've got a friend that was acting in a play at <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> that I'd said I'd go and support her <pause dur="short"/> but then <pause dur="short"/> I'd got a rehearsal Tuesday night I'd got a rehearsal Thursday night <pause dur="short"/> myself <pause dur="short"/> which only <trunc>l</trunc> and then the boys had got <trunc>f</trunc>football practice on Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> which only left Friday but we wanted to go and see Peter Pan because our <pause dur="short"/> friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was playing Peter Pan and we wanted to go and see that <pause dur="short"/> at the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had got a Gothic reading that he wanted me to come to</u>
<u n="198" who="S0517">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> gosh</u>
<u n="199" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm said oh I'm gonna do a jewellery party do you want to come? all all on the same night and all on the same week and everything and I just had to say no to everybody really <pause dur="short"/> and we did go to see Peter Pan in the end <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0517">at the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0517">was it good?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0518"><vocal desc="sigh"/> it was okay it was</u>
<u n="204" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0518">it was very good because technically <pause dur="short"/> it it was <pause dur="short"/> for the <anon type="place"/> and it was <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> musical theatre company <pause dur="short"/> doing it</u>
<u n="206" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh so it was <trunc>a</trunc>amateur dramatics?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0518">and <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but they were flying</u>
<u n="212" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="213" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and so <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he'd all flying lessons so he was Peter Pan</u>
<u n="214" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0518">so there's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm so Peter Wendy Michael John all them the four of them all flying <pause dur="short"/> on the <anon type="place"/> stage well I know what the wings are like <pause dur="short"/> so as they were going you know <pause dur="short"/> second star and beyond like this <pause dur="short"/> and then flying off</u>
<u n="216" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0518">I just got visions of them all crashing into the wings like oh <pause dur="short"/> you know like this</u>
<u n="218" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="219" who="S0518">they didn't look like that from the stage it looked beautiful</u>
<u n="220" who="S0517">oh really</u>
<u n="221" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and it was all twinkly and sparkly and loads of dry ice and <pause dur="short"/> you know they were up in the air singing as well and I just thought I've see them on Dancing On Ice flying and</u>
<u n="222" who="S0517" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="223" who="S0518">the grown-up rugby players are vomiting it's so scary and <pause dur="short"/> makes you feel all</u>
<u n="224" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0518">disorientated and they were <pause dur="short"/> doing it and singing and the little boy that played Michael was had a beautiful voice he was really good <pause dur="short"/> erm <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="226" who="S0517">oh wow</u>
<u n="227" who="S0518">but as a story it felt more pantomimey</u>
<u n="228" who="S0517">oh it wasn't</u>
<u n="229" who="S0518">so</u>
<u n="230" who="S0517">it wasn't a <trunc>panto</trunc>? wasn't supposed to be a pantomime</u>
<u n="231" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> no it was <pause dur="short"/> the musical</u>
<u n="232" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="233" who="S0518">so Peter Pan</u>
<u n="234" who="S0517">when you said it I assumed it was a pantomime actually</u>
<u n="235" who="S0518" trans="overlap">The Musical <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="236" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="237" who="S0518">Peter Pan The Musical <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0517">cos I was gonna say that was early to have your pantomime already</u>
<u n="239" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0517">but it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="242" who="S0517">that explains it</u>
<u n="243" who="S0518">but it felt a bit <pause dur="short"/> more like that because the crocodile <pause dur="short"/> they have that dog don't they? Nanny who's like a big dog <pause dur="short"/> and that was obviously somebody in a costume crawling around and the crocodile was people inside a sort of fabricky costume and <pause dur="short"/> when Captain Hook erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> came on some people just booed anyway which made it a bit pantomimey</u>
<u n="244" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0518">and it was like come on <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ch</trunc> do do we believe in fairies? clap if you do <pause dur="short"/> which <pause dur="short"/> again it's a bit more</u>
<u n="246" who="S0517" trans="overlap">a bit more pantomime yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0518" trans="overlap">pantomimey <pause dur="short"/> so I prefer a musical a bit more like Miss Saigon or Les Mis or something like that that's</u>
<u n="248" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> are you? are you going to see Les Mis? at school?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0518">well we should do yes</u>
<u n="250" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I've booked my tickets <pause dur="short"/> to go with my sister actually on <pause dur="short"/> the Thursday I think</u>
<u n="251" who="S0518">see I have drama rehearsal on Thursday so</u>
<u n="252" who="S0517">it's Wednesday to Saturday isn't it? is it the week week after next?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>bet</trunc> Les Mis'll sell out <pause dur="short"/> so better get tickets <pause dur="short"/> actually <pause dur="short"/> might try and get some tickets</u>
<u n="254" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0517">so I'll go and erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>so</trunc> they're going on the Saturday though <pause dur="short"/> erm he was in something at the village like in <anon type="place"/> but I didn't go and watch it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what it was like <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> put pictures on Facebook of erm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0518">there was something <trunc>a</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I saw in the paper something no I know what it was <pause dur="short"/> it was <pause dur="short"/> it was that Strictly Come Dancing On Ice X-Factor <unclear><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></unclear></u>
<u n="258" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0518" trans="overlap">wasn't it? <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0517">but he wasn't in that</u>
<u n="261" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0517">there were two <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise</u>
<u n="263" who="S0518">two halves wasn't it?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0517" trans="overlap">there were two plays <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc>that that were separate and he was in the first one <pause dur="short"/> called Marble Arch or something</u>
<u n="265" who="S0518">I don't know</u>
<u n="266" who="S0517">and then there was another one afterwards <pause dur="short"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> being <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know what he's like was <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc>they were going to watch <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the first one and was wondering whether he'd get away with leaving at the interval <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> leaving</u>
<u n="268" who="S0517">depending on how <vocal desc="laugh"/> how how he was feeling at the happy acting</u>
<u n="269" who="S0518">well I remember now because I saw my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had put it on Facebook</u>
<u n="270" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="271" who="S0518">with a fish and chip supper <pause dur="short"/> and I thought <vocal desc="gasp"/> oh think that's the thing you told me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was involved in yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but that's finished now so</u>
<u n="273" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0517">that one's done and it's just the school show but I should go and see him <pause dur="short"/> see the school one</u>
<u n="275" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0517">cos I think Les Mis'll be good</u>
<u n="277" who="S0518">yeah and the school version is good as well so I think it will be</u>
<u n="278" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="280" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so I'm down with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to see that</u>
<u n="281" who="S0518" trans="overlap">directing it <pause dur="short"/> so yeah we must go and see that <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0517">and then I'm going to a barn dance on <trunc>Fr</trunc> week on Friday I can't remember the last time I went to a barn dance</u>
<u n="283" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> I love a good barn dance</u>
<u n="284" who="S0517">well yes I I mean and you know they are always good fun aren't they?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0518" trans="overlap">did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go with you?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="287" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0517">of course not</u>
<u n="289" who="S0518">I couldn't imagine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0517">oh gosh do you know? <pause dur="short"/> there's a it's a our friend in the village <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s the physio that I took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to actually so but it's her son who was at school with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but he's now gone to <anon type="place"/> school and he's raising funds for something</u>
<u n="291" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="292" who="S0517">I forget what but he's raising funds and he's got to raise the funds <trunc>t</trunc> for this trip <pause dur="short"/> himself so one of things he's doing is organising a barn dance <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> are all going <pause dur="short"/> because <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s always support them when they're fundraising <pause dur="short"/> and I thought you know it'll be fun <pause dur="short"/> could I drum up any interest from my family? <pause dur="short"/> no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was just an outright <pause dur="short"/> no way can't think of anything worse <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be fair <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't wanna go but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has made him</u>
<u n="293" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he has to</u>
<u n="294" who="S0517">he has to <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just looked at me as if I was <pause dur="short"/> deranged</u>
<u n="295" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and said <pause dur="short"/> mum <pause dur="short"/> I'm going you want me to go to a barn dance you know he didn't even know what a barn dance was but I think just the fact it had dance in the title</u>
<u n="297" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="298" who="S0517">in the no <pause dur="short"/> and so of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said no but actually and I probably could've persuaded <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to come because it is his friend <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> it'll be a late night and it's the following day he's running for in his cross-country</u>
<u n="299" who="S0518">oh right</u>
<u n="300" who="S0517" trans="overlap">county</u>
<u n="301" who="S0518">yes</u>
<u n="302" who="S0517">thing</u>
<u n="303" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0517">so in all fairness <pause dur="short"/> I would rather he had</u>
<u n="305" who="S0518">a good night's sleep</u>
<u n="306" who="S0517">a bowl of pasta and a good night's sleep so I'm going by myself <pause dur="short"/> but another friend of ours <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she said <pause dur="short"/> she felt she should go and support <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and none of her family wanted to go so I said well you can come with me</u>
<u n="307" who="S0518">there you go</u>
<u n="308" who="S0517">but I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know is it one of those do we need partners? no no no there's lots of mums going on their own <pause dur="short"/> which just goes to show none of the</u>
<u n="309" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0517">men really are interested</u>
<u n="311" who="S0518">I think er barn dancing</u>
<u n="312" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they don't think it'll be fun</u>
<u n="313" who="S0518">they normally say right come on we need eight people for the next dance in you know in groups of eight</u>
<u n="314" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0518">or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and you just <pause dur="short"/> ask just <unclear>get</unclear> someone don't you?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you just get on and yeah yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0518">you know?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0517">so I've got a check shirt so I'll be sorted</u>
<u n="319" who="S0518">you'll be fine</u>
<u n="320" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so that's a week <vocal desc="laugh"/> on Friday <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0518">you'll be fine</u>
<u n="322" who="S0517">and then the that night actually the Saturday we've been invited to a birthday party in <anon type="place"/> from somebody at the tennis club <pause dur="short"/> so we've got a busy weekend that one</u>
<u n="323" who="S0518">which <trunc>we</trunc> I don't know which weekend we're talking about now</u>
<u n="324" who="S0517">that was the thirteenth and fourteenth of</u>
<u n="325" who="S0518" trans="overlap">of November</u>
<u n="326" who="S0517">November</u>
<u n="327" who="S0518">and was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> alright when you said you couldn't come for the Christmas party?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> yes she was cos I did it by text which was a bit naughty</u>
<u n="329" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0518"><unclear>so funny</unclear></u>
<u n="332" who="S0517">well actually I texted her <pause dur="short"/> immediately after she had phoned me <pause dur="short"/> cos she phoned me up <trunc>phone</trunc> when she was phoning round just to say and I <trunc>s</trunc>said <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> let me get back to you cos that date sounds really familiar <pause dur="short"/> and er so I went back to her that night said I'm ever so sorry <pause dur="short"/> and do you know what in actual fact the excuse I gave is <trunc>d</trunc> like <pause dur="short"/> in all likelihood is gonna come true</u>
<u n="333" who="S0518">well when you <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="334" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0518">when you said it to me</u>
<u n="336" who="S0517" trans="overlap">what what was the date of the? what's the date of that <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>christm</trunc>? is it the?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0518">the <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="338" who="S0517">twelfth eleventh <trunc>u</trunc> is it that weekend?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0518">twelfth <pause dur="short"/> yeah the twelfth I think it is</u>
<u n="340" who="S0517">you see the weekend before is actually <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mother's birthday the sixth</u>
<u n="341" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0517">which is a Sunday and which would've been perfect <pause dur="short"/> but we've said yes <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I told you to an adoption party you know that? <pause dur="short"/> the chap in work that <pause dur="short"/> adopted two little girls this year?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0518">right no you didn't tell me no you told me about that but <unclear>not erm</unclear></u>
<u n="344" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah well he's he's <trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> the adoption <pause dur="short"/> I think it should be official I think it today or one day this week they're going to <trunc>co</trunc> it's all becoming official so they've invited us to an adoption party</u>
<u n="345" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="346" who="S0517">on the sixth of December which <pause dur="short"/> we said yes to cos I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that we should definitely go to that they've had such a you know a tough time getting there</u>
<u n="347" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0517">so that's actually and then <trunc>whe</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she was here last week she said oh will you be coming down in December for my birthday? <pause dur="short"/> and I said well unfortunately we have got this but maybe the following weekend</u>
<u n="349" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0517">we could come down so in actual fact <pause dur="short"/> and she said oh I would like to see you in <trunc>a</trunc> on you know</u>
<u n="351" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0517">you cos I haven't been down to <anon type="place"/> since last December</u>
<u n="353" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0517">just because the boys are always so busy</u>
<u n="355" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0517">so I don't I didn't feel bad because they in fact it's all it's likely to be true</u>
<u n="357" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0517">that we won't be here <pause dur="short"/> although we probably come back <pause dur="short"/> that night because there's likely to be a football match on the Sunday isn't there?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0518">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> because sometimes he</u>
<u n="360" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so it</u>
<u n="361" who="S0518">if he <trunc>n</trunc> if it's the Christmas party sometimes he he doesn't</u>
<u n="362" who="S0517">he tries to not to</u>
<u n="363" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0517">either way <pause dur="short"/> because I mean she's in her eighties she prefers to do lunchtime things anyway so we could go down there have the whole afternoon and drive back Saturday night</u>
<u n="365" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0517">and then</u>
<u n="367" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah but you wouldn't want to go to Christmas party then would you?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well no no no</u>
<u n="369" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="370" who="S0517">no not if you've been out for a big lunch but er you know and then driven back no</u>
<u n="371" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="372" who="S0517">but there's not so many going are there this year?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0518">well I heard her cos you said <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are doing <pause dur="short"/> but then <pause dur="short"/> I heard her say the other week she was collecting deposits I don't know if you were there <pause dur="short"/> can't remember now I just heard her say oh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're you can't come anymore can you? <pause dur="short"/> so he said no no sorry about that <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether</u>
<u n="374" who="S0517">well er he <trunc>sai</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> he asked me where we're going and I said oh we're not going actually this year <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and he went oh bugger <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s already <pause dur="short"/> paid the deposit or we were caught on the hop <pause dur="short"/> or something and cos I was surprised but anyway <pause dur="short"/> because they didn't actually looked like they enjoyed it I enjoyed it <pause dur="short"/> it was <trunc>m</trunc> it's my husband that's a little bit antisocial <pause dur="short"/> as we know</u>
<u n="375" who="S0518">I <trunc>m</trunc> can't say anything about that</u>
<u n="376" who="S0517">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>they're so pleased he missed a</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> well you know if we're gonna spend a hundred I'd rather go out for dinner with you <vocal desc="laugh"/> type of things</u>
<u n="377" who="S0518">oh but I <trunc>d</trunc> <trunc>sai</trunc> text you didn't I? and you said well we'll discuss it <pause dur="short"/> should we? should yeah we should</u>
<u n="378" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yes we <trunc>shou</trunc> well</u>
<u n="379" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0517">if you want to cos that's that's quite expensive for you cos you are going to the <pause dur="short"/> to the Christmas one aren't you?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0518">yes I know but <pause dur="short"/> it</u>
<u n="382" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes that would be nice</u>
<u n="383" who="S0518">you know <pause dur="short"/> I said it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't be able to go to the erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> to the Christmas party <pause dur="short"/> so I said I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that maybe it'll be nice just to get together and go out for erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> you know our own Christmas get-together or whatever</u>
<u n="384" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0518">and <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> I said didn't I <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="387" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and you said oh I don't know whether they're gonna go or not or whatever</u>
<u n="388" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes and I haven't actually asked them since then cos I've barely seen them since then to be honest</u>
<u n="389" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0517">I saw <pause dur="short"/> so was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keen?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0517">yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was too</u>
<u n="393" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> he said</u>
<u n="394" who="S0517" trans="overlap">in fact cos they well those are the only those are the people I talk to anyway so he was <pause dur="short"/> he was happy with that</u>
<u n="395" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <pause dur="short"/> like I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> better than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is very easy to</u>
<u n="396" who="S0517">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0518" trans="overlap">chat to anyway isn't he so?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0518">erm <pause dur="short"/> or it doesn't <trunc>ha</trunc> you know if they don't want to it doesn't have to be them it could just be <trunc>s</trunc> like you know</u>
<u n="400" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>so it's a bit</unclear> no but no that would be nice but it'll we'll have to find a date</u>
<u n="401" who="S0518">because we don't at football <pause dur="short"/> I know we talk and then and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looks disapprovingly</u>
<u n="402" who="S0517">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> so he says are you actually watching this game?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0518" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0517">or are you just chatting?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0518">what did he say last week? oh they're being paid to talk I can't believe that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0517" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>don't know what you're talking about</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0518">oh no</u>
<u n="409" who="S0518" whoConfidence="low">oh I know</u>
<u n="410" who="S0517">well see I can't <pause dur="short"/> I can't <pause dur="short"/> not look at somebody when I'm talking to them</u>
<u n="411" who="S0518">no I can't</u>
<u n="412" who="S0517">so that's <pause dur="short"/> why I miss all the game</u>
<u n="413" who="S0518">but</u>
<u n="414" who="S0517" trans="overlap">because I turn and <pause dur="short"/> look at the person I'm talking to</u>
<u n="415" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0517">he doesn't he <trunc>c</trunc> he can if he does talk while the game is on he's watching it as well</u>
<u n="417" who="S0518">but I should not talk to you that's the thing</u>
<u n="418" who="S0517">yeah that's the thing</u>
<u n="419" who="S0518">should not talk to you</u>
<u n="420" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="421" who="S0518">but obviously when you arrive and you say hi how are you had a good week? la-la-la-la you know like erm yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then before you know it an hour's passed</u>
<u n="423" who="S0518">like oh did <trunc>Mis</trunc> did you hear Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said this duh-duh?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="425" who="S0518" trans="overlap">they're like oh no I didn't oh you know</u>
<u n="426" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0518">then you just <pause dur="short"/> that's how it is</u>
<u n="428" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="429" who="S0518">and yet when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes and talks I think oh no <pause dur="short"/> cos I find her really irritating <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0517">oh do you?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0517">yeah well I'm glad you've said that cos I thought it was maybe just me</u>
<u n="433" who="S0518">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos I think I'm probably like this <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="435" who="S0518" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> she just seems to come recently and go <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0517">there's always a big sigh <pause dur="short"/> not <vocal desc="laugh"/> not that we've had the most upbeat conversation today <pause dur="short"/> but there's always a big sigh and it's always <pause dur="short"/> she's always so down</u>
<u n="437" who="S0518">well she's always so busy with work and</u>
<u n="438" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="439" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> my doggy's died and <trunc>s</trunc> and the thing is and I you know I'm gonna be <pause dur="short"/> saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll probably say to me how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad? and then I'll <pause dur="short"/> tell her <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> you know and <pause dur="short"/> so I'll be having the same sort of conversation but I don't think I'll arrive and just go <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0517">no I know waiting for somebody to say are you alright?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0518">because she was doing it <pause dur="short"/> and I was like hi how are you? and she's like <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought I'm not even gonna ask you</u>
<u n="442" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="443" who="S0518">yeah <trunc>me</trunc>mean of me</u>
<u n="444" who="S0517" trans="overlap">just those people just <trunc>p</trunc> I know those people put a little bit of a face on <pause dur="short"/> to <unclear>cover it up</unclear></u>
<u n="445" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it's so mean of me <pause dur="short"/> so mean of me</u>
<u n="446" who="S0517">yes you're a bad person <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0517">you're a bad person</u>
<u n="449" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I just thought I'm not gonna ask you <pause dur="short"/> there's a story coming <pause dur="short"/> and selfish reasons <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to know <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to know</u>
<u n="450" who="S0517">see who <trunc>i</trunc> who is going? <pause dur="short"/> there's you two there's</u>
<u n="451" who="S0518" trans="overlap">think there's only about eleven people going</u>
<u n="452" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0517">oh she's the odd one isn't she?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> yeah so is there only nine of us going then? <pause dur="short"/> or is there <unclear>one of the people</unclear>?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0518"><unclear>is it?</unclear></u>
<u n="458" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0518">yeah but I dunno if they're not going anymore</u>
<u n="460" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really? that's who were the was the other two <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0518">okay so if there's eleven it's those two</u>
<u n="462" who="S0517">you didn't go to the drop-in clinic did you the <unclear>pain</unclear> clinic?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="464" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I'd forgotten that was over half-term I'd forgotten about that</u>
<u n="465" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I thought you had to be a man</u>
<u n="466" who="S0517">no no you didn't have to be a man it was open to everyone no no</u>
<u n="467" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="468" who="S0517">so</u>
<u n="469" who="S0518">no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I did go into Tesco but I put on a disguise</u>
<u n="470" who="S0517" trans="overlap">put your head down and said no yeah mm mm kay</u>
<u n="471" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="472" who="S0517">well er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> should be back at training this week but I won't get to the match on Sunday are you going on Sunday?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0518">I don't know I think it's my turn to watch <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but</u>
<u n="474" who="S0517">oh is it?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0518">I'll have to see what's happening with everything</u>
<u n="476" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0518">what</u>
<u n="478" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0518">how is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? is he alright?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0517">he's fine he's absolutely fine now thank you he had two weeks where he did nothing <pause dur="short"/> cos he was <trunc>comp</trunc> still complaining about his back and I thought you know <pause dur="short"/> he's so</u>
<u n="481" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0517">young <vocal desc="laugh"/> to be moaning <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er is a physio at the <anon type="place"/> so on last <trunc>Sa</trunc> the first Saturday of half-term <pause dur="short"/> I took him out there <pause dur="short"/> and she had him <pause dur="short"/> she said <pause dur="short"/> tell him to come in his shorts <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was winding him up saying oh she's gonna give you a deep</u>
<u n="483" who="S0518" trans="overlap">she wants to see your legs</u>
<u n="484" who="S0517">a deep tissue massage <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh you know oh this isn't yeah he was really winding him up anyway we <vocal desc="laugh"/> I took him and he went</u>
<u n="485" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0517">and she just had him doing all sort of <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>exerc</trunc> well not exercises <trunc>lift</trunc> she was she was feeling his</u>
<u n="487" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="488" who="S0517">back at the two points where his <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>s</trunc> she said it was where his pelvis meets his spine or something and then she made me feel it so I could see that one <pause dur="short"/> was moving freer than the other</u>
<u n="489" who="S0518">oh right</u>
<u n="490" who="S0517">you <trunc>kn</trunc> all of this <pause dur="short"/> she gave him a few stretches she looked at his shoes and she thought maybe his <pause dur="short"/> astroTurf trainers weren't didn't have enough shock absorbency in them</u>
<u n="491" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="492" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm not buying more shoes I said he's got running shoes <pause dur="short"/> he's got spikes he's got football boots he's got tennis shoes he's got <trunc>thi</trunc> I said I'm not buying anymore <pause dur="short"/> she said don't panic <pause dur="short"/> and she showed me these insoles that she recommended</u>
<u n="493" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="494" who="S0517">she said <pause dur="short"/> definitely need AstroTurf trainers which I suppose he'd done all the <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> hockey in</u>
<u n="495" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0517">his running shoes have got</u>
<u n="497" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and if he's bending funny like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so</u>
<u n="498" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah his running shoes have got erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> are padded</u>
<u n="499" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0517">cos they're proper running shoes <pause dur="short"/> but also she said his hockey stick is supposed to be up to his waist I think I can't remember his waist or his hip</u>
<u n="501" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0517">but it's not but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says but these are full-sized hockey sticks <pause dur="short"/> so it <trunc>i</trunc> he is with a full-size hockey stick and he you know he's not <pause dur="short"/> he's not <trunc>extr</trunc></u>
<u n="503" who="S0518">well what do <trunc>m</trunc> grown-up men do?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well exactly exactly so I don't know anyway she said to us <pause dur="short"/> do these stretches she gave him some stretches three times a day <pause dur="short"/> and she said if I were you I'd <trunc>ha</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> not do any sport for another week she said</u>
<u n="505" who="S0518" trans="overlap">did she say warm up before you do <pause dur="short"/> sport as well?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0517">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah she did yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0518">I suppose they do though don't they?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but well they do at <pause dur="short"/> tennis I don't know what they do at</u>
<u n="511" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> they do at football cos they <unclear><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would just</unclear> get there at quarter past and the match isn't starting till two</u>
<u n="512" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="513" who="S0518">they do warm up</u>
<u n="514" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah they do warm up</u>
<u n="515" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0517">but I think when they've been doing these <vocal desc="cough"/> <trunc>excu</trunc> cross-country runs <pause dur="short"/> erm I think Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> whoever which P whichever PE teacher took them said well I hope that's a lesson to you all cos they're all stood there freezing</u>
<u n="517" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0517">cos they had about an hour to wait before their race and they're <trunc>a</trunc> none of them had anything other than their <pause dur="short"/> pE kits on</u>
<u n="519" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0517">which is ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> but anyway she said just rest him for another weekend if he's not better take him to the doctor</u>
<u n="521" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="522" who="S0517">because it's not normal <pause dur="short"/> for <pause dur="short"/> children this age</u>
<u n="523" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0517">but he was absolutely fine I mean of course he was just driving himself mad in half-term because he's</u>
<u n="525" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> I can imagine</u>
<u n="526" who="S0517">he does he does everything and he he wasn't doing anything</u>
<u n="527" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> and they erm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear>but he</unclear></u>
<u n="529" who="S0518">they've got a pitch at you know the AstroTurf? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <pause dur="short"/> a few of them got on last Wednesday</u>
<u n="530" who="S0517">oh did they?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0517" trans="overlap">did they go down there and?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had said he couldn't come or what but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't come cos his back's still bad <pause dur="short"/> erm I didn't know whether they had like not asked him because they knew his back was bad or</u>
<u n="534" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I see or <trunc>i</trunc> well</u>
<u n="535" who="S0518" trans="overlap">if it cos it was a message on</u>
<u n="536" who="S0517">oh the whole</u>
<u n="537" who="S0518" trans="overlap">Instagram or whatever it is going backwards and forwards but</u>
<u n="538" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to him</u>
<u n="539" who="S0518">Snapchat or</u>
<u n="540" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well if you do too much <pause dur="short"/> it'll start to hurt again and then you won't be fit to do anything so you may as well do as you're told</u>
<u n="541" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="542" who="S0517">and rest it and he played tennis on Saturday and he said it was absolutely fine</u>
<u n="543" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0517">so and now we've got these insoles in the <trunc>sh</trunc> that for the shoes so he should be okay</u>
<u n="545" who="S0518">good</u>
<u n="546" who="S0517">back to you know?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0518">and did he trick or treat?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0517">no <pause dur="short"/> what a performance that was he drove me mad with it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0518">did he find <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s number?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0517">er yes he did get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <trunc>t</trunc> send it to me actually</u>
<u n="551" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="552" who="S0517">erm <pause dur="short"/> I didn't bother texting or anything cos the whole week I kept thinking I'm gonna talk him out of this but he's only ever trick or treated in the village</u>
<u n="553" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0517">you know everybody</u>
<u n="555" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0517">and last no he didn't go last year cos we were away on holiday but the year before which is the last time he went <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> they took a friend who had a little brother <pause dur="short"/> who's like you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you are <trunc>f</trunc> about five foot ten now</u>
<u n="557" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0517">you're fourteen you can't go <pause dur="short"/> trick or treating to people that <pause dur="short"/> don't know who you are because</u>
<u n="559" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0517">you know it's intimidating and he was like oh well there's a sixth-former going there's so-and-so going and it's on the <anon type="place"/> estate and <trunc>u</trunc><trunc>u</trunc> and that's fine but I don't know anyone that lives on the <anon type="place"/> estate and</u>
<u n="561" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="562" who="S0517">if it was in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I would've let him go because</u>
<u n="563" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0517">lots of people know who he is <pause dur="short"/> and they've got loads of sweets out for kids but I just said you're too old so we had this ongoing debate all week <pause dur="short"/> and then because we'd had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to stay she said erm <pause dur="short"/> she'd like to take us out for a meal on</u>
<u n="565" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="566" who="S0517">Saturday night her last night <pause dur="short"/> so I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well granny wants to take us out for dinner now so you can <trunc>c</trunc> <vocal desc="gasp"/> oh you know it's I said look <pause dur="short"/> nobody's said yes or no and <trunc>y</trunc> all week he had been on and on and on and on <pause dur="short"/> but in the end I just said <pause dur="short"/> no actually I think I made him feel really bad I said do what you want <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> do what you want it's up to you I said but <pause dur="short"/> we're going out for dinner <pause dur="short"/> I'm not cooking <pause dur="short"/> so if you go out trick or treating and eat a whole load of sugar <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> you know there will be no food for you</u>
<u n="567" who="S0518">and how you gonna get yourself there and how you gonna get yourself back?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how you gonna get yourself there? <pause dur="short"/> yeah and we're going out in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> to the pub there to eat so you know? <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> so I was just mean to him really until he eventually said yes <pause dur="short"/> he'd come with us <pause dur="short"/> and it got to about <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> five o'clock on the Saturday and I said have you told your friends you're not going? <pause dur="short"/> he said no not yet</u>
<u n="569" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0517">I said what are you gonna say? he said I'm just gonna blame you I'm gonna say it's all you I said fine say it's all me</u>
<u n="571" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0517">but really I was so relieved cos he <pause dur="short"/> do <trunc>y</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I have lots of people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister said oh no he can go trick or treating</u>
<u n="573" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0517">but to me fourteen he's like so big</u>
<u n="575" who="S0518">I don't know I have got a different <pause dur="short"/> perspective cos I've grown up with it my mum's American <pause dur="short"/> and from the time we went to school <pause dur="short"/> er all the way</u>
<u n="576" who="S0517">oh you see I don't like I don't like Halloween so I'm probably a little bit</u>
<u n="577" who="S0518" trans="overlap">we had a <trunc>Ha</trunc> had a Halloween party</u>
<u n="578" who="S0517">biased anyway because I just don't like Halloween</u>
<u n="579" who="S0518">what we do we live in a lane where there's about <pause dur="short"/> seven nine houses something like that <pause dur="short"/> and I never knew this when I was little but she <pause dur="short"/> erm in our village she was always called oh you know the American who lives down <anon type="place"/> Lane that's what they always called her and erm <pause dur="short"/> she went to all of our neighbours and the houses down and say <pause dur="short"/> having a Halloween party for the girls there'll be about twelve little children <pause dur="short"/> I'll be coming round</u>
<u n="580" who="S0517" trans="overlap">can they come trick or treating?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0518">can they come to your house?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0518">and then she supplied them with all the stuff</u>
<u n="584" who="S0517">oh she supplied them with the all sweets?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0517">ah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0518">so then she went she made up all these different bags and whatever and went round the day before and gave them all out</u>
<u n="588" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0518">and then what happened was <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>l</trunc>lots of people said erm <pause dur="short"/> oh we'd like to give something as well <pause dur="short"/> and because they were all <pause dur="short"/> it was a village and it it they were all of our neighbours <pause dur="short"/> they then used to look forward to it and would say oh you are gonna come and they'd <pause dur="short"/> come in and then they'd say oh we've got drinks and we've got apple bobbing and <pause dur="short"/> it used to take ages to do the trick or treating because everyone let's have a look at you can we take photographs? and all of this</u>
<u n="590" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0518">and erm and then we'd go back and we'd have a Halloween tea <pause dur="short"/> and so we did that for years and years and years <pause dur="short"/> now my sister has <pause dur="short"/> taken over that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and we've always gone <pause dur="short"/> to her <pause dur="short"/> party <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was <trunc>al</trunc> too tiny but the last few years she's been a <pause dur="short"/> you know? five and six and er she's wanted to go out trick or treating herself <pause dur="short"/> but they live on a sort of cul-de-sac <pause dur="short"/> where again <pause dur="short"/> they know the neighbours</u>
<u n="592" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0518">and they know and and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying well we can't go to number six because they don't like it <pause dur="short"/> but then <pause dur="short"/> in it's like it is</u>
<u n="594" who="S0517">and and that's how it was here when the boys were small</u>
<u n="595" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know don't you?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0517">we'd cos you'd all been to the toddler groups and they'd all started school together and you'd go around to the houses of the of their friends</u>
<u n="597" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0517">basically or you knew</u>
<u n="599" who="S0518" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0517">that they were in and that and you know and <trunc>y</trunc> the <trunc>m</trunc> the mums would all talk beforehand and they'd say oh you in <pause dur="short"/> but no but <trunc>y</trunc> and that's fine because you had to be with them because they were small they were six seven eight years of age but now</u>
<u n="601" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0517">to go off on your own to just knock on people's door I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm not buying you a Halloween outfit <pause dur="short"/> and what are you gonna wear? said oh I just wear black and put a mask on <pause dur="short"/> I thought well <pause dur="short"/> so you're making no effort to dress up</u>
<u n="603" who="S0518" trans="overlap">just to get sweets</u>
<u n="604" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you just <trunc>w</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> said I'll buy you sweets alright I will buy you sweets <pause dur="short"/> and it just the whole thing just annoyed because <trunc>u</trunc> it's just <pause dur="short"/> he should've outgrown it</u>
<u n="605" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0517">he really should've outgrown it</u>
<u n="607" who="S0518">well like I say we <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> we go to my sister she makes a huge effort</u>
<u n="608" who="S0517">but she's still got a <trunc>l</trunc> a <trunc>f</trunc> a six-year-old a seven-year-old</u>
<u n="609" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but we've got a six-year-old</u>
<u n="610" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah you've still got</u>
<u n="611" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0517">you've still got</u>
<u n="613" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0517">an appropriately aged <pause dur="short"/> child <vocal desc="laugh"/> to do it</u>
<u n="615" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> we took her out and like I say we only went to the houses that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said we could go to</u>
<u n="616" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0518">that knew we were coming basically and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0517">and that and that was my issue with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanting to go</u>
<u n="619" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I'm too old <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <unclear>way</unclear> too old yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to go onto the to the new Waitrose estate and all around there</u>
<u n="621" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="622" who="S0517">but it was two years ago that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to go last year as I say we're away but two years ago <pause dur="short"/> when he would've been twelve <pause dur="short"/> just turned twelve <pause dur="short"/> and he asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just looked at him and said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you are far too old to <trunc>b</trunc> don't be ridiculous you know it's just so</u>
<u n="623" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0517">no well that's your friend who's also twelve who just wouldn't entertain the idea of going out trick or treating</u>
<u n="625" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0517">cos it's for little kids</u>
<u n="627" who="S0518">well when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s there <trunc>d</trunc>do you mind if I stay in the house? he said oh oh cos they have loads of trick or treaters <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was cooking <pause dur="short"/> erm my dad was there obviously he couldn't get up and down my mum was there <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I'll stay in the house and I'll give treats out to the people that come here is that alright? so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said yes <pause dur="short"/> my mum said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're never too old to trick or treat she said my father <pause dur="short"/> she said every year dressed up as a toy soldier with a monocle <unclear>and erm</unclear></u>
<u n="628" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0518">and <trunc>we</trunc> and I said yes but he came round <pause dur="short"/> with you and all the children in the neighbourhood didn't he? so he was a bit of a <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> character my grandpa was and <pause dur="short"/> so yes he was a grown-up man <pause dur="short"/> dressed up <pause dur="short"/> but he was going round with eight little girls</u>
<u n="630" who="S0517" trans="overlap">with children yes</u>
<u n="631" who="S0518">you know?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0518">he wasn't going up</u>
<u n="634" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0518">as a grown-up <pause dur="short"/> dressed up you know?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0517">and that was and that was how it started originally <trunc>w</trunc> he was gonna go with <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know in the year?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0517">he's got a little brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and he was gonna be their excuse</u>
<u n="639" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0517">but and and <trunc>a</trunc>and I did let him do that</u>
<u n="641" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="642" who="S0517">again because I know the people in <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s small <pause dur="short"/> but not <pause dur="short"/> into <anon type="place"/> where I don't know anyone</u>
<u n="643" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0517">and he's just</u>
<u n="645" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0517">imagine if he knocked on the wrong door and some old person came and <pause dur="short"/> he said mum you don't get old people on the new estate and he's probably <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0517">right he's probably right but <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos you know they're they're just geared to families aren't they the that new estate? <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I was like oh stop it you know I can't bear it when they've got an answer for everything <pause dur="short"/> I said no <pause dur="short"/> so he didn't go <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="649" who="S0518">well I did say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said I feel a bit uncomfortable cos I said this is basically like <pause dur="short"/> knocking on someone's door <pause dur="short"/> and asking for sweets <pause dur="short"/> hi can we have sweets?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0517">sweets <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and I and I said <pause dur="short"/> if that's why we're only going to the houses that are dressed up <pause dur="short"/> that we know are expecting people</u>
<u n="652" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0518">and people that had got pumpkins outside and witches hanging off their garage doors and stuff like that</u>
<u n="654" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0518">they're obviously geared up for it</u>
<u n="656" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="657" who="S0518">and they wanted people to come</u>
<u n="658" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean we've had pumpkins out <trunc>o</trunc><trunc>o</trunc> in the years gone by we weren't we were as it turns out we weren't in this year cos we went out for a meal but</u>
<u n="659" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="660" who="S0517">you know and we'll happily put the pumpkin out and that's you know just like a sign isn't it yeah knock on the door we've bought sweets and that that's</u>
<u n="661" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0517">fine and we get loads but erm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> yeah I wouldn't trust <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be sensible <pause dur="short"/> when he's with his friends at the minute</u>
<u n="665" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>would he</unclear></u>
<u n="666" who="S0517">on</u>
<u n="667" who="S0518">I know</u>
<u n="668" who="S0517">no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> no <pause dur="short"/> he just doesn't think</u>
<u n="669" who="S0518">oh gosh</u>
<u n="670" who="S0517">goes in one ear and out the other with that boy</u>
<u n="671" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="672" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's just a typical fourteen-year-old I think he just doesn't <pause dur="short"/> I dunno he just <trunc>d</trunc> he nothing seems to go into his head <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> nothing sensible <pause dur="short"/> and if you pull him on it he just <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> ah let's hug it out mum</u>
<u n="673" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0517">you know he just <trunc>u</trunc></u>
<u n="675" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he <trunc>s</trunc> he sounds like how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is to be honest</u>
<u n="676" who="S0517">is <trunc>sh</trunc> oh no chill out mum</u>
<u n="677" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah like</unclear></u>
<u n="678" who="S0517">yeah I had <trunc>forgo</trunc> yeah let's hug it out come on <pause dur="short"/> come on bring it in he goes <vocal desc="laugh"/> just do what you've been told <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0518">parents evening'll be interesting er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0517">oh I know when is it?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0518">I don't know it's not till <pause dur="short"/> probably next year for them is it?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0517">no probably not no probably after Christmas</u>
<u n="683" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah we had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="684" who="S0517">oh how did he get?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0518" trans="overlap">how? <pause dur="short"/> are we alright for time?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0517" trans="overlap">has he <trunc>ha</trunc>?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0518">do I need to?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0517">yeah no no</u>
<u n="689" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0517">well what time do you need to be back for? <pause dur="short"/> do you need to be back before your boys get home?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0518">well I told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm coming for a cup of tea with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and erm he said oh that could take some time then</u>
<u n="692" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm but they get back in about four <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>o'clock</unclear> ish</u>
<u n="694" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll be home at about four <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't on the bus cos he starts his FA course tonight</u>
<u n="695" who="S0518">oh does he? for the <trunc>c</trunc> for the refereeing?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="697" who="S0518">so is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? well surely <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s doing it</u>
<u n="699" who="S0518">well I don't know cos I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other day and then he said oh I'll ask Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> about again</u>
<u n="700" who="S0517">it's today <pause dur="short"/> surely <pause dur="short"/> have you paid for it?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0518">no <pause dur="short"/> we had this form and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> about it Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said oh I'll let you know <pause dur="short"/> he said I've struggled to get enough people to do it <pause dur="short"/> he said so I'll let you know when it's going ahead</u>
<u n="702" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's today</u>
<u n="703" who="S0518">oh okay</u>
<u n="704" who="S0517">oh I wonder what's gone wrong there then</u>
<u n="705" who="S0518">I don't know</u>
<u n="706" who="S0517">because <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>d</trunc> he <pause dur="short"/> cos you know I'd I'd sent him that email and said is it just for GCSE students? he said no mostly GCSE students and sixth-formers but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can do it</u>
<u n="707" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="708" who="S0517">and erm <pause dur="short"/> I asked who's the cheque out to? and he you know you pay the FA and I think the week before half-term <pause dur="short"/> he sent me an email with a link <pause dur="short"/> he said this is the link you need to make the payment</u>
<u n="709" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> perhaps I need to get in touch then because</u>
<u n="710" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> and it starts today</u>
<u n="711" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="712" who="S0517">erm for however many weeks it's quarter past four till six</u>
<u n="713" who="S0518">at school?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0517">at school <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> I think it's is it about eight nine weeks? I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> but also cos I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in year seven does his <pause dur="short"/> football training on a Monday night</u>
<u n="715" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="716" who="S0517">and it's always been straight from school half past three till five o'clock <pause dur="short"/> and they had a letter saying that the times were changing <pause dur="short"/> quarter past four <pause dur="short"/> till six on a Monday <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh yeah that's because there's a referee course on and we've got to be the</u>
<u n="717" who="S0518">oh right</u>
<u n="718" who="S0517">the children they put they they learn on</u>
<u n="719" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="720" who="S0517">so I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh you'll be doing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s erm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0518">so have you got to go and pick him up at six?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0517">yes <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s doing tennis <pause dur="short"/> five fifteen till six thirty</u>
<u n="723" who="S0518">right okay</u>
<u n="724" who="S0517">so er so <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll be home on the bus <pause dur="short"/> and then I'll go I don't need to go out till five o'clock</u>
<u n="725" who="S0518">what time is it now? oh twenty</u>
<u n="726" who="S0517">half past three so yeah another</u>
<u n="727" who="S0518" trans="overlap">past <pause dur="short"/> three <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0517" trans="overlap">half an hour but oh well no that'll be a real shame if he's <pause dur="short"/> missed it because it was you that told me about it</u>
<u n="729" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I must er <pause dur="short"/> yeah I said to him <trunc>h</trunc>has anything been said? and he said no I asked Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then he said I asked him and he said it's still going ahead <pause dur="short"/> but I just was struggling to get the right amount of numbers and I'll let you know <pause dur="short"/> the dates when it's starting</u>
<u n="730" who="S0517" trans="overlap">because <pause dur="short"/> I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> what are you gonna do for forty-five minutes after school now? I said no point coming home cos as soon as you walk through the door we'd have to turn round and go back <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> and he said oh there's a couple of others doing it in his year <pause dur="short"/> I said are there? <pause dur="short"/> he said yeah because they announced it in PE <pause dur="short"/> I said a long time ago or recently no recently so they're obviously still trying to get up <pause dur="short"/> get numbers <pause dur="short"/> and a couple of others in his year but</u>
<u n="731" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>I bet he just yeah</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah because we had parents' evening the other week and we were talking to Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and he was saying <pause dur="short"/> erm he said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s one of my one of the <trunc>f</trunc> my most favourite boys I've ever taught <pause dur="short"/> and he said if I can't get him an A for PE he said <pause dur="short"/> I might retire</u>
<u n="732" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="733" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but so <pause dur="short"/> and then he was talking about you know because they have to pick their four best</u>
<u n="734" who="S0517">oh sports?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0518" trans="overlap">sports to</u>
<u n="736" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="737" who="S0518">that they've got the highest marks on <pause dur="short"/> and then he was but then he was saying and on top of that then obviously <trunc>becau</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>n</trunc>now unless he was talking about <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does badminton after school on a Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> and he said I think he said I want to train <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be a badminton referee <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="738" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="739" who="S0518">he said because that's an area that not many people go into and it's you can get really good <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> marks on that <pause dur="short"/> so I'm wondering whether he's <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> you can't at the moment it's too much to do football refereeing and badminton</u>
<u n="740" who="S0517">oh is there a course coming up for the <pause dur="short"/> badminton refereeing then?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and <pause dur="short"/> well er Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s <trunc>s</trunc> well he said <pause dur="short"/> I got the feeling that it was basically gonna be him <vocal desc="laugh"/> coaching him</u>
<u n="742" who="S0517">well he that was his sport wasn't it?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0518">is?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0517" trans="overlap">Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="745" who="S0518">is it? <pause dur="short"/> badminton?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0517">when he was</u>
<u n="747" who="S0518">ah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0517" trans="overlap">younger that was his sport that he played to a very good level</u>
<u n="749" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="750" who="S0517">cos he's trying to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in <pause dur="short"/> er and and <pause dur="short"/> and I said to him but he's a tennis player he shouldn't play badminton and he said I know that he said I was a badminton player and I was not allowed to play tennis</u>
<u n="751" who="S0518">oh right</u>
<u n="752" who="S0517">erm I said well stop <vocal desc="laugh"/> stop encouraging him then</u>
<u n="753" who="S0518" trans="overlap">just stop it <pause dur="short"/> stop it</u>
<u n="754" who="S0517">yeah but he <trunc>sai</trunc> but he is erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> but that's a bit unfair though isn't it? I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to do the course because he wants to earn money from it</u>
<u n="755" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0517">he wants to go on a Saturday morning and referee the little ones <pause dur="short"/> which I assumed was why <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was doing it or is that?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0518">well</u>
<u n="758" who="S0517">was it part of his GCSE?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0518">it was a mixture of things because he came home and said Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> has asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and me <pause dur="short"/> whether <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> erm <pause dur="short"/> he thinks that we would <pause dur="short"/> be suitable for this and whether we would like to do it and I want to do it and it's this referee course because obviously you can referee and get money</u>
<u n="760" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="761" who="S0518">but also <pause dur="short"/> it's all <pause dur="short"/> extra goes towards your GCSE <pause dur="short"/> and if as well if you see erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> like the last few football matches that they played at school <pause dur="short"/> there's been a ginger-haired boy refereeing it</u>
<u n="762" who="S0517">oh yes</u>
<u n="763" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> one of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="764" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I was gonna say he looks like he's in school</u>
<u n="765" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's a</u>
<u n="766" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0518">he's a year eleven and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how come <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is reffing it? and he said oh it's to get him more points for his GCSE <pause dur="short"/> so I'm like well why aren't you? and he said because I've <pause dur="short"/> got more points elsewhere</u>
<u n="768" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="769" who="S0518">so he's he's he</u>
<u n="770" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> see but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to do it so he can earn money from it like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did</u>
<u n="771" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well so some people are</u>
<u n="772" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="773" who="S0518">doing it to erm <pause dur="short"/> help their GCSEs and some people are doing it for <trunc>oth</trunc>other reasons <pause dur="short"/> but I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like I say when we had the last conversation about it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>a</trunc> what has happened? has Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said anything more? and he says oh I'll ask him then he said well just what I told you <pause dur="short"/> he's <trunc>w</trunc> got trying to <pause dur="short"/> it's not starting yet cos he hasn't got enough people</u>
<u n="774" who="S0517">I think it was Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> that was organising it</u>
<u n="775" who="S0518">oh well maybe I'm saying the wrong name then <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'm saying the wrong name</u>
<u n="776" who="S0517" trans="overlap">because I know I think I started with Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and he referred me to Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and I <trunc>th</trunc> I'm pretty sure it was Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> that sent me the email link</u>
<u n="777" who="S0518">I'll have to check</u>
<u n="778" who="S0517">and it was a hassle you had to you had to <pause dur="short"/> you had to register with the FA and get a</u>
<u n="779" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="780" who="S0517">yeah they called it an FAN number</u>
<u n="781" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="782" who="S0517">I don't know whether that stands for FA number <pause dur="short"/> so you had to register set yourself up as a user</u>
<u n="783" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0517">and then go on and then you could pay <pause dur="short"/> and it said at the <unclear/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0518">I'll find out because as I say</u>
<u n="786" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="787" who="S0518">at parents' evening he was on about <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> he's got this many and it's like <pause dur="short"/> there was swimming <pause dur="short"/> life-saving skills <pause dur="short"/> rugby <pause dur="short"/> cricket <pause dur="short"/> football</u>
<u n="788" who="S0517">all sorts yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><trunc>af</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is one of the ones that does the cross-country</u>
<u n="790" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="791" who="S0518">so athletics was one of them he's quite good at that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <trunc>th</trunc>there's all the sports <pause dur="short"/> circuit training</u>
<u n="792" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0518">and then one of and badminton <pause dur="short"/> now Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because he's a good <trunc>sportsm</trunc> all-round sportsman he you know <pause dur="short"/> his badminton is fine <pause dur="short"/> but he said <pause dur="short"/> not that many people do badminton umpiring and he said I think you can get more marks doing that</u>
<u n="794" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> that's really weird because he's told er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for A level you only have to do two sports</u>
<u n="795" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0517">so obviously he's got tennis</u>
<u n="797" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="798" who="S0517">and potentially he's got hockey although he doesn't play that to a to a particularly good level <pause dur="short"/> but I said you know he's done his <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>l</trunc> in the half-term he said he's er <pause dur="short"/> done his next level of <pause dur="short"/> coaching course for tennis you know?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0518" trans="overlap">right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0517">cost us three hundred quid it's a good qualification <pause dur="short"/> and so he said to Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> or Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> whichever <pause dur="short"/> er well can I do tennis coaching as my second one? and he said <pause dur="short"/> you don't really get so <pause dur="short"/> er so many points for that but what you would be good is if you were a tennis umpire <pause dur="short"/> I said but there's no skill involved in that you've just gotta</u>
<u n="801" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0517">call out the score</u>
<u n="803" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="804" who="S0517">and he said I know but <pause dur="short"/> they say that you can get more points if you're just a tennis umpire I said well <pause dur="short"/> at <trunc>juni</trunc></u>
<u n="805" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so that's after badminton?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes which is why I think that's weird cos again you're just</u>
<u n="807" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>interesting</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0517">watching a game and</u>
<u n="809" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0517">calling out the <pause dur="short"/> the score whereas <pause dur="short"/> coaching <pause dur="short"/> I would've thought and I must be wrong but you'd've thought <trunc>th</trunc>there'd be way more skill involved in that wouldn't you? because you've got to watch what they're doing analyse it tell them how to improve</u>
<u n="811" who="S0518" trans="overlap">there's more skill <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> you would <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="812" who="S0517">but if you're <pause dur="short"/> you've just basically gotta say well <pause dur="short"/> in or out that makes the score that</u>
<u n="813" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="814" who="S0517">er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0518">well I was just saying</u>
<u n="816" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="817" who="S0518">it's you've got to have a loud voice a clear voice you've got to be decisive you've got to make the right call obviously the scores the right way round</u>
<u n="818" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="819" who="S0518">erm serves and things like that you know if they're out or whatever you have to just <trunc>m</trunc> be <pause dur="short"/> and he said I think it'd be good for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for his erm confidence <pause dur="short"/> because you have you have to control the game in a way <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> and he just said although his <pause dur="short"/> yeah his badminton is is good <pause dur="short"/> it's not outstanding <pause dur="short"/> it you know it's</u>
<u n="820" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0518"><trunc>m</trunc>middle</u>
<u n="822" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="823" who="S0518">it is solid <pause dur="short"/> whereas he said I think umpiring</u>
<u n="824" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you could do it so there must be something and they'll maybe there's just not many people that do it but it was weird that he said the same to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="826" who="S0517">with tennis</u>
<u n="827" who="S0518">that is weird</u>
<u n="828" who="S0517">cos you're it's not something you'd think would count towards a <pause dur="short"/> gCSE or an A level really is it? but anyway</u>
<u n="829" who="S0518">no but there we go <pause dur="short"/> I'll ask him then about <pause dur="short"/> so he might just say oh yeah I was told because of doing <pause dur="short"/> twelve <trunc>ex</trunc>twelve exams <pause dur="short"/> and I'm doing this and I'm doing badminton umpiring <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="830" who="S0517">and he's got his Duke of Edinburgh hasn't he he's doing?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0518">this year it's too much to take on or</u>
<u n="834" who="S0517">maybe</u>
<u n="835" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might've decided himself it's too much to take on I don't know</u>
<u n="836" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="837" who="S0518">I don't know because with <anon type="place"/> City he trains twice a week and has a match <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="838" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he trains twice a week?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0517">oh does he?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0518">they train Saturdays and Wednesdays</u>
<u n="842" who="S0517">oh I didn't realise that</u>
<u n="843" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="844" who="S0517">and then play Sundays</u>
<u n="845" who="S0518">mm <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>u</trunc> he might</u>
<u n="846" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="847" who="S0518">and so he's doing badminton Tuesdays football Wednesdays football Saturdays <pause dur="short"/> works every other Saturday and then plays matches on Sundays <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> this half-term he had nine pieces of homework well you've been through it so you know what it's like but</u>
<u n="848" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0518">you know it's erm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0517">it's too much sometimes I <trunc>t</trunc> whereas <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came home and he said <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>w</trunc> I have got homework but all the teachers said the same apparently the headmaster said something different <pause dur="short"/> but all the teachers said we don't think you should have homework during half-term so we're going to set it because we have to but you've got until the Friday</u>
<u n="851" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="852" who="S0517">of the first week so in effect if you don't want to do</u>
<u n="853" who="S0518">well in your holiday time</u>
<u n="854" who="S0517" trans="overlap">your <trunc>ho</trunc> in your holiday you've still got the week when you go back</u>
<u n="855" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0517">but apparently the headmaster had a different idea <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="857" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="858" who="S0517">and I don't know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is doing he was <trunc>rev</trunc> learning a speech</u>
<u n="859" who="S0518">oh yeah</u>
<u n="860" who="S0517" trans="overlap">about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they have they have to</u>
<u n="862" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0518">choose their</u>
<u n="864" who="S0517">choose <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0518">favourite Briton or the best Briton <pause dur="short"/> and then they had to research it write a speech <pause dur="short"/> and then put it on bullet points and then present it</u>
<u n="866" who="S0517">how long was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s do you know?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0518"><vocal desc="sigh"/> he had six little cards of bullet points <pause dur="short"/> didn't last terribly long <pause dur="short"/> he wrote it all out</u>
<u n="868" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wasn't particularly long</u>
<u n="869" who="S0518">he wrote it all out <pause dur="short"/> typed it all out on the computer and it's one sheet of A4</u>
<u n="870" who="S0517">oh okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s was probably three quarters</u>
<u n="871" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> you're not allowed to read it so you <unclear>need to bear that in mind</unclear> mm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no oh that's <trunc>b</trunc> that's alright then his cos I thought at one point it looked really short but it did get a bit longer <vocal desc="laugh"/> on the A4</u>
<u n="873" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0517">and then he was trying to learn something in French too</u>
<u n="875" who="S0518">yes that's it they've there and and they've got a plan I think they're gonna do some of it at break time</u>
<u n="876" who="S0517">oh right okay</u>
<u n="877" who="S0518">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like did some <pause dur="short"/> over the weekend French and then he <pause dur="short"/> went through it this morning and he said but I think we'll just get together at break time and just go over it again</u>
<u n="878" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0518">but you do know mum don't you? <pause dur="short"/> that erm I have been working on it? I said yeah I do know I do know</u>
<u n="880" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I need to spend a penny</u>
<u n="882" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh well you can</u>
<u n="883" who="S0518" trans="overlap">is that I know but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="884" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> shall I pause this for a moment then?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0518">what the builders quoted and see whether you think it's good or not</u>
<u n="886" who="S0517">oh yes but I must just tell you about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s course just quickly</u>
<u n="887" who="S0518">oh right</u>
<u n="888" who="S0517">he did his two days it was Thursday and Friday <pause dur="short"/> nine till five each day coaching cost us three hundred pounds this course <pause dur="short"/> he came home on Thursday he said oh yeah he said <trunc>u</trunc> you know it was good he said but I've got homework to do <pause dur="short"/> erm and Thursday's men's night so he was out playing tennis from seven till half nine I said well <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he said oh he said this is more stressful than my GCSEs mum I've got loads to learn <pause dur="short"/> and tomorrow there's a an hour's written exam</u>
<u n="889" who="S0518">my word</u>
<u n="890" who="S0517">and I have to do thirty minutes coaching to the guy and they assess me on my skills I said blimey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that <trunc>i</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> he said yeah it is high pressure he said <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> but let me tell this he said mum <pause dur="short"/> they've given me this and he pulls out this <pause dur="short"/> waterproof coat with the logo on and it's a nice coat with the logo of the course and everything he said but if I fail mum this coat will only have cost you three hundred quid <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="891" who="S0518">ah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0517">I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're not gonna fail</u>
<u n="893" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0517">I said don't you fail <pause dur="short"/> and of course my mother-in-law's going</u>
<u n="895" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="896" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you mustn't put so much pressure on him he can resit it I said <pause dur="short"/> not at three hundred quid he can't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said you better pass that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> anyway we haven't heard cos <pause dur="short"/> there was a written exam</u>
<u n="897" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="898" who="S0517">so it has to get marked so hopefully he'll pass it this <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>do well</unclear></u>
<u n="900" who="S0517">we'll hear this week but he was just so funny</u>
<u n="901" who="S0518"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0517"><trunc>j</trunc>just doesn't faze him at all <unclear>he says</unclear> yeah it's a nice coat which will only have cost you <pause dur="short"/> three hundred quid if I fail</u>
<u n="903" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so that was worth it</u>
<u n="904" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so yeah <trunc>u</trunc> bargain anyway so yeah tell me about your</u>
<u n="905" who="S0518">haven't asked about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> either though</u>
<u n="906" who="S0517">she's okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah she she looked well actually I mean she's <pause dur="short"/> she's quite slow and old</u>
<u n="907" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="908" who="S0517">but she's just waiting for her radiotherapy appointments which</u>
<u n="909" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="910" who="S0517">erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <trunc>u</trunc> I think <pause dur="short"/> will be the end of November before they start</u>
<u n="911" who="S0518">and she</u>
<u n="912" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but she was okay</u>
<u n="913" who="S0518">did you get on alright with her <unclear>though? cos she said we're going to</unclear> another cup of tea <trunc>t</trunc> at the garden centre</u>
<u n="914" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh well you know what you'll <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0517">I don't know I mean she's what? eighty-three and she walks quite slowly but she likes to walk <pause dur="short"/> a little way</u>
<u n="917" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="918" who="S0517">each day <pause dur="short"/> I mean <unclear>had</unclear> that many cups of tea our <pause dur="short"/> or you know coffee it was the morning tea it's if the afternoon and you can't really deviate from that <pause dur="short"/> we had lunch out <pause dur="short"/> er it it was fine but we didn't <pause dur="short"/> we didn't do very much you know I did feel like I'd slowed down to a real</u>
<u n="919" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="920" who="S0517">old lady pace</u>
<u n="921" who="S0518" trans="overlap">eighty-something pace <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="922" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well yes but you know it was just a week it was fine it was fine</u>
<u n="923" who="S0518">but you've got somebody in your house for the whole time haven't you and?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="925" who="S0518">you you you you just have to be</u>
<u n="926" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="927" who="S0518">mindful of that <unclear>sometimes</unclear></u>
<u n="928" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> but I mean she you know she she likes to read a lot and she does her sudoku and <pause dur="short"/> she's alright <pause dur="short"/> but she just watches sport she doesn't watch anything on the telly that you'd normally watch</u>
<u n="929" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="930" who="S0517">like Downton Abbey or</u>
<u n="931" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you know all the things that you? <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't watch any of it she watches sport</u>
<u n="933" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="934" who="S0517">it doesn't mater</u>
<u n="935" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well there's been some athletics on hasn't there?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0517">well we've got Sky Sports so there's always something on</u>
<u n="937" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="938" who="S0517">but er one night actually I was going out with <pause dur="short"/> to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I hadn't seen her in half-term <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> it was Thursday so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had gone out to play tennis and I said oh I'm going out to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <trunc>sh</trunc> so I I left her in charge of the zapper for the telly and she settled on <pause dur="short"/> golf</u>
<u n="939" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="940" who="S0517">I mean <pause dur="short"/> who watches <pause dur="short"/> golf on the telly?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0518" trans="overlap">cos it's exciting isn't it?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0517">no and I said you know there was even tennis on and she quite likes tennis I think there was <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <trunc>the</trunc><trunc>the</trunc>there's always stuff on isn't there? <pause dur="short"/> golf and I said golf <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? she said <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I find it quite restful <pause dur="short"/> much more restful than some of the other sports and the scenery is often nice</u>
<u n="943" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="944" who="S0517">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I got I got in about half past ten quarter to eleven I can't remember and <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was upstairs in bed reading I said you alright? he said yes er <pause dur="short"/> said I got home at half past nine my mother was watching golf <pause dur="short"/> I said oh I went out at seven and she was watching golf <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="945" who="S0518">so you didn't have to stay with her the whole time?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no no that's the only er <pause dur="short"/> no and she would've</u>
<u n="947" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="948" who="S0517"><trunc>sh</trunc> no but you know who watches golf? and she doesn't watch anything <pause dur="short"/> well we made her watch <pause dur="short"/> strictly Come Dancing and X Factor <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="949" who="S0518" trans="overlap">that's probably not very relaxing for her then</u>
<u n="950" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says I reckon she's into it I reckon we could probably talk to her about it next week cos we've got her hooked</u>
<u n="951" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's hooked</u>
<u n="952" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> but no she was fine</u>
<u n="953" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0517">she was fine we just didn't do much but</u>
<u n="955" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0517">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>w</trunc>what about your appointment?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0518">I don't like the lady</u>
<u n="958" who="S0517">oh no</u>
<u n="959" who="S0518" trans="overlap">don't like her <pause dur="short"/> she's</u>
<u n="960" who="S0517">who is this through the doctor's surgery?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't I I I <pause dur="short"/> she made me feel really guilty for being there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0517">oh did she?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as if I was <pause dur="short"/> far too <trunc>sor</trunc> she what she actually said to me</u>
<u n="964" who="S0517"><unclear>er do you want another?</unclear></u>
<u n="965" who="S0518">er no I'm alright at the moment thank you</u>
<u n="966" who="S0517" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="967" who="S0518">you have one while you're listening <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="968" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no go on <pause dur="short"/> you're just tempting me</u>
<u n="969" who="S0518" trans="overlap">she she actually said to me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I think it might've been a bit of a clumsy compliment <pause dur="short"/> she said <pause dur="short"/> do you know? she said <pause dur="short"/> you are my <pause dur="short"/> best outcome <pause dur="short"/> so I said sorry? she said <pause dur="short"/> if I could get <pause dur="short"/> most of my clients to be anywhere near <pause dur="short"/> how you are today <pause dur="short"/> by the time they've finished with me she said <pause dur="short"/> I'd be so happy</u>
<u n="970" who="S0517">and that was your first session?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I said do you not think this is the right thing for me then?</u>
<u n="972" who="S0517">I was gonna say that sort of suggests you don't need <pause dur="short"/> whatever therapy she is offering</u>
<u n="973" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I said <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I'm not <pause dur="short"/> do you think I I? <pause dur="short"/> but I think what it is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's because like I say I've <pause dur="short"/> I didn't want to be signed off sick <pause dur="short"/> I felt <trunc>ash</trunc> you know ashamed embarrassed duh-duh-duh-duh all of these things <pause dur="short"/> I haven't spent the six weeks wallowing in it <pause dur="short"/> I've been and seen people and had coffee and lunch and stuff and <pause dur="short"/> but I've done loads of exercise but I've also worked quite hard at <pause dur="short"/> sorting my own brain out and <pause dur="short"/> making myself</u>
<u n="974" who="S0517">mm yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0518">better and trying to put things in order and <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> understand things and <pause dur="short"/> think I told you about a friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on the train who</u>
<u n="976" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yes you did yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0518"><unclear>we had</unclear> some stuff to look at and everything and then I <pause dur="short"/> when erm the doctor puts you in touch with these counselling people and they're well-being <pause dur="short"/> and it's not <pause dur="short"/> and they <pause dur="short"/> contact you and they do this stuff over the phone to start off with to decide whether the theme <pause dur="short"/> works with it</u>
<u n="978" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0518">and whether it's the right thing <pause dur="short"/> and they make it quite clear <pause dur="short"/> we're not counsellors it's <pause dur="short"/> this is cognitive behaviour therapy</u>
<u n="980" who="S0517">was she the lady you'd had the phone interview with?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="982" who="S0517">oh it was somebody else again?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> somebody more superior so</u>
<u n="984" who="S0517">what she was?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0518">yes</u>
<u n="986" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the the the <pause dur="short"/> face-to-face one?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0518" trans="overlap">she she's the actual</u>
<u n="988" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="989" who="S0518" trans="overlap">doer <pause dur="short"/> if you like the other people <pause dur="short"/> work in an office</u>
<u n="990" who="S0517">are just screeners?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0518">yeah and they do the initial questions and talk you through some stuff and then make an assessment on you <pause dur="short"/> and decide <pause dur="short"/> what's the most beneficial <pause dur="short"/> so she said to me</u>
<u n="992" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="993" who="S0518">you were speaking to my colleague <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like yes <pause dur="short"/> and then she said erm <pause dur="short"/> she's put you through to me at a level three <pause dur="short"/> this is somebody that <trunc>n</trunc> has got quite complicated issues <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="994" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0518">needs a more in-depth approach on a one-to-one basis rather than just group workshops <pause dur="short"/> so I was like oh mm</u>
<u n="996" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="997" who="S0518">okay</u>
<u n="998" who="S0517">in-depth issues? <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="999" who="S0518">I think what it was is they couldn't <pause dur="short"/> pull apart whether it was <pause dur="short"/> real issues <pause dur="short"/> or <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>h</trunc>health issues or relationship issues <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> health issues they can't deal with unless it's mentally <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>men</trunc> affecting your mental health <pause dur="short"/> so if it's just side effects</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but also one of the side effects was panic attacks and and that's mental isn't it so?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and on the four sections of questions <pause dur="short"/> two of them <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>u</trunc> you know were not a worry but erm anxiety and low moods I scored highly on <pause dur="short"/> because obviously <pause dur="short"/> when I was asked the questions <pause dur="short"/> I was having daily panic attacks <pause dur="short"/> how often do you feel anxious or panicky?</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0517">every day</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0518">every day <pause dur="short"/> so that gives you a high score</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0518">you know? <pause dur="short"/> how often do you feel?</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but you didn't though did you?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0518">what?</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0517">you didn't <trunc>y</trunc>you haven't always felt anxious or? <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="1009" who="S0518">no but they ask you it's based on the last two weeks</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's <pause dur="short"/> last</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0518">so every time</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> but that I mean you've been on the drugs for the last two weeks?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0518">yeah so</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0518">when they first asked me the set of questions <pause dur="short"/> they say <pause dur="short"/> only answer how you felt in the last two weeks <pause dur="short"/> don't think back to the past don't think how you've been <pause dur="short"/> previously or whatever <pause dur="short"/> how have you felt?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0518">during the last two weeks? <pause dur="short"/> and then I think I told you I was <trunc>l</trunc> not a high-risk person because I hadn't <pause dur="short"/> entertained <pause dur="short"/> taking my own life or self-harming or anything that was <pause dur="short"/> not a problem <pause dur="short"/> and then there's a whole series of questions like how much does this affect you? <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> carrying out your social life so are you able to go out and meet people? doesn't affect me at all yes I go out <vocal desc="laugh"/> and meet people I actually feel better for meeting people</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0518">so all of those questions <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="short"/> scored really low on so they're not an issue <pause dur="short"/> but obviously anxiety and low moods because the questions that come up in low moods are <pause dur="short"/> during the course of last fortnight and it it's sort of a choice between erm <pause dur="short"/> never <pause dur="short"/> it ranges between never <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="1020" who="S0517">occasionally frequently <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc> yeah those aren't quite the words but basically every day</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0518">er all the time how often do you feel erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> as a person <pause dur="short"/> er that you are letting your <trunc>s</trunc> or others down? <pause dur="short"/> so from <pause dur="short"/> every day <pause dur="short"/> because that's how <trunc>s</trunc> you know just being off work I'm letting people down <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0517">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0518" trans="overlap">every day <pause dur="short"/> so that's why I score highly in those two areas</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0518">probably not reflective of how I am <trunc>a</trunc>all the time</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc>normally yes yeah</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but that's how they have to do it <pause dur="short"/> and so I think because there are all these <trunc>thi</trunc> issues the girl that made the assessment put me through to level three <pause dur="short"/> then <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> I went to meet this woman she's called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then erm <pause dur="short"/> she's</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is that at the surgery or?</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0518">yes but it's part of the well-being <pause dur="short"/> team</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0518">and they did make it clear to me on the phone this is cognitive behaviour therapy <pause dur="short"/> so it's not counselling <pause dur="short"/> you don't need counselling counselling is all dredging up the past <pause dur="short"/> what's gone wrong in your life to you know? where you abused as a child? whatever you know were your parents alcoholics?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> you wanted a bit of counselling though didn't you?</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> yeah but I think <pause dur="short"/> you've given me that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1037" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0517">hardly I'm not a qualified counsellor at all by any stretch</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> we all <trunc>ha</trunc> we all have things that make us what we are today <pause dur="short"/> there's nature <pause dur="short"/> and there's nurture <pause dur="short"/> so there's the way we are naturally and there's stuff that happens to us <pause dur="short"/> and I know that and I've told you what my stuff is you know? <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> brought up a Catholic <event desc="sound of mobile phone receiving message"/></u>
<u n="1040" who="S0518">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s asking me where I am</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0518">brought up a Catholic <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you want to answer him?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0518">shall I just text him back and just say?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah just tell him <pause dur="short"/> cos he'll've <unclear>forgotten</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> just text back and say shouldn't you be at a referee course? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1046" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> just had <pause dur="short"/> they're really bothered if I'm not there</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0517">well <pause dur="short"/> again it's the sort of thing my if I tell my boys they just forget <pause dur="short"/> they forget why where I am and then ring <pause dur="short"/> they're the same where are you? <pause dur="short"/> they're used to you being there</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0518">well now I'm off work they are</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0517">mm <pause dur="short"/> they'll notice it when you go back</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0518">yeah they they're quite happy for me to be off</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0517">I bet they are</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0518">now will it send no network</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0517">oh <pause dur="short"/> put it up on the windowsill <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah I forgot <pause dur="short"/> it should do because it came in</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I managed to get them here <pause dur="short"/> oh it's gone now</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0517">oh well there you go it's better on the windowsill the signal</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0518">I'll leave it now a second erm</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0517">see if he replies <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0518">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> duh-duh-duh-duh-duh <pause dur="short"/> duh-duh <pause dur="short"/> er yes so I've so you know my Catholic guilt all of that kind of stuff which we laugh about <pause dur="short"/> the fact that erm <pause dur="short"/> we've had this conversation before <pause dur="short"/> generally make better friends with men because I was in an all-girls environment where I found girls were</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0518">just let you down and erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc><trunc>u</trunc><trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> and I suppose all of that and my dad's expectations and I just felt like <pause dur="short"/> what he really wanted me to do cos he always used to say <pause dur="short"/> do something the world can't be without <pause dur="short"/> a solicitor a doctor surgeon something like that and be <trunc>l</trunc> I'd love you to go to university in York or Bath or somewhere cos he's an architect that's got really nice</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0518">you know? <pause dur="short"/> and I did a design degree <event desc="sound of mobile phone receiving message"/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0518">and went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1065" who="S0518">do you know what I mean? <event desc="sound of mobile phone receiving message"/></u>
<u n="1066" who="S0518">oh <unclear>now it's crashing Windows</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> but what <trunc>a</trunc> but what about the refereeing?</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0517">he said that?</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> can I just ring him?</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0517">yeah of course</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0518">I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you want to use the home phone because you won't get good signal there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>can I try?</unclear></u>
<u n="1073" who="S0517">no no you well try but <pause dur="short"/> you you might not</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0518">I <trunc>ha</trunc> I can't <pause dur="short"/> have I completely forgotten something then?</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0517">well if there's refereeing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he's just gotta be back round at school <pause dur="short"/> at quarter past four</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0517">do you want to use that because you won't erm</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0518" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0517">you won't get good signal?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0518">what's his number?</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0517">will will you not ring the home phone number?</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0518">well I don't know where he is now you see do I?</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0517" trans="overlap">can you?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0518">oh god what have I? I've <trunc>d</trunc> pressed the wrong buttons how do I get them off?</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1086" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0517">right what number do you want? hang on</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I'd like <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0517"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1090" who="S0518"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1091" who="S0517"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1092" who="S0518"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1093" who="S0517"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1094" who="S0518"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0517">there you go</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0518">thank you</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0517">there's a small fee for ringing mobiles</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0518">well</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1100" who="S0518">just take it off my bill</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1102" who="S0518">put it on my bill</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0517">it's not in er it's not in my package <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1104" who="S0518">oh god it's like literally you mean that truly don't you?</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0517">no I'm joking</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0518">it's just cos I don't know where he is I just thought</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0517">so he said what about the refereeing course?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0517">well it starts at four fifteen he needs to be just back at school</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he said</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0517">is he not answering now?</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> not on his mobile</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0517">do you want to try the home number?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0518">shall I?</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0517">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if he's anything like mine he won't pick up a message</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0518">it's just <pause dur="short"/> it's gone to voicemail I would leave a message <pause dur="short"/> hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's mum I've just come for a cup of tea to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> when you say what about the refereeing? <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> can you just I don't know exactly what you mean it starts at quarter past four <pause dur="short"/> till six <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't know that you were doing it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> if you can give me a call on mobile <pause dur="short"/> thanks bye</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well do you want to give him this home number?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0518">erm</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0517">in case?</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0518">or you could ring <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on this number which is</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0517" trans="overlap">if he doesn't get through <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1122" who="S0518"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0517"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1124" who="S0518"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1125" who="S0517"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/></u>
<u n="1126" who="S0518"><anon type="telephoneNumber"/> just cos the signal's very poor <pause dur="short"/> but I was gonna come home soon anyway <pause dur="short"/> bye <pause dur="short"/> and what do I switch? how do I switch it off?</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0517">oh there <pause dur="short"/> so what so what did the? <pause dur="short"/> he you said you were here and he said what about the refereeing?</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0518">yeah he said</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0517">he must've come home then</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0518">question mark kind of mean like where are you?</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1132" who="S0518">erm <pause dur="short"/> just having a cup of tea with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> home shortly but what about the refereeing?</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0517">so does he has walked home then and will it take him too long to walk back?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0518">should I try the home phone?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0517">yeah <pause dur="short"/> again ring it from that because you won't get</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0518">I might have meet for another conversation</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <event desc="sound of dialling number"/></u>
<u n="1138" who="S0518"><unclear>anyway</unclear></u>
<u n="1139" who="S0517">but you haven't paid <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he may <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1140" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I haven't paid</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0517">he may not</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0518">he's not signed up I haven't paid</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0517">I had to you had to fill out a a form before you <pause dur="short"/> before you've paid for them</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0518">he's not picking up this phone <pause dur="short"/> I reckon he's come in and gone to the toilet oh hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's mum <pause dur="short"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there? <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> okay I've just had erm I'm at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah so I've just come to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s for a cup of tea <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just text me and said where are you? <pause dur="short"/> and I said I'm having a cup of tea with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then he's text me back what about the refereeing? question mark <pause dur="short"/> so I've rung his mobile but he's not picked up so I don't know anything about this refereeing <pause dur="short"/> but he's not home yet <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> you don't know anything? <pause dur="short"/> yeah and you know that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is doing it? <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> right erm I don't know what to say then? <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0517">well get him to ring you if comes home but if he doesn't he'll want picking up at six</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1148" who="S0518">if can you erm if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> comes in can you get him to ring me? <pause dur="short"/> I've left a voicemail <pause dur="short"/> on his mobile phone <pause dur="short"/> alright then I'll be coming home shortly you alright? <pause dur="short"/> I yes I am fine thank you <pause dur="short"/> I'll see you in a bit <pause dur="short"/> bye bye <pause dur="short"/> where's the?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0517">that one yeah</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0518">thank you thanks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1151" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh so he hasn't come home even</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0518">so he's not home yet so has he been texting?</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I wonder if he stayed at school</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0518">I'll just say I'll just text him back again and say <pause dur="short"/> where are you?</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> again you'll have to put that up on the windowsill</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0518">is it on? <pause dur="short"/> are you doing it?</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0517">it is on</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0518">I don't oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's on for him</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0517">right yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0518">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0517">unless they've reminded them first day back I don't know</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0518" trans="overlap">maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe he's perhaps <trunc>ha</trunc> he's had an assembly this morning they've perhaps they've all those that want to do the refereeing course can</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0517" trans="overlap">maybe yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm sure it's not a problem if he's there you can always</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0517">pay afterwards</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0517">it's won't be a problem</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0518">no no no <pause dur="short"/> it's just that's so weird because we've had no conversation about it until you</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0517" trans="overlap">until today</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0517">yeah when I said <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0518">and he actually took his PE kit this morning and said I've got no idea whether PE today is practical or theory so I'll just take everything just in case</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0517">oh oh well at least he's got his stuff</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0517">because I think I read somewhere they need you know shin pads and notepads it's a bit indoors a bit outdoors bit of <pause dur="short"/> theory</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0517">mm <pause dur="short"/> but anyway so you didn't like this woman?</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I didn't like her because and <trunc>may</trunc> she said <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm not a counsellor <event desc="sound of mobile phone receiving message"/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1180" who="S0518">this is cognitive behaviour therapy which is what I wanted <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know I was doing it either because I didn't know it was today</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0517"><unclear>what? <pause dur="short"/> oh</unclear></u>
<u n="1182" who="S0518">can you just call me?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> kids eh?</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0518">I bet Mr Whoever <pause dur="short"/> has said to him <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you're meant to be doing it yeah</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> as they call them <pause dur="short"/> do they call yours?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0517">er big <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> big <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was called</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1190" who="S0518">when we were in parents evening the other night he comes out in the corridor <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1191" who="S0517">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1192" who="S0518">in out like this</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0518">and then but then he calls <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that as well</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0517">oh does he?</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I was I knew it was cognitive behaviour therapy and I <trunc>l</trunc> we'd done some research and they use it a lot <pause dur="short"/> in terms of erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> people suffering with food erm things <event desc="sound of mobile phone ringing"/></u>
<u n="1199" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0517">no no you take it <pause dur="short"/> maybe stand up</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0518">hello</u>
<u n="1202" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0518">hello I'm just having a cup of tea with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> now I didn't know until today that this course was on only cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is doing it <pause dur="short"/> so how have you?</u>
<u n="1204" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="1205" who="S0518">right so has Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> or Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> told you you're on it or something?</u>
<u n="1206" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>well <pause dur="short"/> I've already given him like <pause dur="short"/> all last week</unclear></u>
<u n="1207" who="S0518">oh right I haven't paid him anything though have I?</u>
<u n="1208" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0518">okay <pause dur="short"/> so you're gonna stay and do it then?</u>
<u n="1210" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>yes but that will probably won't pass the test sort of thing</unclear></u>
<u n="1211" who="S0518">yeah that's fine and I'll pick you up at six?</u>
<u n="1212" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0518">okay</u>
<u n="1214" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay <pause dur="short"/> that's all I needed to know</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> alright then <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> see you at six</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1217" who="S0518">bye <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that was easy then <pause dur="short"/> he's there and he's gonna do it</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0518">I'm here I'm doing it I said I haven't paid he went no but you have filled all the details in on a form remember? <pause dur="short"/> last year <pause dur="short"/> so he said I'm I'm on it</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0517">oh well that's alright then</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and so he said <pause dur="short"/> if I stay today though you will have to pay I said yeah no that's fine</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1223" who="S0518">I was intending to you know?</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0517">oh well have they not sent you the link then cos I couldn't</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="1226" who="S0517">do you want me to send it to you when I find it?</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0518">can you email it to me? I've got my emails attached to my phone now</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0517">I can email it to you erm because the school emailed it to me and it was just <pause dur="short"/> I'll just forward what they sent to me and it's just a link <trunc>i</trunc> and you have to fill out their <pause dur="short"/> form</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0518">I'm at school where it will be it is on and yes I'm doing it but I think that will mean I have to pay</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> obviously</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0518">that was yeah that's fine <pause dur="short"/> perhaps he was just worrying thinking</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0517">thinking</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0517">can I stay if I haven't <trunc>pai</trunc>?</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc> can I? <pause dur="short"/> what if mum doesn't know?</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah probably</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0518">but well I wouldn't've filled in all the forms and sent it all back would I?</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0518">well that answers the question doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0517">well there you go he is doing it excellent good</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so cognitive behaviour therapy <pause dur="short"/> I thought <pause dur="short"/> it would be really good because it would be used <pause dur="short"/> it they use it a lot in people with food disorders like <pause dur="short"/> anaemia not anaemia not anorexia and bulimia and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0518">and obviously er a lot of <pause dur="short"/> things that I worry about are to do with food like <pause dur="short"/> oh come round for a meal then you erm <unclear>have to</unclear> say <pause dur="short"/> feel really embarrassed like I you know what we gonna eat and <trunc>have</trunc> you have to know all of this ahead of time and did I say it to you thinking about when I was growing up and my mum was saying you finish everything on the plate?</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah but it all and it often did make you sick</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0518">and it made me poorly and her not just saying oh I'm not having this I'm not having this</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0518"><unclear>faddy</unclear> you know business and all this sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> so I thought it would be really useful for that <pause dur="short"/> we didn't talk about that at all</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0518">and she just sort of <trunc>s</trunc>said to me <pause dur="short"/> I think you've got a really from the sounds of it you've got a really close network of friends people that care about you a lot people that've been worried about you a lot can I tell you that most people that come through my doors <pause dur="short"/> do not have one single person to talk to <pause dur="short"/> they could not speak to anybody face-to-face they would not go out they would not socialise they would not go and see friends</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so she was pretty much saying <pause dur="short"/> you didn't need to be there <pause dur="short"/> you didn't</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I said that to her are you saying that I'm not suited to this and that actually?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0518">cos I said the last thing I want to do is waste your time <pause dur="short"/> but I said er obviously I've done a lot of research I've looked into a lot of stuff myself and <pause dur="short"/> I've done a lot to help myself I said <pause dur="short"/> I'm not somebody for just sitting around in a corner and not</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0518">you know​? <unclear>and</unclear></u>
<u n="1256" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but at the end of the day you were at the <pause dur="short"/> doctors for all these medical reasons they referred you</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I said that to her</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you had to to all the phone tests it's this hasn't come from you this has come from them</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I said that to her</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0517">so to make you feel like you're wasting her time was</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0517">bang out of order really</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0518">well I said that to her I said I'm here because my GP referred me and hello</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0517">hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0518">you alright?</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how was school?</u>
<u n="1268" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes thank you</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0517">yeah you can have a chocolate just the one</u>
<u n="1270" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">thanks</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0518"><unclear>yeah she's okay</unclear></u>
<u n="1273" who="S0517" trans="overlap">we're just in the middle of a conversation</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0518">you can join in?</u>
<u n="1275" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh what you earning money?</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1277" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I'm not</unclear></u>
<u n="1278" who="S0517" trans="overlap">did you give your geography cheque in?</u>
<u n="1279" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">tomorrow</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0517">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> did you?</u>
<u n="1281" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">can I have another please?</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0517"><vocal desc="sigh"/> oh go on then one <trunc>m</trunc> did you hear about your <pause dur="short"/> if you passed your course yet?</u>
<u n="1283" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er <pause dur="short"/> upstairs now</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0517">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="1285" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've gotta go check my emails</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0517">oh oh okay then not on your phone? <pause dur="short"/> oh well <trunc>le</trunc> did they say today? <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>le</trunc></u>
<u n="1287" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got his</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0517">what did he get?</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1290" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he got the bottom grade</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0517">did he? how come?</u>
<u n="1292" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">dunno <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1293" who="S0518">but he has passed?</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0517">but he's passed?</u>
<u n="1295" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah he's passed I'll go and have a look now</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0517">oh gosh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's not good is it? because <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really bright</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0518">do you want me to go?</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0517">no <pause dur="short"/> see there's me I'm laughing about this three hundred pound waterproof it better not be</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but it could be true</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0517">yeah it could be could be</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it could all be true <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it'll be fine</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so what did she say when you said to <unclear>not</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so I said the doctor referred me <pause dur="short"/> I said I've been I had an initial <pause dur="short"/> er consultation and then I had the consultation with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's the one that's taken all these notes and passed them to you and that's the reason why I'm here <pause dur="short"/> and she said <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> no offence to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but she said she's quite new to this role and she said I really feel that she's been unprofessional and out of order because she's said things to you and promised things to do you and discussed things with you <pause dur="short"/> she said that are really my position <pause dur="short"/> and she said it's up for to me on meeting you and going through things in more detail to decide whether really this is the right form of er of support for you <pause dur="short"/> so I said and what do you think then?</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1306" who="S0518">no? <pause dur="short"/> and she said erm I said cos I get the vibe from you that you think <pause dur="short"/> I'm far too sorted <pause dur="short"/> and able to <pause dur="short"/> you know I've got lots of stuff that's going for me</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0518">I said I know you can't help me with erm relationship problems <pause dur="short"/> and I know you can't help me with medical problems</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0518">and she said <pause dur="short"/> mm she said but it's</u>
<u n="1311" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm not sure if the guy's an idiot or something but there was another man on the course called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and my email starts with hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1312" who="S0518">oh no</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> how did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do?</u>
<u n="1314" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he got instructor two</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0517">he got what?</u>
<u n="1316" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">the bottom one as well</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0517">but you don't know if that's for you or not?</u>
<u n="1318" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0518">but you're <unclear>called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></unclear></u>
<u n="1320" who="S0517" trans="overlap">because it said hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1321" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah it says hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1322" who="S0517" trans="overlap">what did the grades go? fail instructor two instructor one pro?</u>
<u n="1323" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0518" trans="overlap">can you email back and say?</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can you hit reply? who's it from?</u>
<u n="1327" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I'd just ring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1328" who="S0517">well no why would he know?</u>
<u n="1329" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">he knows the guy</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0517">no I'd go no go back to the guy</u>
<u n="1331" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">right <pause dur="short"/> I need the toilet first</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0517">okay go <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1334" who="S0517">oh gosh that's not good is it?</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> that's awful</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0517">that's that's very unprofessional</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0518">and it makes you think has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got the right mark or have they got someone else's?</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> goodness <pause dur="short"/> I hope he got <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh anyway</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0518" trans="overlap">demand a recount</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0517">yeah that's weird isn't? well the way they did it just to <trunc>digre</trunc> you know they were <trunc>say</trunc> I said there was those three tests</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0517">the written the the skills and the coaching? <pause dur="short"/> they didn't then <pause dur="short"/> mark each one and take an average <pause dur="short"/> you got the bottom <pause dur="short"/> one</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0517">that's that cos that's what he came back and said on the first day so you know if you're <pause dur="short"/> cos there was one chap on the course who's <pause dur="short"/> who's a good instructor he he's really good with the little kids and everything very good but his actual <pause dur="short"/> his tennis skills are <trunc>n</trunc> fantastic you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a better tennis player <pause dur="short"/> erm cos I said oh that's a shame cos <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> may be <pause dur="short"/> marked lower he said well that's what they've said they do so <pause dur="short"/> so for instance with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with his you know</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0517">the way he is with his <pause dur="short"/> dyslexia <pause dur="short"/> his written one could've been low <pause dur="short"/> cos I think his coaching and his and his er skills would've been fine but you don't know about that written one</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0517">which was an hour's test so he said no they just take the bottom one</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0518">well I think that's a bit unfair</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0517">I do too but anyway that's that's how it was done so</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0518">I think that's a little bit unfair</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0517">so is she gonna have you have you back or not?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> because <pause dur="short"/> I think then she felt that she maybe had been er a bit out of order <pause dur="short"/> because you know I was quite upset as well during it <pause dur="short"/> and she said to me she said <pause dur="short"/> I don't really understand why you have low self-esteem issues <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> she said er seems to me that you know you've got great friends and a great support network <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> I I I <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> said to her tried to explain to her that I don't actually believe what people say <pause dur="short"/> and erm so I said my manager at work will <trunc>sel</trunc> say to me <pause dur="short"/> you've done a great job so I'm gonna put you into this erm <pause dur="short"/> quality position <pause dur="short"/> and I said and I'll just think oh <pause dur="short"/> it there's some ulterior motive and actually I don't trust her and that <pause dur="short"/> and I said that's because of a <pause dur="short"/> I know what it's from I said a major life thing that happened to me which I told about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> where the person that I trusted the most <pause dur="short"/> had been lying to me for years and years and years <pause dur="short"/> so now I just always have my guard up <pause dur="short"/> and she said but you seem a really open loving erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> er you know <trunc>c</trunc><trunc>talk</trunc>talkative person that erm</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0518">not as if you have a guard up and I said yeah but I said it's like <pause dur="short"/> so you know right <anon type="place"/>? I said I've done the <anon type="place"/> thing <pause dur="short"/> and I said where? <pause dur="short"/> and picked up this pencil and I said <pause dur="short"/> my natural <pause dur="short"/> leaning to <trunc>wr</trunc>write with my right hand <pause dur="short"/> that's what I do naturally <pause dur="short"/> but if I need to <pause dur="short"/> I can make myself write with my left hand <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I said <event desc="sound of mobile phone receiving message"/></u>
<u n="1356" who="S0518">oh <pause dur="short"/> sorry <event desc="sound of mobile phone receiving message"/></u>
<u n="1357" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> who is it? <pause dur="short"/> is that a phone call?</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0518">on it's three texts I wonder if they've been queueing up to come in</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0517">oh probably cos you're in <anon type="place"/> now don't forget</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0518">that <trunc>m</trunc> the the other two don't matter I don't realise <pause dur="short"/> but the refereeing course is on tonight till six <unclear>I'm over there</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> oh the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s obviously sent them they're all coming through in the wrong order because this all makes sense now</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0517">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's because of where you are <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1362" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah I don't need to respond to them that's fine</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh fine yeah it's yeah they do they come this is what happens to me all the time</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0517">comes through randomly you don't know when you've sent me a</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he obviously sent obviously sent that one earlier</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0517">then I think that like that time do you remember I said oh our texts have</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0517">passed?</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0518">yes</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0517">and you said no I sent mine five hours ago</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0517">yeah it's</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0518">or I text you at midnight which I hadn't</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0517" trans="overlap">hadn't yeah it's just</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0518">of course of course</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's just it's where you are I'm afraid</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> of course <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> so I actually said to her you know? <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="short"/> naturally my instinct and my leaning is to to trust people I want to do that and I am a very open I love people I love people <pause dur="short"/> and I said but all the time in the back of my mind there's this little guard <pause dur="short"/> that when someone gives me a compliment or says I've done a good job <pause dur="short"/> I don't trust that <pause dur="short"/> so I said when my friends say we're worried about you and we want you to be feel better and I'm not thinking of you in this <pause dur="short"/> at all <pause dur="short"/> but like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> I think that they have an ulterior motive because they want me to feel better <pause dur="short"/> because actually they're needy and they don't like it when I'm poorly <pause dur="short"/> because they're like woah we don't like you like this</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0518" trans="overlap">cos who's gonna look after us?</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0518">so she <trunc>s</trunc> and I said about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> following her into the shop she said well someone following you to the shop sounds like somebody who really cares <pause dur="short"/> I said <pause dur="short"/> let me just put it into perspective <pause dur="short"/> I probably wasn't helping myself <pause dur="short"/> I said I've got a friend called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I said</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0518">when I was poorly one weekend <pause dur="short"/> I said I can't do this because I'm not very well duh-duh-duh <pause dur="short"/> and she said sorry to hear about that I'm in <anon type="place"/> do you need any shopping? <pause dur="short"/> and I said I'm absolutely fine but thank you for offering <pause dur="short"/> brilliant <pause dur="short"/> you know where I am <pause dur="short"/> shout up <pause dur="short"/> have a good rest <pause dur="short"/> and I said that is somebody being supportive <pause dur="short"/> can I help? <pause dur="short"/> I said no I'm fine <pause dur="short"/> I understand that <pause dur="short"/> but ask me if you need <pause dur="short"/> I said that <pause dur="short"/> is a supportive friend <pause dur="short"/> I'm not very well I can't duh-duh-duh-duh <pause dur="short"/> shall I drive round and see you? no I'm fine <pause dur="short"/> I'm outside your door are you sure you don't want to see? no I'm fine go away <pause dur="short"/> don't want to freak you out but I'm running up and down outside your house cos I need to be close to you cos I'm worried about you</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's not normal</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0518" trans="overlap">like shall I call you? shall I call you? shall I call you? I'm parked in a lay-by shall I call you? <pause dur="short"/> god alright call me then <pause dur="short"/> oh now I've made you cry wish I hadn't called you <pause dur="short"/> so I <trunc>s</trunc> and then</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah that's not <pause dur="short"/> that's not normal</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so then she said <pause dur="short"/> I can't pick your friends for you</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0518">I said I'm not asking you to I'm trying to tell you why <pause dur="short"/> I feel sometimes when my friends are being supportive <pause dur="short"/> I'm doubtful what their actual motives are <pause dur="short"/> because I said I don't feel that <pause dur="short"/> for stalking me <pause dur="short"/> was a supportive motive I feel it was <pause dur="short"/> a needy person going <pause dur="short"/> oh god</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0517">I want you to be alright yeah I need you</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I want you better because I need you for me <pause dur="short"/> so she said well I'm sorry she said <pause dur="short"/> if you want your friends to be a certain way she said I think that's quite prescriptive of you and she said <pause dur="short"/> I said no I don't I'm not saying that</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0517">oh god she sounds like a bit of a</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I didn't like her <pause dur="short"/> I didn't like her at all</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so have you got another? <pause dur="short"/> appointment?</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so <trunc>anyw</trunc> at the end of it she said <pause dur="short"/> everything that we do is evidence-based <pause dur="short"/> and she said I cannot go to my superior and say <pause dur="short"/> I'm just helping her with a bit of this and bit of that <pause dur="short"/> so she said I need to go with a proper plan so she said I need to know that there's definitely an area that we can work on <pause dur="short"/> so she says to my mind <pause dur="short"/> she said I think erm there are some <pause dur="short"/> self-esteem issues she said not <pause dur="short"/> true self-esteem issues but more <pause dur="short"/> your perception of how you think other people perceive you <pause dur="short"/> so she she gave it a name and I've forgotten what it was</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0518">so she said it's expectations <pause dur="short"/> the expectations that people put on you and your perception of what that should be <pause dur="short"/> and she said and you understanding that <pause dur="short"/> just because you've got all this Catholic guilt and stuff on you <pause dur="short"/> and other people have lied to you in the past not everybody <pause dur="short"/> is going to continue to do that <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0517"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1402" who="S0518"><trunc>sh</trunc> we need to look at that and <pause dur="short"/> you just <pause dur="short"/> being able to say <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> actually some things I'm not great at but some things I am really great at <pause dur="short"/> and just understanding <pause dur="short"/> that you are <pause dur="short"/> and she said and then <pause dur="short"/> I can't <trunc>a</trunc>anxiety that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but she said I'm I'm struggling on that because she said <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> you have been knocked off your feet she said you've been put had these operations you've been put on this drug <pause dur="short"/> you had to eat a bad diet that made you poorly you didn't take any time off work <pause dur="short"/> you've got lots of family pressures on you <pause dur="short"/> and she said I think a lot of the anxiety is to do with the drugs that you've been on <pause dur="short"/> and she said I want to monitor you <pause dur="short"/> now you're on the reduced <pause dur="short"/> level of drugs just to see if that anxiety gets better <pause dur="short"/> which you know panic attacks I think has got is better</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah yes</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0518">so she's given me some homework to do and she's booked another appointment for a fortnight so she said I want you to go away <pause dur="short"/> read these things <pause dur="short"/> answer these questions and see whether you think there is some mileage in this for you <pause dur="short"/> but when I go back I'm gonna say to her <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc>what about <pause dur="short"/> helping with the actual because <pause dur="short"/> whatever drug I'm on it's only gonna help me to a certain extent so <pause dur="short"/> is there no cognitive therapy behaviour that's gonna help me with the food intolerances</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0517">well yes and like you say the triggers that make you panic</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0517">because somebody says <pause dur="short"/> do you want a biscuit with your tea?</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0518">yeah it's <trunc>u</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0518">and I don't panic</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0517">no I know but they that sort of uncomfortable feeling if it's somebody you don't know that you've then got to go in to start telling them your</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0517">all your food issues to you know? it</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and saying like the Christmas party with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and that she's fallen out the trouble we had last year to ring up and see what the options are and all of that</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah it became a bit of a <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="1416" who="S0518" trans="overlap">said it's not gonna <trunc>c</trunc> it's not gonna cure that</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0517">no but just ways to</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0517">that's like that like you say that was supposed to be <pause dur="short"/> the point of the therapy wasn't it? to give you</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I thought <pause dur="short"/> to look at the things that</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0517">and <trunc>s</trunc> you could go back and say to her well <pause dur="short"/> I have thought <trunc>th</trunc> all this through I've <pause dur="short"/> taken on board what you said and actually this is the area I would like to work on</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and see what she says</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0517">you know?</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0518">and if she says</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0517" trans="overlap">take this to your superior and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1428" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and if she says no I'll say well thanks I don't think it's for me I honestly thought I could do better myself done better myself <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well like you said if you've been researching it on the internet and how you're suppose to sort of <pause dur="short"/> I don't know anything about it but <pause dur="short"/> you probably could do better <pause dur="short"/> you</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><trunc>co</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> er they if you look it up it'll tell you stuff so it's quite interesting</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0518">and it's it's <pause dur="short"/> stuff that's happened all goes to shape the person that we are we can't do anything about that because that's happened <pause dur="short"/> but it's when we come up against something that potentially <pause dur="short"/> can <pause dur="short"/> trigger something off <pause dur="short"/> that you pick the right attitude to deal with it</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0518">so certain things <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="short"/> do anyway <pause dur="short"/> and that's why <pause dur="short"/> I was going to work <pause dur="short"/> because <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>w</trunc> have the attitude where I don't take my problems to work <pause dur="short"/> I leave them on the doorstep <pause dur="short"/> and then I go in and put this and do a professional job</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0518">and I can do that quite easily and I probably <pause dur="short"/> employ <pause dur="short"/> quite a few <pause dur="short"/> acting skills in <pause dur="short"/> in</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0517">yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0518" trans="overlap">doing that <pause dur="short"/> so I can make those choices <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> and I think you said to me I think it's just women <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said you've got a busy mind everything all goes across in your <trunc>br</trunc> once you need <pause dur="short"/> separate out</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh yeah but there's always so much going on <trunc>d</trunc> isn't there?</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> yeah but I think sometimes a <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> a logical decision <pause dur="short"/> my logical mind'll tell me this but my emotional <trunc>j</trunc> thing will just get in the way of it</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0518">to be honest</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0518">but <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc><trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> on Friday</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was really upset on Friday and I had a whole diatribe</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh did you see him?</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0518">yeah cos he was at the theatre with his family when we were there</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0517">oh gosh we'll have to have that for another time cos I'm gonna have to take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to the tennis club</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>g</trunc> I'm so sorry <unclear>I didn't know you</unclear> do the er</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no no no that's fine so shall I shall I?</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0518">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0517" trans="overlap">shall I stop this anyway and we'll erm?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0518">the long and short of that <trunc>w</trunc></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
