<text id="S9GP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:28:45</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-03-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0327</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Paris, languages, travel, family, university, bees, German, Classics, computer problems, Italy</topics>
		<activity>lunch </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0327">
				<exactage>76</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Vienna</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Italy</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Austria</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>74</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Artist</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0326">hello <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0327">lovely to see you it's been ages</u>
<u n="3" who="S0326"><unclear>mm it's been a while</unclear></u>
<u n="4" who="S0327">what happened with the train? <unclear/> Sundays</u>
<u n="5" who="S0326">yeah I dunno it's I just it's alright cos I got to <anon type="place"/> then I walked</u>
<u n="6" who="S0327">you walked from <anon type="place"/>? well very good for you</u>
<u n="7" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0327">excellent</u>
<u n="9" who="S0326">it's only about half an hour</u>
<u n="10" who="S0327">okay yes that's right well I haven't put the pizza in yet what can I offer you? cup of tea? cup of coffee? <trunc>gla</trunc> there's some nice wine actually</u>
<u n="11" who="S0326">erm I'll just have some water <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0327">just want water?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0326">and and actually I'll have er a tea as well please</u>
<u n="14" who="S0327">a tea and a water no problem <pause dur="short"/> sit down er there are a couple of things I'm gonna ask you to do before lunch</u>
<u n="15" who="S0326" trans="overlap">that's alright</u>
<u n="16" who="S0327">one is put a chair outside and the other is er of course I can't resist asking you with er computer problems</u>
<u n="17" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> let's make some tea <pause dur="short"/> so is this what is this? half-term? this is Easter break? I can't</u>
<u n="19" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah sort of Easter break spring break</u>
<u n="20" who="S0327">spring break</u>
<u n="21" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0327">so now you're halfway through your second year?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> halfway through the whole thing</u>
<u n="24" who="S0327"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's goes so fast <pause dur="short"/> goes so fast before you know where you are you'll be <unclear/> your old age pension</u>
<u n="25" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0327"><unclear/> this put the oven on <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0326">which is the chair you wanna put outside?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0327">erm erm it's one from the this is a chair that I got last year and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was here <unclear/> the time but that one's not very good so maybe let's put that out if you can fold that up</u>
<u n="29" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0327">put it with the other ones put that out and then I'll see what I've got there it'll be really great <unclear/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0326">wait which one? <trunc>s</trunc> fold up the one in?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0327" trans="overlap">so you can fold up the green one <unclear/> which is tricky</u>
<u n="33" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0327">and stick it against the other ones at the door and and see I mean I'm hoping this is an easier one to handle <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0326">erm I'll just do it in a minute it's</u>
<u n="36" who="S0327"><unclear/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0326">it is it is quite warm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0327">it's relatively warm <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> so let's give you a cup of tea</u>
<u n="39" who="S0326">I'm really looking forward to it being warm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0327">what?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0326">I'm really looking forward to it being warm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0327">oh er so am I I mean mind you you've just come back from Paris haven't you?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0327">how was that?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0326">that was alright but it's er <trunc>sor</trunc> basically the same temperature</u>
<u n="46" who="S0327">I guess so Paris can also be quite cold did you er did you just go to see someone <unclear/> have a good time or what?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0326">erm sort of both a friend of me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s from New York was there for work <pause dur="short"/> and we and he stayed on a bit longer so we all hung out together</u>
<u n="48" who="S0327">oh right</u>
<u n="49" who="S0326">in Paris for a few days</u>
<u n="50" who="S0327">where do you stay?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0326">erm we stayed in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend has an apartment in <anon type="place"/> in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="53" who="S0326">arrondissement so we stayed there</u>
<u n="54" who="S0327">well that sounds nice</u>
<u n="55" who="S0326" trans="overlap">in a very tiny tiny tiny little apartment</u>
<u n="56" who="S0327">is it?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0326">it's like one room</u>
<u n="58" who="S0327">they do of course the French yeah they've always lived in these miniscule places they have all their social life in cafés don't they?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0327">erm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0326">this is what erm you got for Christmas <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes it's too turned out to be too small for the butter</u>
<u n="63" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0327">erm so you could have everything there and when the pizza's ready we'll have a drink of that then I'll show you the erm <pause dur="short"/> so tell me what is the latest with er <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> nothing really I just I suppose all er I just have to do exams in a couple of months</u>
<u n="66" who="S0327">oh do you?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0326">yeah which is a bit of a drag</u>
<u n="68" who="S0327">what are they called? the second year exams?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if they have a name</u>
<u n="70" who="S0327">don't they? right</u>
<u n="71" who="S0326">erm it's the end of part one <pause dur="short"/> and then the next year's finals</u>
<u n="72" who="S0327">gonna try for a first?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0326">tut erm maybe yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll see how it goes this year but I mean I think if I I put I'm capable of it it's really</u>
<u n="74" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh we we know you're capable of it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is are you gonna be arsed is the is the question</u>
<u n="75" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it is the question</u>
<u n="76" who="S0327">you know what I would say? I would say it's worth it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> if if you can do it er cos I mean getting it you know you are in a very special position having having the wherewithal to do it not everybody does and I suspect a first will stand you well in stead in various whatever happens in your life</u>
<u n="77" who="S0326">yeah well er it's just sort of satisfying as well</u>
<u n="78" who="S0327">and it's satisfying exactly erm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0326">like if you <trunc>d</trunc>do something you might as well do it I mean <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="80" who="S0327" trans="overlap">well are you enjoying it?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0326">yeah I enjoy I like it I like the work and stuff</u>
<u n="82" who="S0327" trans="overlap">that's nice</u>
<u n="83" who="S0326">it's interesting</u>
<u n="84" who="S0327">are you learning stuff?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0327">and you're pleased with your tutors?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0326">yeah they're all good</u>
<u n="88" who="S0327">well I'm very glad to hear it cos you know really <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't have a very good time with her tutors  she finds them incredibly difficult to get hold of</u>
<u n="89" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0327">and not very helpful</u>
<u n="91" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0327">and you know both her mum and I have said look you're paying nine thousand a year you wanna get your</u>
<u n="93" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear>it's a</unclear> demand yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0327">money's worth</u>
<u n="95" who="S0326">cos also lots of</u>
<u n="96" who="S0327" trans="overlap">but she's also finding the work <trunc>interes</trunc> I think she works she probably has to work harder than you do to to get as far but erm I think she's also finding it interesting</u>
<u n="97" who="S0326">yeah she er erm messaged me the other week cos she's doing a <trunc>s</trunc> a dissertation about beekeeping in the</u>
<u n="98" who="S0327" trans="overlap">I think yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0326">in the ancient Mediterranean</u>
<u n="100" who="S0327">I think that's really interesting</u>
<u n="101" who="S0326">so I was telling her some texts er sort sort of cos the Romans were really obsessed with bees</u>
<u n="102" who="S0327">were they?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0327">were they?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0326">they think they could <trunc>l</trunc> they they thought you could sort of tell <trunc>y</trunc>you know sort of augury with birds? they did the same thing with bees <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0327">did they <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah and then Virgil wrote a whole sort of book of poetry about bees <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he says they're like er</u>
<u n="108" who="S0327" trans="overlap">well I think it'd be really great if she can put together a thesis on that</u>
<u n="109" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0327">because erm I mean I suppose there are some are there? some complete what's happened there?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0326">oh it got smashed up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0327">erm well she ought we ought to pick your brains then</u>
<u n="113" who="S0326">yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah they really like them and they were interested in them and they think they can they think if they sort of if there's a swarm of bees they <trunc>m</trunc> it means so and so's gonna happen er you know?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0327">I don't think we've got any further erm much since then</u>
<u n="115" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0327">you know I would just as soon put my faith in a swarm of bees as I would in the in the weather forecast these days <vocal desc="laugh"/> frankly erm <pause dur="short"/> yes no I think that's that's really really good and I mean the the best thing is to of course to be interested</u>
<u n="117" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> and what do you have to choose a thesis? or are you?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0326">erm I don't have I mean I probably will do a dissertation next year but I haven't I can't really <trunc>dec</trunc> think of something to do it about <pause dur="short"/> erm I'll probably do something er sort of reception <trunc>y</trunc>you know like sort of reception theory</u>
<u n="120" who="S0327">no what's reception theory?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0326">it's kind of like just the way you I think it it just makes classics sort of relevant to me the way <pause dur="short"/> you interpret er instead of trying to <trunc>ac</trunc> think like a Roman you think like a sort of someone from the twenty-first century when you read the texts so <pause dur="short"/> it's sort of like books like <vocal desc="cough"/> like Homer in the twentieth century <pause dur="short"/> how to interpret differently</u>
<event desc="sound of cooking"/>
<u n="122" who="S0327">did they say twelve minutes for this? <pause dur="short"/> twelve minutes</u>
<u n="123" who="S0326">ah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0327">oh <pause dur="short"/> I'm just trying to get my head round that</u>
<u n="125" who="S0326">so it's just the way sort of it's it's really sort of simple it's just the way you respond to something it's the way you receive it</u>
<u n="126" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="127" who="S0326">but it's in classics it's interesting because there's sort of a <trunc>dialo</trunc> so if you look at Homer people have been receiving that sort of all the way through from like Roman to from Greek to Roman to the Middle Ages to now and it's I think it's it's counter-intuitive if you think everybody's response responds the same way to things erm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0327">er <trunc>r</trunc> you mean everybody within a <trunc>perio</trunc> or everybody over a very long period?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0326">over sort of it make it makes the the work sort of <trunc>s</trunc> you you can like free it from its position er and and sort of rework it and look at it new</u>
<u n="130" who="S0327" trans="overlap">and look at it new yes <pause dur="short"/> well I mean to some extent we do that anyhow don't we?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah it's it's that's why it's like sort of simple but</u>
<u n="132" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="133" who="S0326">I <trunc>th</trunc> I just think it's a bit it's helpful to think erm try and get into the mindset of of sort of Greek and Romans but it's not</u>
<u n="134" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="135" who="S0326">the it's not the end all and be all</u>
<u n="136" who="S0327">right <pause dur="short"/> I mean <trunc>f</trunc> you know it seems to me that politically a lot of stuff people think oh they shouldn't have done this or they shouldn't have <trunc>d</trunc> you know you take something like I don't know anti-Semitism well anti-Semitism say in the early nineteenth century</u>
<u n="137" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0327">er was going to be er seen very differently from the way it is now</u>
<u n="139" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0327">and lots of people can't do that they can't make that leap erm you know there's erm a that's that's one of the things I didn't like about postmodernism when it came in or or literary theory that that everything was judged from the viewpoint now er I mean <trunc>w</trunc> I'm talking about within art so you take someone like Gauguin and you would deconstruct and look at him in terms of colonialism and so on but actually that really wasn't his fault</u>
<u n="141" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0327">that was the world he was born into he why would he have taken much notice of that? he was an artist so you can't say these paintings aren't any good or not to be taken seriously or we dismiss them erm because they are politically doubtful</u>
<u n="143" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and so it er kind of keeps things alive because they're not <trunc>f</trunc> really fixed</u>
<u n="144" who="S0327">not er they're not fixed very little is fixed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's interesting yeah exactly which is just sort of <pause dur="short"/> it's I think it's it frees you up from kind of sort of lots of academic stuff you try and fit things into little straightjackets</u>
<u n="146" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0326">erm and I think it's just more interesting and more more good to think with like more sort of gives your er your own ideas</u>
<u n="148" who="S0327">well I know that at some point a few months ago <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that what they what they want from them in their what is she? in her third year is a personal view of er</u>
<u n="149" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0327">and I thought actually for archaeology that is really difficult <pause dur="short"/> I mean how can you have a <trunc>p</trunc>? I can see what you're doing <trunc>y</trunc>you know in a way <vocal desc="cough"/> things are more general erm because you're looking at the way that all society responds to things but for archaeology when you're talking about artefacts which have been scientifically</u>
<u n="151" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0327">and chemically dated and so on how are you supposed to be original about that?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0326">it's not easy really</u>
<u n="154" who="S0327">I mean I think those Tudors were just bored and they've come up with they want to be entertained a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0326">but they might <unclear>as well</unclear> ask people to do that because it's it's more <trunc>int</trunc> it's more <trunc>in</trunc>interesting for yourself as well</u>
<u n="156" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="157" who="S0326">instead of just copying things out of books</u>
<u n="158" who="S0327" trans="overlap">exactly otherwise you know er erm and you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a rather piercing and original mind and er but she can also just absorb facts you can both do that in a way I never could it's very very impressive how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> getting on?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0326">he's er I think he's alright he's actually I saw him last night he's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="161" who="S0326">erm I think he's <trunc>d</trunc> I think I think he's sort of finished for the year</u>
<u n="162" who="S0327">oh has he?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0326">I mean he has like a sort of study period that he er and then does exams I think</u>
<u n="164" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="165" who="S0326">but I think his sort of tuition has ended already <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0327" trans="overlap">okay really? and we're only in March</u>
<u n="167" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well it ends er or it ends in ends in <pause dur="short"/> good Friday</u>
<u n="168" who="S0327" trans="overlap">and is he supposed to do stuff on his own?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0326">yeah I think they er I think he'll he'll have work to do but he doesn't have to be in <anon type="place"/> necessarily</u>
<u n="170" who="S0327">right <pause dur="short"/> and has he got over being dumped?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0326">dunno</u>
<u n="172" who="S0327">you don't know?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0327">you don't know if there's a new girlfriend on the scene?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0326">erm I don't know if there is should be <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0327">well it's perfectly possible to go for a little while without</u>
<u n="177" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0327">erm and you've still got your lovely cake-maker?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0326">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0327">well done</u>
<u n="181" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was her birthday yesterday</u>
<u n="182" who="S0327">was it? did she make a special cake?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no we just sort of went out for a <trunc>w</trunc> party</u>
<u n="184" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc>what did you give her for her birthday?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0326">I'm taking her I'm er taking her tomorrow to erm <anon type="place"/> do you have you know there? have you been there?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0327" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="187" who="S0326">it's in <anon type="place"/> and it's erm it's attached by sort of a Roman causeway which at high tide you know it's cut off from the mainland</u>
<u n="188" who="S0327">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0326">and they you can go you go there and there's erm it's famous for sort of seafood shacks where you can get oysters and stuff</u>
<u n="190" who="S0327">oh those sorts of places are wonderful</u>
<u n="191" who="S0326">yeah and it's sort of really a bit strange and spooky</u>
<u n="192" who="S0327">oh how nice what fun</u>
<u n="193" who="S0326">yeah and <unclear>then</unclear> gonna go fishing there</u>
<u n="194" who="S0327">you're gonna go fishing?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0326">she likes fishing <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so I was I've been emailing this fisherman in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="197" who="S0326" trans="overlap">just take</u>
<u n="198" who="S0327">can you fish? have you ever fished?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0326">mm only in sort of line fishing</u>
<u n="200" who="S0327">well what else is there?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0326">rod fishing <pause dur="short"/> you know so <trunc>w</trunc>when we went to Scotland with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we just sort of put a line over and <trunc>h</trunc> leave it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0327">oh right</u>
<u n="203" who="S0326">and then when you catch something you er</u>
<u n="204" who="S0327" trans="overlap">and then you catch something or you don't</u>
<u n="205" who="S0326">you just pull it up yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0327">but rod fishing you throw it in with a fly and</u>
<u n="207" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0327">and all that</u>
<u n="209" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0327">yes quite I tried to do it once I just couldn't cope with the flies or the maggots</u>
<u n="211" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we went in erm when we were in Mexico did I see you since we went I went to Mexico?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0327">actually no no you're such a traveller</u>
<u n="213" who="S0326">we went to Mexico and our friend erm he had sort of got a really expensive <trunc>fish</trunc> did a fishing trip sort of sports fishing it's er seven hours long in deep sea and you're meant to catch like huge fish</u>
<u n="214" who="S0327">oh how wonderful</u>
<u n="215" who="S0326">but it was seven hours didn't catch anything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0327">no</u>
<u n="217" who="S0326">and then he spent the whole time</u>
<u n="218" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><unclear>what er</unclear> sea?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0326">what sea?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="221" who="S0326">Pacific Ocean</u>
<u n="222" who="S0327">Pacific?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0326">there's not enough in there anymore <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then he spent the whole time being sick <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0327">seasick? oh there's nothing worse than that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is there? so it was rocky?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0326">yeah well it was a bit sort of like that</u>
<u n="226" who="S0327">I only have to think of a ship <unclear>and I a</unclear> boat and I get seasick it's really horrible</u>
<u n="227" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0327">when I was first with your grandad erm we used to often go to France <unclear/> by boat <unclear/> three-hour trips and one erm on one occasion I remember I felt so awful and I went downstairs to the loo and the boat I didn't realize that the boat docked completely emptied and I heard this pathetic voice calling my name outside the door</u>
<u n="229" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0327">and I was sitting kneeling with my head in the loo and it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> calling <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> where are you?</u>
<u n="231" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0327">apparently a lot of sailors get seasick for the first twenty-four hours cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to erm be a skipper</u>
<u n="233" who="S0326">right</u>
<u n="234" who="S0327">er for a while and he said for the first twenty-four hours he was usually he was usually sick</u>
<u n="235" who="S0326">yeah and er sort of once you've been on a boat for ages getting back onto land <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0327">yes yes but that's slightly better well it doesn't seem natural to me <pause dur="short"/> and your social life is still in <anon type="place"/> rather than <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0326">yeah mainly I mean it's er I've I've got friends in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> who have you made friends with?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0326">just sort of <trunc>s</trunc>sort of the same people as last year but like one sort of quite good friend erm <pause dur="short"/> and then there's sort of I dunno if you ever met erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who went to <anon type="place"/>? <pause dur="short"/> he's</u>
<u n="240" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear>I think</unclear> there's only one there's only one friend of yours I remember meeting</u>
<u n="241" who="S0326">so er he's er he's it's funny to to be at school with him again because we went different places for sixth form and he's er in the year above</u>
<u n="242" who="S0327">and he's at <anon type="place"/> now?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0327">and what's he doing?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0326" trans="overlap">at the same college <unclear>so</unclear></u>
<u n="246" who="S0327">at the same college?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0327">right does that give you a bond erm being in the same school?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0326">yeah but it's funny it's sort of just like erm sort of started off together and then finished together</u>
<u n="250" who="S0327">that's interesting what does he want to do?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0326">I don't know I <trunc>th</trunc>I think he'd make a really good sort of left left-wing little bit corrupt mayor of London <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know sort of wheeler-dealer he does politics</u>
<u n="252" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="253" who="S0326">but he's <trunc>w</trunc> you know he's quite er</u>
<u n="254" who="S0327" trans="overlap">we've got perfectly good left-wing actually no perfectly good corrupt mayor now don't think we ever want another not left-wing</u>
<u n="255" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm but but he's he's erm corrupt for sort of big business you know?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0327">is he?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0326">erm er my friend is is er quite I think quite passionate about leftist politics on</u>
<u n="258" who="S0327">so who's he gonna vote for?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0326">dunno probably Green <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0327">what I haven't worked out is what happens if you vote for Green</u>
<u n="261" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0327">cos that's what I I mean I can't bring myself to vote for any of the others what are you gonna vote?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0326">I don't know really</u>
<u n="264" who="S0327">it's difficult isn't it?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0327">I mean the Greens <vocal desc="sigh"/> of course it won't make any difference they won't get in and if they did get in it would be</u>
<u n="267" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well they might get a seat somewhere I mean they do have seats</u>
<u n="268" who="S0327">they might get a couple of seats er which <trunc>w</trunc>which would be good</u>
<u n="269" who="S0326">I mean it'd be good if they got quite a few seats and then they could do a <trunc>co</trunc>coalition with Labour and sort of <trunc>s</trunc> that would be like a good</u>
<u n="270" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0327">and people keep saying that you know look what happened when they had the council in Brighton the there was a huge mess in Brighton er</u>
<u n="273" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0327">you know they couldn't get the rubbish cleared or anything</u>
<u n="275" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0327">it's a very <pause dur="short"/> it's a rather unpolitical period it seems to me I'm just trying to finish this really very interesting book which I doubt if you have read by somebody called Victor Klemperer have you ever er have you heard of Klemperer's diaries? he wasn't the conductor he was a distant cousin of er of Otto Klemperer the cousin and he was Jewish but he was married to an Aryan and he stays one of the very few who stayed in Germany throughout the whole war and he kept a diary from between nineteen thirty-three and I think something like nineteen fifty-nine so you can imagine how long that is</u>
<u n="277" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0327">I got it on Kindle so at least I can a lot of it's very boring</u>
<u n="279" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0327">erm but I imagine the book must be this big erm so I I read through the whole war period which was rather terrifying I mean it was you know er he did he managed to survive that and then he decided after the war to <trunc>m</trunc>to move to the to East Berlin and I'm just now reading the bit where it's it's <trunc>b</trunc> er you know they're putting up the the wall and so on erm <pause dur="short"/> but it's very interesting reading about and he was erm an academic he was erm <pause dur="short"/> sort of eighteenth-century French literary that was his that was his erm <pause dur="short"/> his subject erm <pause dur="short"/> and he's trying to sort things out in East Germany to get himself a position to get publishing again all that so you you know you you get a sense of the building up in the <pause dur="short"/> from the late forties</u>
<u n="281" who="S0326" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0327">early fifties I think haven't quite got to the early fifties yet erm and everything is political every time he eats a sandwich or takes a piss it's political one way or the other</u>
<u n="283" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0327">it's <trunc>compl</trunc> it's so extraordinary so utterly unlike society here</u>
<u n="285" who="S0326">yeah I wonder if that's <trunc>w</trunc> if <trunc>s</trunc> er if that's sort of something that places have to go through like sort of growing pains where everything is political and it kind of cos if you think about the <trunc>Mi</trunc> like in the Middle East now it's sort of <trunc>s</trunc> not that <trunc>dif</trunc> sort of different from Europe</u>
<event desc="sound of alarm"/>
<u n="286" who="S0326">in erm in the twentieth century</u>
<u n="287" who="S0327" trans="overlap">well it's difficult to know what politics means in the Middle East isn't it?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0327"><unclear>just put this off</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's all such a nightmare it's it's a nightmare I'll tell you what the the pizzas are ready but while it cools down if you can just <pause dur="short"/> clear this thing for me and then yours actually looks rather good <unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0327">just pop into the studio <pause dur="short"/> it's actually to do with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bank account what happened is that <pause dur="short"/> for <trunc>s</trunc> you know when I went through those years when I paid you all erm some money at Christmas?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> and then recently a while ago I paid her something and I inadvertently paid it into that account the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> so it er <trunc>ve</trunc> er luckily they they they sent it away but of course it was terribly confusing</u>
<u n="294" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0327">erm so now I want to get her I've got her bank <trunc>n</trunc> details here let me just get it up <pause dur="short"/> I want to delete what I've got of hers and erm and I can't er find a way of deleting it <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0326">so you want to delete?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0327">I'll show you let me just get in there er log in</u>
<u n="298" who="S0326">wait wait <pause dur="short"/> just er click okay</u>
<u n="299" who="S0327">oh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0326">er it doesn't</u>
<u n="301" who="S0327">do I say okay?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0327" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="long"/> log in <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> <pause dur="short"/> okay so now I want to do a payment and transfer make a payment or transfer <pause dur="short"/> from <pause dur="short"/> there <pause dur="short"/> now if I go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0327">there are two</u>
<u n="306" who="S0326">right</u>
<u n="307" who="S0327">one is and they both are with me as well and I think that goes back to the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> so I what I'd like to do is delete those two and do a whole new one <pause dur="short"/> but if I click on it then it just comes up that I want to pay the money in it</u>
<u n="308" who="S0326" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0327">could I delete?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I mean you could <unclear>you something new into your</unclear> this one and just call it something different?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc> but er when I do what can I call it different? because the thing is though it's the same it's the same account I mean maybe this is alright?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0326">what happens when you click on it? <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't tell doesn't say which is which</u>
<u n="313" who="S0327" trans="overlap">doesn't say which account</u>
<u n="314" who="S0326">tut yeah it's a bit of a <trunc>nu</trunc>nuisance isn't it?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0327">you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0326">yeah but you couldn't just make a new one?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0327">well if I do you see er then it says I've already got that I'll show you name of the person or company <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I can't put a different name because</u>
<u n="318" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="319" who="S0327">it's a bank account so account number is</u>
<u n="320" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but you could do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you could sort of do <trunc>l</trunc>like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so you can remember it</u>
<u n="321" who="S0327">I did that on the other one I could do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> new which I tried</u>
<u n="322" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0327">so I know it's new their account number is <anon type="financialDetails"/> and the sort code is <anon type="financialDetails"/> and the reference if I put <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> I've already got that in the other I don't think it'll make <pause dur="short"/> any difference then add payee I don't know what that means add payee</u>
<u n="324" who="S0326">add it <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0327">look see? you already have a payment instruction set up for this payee</u>
<u n="326" who="S0326">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know how to cos there's no sort of way to edit the list of what you have</u>
<u n="327" who="S0327">no that's exactly <pause dur="short"/> you don't think if I go back?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0326"><trunc>w</trunc> just click <trunc>ge</trunc> click the X instead</u>
<u n="329" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="330" who="S0326">first click cancel</u>
<u n="331" who="S0327">cancel <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> from <pause dur="short"/> er do you think if I ah now that's <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0327">but I didn't <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> let's see er I mean what er why is that like that there? and it's if I click on that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0326" trans="overlap">so erm one of those is the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> and one is</u>
<u n="335" who="S0327">I think so and I just don't know which I don't <trunc>w</trunc> can't go through all that hassle again could I go edit and <pause dur="short"/> delete?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I don't know how to edit to get into that list though that's the <trunc>th</trunc> which is the thing</u>
<u n="337" who="S0327">it doesn't say delete does it? <pause dur="short"/> cos whatever name I put</u>
<u n="338" who="S0326">yeah it'll be the same</u>
<u n="339" who="S0327">be the same <pause dur="short"/> what can I do?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0326">I suppose what the one what you have to do is maybe just sort of do a transfer of sort of two pounds to both and see what what happens sort of communicate and then remember which is the right one</u>
<u n="341" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> ah but I won't I'll only know if it doesn't go into her account</u>
<u n="342" who="S0326">yeah but if you just give so you just you give two pounds to both of the accounts and see which</u>
<u n="343" who="S0327" trans="overlap">ah which gets that's a good idea <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="344" who="S0326">and then er like call <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0327">so</u>
<u n="346" who="S0326">but I dunno if you would need to do it sort of</u>
<u n="347" who="S0327" trans="overlap">shall I do it one at a time?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0326">yeah I think so let's make a <trunc>n</trunc> like write down</u>
<u n="349" who="S0327">make a note</u>
<u n="350" who="S0326">and then ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0327">yes so it's being sent to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stroke <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> it usually goes fairly immediately doesn't it?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0326">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="353" who="S0327">she won't be thrilled to get two pounds</u>
<u n="354" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0327">next <pause dur="short"/> two pounds</u>
<u n="356" who="S0326">wait wait actually this is useful</u>
<u n="357" who="S0327">ah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0326">because it tells you er when you click next which is which so that's the right one</u>
<u n="359" who="S0327">do you think that's the right one?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0326">cos it's the same as this right?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0327">yes ah it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0326">so so maybe if you just <trunc>s</trunc>sort of trial and error and go back and see if the other one is different</u>
<u n="363" who="S0327">oh yes okay maybe they're both okay now who knows? alright so this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> then let's try that one that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0327"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> two pounds next</u>
<u n="366" who="S0326">see that's something else</u>
<u n="367" who="S0327">that's something else</u>
<u n="368" who="S0326">so that's the one you wanna remember</u>
<u n="369" who="S0327" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="370" who="S0326">not to send money to</u>
<u n="371" who="S0327">that's great so that's brilliant erm now if I could mark that and write something on it no I can't</u>
<u n="372" who="S0326">I mean there must be a way to remove people from that list</u>
<u n="373" who="S0327"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear>should I</unclear> delete that?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0326">no that won't work</u>
<u n="375" who="S0327">no it doesn't delete</u>
<u n="376" who="S0326">maybe if I just do a quick Google search er it'll tell me</u>
<u n="377" who="S0327">okay do a quick <trunc>Goo</trunc>Google search and otherwise I'll do this later because at least I know <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the <trunc>ri</trunc> is the okay one <pause dur="short"/> I suppose one could just ask how to delete names from</u>
<u n="378" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0327">at least I've got that <event desc="sound of rustling"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we're deleting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0326">erm down</u>
<u n="381" who="S0327"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0326" trans="overlap">deleting this one?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0327">we're deleting that</u>
<u n="384" who="S0326">how do I know <trunc>y</trunc> where did she go? <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0327">that that one we're deleting</u>
<u n="386" who="S0326">right</u>
<u n="387" who="S0327">great alright that's wonderful thenI'll I'll do it all later thank you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's <trunc>ab</trunc>absolutely great</u>
<u n="388" who="S0326" trans="overlap">that's alright</u>
<u n="389" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> let me just show you something that that will er interest you <pause dur="short"/> if you keep sitting there I can <unclear>go where this is</unclear> erm this is my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's become a very very successful artist he's very clever erm and <pause dur="short"/> where is it? <pause dur="long"/> and <unclear>I'm in</unclear> oh other artists <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> the approach <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> I just went to see it yesterday er three three big <unclear>works</unclear> let's see if we can get them up singularly and they're called <pause dur="short"/> no he's called them the projectionists erm and it's it's actually it's based er do you remember when you sent me the stuff from Pliny about the origin of painting?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0326" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0327">except when we discussed it was the origin of er the line</u>
<u n="392" who="S0326">line yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0327">line drawing and this is he's he's done these erm <pause dur="long"/> about the inauguration of the history of pictorial representation in which projection and the fixing of shadow are always interconnected from painting to photography and cinema they're they're very big enormous silkscreens and they really are rather interesting</u>
<u n="394" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> one more that I liked a lot where's the other one gone? this one is is it's rather fascinating you know big</u>
<u n="396" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0327">this sort of size and then I emailed him to say that I'd been and er and and mentioned this and then he wrote this morning erm he er says it it <trunc>sh</trunc>it should be the origins of drawing but he describes it Pliny describes it as the source of painting painting is literally the daughter of pottery or craft the other in <trunc>b</trunc> ambiguity is that we don't know whether her lover returns from war or whether the thick shadow represents the dead the shade or whether it's a visual prayer to <trunc>re</trunc>reunification of the body</u>
<u n="398" who="S0326"><unclear/> written about certain paintings? or in</u>
<u n="399" who="S0327">er <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc>this this is <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="400" who="S0326" trans="overlap">er shadow in general?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0327">cos I said erm da da da da <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>s</trunc> I wrote <unclear/> I know the ancient story differently that Dibutades had drawn a line round the shadow of her lover and thus created the first line that's what you told me</u>
<u n="402" who="S0326">erm I dunno if I I think I just showed you where where it was cos I haven't read that before</u>
<u n="403" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh oh maybe you gave me a reference that's possible so he's taken that he's not saying it's the first line but it's the shadows <unclear/> of the first painting which is rather interesting isn't it?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but er yeah yeah it is er cos I think I remember that that one thing I er talking to you about was sort of who could was who could draw the thinnest line</u>
<u n="405" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="406" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <trunc>compe</trunc> there's this like this lots of stories about sort of artistic one-<trunc>up</trunc> er one-upmanship between competitive painters er sort of trying to trick each other so someone <trunc>w</trunc> drew a curtain and</u>
<u n="407" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="408" who="S0326">tried to get the other artist to open the curtain that was a painting</u>
<u n="409" who="S0327">yes yes</u>
<u n="410" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> things like that</u>
<u n="411" who="S0327" trans="overlap">well I'll show you a fine line I've just I'm doing these new paintings of <unclear/> getting as about as fine as I I just this morning finished the two red ones you could give me your opinion <unclear>they're still</unclear></u>
<u n="412" who="S0326">yeah I quite like them</u>
<u n="413" who="S0327">what?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0326">I quite like them</u>
<u n="415" who="S0327">yes people do seem to respond to them <pause dur="short"/> which do you like best out of the two reds? <pause dur="short"/> can you see the second division in that one?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0327">that's what I'm not certain about I actually think it's better without I made a technical mistake so I am rectifying it by doing the second one and I don't think it quite works</u>
<u n="418" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah it might be one division but I feel like it when it's sort of barely discernible shades</u>
<u n="419" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="420" who="S0326">if you see what so I sort of I I think er I would like it better as a mix of that and that if you see so one line but closer tones</u>
<u n="421" who="S0327">closer tones than these?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0327">okay well I think I've got to destroy this and do another one so I think that if I can locate the paper cut-outs that's probably what I will do</u>
<u n="424" who="S0326">I like this one too</u>
<u n="425" who="S0327">yeah I think I I think that's good I</u>
<u n="426" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0327">I also rather like that one erm I'm I'm I'm enjoying doing these and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> look at this one he said oh you're going narrative</u>
<u n="428" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0327">and it's true cos there is a narrative element cos I'm doing so badly professionally and I thought I might as well do paintings nobody can see</u>
<u n="430" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0327">erm if they're not gonna look at them anyhow they might mean er just as well be nothing for them to see okay let's go</u>
<u n="432" who="S0326" trans="overlap">er that's nice I really like that I think that's a nice <unclear>sort of set</unclear></u>
<u n="433" who="S0327">yes yes</u>
<u n="434" who="S0326">that's good</u>
<u n="435" who="S0327">I'm pleased cos I'm oh I've got to choose a load to show at the <anon type="place"/> which is almost like throwing them away</u>
<u n="436" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0327">and then one of those horrible art fairs erm <unclear/> <unclear>three walls</unclear> there okay erm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0326"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0327"><unclear/> get this <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh by the way I met your mum's new boyfriend</u>
<u n="440" who="S0326">yeah she said actually</u>
<u n="441" who="S0327">what do you think of him?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0326">he's alright</u>
<u n="443" who="S0327">no better than that?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0326">yeah I dunno I <trunc>th</trunc> I mean I don't think it's er sort of</u>
<u n="445" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh god I you I'll cut it in half shall I <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0327">yes go on</u>
<u n="448" who="S0326">erm I don't I think he's sort of he's not really used to like <trunc>ch</trunc>children being around or some er you know</u>
<u n="449" who="S0327">ah is that right?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0326">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> he find he finds it a bit difficult</u>
<u n="451" who="S0327">does he?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0326">I think so</u>
<u n="453" who="S0327">this is not sibling jealousy of mum's new boyfriend?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0326">no cos it's like well cos it was always <trunc>f</trunc> it was actually always sort of been like fine with with all the other boyfriends <pause dur="short"/> it was never but I think</u>
<u n="455" who="S0327">I know but they were children <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0327">I mean now she's got a real bloke</u>
<u n="458" who="S0326">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0327">I have to admit I really took to him</u>
<u n="460" who="S0326">yeah he is he is charming</u>
<u n="461" who="S0327">he's he's charming he's he's bright isn't he?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0327">but what I don't know and of course you know your mum she won't tell me anything erm <pause dur="short"/> I'll tell you what okay there's masses left here so you can start with that erm <pause dur="short"/> is his work <pause dur="short"/> I mean I talked to him a bit about it but only very very loosely but I er you know he has no professional <pause dur="short"/> he's obviously decided not to erm compete with the world professionally</u>
<u n="464" who="S0326">right</u>
<u n="465" who="S0327">which I have to say is er rather sensible if you can afford to do it erm do you want some bread as well?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0326">erm no I think I'm alright</u>
<u n="467" who="S0327">no? here's a bit of salad</u>
<u n="468" who="S0326">thank you</u>
<u n="469" who="S0327"><unclear/> vegetables do you want another tea?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0326">sure</u>
<u n="471" who="S0327">here we are</u>
<u n="472" who="S0326">thanks</u>
<u n="473" who="S0327">and then I've got some little chocolate creams for for afterwards erm so he's not interested in in you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0326">well <pause dur="short"/> I think I mean I think it's <pause dur="short"/> I haven't really spent that much time with him really</u>
<u n="475" who="S0327">no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> well I I thought he was very interesting and erm <pause dur="short"/> and he not only is he Jewish he's really Jewish</u>
<u n="476" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> he went to a bat <trunc>mitz</trunc> bar mitzvah yesterday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0327">I mean that has really surprised me</u>
<u n="478" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> not only is he Jewish he's really Jewish <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0327">well he said he grew up erm in a community in I think either <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> I can't remember</u>
<u n="480" who="S0326">in <anon type="place"/> I think</u>
<u n="481" who="S0327"><anon type="place"/> with only it's three thousand Jews and that's all <unclear>I mean</unclear> so he has not quite escaped that</u>
<u n="482" who="S0326"><unclear>I mean</unclear> what do you mean?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0327" trans="overlap">and I wanna know what he does that's what I want to know and I I couldn't quite be rude enough to say what do you actually do?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0326">yeah I don't really know</u>
<u n="485" who="S0327">you don't know?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0326"><unclear>oops</unclear> catch it?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0327">yes I did</u>
<u n="488" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0327">that was clever wasn't it?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0326">erm cos I know he has quite sort of quite a lot of property and things</u>
<u n="491" who="S0327">so he's quite rich?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0326">I think so</u>
<u n="493" who="S0327">well I tell you what good for your mum <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0326">yeah well his house in in you know is really big and nice</u>
<u n="495" who="S0327">in <anon type="place"/>? oh he's got a house in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0327">is that right?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0326">sort of round just round the corner</u>
<u n="499" who="S0327">oh really?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0326" trans="overlap">with like with like a huge garden and</u>
<u n="501" who="S0327">is that right? <pause dur="short"/> nobody tells me anything I have to rely on</u>
<u n="502" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0327">the children to tell me erm <pause dur="short"/> start <pause dur="short"/> well it struck me I have to say but don't repeat this to her that your mum has finally met her match</u>
<u n="504" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0327">cos he's a <trunc>s</trunc> obviously a strong character whereas <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> before who seemed terribly sweet <pause dur="short"/> but wasn't a very strong character</u>
<u n="506" who="S0326">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="507" who="S0327">well it can't be easy for you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> all this <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not easy for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> either</u>
<u n="508" who="S0326">what's that about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0327">well I think er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually probably finds it quite difficult to have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> around all the time</u>
<u n="510" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0327">you know they're both both <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are quite demanding people <pause dur="short"/> to put it mildly</u>
<u n="512" who="S0326" trans="overlap">what is what is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s up to at the moment?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0327">yes he's got he's doing something <trunc>goi</trunc> planning to do something really good he's planning to go with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <trunc>Sou</trunc>South America for three months <pause dur="short"/> partly get a job there <pause dur="short"/> mm er and probably <trunc>th</trunc> you know <pause dur="short"/> not probably if he can manage if he can take enough money with him not to have a job</u>
<u n="514" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0327">erm and to go to however many <unclear/> countries they can go to <vocal desc="sigh"/> well I think that's you know I'm all in favour of all you young people travelling as much as you can early on I mean you've managed to do it anyhow</u>
<u n="516" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0327">but it I mean it's been great the places you've been to <pause dur="short"/> oh <unclear>that's quite</unclear> hot <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so I think it'll be very very good for him <pause dur="short"/> I think he hasn't finally chosen <pause dur="short"/> which place he's gonna go to he's he's got a couple of he's been offered <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0327">and somewhere else but I think he may be waiting to hear if he's got into <anon type="place"/> college <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> help yourself <vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0326">it'll be good to go for him to go to South America probably</u>
<u n="521" who="S0327">yeah I mean if he goes somewhere like Peru <pause dur="short"/> you've been to <trunc>Sou</trunc> yes you've been to Mexico</u>
<u n="522" who="S0326" trans="overlap">just to Mexico yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0327">right mm <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>w</trunc>where did you actually go?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0326">erm went to er started off in a place called erm <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> which is like a really sort of beautiful town sort of in the mountains with hot springs</u>
<u n="525" who="S0327">oh right</u>
<u n="526" who="S0326">and er sort of lots of like bit <trunc>hip</trunc> like sort of hippyish you know?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="528" who="S0326">sort of lots of like quite a lot of <trunc>ex</trunc> like expatriates</u>
<u n="529" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0326"><unclear/> drifted there erm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0327">and what do they do? just hang around?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0326"><unclear/> a few a lot of people that hang out there are jewellery designers</u>
<u n="533" who="S0327">oh</u>
<u n="534" who="S0326">because there's silver mines there and the silver's really cheap</u>
<u n="535" who="S0327">ah <pause dur="short"/> oh that's right that's why</u>
<u n="536" who="S0326" trans="overlap">a really special kind of silver</u>
<u n="537" who="S0327">is it?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0326">so I</u>
<u n="539" who="S0327" trans="overlap">did you bring some back?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0326">no <pause dur="short"/> erm so it so you can go there and sort of <trunc>o</trunc>one friend she sort of started a school <trunc>t</trunc>to teach people how to make jewellery <pause dur="short"/> there's some art schools there <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> which is I <trunc>expe</trunc> I think that must be a sort of there's nobody in er it's like a small town quite small and if they've got you know two art schools and erm my other friend had a restaurant there</u>
<u n="541" who="S0327">and they sell this <unclear>internationally</unclear> do they? this jewellery?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0326">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0327">well</u>
<u n="544" who="S0326">and it's sort of <trunc>re</trunc> sort of it's <trunc>ch</trunc> sort of very cheap to live there and you know it's a good <trunc>ba</trunc> good sort of <trunc>b</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc> er base <unclear/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0327" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="546" who="S0326">sort of launch operations from</u>
<u n="547" who="S0327">and how far from Mexico City?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0326">erm it's about three hours north</u>
<u n="549" who="S0327">right <pause dur="short"/> was it cold when you went?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0326">it's nice because it's really hot in the day and then cooler in the evenings <unclear/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh that's lovely</u>
<u n="552" who="S0326">and then we rented a car and sort of drove to the coast to a place called <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> which is a er a sort of a <trunc>tropica</trunc> kind of tropical very like sort of run-down not really any tourists but like finding sort of finding hotels cost like three pounds a night or something yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0327" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0327">how nice that there still are such places</u>
<u n="556" who="S0326">on the sort of on the Pacific coast</u>
<u n="557" who="S0327">who did you go with? remind me</u>
<u n="558" who="S0326">went with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well it's just originally it was just gonna be me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but we went to New York on Christmas Day and I had a really good time there and er sort of picked up two more people</u>
<u n="559" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0326">which is erm like a friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's who we were in Paris with who's a chef and then er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm tut <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so we had four of us sort of and then had friends already in San Miguel so the <trunc>f</trunc> but the four of us got a car and drove it to the the coast</u>
<u n="561" who="S0327" trans="overlap">that sounds really great <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0326">it was good</u>
<u n="563" who="S0327">and was it expensive?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0326">no really cheap everything was cheap</u>
<u n="565" who="S0327">cos there's nowhere cheap in Europe left is there? not really</u>
<u n="566" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0327">is East Berlin still cheap?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0326">probably in the outskirts of Berlin like <unclear>they'll be they live</unclear> really cheap</u>
<u n="569" who="S0327">mm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0326">and Athens maybe</u>
<u n="571" who="S0327">ah but you haven't been to Peru?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0326">no <pause dur="short"/> I mean I suppose that er Mexico's not really South America it's Central America</u>
<u n="573" who="S0327">no <pause dur="short"/> are there any ancient sites there?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0326">in Mexico?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0327">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0326">yeah there's lots of <trunc>f</trunc> sort of <trunc>pyrami</trunc> you know those pyramids?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0327">oh yes they're wonderful</u>
<u n="578" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0327">they're cleaning those all up now aren't they? <pause dur="short"/> I don't know anything about South America <pause dur="short"/> I've never actually been very attracted to the culture</u>
<u n="580" who="S0326">it's strange cos it's very like it's obviously it's very sort of Catholic but it's like infused with er something really sort of pagan it's like it's like really kind of pagan quality of Catholicism and very like strange really colourful like in a church there'll be sort of <trunc>s</trunc> bit like like Halloween <vocal desc="laugh"/> style</u>
<u n="581" who="S0327">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0326">erm <trunc>sk</trunc>skeletons and</u>
<u n="583" who="S0327" trans="overlap">well I suppose that is exactly what it is it's a <trunc>c</trunc>combination of what they got from the Spanish</u>
<u n="584" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0327">plus their own <pause dur="short"/> I've seen churches in southern Spain which are very peculiar because you know they they look as though they were originally Spanish but then built by people who had been to South America who couldn't quite remember how they were</u>
<u n="586" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I went to a talk in <anon type="place"/> the other week er quite interesting about erm sort of <trunc>neo</trunc>neo-Latin epic so when the Spanish went to the New World these people wrote epic poems about it in Latin</u>
<u n="587" who="S0327">oh really?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0326">and pretending to be sort of Virgil erm <pause dur="short"/> so they all sort of the hero's always Columbus <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0327">really? <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't have thought that would be the case seeing that they made them suffer so much</u>
<u n="590" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear>no</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0327">I must say they were absolutely vile <pause dur="short"/> I mean the Spanish do have a a reputation for terrible cruelty</u>
<u n="592" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0327">I suppose it's different now <pause dur="short"/> you don't speak Spanish?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0326">no kind of a nuisance</u>
<u n="595" who="S0327">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0326">actually I sort of <trunc>s</trunc> I wish I could speak more languages better <pause dur="short"/> don't really learn it in er in this <unclear>world</unclear></u>
<u n="597" who="S0327">well I mean do think you've got a talent? I mean you taught yourself Greek if you have a talent you can probably</u>
<u n="598" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="599" who="S0327">teach yourself <pause dur="short"/> so you know German Latin and Greek well if you ask me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that is a basis of so much</u>
<u n="600" who="S0326">yeah well I I mean I know I don't really know German but I can talk it yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0327"><trunc>s</trunc> oh you picked German up you didn't <unclear>learn it</unclear>?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0326" trans="overlap">no I did it did it in school for GCSE but I would struggle to read a German newspaper you know</u>
<u n="603" who="S0327">German is terribly difficult erm <pause dur="short"/> that was how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> learnt actually when he went to live there he learnt by reading newspapers and looking <unclear>at</unclear> words <vocal desc="cough"/> and I get very annoyed by how good his German is but then he was there for thirty years <pause dur="short"/> so you you expect that</u>
<u n="604" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0327">and you never did any French?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0326">not in school</u>
<u n="607" who="S0327"><unclear>nobody</unclear> does any French anymore</u>
<u n="608" who="S0326">yeah I dunno I mean I did when I was with the other <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <trunc>s</trunc>she knew French so I I spoke French with her a bit and learnt a bit but</u>
<u n="609" who="S0327" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="610" who="S0326">like in <trunc>th</trunc> I can speak French sort of in theory but as soon as I'm in France I get too <trunc>s</trunc>sort of shy and er all comes out wrong</u>
<u n="611" who="S0327" trans="overlap">it's it's yes and also they're rude they're not if you if you go to Italy and just say good evening they they say oh you know your Italian's so wonderful <pause dur="short"/> and so marvellous and and you say good evening in French they walk away if you haven't said it perfectly</u>
<u n="612" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm going to Italy actually</u>
<u n="613" who="S0327">but I think you can <pause dur="short"/> the younger you are the better</u>
<u n="614" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember meeting a child that like in in Ibiza once who could like he was like <trunc>s</trunc> five and spoke five languages <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0327">er they are er it is astonishing I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> mm what that does I mean does it mean you can ever quite say what you want to say?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0327">are you at home in all those languages?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0326">yeah it's interesting er I I remember sort of reading something about being bilingual sort of er <trunc>r</trunc> being raised bilingually er erm opens up I think the sort of synapses that aren't always erm <trunc>d</trunc> aren't sort of engaged er and you can't can't be engaged any other way <pause dur="short"/> they think er people just think differently</u>
<u n="619" who="S0327">well words sound the same <pause dur="short"/> words have very very different meanings erm I mean German has both an incredible richness and a kind of brutality you know if you think of the <trunc>se</trunc> the word for leg in German is <foreign lang="ger">Bein</foreign> which means bone <pause dur="short"/> the word for meat is <foreign lang="ger">Fleisch</foreign></u>
<u n="620" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0327">which means flesh <pause dur="short"/> which is much cruder and more brutal isn't it? erm but there are some words I just can't think of an example which <unclear>are</unclear> which just <unclear>sound</unclear> much better just that much different even though we both only have that one</u>
<u n="622" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0327">one word <pause dur="short"/> I personally think that swearing in German is slightly more effective</u>
<u n="624" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0327">but then that might be to do with how used to one is to <pause dur="short"/> people swearing now you know like now it's common as muck but when I was young if you heard somebody say fuck it that was really shocking <pause dur="short"/> I mean I personally think that <foreign lang="ger">Scheiße</foreign> is stronger than shit</u>
<u n="626" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0327">if you make a mistake and you say oh shit but if you say <foreign lang="ger">Scheiße</foreign> it's somehow a bit shittier than</u>
<u n="628" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well yeah cos the interesting thing this I <trunc>d</trunc>I <trunc>d</trunc>I doubt that Germans say shit <pause dur="short"/> if you if you know what I'm saying? they just say <foreign lang="ger">Scheiße</foreign> all the time</u>
<u n="629" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="630" who="S0326">where in English people say both probably because the German one is more <trunc>eff</trunc> there's no need er if you're German to say shit cos you have <foreign lang="ger">Scheiße</foreign></u>
<u n="631" who="S0327">yes no they wouldn't say shit</u>
<u n="632" who="S0326">but an English person might well say <foreign lang="ger">Scheiße</foreign></u>
<u n="633" who="S0327">do you think?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0327">no why would they?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0326">no? just er they cos</u>
<u n="637" who="S0327">only educated people like you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0326">no I er you know I on even on like TV and stuff I've seen people <unclear>they say it</unclear> funny <unclear>you know</unclear> if they think it's <pause dur="short"/> I think it's sort of more in vernacular vocabulary than in in in in shit in German</u>
<u n="639" who="S0327">it's true when I was young <pause dur="short"/> people would say <foreign lang="fre">merde</foreign></u>
<u n="640" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0327">I haven't heard that for years <pause dur="short"/> can you press this down as well?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0326">mm maybe the top half of it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="643" who="S0327">it's got chilli and tomatoes on and I'm not <unclear/> bigger half <pause dur="long"/> so what would you like to learn?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0326">erm <trunc>Fr</trunc> I'd like to learn French and and German like properly</u>
<u n="645" who="S0327">well I think <trunc>y</trunc>you know you have Latin and Greek you're not gonna find <trunc>F</trunc>French very difficult</u>
<u n="646" who="S0326">no I mean I</u>
<u n="647" who="S0327">I mean to learn to speak it really really well that's another thing</u>
<u n="648" who="S0326">I find it easier actually to <trunc>r</trunc>to read French than read German</u>
<u n="649" who="S0327">my mother used to <unclear/> spoke about five or six languages she and then I think actually no she took up Russian in her fifties she said that Russian was much easier than German <pause dur="short"/> I'm <trunc>r</trunc>really sorry I didn't learn proper German <unclear/> but I speak the German of a twelve-year-old maybe a nine-year-old</u>
<u n="650" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="651" who="S0327">erm and then er also you need to so much you know we don't have grammar in in English do we? so it's quite difficult to</u>
<u n="652" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0327">I suppose you grasped that through Greek and Latin</u>
<u n="654" who="S0326">well yeah <trunc>s</trunc> I think it's er just like really er <trunc>uninfl</trunc><trunc>un</trunc>uninflected language is what they call it</u>
<u n="655" who="S0327">it's a what?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0326"><trunc>un</trunc> er uninflected</u>
<u n="657" who="S0327">what is?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0326">English</u>
<u n="659" who="S0327" trans="overlap">English</u>
<u n="660" who="S0326">as in sort of ending so long <unclear/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="662" who="S0327">mm who's ringing at lunchtime? hello? <pause dur="short"/> hello sweetie-pie I'm just having a lovely lunch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0327">ah er er Tuesday I think <pause dur="short"/> er well it's in my book for Tuesday check it with him <pause dur="short"/> I will er shall we have a chat later? will you ring me after? well I shall have a nap ring me about half past four? <pause dur="short"/> okay cos I'd like to find out how you are <pause dur="short"/> alright sweetheart bye <pause dur="short"/> that's your auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0326">I haven't seen her for a while</u>
<u n="666" who="S0327">no but maybe in the summer we'll do a family party shall we? erm <pause dur="short"/> and get erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to meet all the monsters</u>
<u n="667" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0327">is he living in your house now?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0326">I don't really know</u>
<u n="670" who="S0327">you don't know?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0326">I mean he has a house round the corner but I think he <trunc>w</trunc> sort of wants to sell it or something</u>
<u n="672" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="673" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> but I think when er <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc>sort of <pause dur="short"/> I think er <trunc>f</trunc> I think pretty much when me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> aren't there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="674" who="S0327">no point having a house that's not lived in <pause dur="short"/> the spiders get in</u>
<u n="675" who="S0326">I'm just gonna get some water do you want some?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0327">erm no but you can make yourself some more tea if you want? put the kettle on</u>
<u n="677" who="S0326">I'll have <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> switch to water</u>
<u n="678" who="S0327">if you er water's in the jug in the fridge <pause dur="short"/> still <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you won't have time while you're at <anon type="place"/> to learn any languages will you?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0326">yeah I mean there is <trunc>la</trunc>language <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> there's a language school which you can go to sort of</u>
<u n="680" who="S0327">do you have time for that?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0326">yeah probably <pause dur="short"/> but I I'll I'll <trunc>ha</trunc>I'll have to ask someone who's who's done it if it's any good</u>
<u n="682" who="S0327">I mean the thing about French or German of course is you can er you learn it and then you go there</u>
<u n="683" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0327">and you go there with no English-<trunc>speak</trunc>speaking people you go and get a job or something for a month</u>
<u n="685" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0327">where you're supposed to talk and that really makes a huge difference</u>
<u n="687" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the problem is that it's er <trunc>y</trunc> everybody <trunc>s</trunc>sort of knows enough knows enough</u>
<u n="688" who="S0327" trans="overlap">you still don't eat your crusts</u>
<u n="689" who="S0326">er</u>
<u n="690" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0326">everybody sort of knows enough English to get by with each other</u>
<u n="692" who="S0327">everybody knows enough English to get by that's right but I mean I'm sure you could find something for a short period some sort of relatively easy job erm <pause dur="short"/> or you go you don't go to Berlin or somewhere like <trunc>w</trunc> I've probably got some ice cream as well would you like some ice cream?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0326">no I <trunc>d</trunc> I'm quite full now</u>
<u n="694" who="S0327">are you? oh right</u>
<u n="695" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> thank you though</u>
<u n="696" who="S0327">perhaps you've got over your majorly eating</u>
<u n="697" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0327">although not er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know though I still see him regularly which is lovely I actually can't feed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0327">I mean it's impossible to get you know he can just eat so much</u>
<u n="701" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0327">but he's very big <pause dur="short"/> he was ill recently had a wisdom tooth he'd never been to the <trunc>den</trunc>dentist in his life and then suddenly got a wisdom tooth problem he was up for young critic of the year</u>
<u n="703" who="S0326">that's good</u>
<u n="704" who="S0327">he didn't get it to his annoyance but er it's good to be shortlisted <pause dur="short"/> or you teach yourself</u>
<u n="705" who="S0326">yeah I mean I had a I had a language program on the computer which was good for French</u>
<u n="706" who="S0327">right <pause dur="short"/> for free?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0326">I <trunc>g</trunc> er I got it as a present from my dad once</u>
<u n="708" who="S0327">oh right</u>
<u n="709" who="S0326">but like <trunc>pr</trunc> quite a proper one</u>
<u n="710" who="S0327">what languages does he speak?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0326">he speaks <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>pr</trunc> all of them pretty much</u>
<u n="712" who="S0327">French? German?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0326">well he speaks I mean he doesn't really speak German but he speaks French erm and like <trunc>whe</trunc>when we went on holiday he didn't within like two days he was just talking to people in er in a language</u>
<u n="714" who="S0327">was he? yes</u>
<u n="715" who="S0326">cos he knows <trunc>La</trunc>Latin too I guess</u>
<u n="716" who="S0327">well I told you about my dad who knew Latin not Italian just spoke Latin with Italian endings and <pause dur="short"/> got around perfectly well</u>
<u n="717" who="S0326">I'm going to erm <trunc>It</trunc>Italy</u>
<u n="718" who="S0327">are you?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0326">in a few weeks yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0327">where?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0326">erm first to Rome and then to to er <trunc>Tu</trunc> a place in Tuscany</u>
<u n="722" who="S0327">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I love Italy Italy is er you <trunc>me</trunc></u>
<u n="723" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I've never really been</u>
<u n="724" who="S0327">you've never been?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0326">just drove through it one for one day once yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0327">it's just there's nothing like Italy it is a magical place Rome so you're <trunc>g</trunc> next month? April okay that's quite a good time it won't be too hot yet erm cos it can get very hot in summer and it's actually quite an exhausting city it's an enormous city</u>
<u n="727" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="728" who="S0327">and you walk a lot er make sure you have really comfortable shoes and a change of shoes erm <pause dur="short"/> who are you going with?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0326">erm I'm going with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and two of our friends because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <trunc>g</trunc> erm been asked to go and do something there for some sort of <trunc>ca</trunc>cake thing and so</u>
<u n="730" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh great great</u>
<u n="731" who="S0326">everyone's going <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0327">oh that'll be lovely well there's a lot of stuff to see in Rome erm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0326">yeah I think we're only gonna be in Rome <trunc>s</trunc> for sort of two two or three days</u>
<u n="734" who="S0327">right well you won't see it all then</u>
<u n="735" who="S0326">and then <trunc>ge</trunc>getting a car</u>
<u n="736" who="S0327">and how far is this place from Rome?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0326">in Tuscany? I don't know actually how far away it is</u>
<u n="738" who="S0327">Tuscany's quite a way up probably about six hours' drive</u>
<u n="739" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but we'll probably sort of stop places</u>
<u n="740" who="S0327">yes <pause dur="short"/> I've never got over the magic of Italy even though you know they do their best to ruin the cities like everywhere else but they have very stringent planning laws so the centres of cities still remain pretty well the same</u>
<u n="741" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="742" who="S0327">erm and then that's such a beautiful language <pause dur="short"/> so try your Latin out with Italian er endings</u>
<u n="743" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0327">what is <foreign lang="ita">buongiorno</foreign> in in Latin? good day</u>
<u n="745" who="S0326"><foreign lang="lat">salve</foreign></u>
<u n="746" who="S0327"><foreign lang="lat">salve</foreign>?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0327">well you can learn <foreign lang="ita">buongiorno</foreign></u>
<u n="749" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="750" who="S0327">or <foreign lang="ita">buona sera</foreign> erm</u>
<u n="751" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0327">how about can you can you tell me the way to the post office?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0326">there's no post offices <unclear>then</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> you see that's the funny thing about learning Latin and Greek is you don't learn how to say can I have two tickets to? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0327">no of course not</u>
<u n="755" who="S0326">where is the toilet?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0327">course not</u>
<u n="757" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so you don't really learn a <trunc>prac</trunc> it's not really practical language</u>
<u n="758" who="S0327">alright tell me something else er that I've never quite understood how did ancient Greece you know from which really every I mean that's what we're still living on in a way isn't it? culturally</u>
<u n="759" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0327">well how <trunc>w</trunc> how did that happen?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0326">don't know really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0327"><unclear/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0326">no one knows I mean that's like why people are so fascinated by it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> they must there's just sort of something about that culture that which sort of er I think <trunc>unders</trunc>understood sort of human life well enough to sort of cast</u>
<u n="764" who="S0327">how was society set up? let I mean erm the peak of the the classical period is what year?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="766" who="S0327">four hundred and something?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0326">like four fifties</u>
<u n="768" who="S0327">four fifties well what about what was going on in five fifty?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0326">in five fifty they were sort of laying the groundwork erm they had that guy called Solon who sort of laid down some democratic laws</u>
<u n="770" who="S0327">oh did they?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0326">and then they had a problem with sort of tyrants erm they couldn't really make democracy work until the fifth century until the two these two this sort of er <trunc>l</trunc> boyfriend pair lovers killed a tyrant but not er out of any political motivation just because the tyrant was making advances <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0327">is that right?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0326">that's really sort of where democracy in Athens comes from <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0327">how absolutely fascinating</u>
<u n="775" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear>an affair</unclear> I mean I <trunc>wr</trunc> actually wrote an essay about sort of why why the tut naked male body is so dominates so much classical sculpture and er I just basically kind of wrote a lot about erm cos there's a famous famous statues of those tyrant killers and they're naked and er and the idea that</u>
<u n="776" who="S0327" trans="overlap">what's his name?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0326">erm the tyrant or the killers? they're called erm Harmodius is one of them and I can't remember the other one</u>
<u n="778" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="779" who="S0326">but erm I mean there are statues of them but erm sort of the whole <trunc>ideolog</trunc>ideology of erm democracy in Athens is sort of rooted in sort of homoerotic desire it's like an erotic ideology <trunc>someh</trunc>somehow</u>
<u n="780" who="S0327"><unclear>huh</unclear></u>
<u n="781" who="S0326">because of because that's where the democracy came from sort of er an affair killing sort of <trunc>p</trunc> crime of passion and then they cut and then they have</u>
<u n="782" who="S0327" trans="overlap">I've never heard that how fascinating</u>
<u n="783" who="S0326">well it's not really it's just sort of</u>
<u n="784" who="S0327" trans="overlap">I mean I suppose it's not quite that simple</u>
<u n="785" who="S0326">yeah that's like what I was</u>
<u n="786" who="S0327" trans="overlap">maybe it is</u>
<u n="787" who="S0326">what I was writing about <pause dur="short"/> sort of that's like the personal view thing I guess</u>
<u n="788" who="S0327">so who were the couple?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0326">erm they were sort of just</u>
<u n="790" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><unclear>presumably men of</unclear> power?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0326">yeah I think so sort of aristocratic erm <pause dur="short"/> youth one youth one young man</u>
<u n="792" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="793" who="S0326">and one older man</u>
<u n="794" who="S0327">right and they were a couple and then the they got fed up with the tyrant</u>
<u n="795" who="S0326">yeah who was <trunc>c</trunc> but only <trunc>becau</trunc> not <trunc>b</trunc> not sort of <trunc>ou</trunc>out of any political not or</u>
<u n="796" who="S0327" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="797" who="S0326">maybe that was part of it but also the main reason why they killed him was because the tyrant was just sort of trying to get off with the</u>
<u n="798" who="S0327" trans="overlap">with the younger one</u>
<u n="799" who="S0326">with the younger one <pause dur="short"/> but then there were sort of <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> erm er sort of held up as erm sort of end ending tyranny and bringing democracy to Athens so it was sort of gift <trunc>gi</trunc>given er public monuments which is didn't really have then up to that point so</u>
<u n="800" who="S0327">oh didn't they?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0326">it wasn't very I mean they did but it was <trunc>f</trunc> especially for sort of living people <pause dur="short"/> they weren't really it wasn't really er portraiture or or erm public sort of <trunc>m</trunc> commemorative statues of er real life people</u>
<u n="802" who="S0327">so that started also what? in the</u>
<u n="803" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0327">fifth century?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0326">about then yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0327">maybe because there was some particularly skilled sculptors perhaps?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0326">well no well I it's I mean er portraiture really becomes a thing er sort of in the Hellenistic period and it's interesting when er</u>
<u n="808" who="S0327">and that isn't <unclear>another</unclear> couple of years a <trunc>h</trunc> couple of hundred years later</u>
<u n="809" who="S0326">yeah it sort of starts at three two three BC</u>
<u n="810" who="S0327">yeah I see I mean that two hundred years is actually quite a long time</u>
<u n="811" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0327">if one thinks of of being er well it is and it isn't erm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="813" who="S0326">but yeah er</u>
<u n="814" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh I see so erm and this was in Athens?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not really er er like just er it's not that simple it's not just like <unclear/> of it but</u>
<u n="816" who="S0327" trans="overlap">no of course not</u>
<u n="817" who="S0326">it's in er it's <trunc>w</trunc>it's what I was thinking about when I did this essay sort of how cos the way that people when sort of Pericles in his famous funeral oration he talks about sort of loving the city but he uses <trunc>Ero</trunc>Eros as in you're meant to love it's er it's er like er Plato says you <unclear/> you need to love knowledge and you have to have Eros for it it's all sort of erotic <pause dur="short"/> like I think eroticism is <trunc>r</trunc> at sort of er the <trunc>c</trunc>the core of a lot of er sort of deeper things about Athenian life</u>
<u n="818" who="S0327">erm do you think that it's possible that because those two were powerful they kind of er <trunc>li</trunc>liberated homosexuality in some way? <trunc>th</trunc>they made it okay?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0326">in <trunc>n</trunc> they didn't it wasn't really a problem with that in Athens it was always okay it was er it was</u>
<u n="820" who="S0327" trans="overlap">it was always okay was it?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0326">it was er it was what you're it was sort of it was the norm it wasn't sort of deviant or like different but it's only <trunc>s</trunc> it's</u>
<u n="822" who="S0327" trans="overlap">how do we know this?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0326">I I mean I don't know <trunc>w</trunc>where you look but it's sort of just taken <unclear/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><trunc>whe</trunc> remind me when Homer was?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0326">erm well it's written down sort of about eight hundred BC</u>
<u n="826" who="S0327">Homer was written at eight hundred BC? as early as that?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0326">but I mean the stories are probably older <trunc>l</trunc>like they're probably from</u>
<u n="828" who="S0327">it is utterly fascinating isn't it?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="830" who="S0327">utterly fascinating cos we still don't really know how we emerged I mean the more and more <trunc>f</trunc> I mean I don't really hardly read <unclear>anything I can't</unclear> keep up with all that but it does seem as though we emerge pretty well with our behaviour patterns in already in place</u>
<u n="831" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0327">rather than evolve I mean have we evolved? psychologically we've certainly not evolved er for the better</u>
<u n="833" who="S0326">mm yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0327">er in some ways I mean there is an aspect of contemporary society where there is a place for empathy now in the last really since post-World War Two</u>
<u n="835" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0327">but it's completely recent</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="837" who="S0326">I <trunc>d</trunc> er yeah I just get er cos it's interesting when you look at sort of east and west sort of this <trunc>Chi</trunc> sort of the Chinese wisdom or Far Eastern wisdom's totally different from Greek</u>
<u n="838" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="839" who="S0326">and those were the two sort of modes of life or sort of patterns of existence that people operate in</u>
<u n="840" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0326">and they come from sort of two small places</u>
<u n="842" who="S0327">well I think we think that it's still probably just slightly more human to have a life in the west if you can ignore all the hundreds of wars there have been I mean to me there is still something fairly horrendous about China I mean if you think of the lives that most sort of the Chinese must live now you know?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0327">working fifteen sixteen hours a day for for a pittance so you you know now they're getting a a middle class and upper class but it does rather frighten me the thought a lot of artists are going over there and they usually have a horrible time</u>
<u n="845" who="S0326">yeah I mean there's that erm I watched a quite good documentary about Apple and er sort of how they make their factories in China and stuff and they're just erm entire cities that are just factories sort of you live there and you work there with like twenty thousand people</u>
<u n="846" who="S0327">apple like in apples?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0326">like er <trunc>c</trunc> Apple computers</u>
<u n="848" who="S0327">oh Apple computers</u>
<u n="849" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0327">yes right oh really?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> and sort of really sort of strange existence of er sort of er these companies set like they just sort of build out of nowhere whole <trunc>s</trunc> towns but all they are is sort of factory and then places where people can sleep and then go back to work and people just sort of <trunc>c</trunc>come from the countryside and live there</u>
<u n="852" who="S0327">they come from the countryside cos they can't manage to</u>
<u n="853" who="S0326">make enough money yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0327">make make enough money to live</u>
<u n="855" who="S0326">there was this</u>
<u n="856" who="S0327" trans="overlap">it's very frightening <unclear/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0326">yeah there was did <trunc>y</trunc> I I haven't actually read them but there was this thing erm this one <trunc>Ch</trunc>Chinese factory worker he erm committed suicide and then erm sort of in his papers he <trunc>f</trunc> he was a poet and he had written all these poems about sort of being a factory worker and sort of <trunc>Orwe</trunc> a bit very kinda Orwellian sort of <trunc>dys</trunc>dystopic existence</u>
<u n="858" who="S0327">I mean <trunc>ev</trunc> <vocal desc="cough"/> even if you've never known anything differently it is so against the grain so unnatural <pause dur="short"/> terrifying <pause dur="short"/> well a lot of it's terrifying right now honestly you know the Middle East has just er vanished <pause dur="short"/> under a load of rubble now we've got ISIS erm wanting to take over the world and doing rather well as far as one can see</u>
<u n="859" who="S0326">yeah er</u>
<u n="860" who="S0327">well with any luck it'll hold off for another ten years so that you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be too old to go and fight</u>
<u n="861" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a bit unfortunate erm there's the cos the goddess Isis every time you er sort of her name is now being sort of <trunc>t</trunc> overlaid with</u>
<u n="862" who="S0327">yes but of course it's got nothing to do with it has it?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0326">yeah nothing to do with it but it's just a sort of <unclear/> force</u>
<u n="864" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><unclear/> very it's awful when that happens I quite agree absolutely awful</u>
<u n="865" who="S0326">especially when it's sort of talking being like <trunc>po</trunc> sort of poems about someone like <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>g</trunc> joining the cult of Isis <vocal desc="laugh"/> and sort of finding like religious like</u>
<u n="866" who="S0327">oh it's it's it's terrible</u>
<u n="867" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="868" who="S0327">there is er quite a well-known composer er I mean he's not so young anymore I don't know whether you've heard of him called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? he's very successful it's rather good music actually I suppose he's in his forties early forties and I have heard one or two pieces went to a couple of concerts a while ago and his mother who I just know to say hello to and have a brief chat very very nice and she's a er er er writes on art erm and when I first met her her name was <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and then they changed it to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> after the whole AIDS epidemic</u>
<u n="869" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="870" who="S0327">same thing <pause dur="short"/> well my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who has this publishing house and used to have a gallery he's just published a book he had erm he's in his early fifties and he's a rather interesting character gay and clever German and er he suddenly got cancer or <unclear>the</unclear> suddenly was erm diagnosed with cancer of the er thyroid and within a rather short time er he happened to be diagnosed while he had three surgeons spending the weekend with him or something like that</u>
<u n="871" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0327">so he had it all done privately and it was an eight-hour operation he had a huge scar and one of his artists gave him as a present erm recuperation time in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0327">and there's another person very very wealthy art dealer called I've forgotten his name <pause dur="short"/> who gave him his credit card so that he could buy anything extra he wanted at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0327">and he wrote this book about it now what happened was I he came out of hospital and he recovered instantly</u>
<u n="877" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="878" who="S0327">I mean fantastically strong man erm he's quite stocky not very tall <pause dur="short"/> erm and he went madly social he <trunc>h</trunc> entertained about a hundred and twenty people a day in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="880" who="S0327">erm and I didn't go to see him for about two weeks and I went in there about twelve o'clock for <trunc>l</trunc> invited me for lunch and he started talking and he didn't shut his mouth for two hours when I left afterwards and now of course that was mostly drugs</u>
<u n="881" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="882" who="S0327">must you know they must have pumped him so full of drugs and he said terrible things happened to him you know in <anon type="place"/> that he he said for instance <vocal desc="cough"/> they'd bring his breakfast in on a trolley and he'd say I don't want breakfast on a trolley I want it on a tray</u>
<u n="883" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="884" who="S0327">and the they'd lay the table for dinner and he'd say no I don't like those glasses</u>
<u n="885" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="886" who="S0327">I want different glasses and so at the same time as doing that he could also see himself doing it and understand how er ridiculous that was and erm so he he then wrote he wrote a book about it <unclear/> he's got a dog called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0327">and all the way through the dog through the <trunc>b</trunc>through the book the the dog isn't named it's it's referred to as the bitch</u>
<u n="889" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0327">and I said I see that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was referred to as the bitch and he said yes he said I couldn't have had it otherwise I wouldn't have been able to say I dragged <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> through the foyer unwillingly she was <trunc>r</trunc>rolling her belly on the marble floor and that kind of thing so</u>
<u n="891" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0327">er I thought that's true rather useful you might quite enjoy it <pause dur="long"/> he says it's a postmodern novel erm it's got pages like like that</u>
<u n="893" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0327">blah blah blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="895" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0327">so have a look so that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that is one of erm he got six little Mondrians tiny little early paintings for something like only sixty thousand each he was very clever but I won't lend it to you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos I don't lend books cos you know how one never gets them back</u>
<u n="897" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> it looks good though</u>
<u n="898" who="S0327">I think you might enjoy it I'll see if I can get you an extra copy I think you'd find it funny <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> started reading it and thought it was terribly good</u>
<u n="899" who="S0326">so it's recent erm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0327">yes so it's all quite recent</u>
<u n="901" who="S0326">that he went to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0327">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a few just a few months ago and he actually wrote it for the second part is I'd be interested for you to read it interested to know what you'd think cos the second part is more imaginary it's imagining what would happen if they er made a film of it with erm Kevin Spacey I don't think that works quite so well <pause dur="short"/> although I've been watching him in have you seen House of Cards?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0326">erm I watched the first two seasons it was <trunc>g</trunc> I thought it was <trunc>g</trunc> quite good</u>
<u n="904" who="S0327">see I think it's er absolutely addictive luckily I haven't finished yet</u>
<u n="905" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="906" who="S0327">erm apparently he is <trunc>s</trunc> Kevin Spacey's supposed to be an absolute bastard</u>
<u n="907" who="S0326">yeah probably <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="908" who="S0327">I think anybody to be that successful don't you? <pause dur="short"/> how's your posh godfather?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0326">oh I haven't really heard from him</u>
<u n="910" who="S0327">have you not?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0326">I got a Christmas card I think</u>
<u n="912" who="S0327">you wanna keep in touch with him he's a good contact <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for</u>
<u n="913" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="914" who="S0327">whatever you want to do later</u>
<u n="915" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0327">you should keep in <trunc>tou</trunc> him in touch with what you're doing I I imagine he'd be quite interested</u>
<u n="917" who="S0326">yeah I mean it's hard I suppose it's just sort of hard to do it not really artificially</u>
<u n="918" who="S0327">yes <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> well you could next time you go somewhere interesting you could just send him a postcard</u>
<u n="919" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0327">and say er we haven't seen each other in so long just to say I hope that you're well I saw him on television the other day briefly and he looked very well</u>
<u n="921" who="S0326">yeah er last time I saw him er he looks good for he's quite old now I suppose</u>
<u n="922" who="S0327">yes he must be <pause dur="short"/> over seventy I would have thought</u>
<u n="923" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0327">erm of course from where I stand <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's not so terribly old</u>
<u n="925" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="926" who="S0327">but it is old but er he he seems quite vigorous</u>
<u n="927" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="928" who="S0327">and he's on the radio every week and I think what he does is very good</u>
<u n="929" who="S0326">the er the other week my erm I I <trunc>w</trunc>woke up to that programme it was it was him and then my erm teacher</u>
<u n="930" who="S0327">at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0326">er yeah erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I was sort of half asleep and I was like what's he doing in my room?</u>
<u n="932" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0327">how many tutorials do you get?</u>
<u n="934" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> two about two a week <pause dur="short"/> I think two or three erm yeah it's good</u>
<u n="935" who="S0327">well it's very nice that <unclear>there are</unclear> still places like that</u>
<u n="936" who="S0326">and I <trunc>l</trunc> I tell them I really <trunc>li</trunc> I <trunc>t</trunc> like <trunc>t</trunc> have one that's <trunc>tw</trunc>two hours <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>o</trunc>one that's generally about an hour</u>
<u n="937" who="S0327">mm</u>
<u n="938" who="S0326">but also any time you wanted sort of extra time you just sort of they would be they're really happy like willing to like to <trunc>t</trunc>talk talk something through with them they like I mean er like they obviously enjoy it and so I think it's <trunc>m</trunc> it's more rewarding than other universities cos you can you have a real relationship with them</u>
<u n="939" who="S0327">oh it's very good that I mean at I don't know what art schools are like now most of them aren't like that but most of my teaching years we had long tutorials you know at least an hour and I <trunc>h</trunc>have several friends who've remained <trunc>f</trunc> close friends who were students</u>
<u n="940" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="941" who="S0327">and that's very that's very rewarding I mean one of the great things about that kind of relationship is you actually can talk about what you're interested in <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> which is not so easy in social life</u>
<u n="942" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0327">you know I mean artists don't talk about art when they're together they they er they complain about their dealers or they talk about money</u>
<u n="944" who="S0326">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="945" who="S0327">sometimes they talk about technique but they don't talk about art</u>
<u n="946" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0327">so presumably it's the same you're not gonna be talking about classics with your mates</u>
<u n="948" who="S0326">yeah no</u>
<u n="949" who="S0327">so it's it is very very nice that was always what I liked about teaching <pause dur="long"/> but that's very interesting what you say about the <unclear/> of course those communities going back to pre-ancient Greece or ancient ancient Greece those communities must have been very small</u>
<u n="950" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0327">I mean that's I think one of the problems that's happened everything is now so enormous and everybody's in touch with everybody</u>
<u n="952" who="S0326">yeah <unclear/> yeah sort of globalisation <unclear>of the</unclear> world</u>
<u n="953" who="S0327">I mean I'm sure there's some very good things about it but</u>
<u n="954" who="S0326">yeah it's er it's lots er sort of er <trunc>mea</trunc> er it means there's a lot less mystery</u>
<u n="955" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="956" who="S0326">kinda cos I think erm I I even I even I can sort of remember just sort of looking at photos and books of other places you know that were sort of like exciting and when you're a child it's like imagine</u>
<u n="957" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="958" who="S0326">but now it's sort of that's would be totally <trunc>unr</trunc> sort of <unclear>unrewarding</unclear> compared to a film or</u>
<u n="959" who="S0327">yeah I think that's that's a problem I mean when I er er started travelling just in Europe it was very exciting but when I then went somewhere like Morocco mind you I suspect there are still places in in</u>
<u n="960" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0327">especially in North Africa where modern life hasn't really impinged <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's some funny sights I could er this must be going back ten years but I remember going to Petra and we were in Wadi Rum which is er the the the part of the desert that erm <pause dur="short"/> what's his name? the famous Arabist? erm tut <pause dur="short"/> world War One time led er led the Arab Revolt</u>
<u n="962" who="S0326">I don't know</u>
<u n="963" who="S0327"><unclear>yeah we do now</unclear></u>
<u n="964" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="965" who="S0327"><unclear>I remember</unclear> erm and there was this guide with all the camels getting onto his mobile</u>
<u n="966" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="967" who="S0327">and that did look very bizarre</u>
<u n="968" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0327"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> firmly from one <unclear/> to another</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="970" who="S0326">yeah even things like telephones sort of er like the world before the telephone</u>
<u n="971" who="S0327">half the time you didn't know where anybody was</u>
<u n="972" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="973" who="S0327">well even in in my childhood</u>
<u n="974" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0327">it was it was very expensive to phone I used to go up you remember in <anon type="place"/> cottage the little room I used to sleep in? up a few stairs</u>
<u n="976" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0327">that was my father's room and I used to go up to phone my friends in the evenings and after five minutes my father'd roar up that's enough</u>
<u n="978" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="979" who="S0327">you er I'm not made of money</u>
<u n="980" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="981" who="S0327">cos it was very expensive</u>
<u n="982" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="983" who="S0327">I'm working on trying to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to get a mobile phone he's a long way from it but</u>
<u n="984" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0327">he's moved up two paces</u>
<u n="986" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes well I think that's cos er well before there was telephones erm do you know that Oracle at Delphi? it was actually er erm they <trunc>h</trunc>had er sort of privileged access to a lot of information cos lots of people passed through</u>
<u n="987" who="S0327">ah yes</u>
<u n="988" who="S0326">and so that's why they're able to sort of give sort of <trunc>goo</trunc> quite good answers to questions cos they they were really <trunc>awa</trunc> had an awareness of what was going on in the Greek world <trunc>w</trunc>which no one else had because no one had things like phones or even like letters really</u>
<u n="989" who="S0327">no</u>
<u n="990" who="S0326">but they had picked up all all the sort of chit-chat from the whole sort of Greek world</u>
<u n="991" who="S0327">terribly hard to imagine living like that now there is a movement er have you ever met my photographer called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? he's a very nice man he's in his mid-thirties now very good photographer and he started a course in some aspect of of politics and there er has been for a few years now some movement to kind of erm I've only just started looking at looking at the the essay that he sent me erm the opposite of sustainable development to rather reduce everything down so that life can in some way be simpler</u>
<u n="992" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="993" who="S0327">and I'm I'm interested in reading it cos I can't imagine how that can happen <pause dur="short"/> cos I get frightened occasionally when you think that you know er the life we lead is so artificial in so many ways you know all you need is electricity to go</u>
<u n="994" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0327">you know and you've got no television you've got no radio you've got no telephone you've got no way of communicating you've got no way of seeing in the evening erm you've got no way of heating you've got no way of cooking</u>
<u n="996" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0327">it's extraordinary</u>
<u n="998" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's why erm sort of it's the idea of like cyber warfare when you can sort of really bring a country to its knees er just by messing with the computer systems</u>
<u n="999" who="S0327" trans="overlap">I'm amazed that no country's managed to do it yet I suppose that there are firewalls everywhere</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0326">mm <pause dur="long"/> but you know even something as as simple as sort of <trunc>m</trunc>messing with traffic lights you know make them all green <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0327">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> hospitals <trunc>w</trunc> you know everything would just stop <pause dur="short"/> well I guess it'll happen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er er somewhere at some point</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0327">only recently wasn't there some enormous storm somewhere in Australia or off on an island off? where everything everything crashed <pause dur="short"/> the lot so that's how it's gonna happen <pause dur="short"/> but then maybe <unclear>all</unclear> people think like that I remember my father saying I'm glad I'm not gonna see what's going to happen to the world next</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1005" who="S0327">would you like to read a story I wrote about an experience of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to renew his passport a year or so ago and he he came here and he told me the story of it it was a complete and utter nightmare and erm I said look <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I <trunc>g</trunc>I've gotta <trunc>wr</trunc> I've gotta turn that into a story can you write that down for me? now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is dyslexic and er for every word that there is he uses six and he sent me this thing it's ten thousand words</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1007" who="S0327">and all about how he was <trunc>h</trunc>his frustration in you know going from queue to queue and so on and I thought I can't do this but then I suddenly saw a way of doing it and turning it into third person</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1009" who="S0327">would you like me to send it to you?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0326">yeah I <unclear>I'd like to</unclear> have a look at it</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0327" trans="overlap">it's it you may find it it well it it is it is boring you know I mean that's the point to it erm but it's er <trunc>fantast</trunc> but if you can sit it out it's worth reading <pause dur="short"/> send <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s story</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0326">but it's a sort of bureaucratic nightmare?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes yes I've called it erm renewing your passport roll over Franz Kafka</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0327">and in fact I'm starting to think about <trunc>c</trunc> doing a collection of stories about the some extreme adventures of my friends and people I know if there's anything really wild that's happened to you already in your life <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> think about it</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0326">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1017" who="S0327">and if it's <trunc>re</trunc> then we can you can you can tell me about that and write it down and erm <unclear/> I just think it'd be quite a nice thing to do</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0326">yeah I wish I <trunc>w</trunc> I remember one time my friend in Berlin told me such er I wish it was recorded her telling me this story about how one time she and her friends they sort of er knew a little bit about <unclear>boats</unclear> but not really they'd like done a bit of sailing on a reservoir and by the end of it they <trunc>w</trunc>went on the computer and faked a boat licence on Photoshop <vocal desc="laugh"/> and rented a yacht sort of a big <trunc>s</trunc> like two million euro yacht <unclear>just like</unclear> sailed it in Greece <pause dur="short"/> and it's like the sort of they didn't really know how to park it so they just kinda didn't wanna get in trouble so they would leave it in the ocean and like row <vocal desc="laugh"/> back and forth</u>
<u n="1019" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1020" who="S0326">they didn't really know like they had to say <trunc>for</trunc>forgot they had to get water and you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1021" who="S0327">yeah that's the kind of thing that you know everybody's got one or two stories like that at some point</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1022" who="S0326">well I think I'd better start</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0327">okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well I'm I can feel my afternoon nap coming on <pause dur="short"/> thank you for doing the chair</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0326">that's alright</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> water the garden so how long are you here for now?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0326">erm go back to <anon type="place"/> straight from Italy so till till about the thirteenth of April I think</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0327">oh quite a quite a long time <pause dur="short"/> okay well maybe we can think of something to do <pause dur="short"/> and tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I can't remember what he looks like</u>
<u n="1028" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1029" who="S0326">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> back from er? when does she get back from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0327">I er saw her a little while ago erm <unclear/> not quite sure <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> don't know but I think you should keep in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I think you two have got erm <pause dur="short"/> I think your work crosses over</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0327">and you can probably interest each other in various things anyhow it's lovely to see you</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0326"><unclear/> thank you for lunch</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0327">see you soon</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0326">yeah see you soon</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0327">and love to the family</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0326">yep</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0327">and make allowances for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1039" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1040" who="S0327">goodbye</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0326"><unclear>bye bye</unclear></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
