<text id="S9KS">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:19:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0441</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Bedroom and Kitchen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>sport, food, friends, catch-up, ex-boyfriends, family, work, house</topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with housemate after holiday</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, requesting, inviting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0441">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Mental Health Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they used to and they used to crack out all those different Coke flavours didn't they? like</u>
<u n="2" who="S0441" trans="overlap">they've brought them back <trunc>vani</trunc></u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">have they?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0441">vanilla and cherry</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">oh yeah I saw the <trunc>fl</trunc> oh yeah I saw the cherry I don't like Cherry Coke though</u>
<u n="6" who="S0441">I quite like Cherry Coke they they do Diet Cherry Coke but it doesn't taste the same <pause dur="short"/> they used to do <pause dur="short"/> what <unclear>else</unclear> did they used to do?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">vanilla cherry</u>
<u n="8" who="S0441" trans="overlap">they've brought that back</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">lime <pause dur="short"/> that was it though wasn't it?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">why did they bring the Vanilla Coke back?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0441">I quite like it</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439"><unclear>but it's like</unclear> it's so sweet</u>
<u n="14" who="S0441">it's very sweet you can't</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's so sweet</u>
<u n="16" who="S0441">like drink a lot of it at all</u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">no not at all</u>
<u n="18" who="S0441">but <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>you alright</unclear>?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just dreading Saturday now</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439"><unclear>well check</unclear> <unclear/> I don't know if I do I might do</u>
<u n="22" who="S0441">it's fine I don't it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">yeah I know but it is just a bit of an effort isn't it? like having all these people come round and we probably that means we have to clean Friday night don't we?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0441">yeah we should <pause dur="short"/> not crazy I suppose it would help anyway</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0441">for when we move out doing like a deep clean I suppose wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439">well I might tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to come on the Saturday then <unclear/> come for Saturday night</u>
<u n="28" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">instead of Friday night <pause dur="short"/> that might be easier</u>
<u n="30" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0441">tell <unclear>them</unclear> to come to mine <unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah cos then if I was there cos if she came on Saturday night I could help clean on Friday we could order a pizza or something <pause dur="short"/> with our Domino's vouchers <pause dur="long"/> oh just cleaning's such an effort although we probably should do it the vacuum cleaner's shit</u>
<u n="34" who="S0441">do you use it with the thingy on it?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439">no I use it with just the sucker</u>
<u n="36" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439">but even the sucker's crap</u>
<u n="38" who="S0441">it is shit erm have you emptied it?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">possibly not no actually</u>
<u n="40" who="S0441">that could be why</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">I could ask mum to bring hers round</u>
<u n="42" who="S0441">or <pause dur="short"/> oh no <unclear/> <unclear>be home will I</unclear>? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was gonna say I could go <trunc>ho</trunc> this is this weekend?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">could see what mum's doing Friday night and ask her if she wants to come round and bring her vacuum cleaner and have dinner with us</u>
<u n="44" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0441"><unclear/> just using her for her vacuum <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah pretty much yeah just be like mum can I have your vacuum cleaner please?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0439">it will will be a good good thing though to bin shit that we don't need</u>
<u n="51" who="S0441">you're right there <pause dur="short"/> I'm I'm gonna do that <trunc>be</trunc>before I move home I'm gonna take even less crap that I bought with me I I got rid of so much crap before I came I'm gonna get rid of even more crap this time and not take half the stuff back</u>
<u n="52" who="S0439">that's the thing though it's just stuff isn't it? like stuff like like teapots and stuff that are so nice but you just never use them but you don't wanna get rid of them because they're really nice but you never use them it's really weird I do that er</u>
<u n="53" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I'm I'm keeping my teapot</u>
<u n="54" who="S0439">oh yeah no no I know that's what I mean like</u>
<u n="55" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0439">there's so much shit like like the Moomin stuff I don't ever use it but I just love it yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0441" trans="overlap">but it's so nice it's so good</u>
<u n="58" who="S0439">I just love it like that napkin holder what is that? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's a plant pot</u>
<u n="60" who="S0439">oh I see <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0441">I just put napkins in it because it was there at the time</u>
<u n="62" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0441">what plant did it have in it? oh it had my plant from my bedroom <pause dur="short"/> I need to get a nice cactus to put in there just one that lasts for ages doesn't just die <pause dur="short"/> it isn't a very good house for plants at all it's too hot</u>
<u n="64" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well that's the thing it's not a very good plant er ah not a very good plant it's not a very good house for like vegetables either</u>
<u n="65" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0439">like I leave my <trunc>carro</trunc> cos I don't normally put carrots in the fridge <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>if</unclear> I put them in the fridge they go crap I leave them out they go crap</u>
<u n="67" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0439">like I <trunc>c</trunc> I I can't buy a bag of carrots because they just go off</u>
<u n="69" who="S0441">do you put them in that drawer?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0439">yeah sometimes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> oh we've got to empty that cupboard as well shit</u>
<u n="71" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we well I think <pause dur="short"/> we should just see what's in there because that that erm TV stand was in there I think but we'll just leave that out I think</u>
<u n="72" who="S0439">yeah it makes sense to be out</u>
<u n="73" who="S0441">erm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0439">ah I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s TV still <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0441">yeah you do</u>
<u n="76" who="S0439">it's not going back to him</u>
<u n="77" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="78" who="S0439">he hasn't actually mentioned it so it's fine</u>
<u n="79" who="S0441">just ignore it then pretend it never happened</u>
<u n="80" who="S0439">yeah <unclear>unless he's like</unclear> yeah so that TV? yeah got rid of it</u>
<u n="81" who="S0441">pawned it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> made some money out of it</u>
<u n="83" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0439">screwed you over bitch <pause dur="short"/> I'm kidding I wouldn't say that to him</u>
<u n="85" who="S0441">erm yeah <unclear/> mow the grass as well</u>
<u n="86" who="S0439">yeah damn it</u>
<u n="87" who="S0441"><unclear/> life <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0439">there's so much to do</u>
<u n="89" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I hate mowing the grass <pause dur="short"/> what's the weather like this week? <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0441">okay it's pretty nice weather er all the way through apart from Monday</u>
<u n="92" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="93" who="S0441">so it's okay to mow the lawn I feel a bit bad that we have that that thing looks so ridiculous <unclear>with like the door</unclear></u>
<u n="94" who="S0439">oh yeah we should cut that yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0441">how are we gonna cut it though?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0439">scissors</u>
<u n="97" who="S0441">scissors?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0441">it'll take fifty thousand years</u>
<u n="100" who="S0439">it's better than nothing what do you want me to do? oh I could ask dad to bring some secateurs over</u>
<u n="101" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0441">ask him to join for dinner as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">it's like mum dad what are you doing on Friday? cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really need some help <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0441">no no no no we really want to invite you for dinner</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we want to have you over we haven't seen you in a while</u>
<u n="106" who="S0441">but please can you bring your vacuum and secateurs?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> secateurs <pause dur="short"/> and the lawnmower</u>
<u n="108" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">and and er <trunc>w</trunc> and some weeding equipment</u>
<u n="110" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">and possibly some varnish and and a sander <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I'm kidding <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not weeding fuck that they can weed themselves if they want to weed that badly</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439"><trunc>w</trunc> yeah also at least it means like if er if the house er er if more tenants move in obviously we'll have to take our beds down which is fine but they'll have to they'll have to like renegotiate with and see whether they can have the bed in his garage</u>
<u n="114" who="S0441">shall we take it out <pause dur="short"/> of his garage?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">erm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I think we probably should because there'll be an inventory won't there?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I think we should</u>
<u n="118" who="S0441">there'll be I'll bet there'll be an inventory check er oh</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">there will be an inventory check</u>
<u n="120" who="S0441">there seems to be all these things that are meant to happen but <unclear>I don't</unclear></u>
<u n="121" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I would feel more comfortable <trunc>m</trunc> <trunc>pr</trunc> <trunc>mo</trunc> leaving it back in the house and then</u>
<u n="122" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">them figuring out themselves yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> we could explain to them that's what happened in the past but just put it back I think</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">yeah yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> erm well the guy who came round last time did the inventory check like when I had that</u>
<u n="126" who="S0441">the I I think he must've been the same guy</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they say he was like a tall older man</u>
<u n="128" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439">like quite not old</u>
<u n="130" who="S0441">glasses</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">but <trunc>glass</trunc> yeah that was him</u>
<u n="132" who="S0441">with a camera round his neck</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439">I don't think he had a camera this time</u>
<u n="134" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">oh he might've done</u>
<u n="136" who="S0441">he had a camera I guess to take photos of</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">but he see he was fine like he was like it's all good condition it's fine</u>
<u n="138" who="S0441">I guess they're just looking at stuff that's like proper broken aren't they?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">yeah we probably should tape up the fridge with some clear tape instead of some colour tape</u>
<u n="140" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes we should <pause dur="short"/> cos he's gonna look in the fridge <unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but also if they try and charge us for anything I'd just be like I'm sorry but you are</u>
<u n="142" who="S0441">utterly ridiculous</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you were appalling yeah like <pause dur="short"/> you are actually the shittest estate agent and we had to clean if they try and charge us for a house clean</u>
<u n="144" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no we're not doing that</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439">I'll be like I'm sorry no when I moved in it was it was disgusting</u>
<u n="146" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it was in such a bad state</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">and we had to spend time and money and cleaning products we had to spend our own money on cleaning products to clean it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">to a satisfactory <trunc>s</trunc> er state so</u>
<u n="150" who="S0441" trans="overlap">cos it was not satisfactory</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">so I'm sorry er you're not I'm not <trunc>char</trunc> you're not charging us for a fucking clean look I'll clean it myself</u>
<u n="152" who="S0441">yeah we'll clean it</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">but I'm not er gonna pay someone else to come in and do a shittier job than I could do</u>
<u n="154" who="S0441" trans="overlap">and I'm not going all out either</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="156" who="S0441">we can clean it to a acceptable standard <trunc>b</trunc>but</u>
<u n="157" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I'm not gonna like scrub all the skirting boards and stuff no way</u>
<u n="158" who="S0441">it was so shit when we came</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">it was disgusting yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it was so horrible</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">like I'll wipe all the drawers down wipe the oven down and stuff</u>
<u n="162" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah like common courtesy stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0439">yeah vacuum but I'm not going to go above I'm not gonna clean the top of those shelves bet they're disgusting</u>
<u n="164" who="S0441">er <unclear/> <unclear>even think about it</unclear></u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">and the lights</u>
<u n="166" who="S0441">those lights are rancid</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">they're disgusting we probably should maybe try and clean the lights <unclear>though</unclear></u>
<u n="168" who="S0441">they're so dusty <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I would not clean</unclear> those lights they're horrible</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">but I wonder if they like they get a <trunc>mess</trunc> if I wonder if they messaged the estate agent tonight and be like we want it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0441">they could do</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">yeah maybe just yeah whenever you send an email to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> be like a few people looked round</u>
<u n="172" who="S0441">know their names were? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0439">oh yeah true yeah shit</u>
<u n="174" who="S0441">if they rob us then <unclear>blaming you</unclear></u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0439">they were like whoever whoever rang up oh no they didn't book in did they book in still? or did they not at all? no okay</u>
<u n="178" who="S0441">I don't know cos er surely they <trunc>mu</trunc> they must've done just in case we didn't let them in</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0441">that would be stupid wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">so just be like whoever booked in at eleven fifteen at the weekend came to see the house tonight</u>
<u n="182" who="S0441" trans="overlap">came came already</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">erm and then tell they yeah <trunc>l</trunc> just be like we also if they want to move in in December we'll move out by December</u>
<u n="184" who="S0441">okay <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I like packing that's weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">I went round to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yesterday cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hates packing cos she's going back to <anon type="place"/> she was like I walked in and she was like <vocal desc="sigh"/> I was like what's wrong <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? she goes I don't know what to pack and I was like well have you er <trunc>c</trunc>categorised your clothes? you know into like just T shirts trousers something like that she goes no</u>
<u n="186" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0439">so we were like what we'll do is like literally she was like a pile of T shirts pile of trousers pile of dresses and then just put them in the suitcase and I was like see how easy was that? and she was like yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">yeah so I was like how did you get yourself in such a state over packing? she was like I don't know</u>
<u n="190" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0441">oh dear</u>
<u n="192" who="S0439">I was like you are not a qualified packer</u>
<u n="193" who="S0441">nah <pause dur="short"/> I love it</u>
<u n="194" who="S0439">I do quite enjoy packing</u>
<u n="195" who="S0441">quite satisfying</u>
<u n="196" who="S0439">like not like holiday packing I'm really lazy with holiday packing</u>
<u n="197" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0439">I just like vaguely plan it and then throw everything in and hope for the best because with holiday packing you know that wherever you go apart from maybe like a bloody jungle or somewhere you can buy whatever you need</u>
<u n="199" who="S0441">you can</u>
<u n="200" who="S0439">like a towel body wash you name it you can probably buy it</u>
<u n="201" who="S0441">see I don't like that idea though I prefer to have it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0439">oh I wouldn't I just I don't care</u>
<u n="203" who="S0441">see</u>
<u n="204" who="S0439">like if I've forgotten it I <trunc>c</trunc> I've forgotten it there's nothing I can do about it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that really really really annoys me</u>
<u n="206" who="S0439">there's nothing you can do about it if you've forgotten it</u>
<u n="207" who="S0441" trans="overlap">and then it's annoying <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0441">it's only my fault that I er haven't got it so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0439">I think it I think I'm in that mindset because of hand luggage because I only take hand luggage bags with me I kind of have</u>
<u n="211" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0439">yeah I have to limit what I take so <pause dur="short"/> like especially if we go to like a hotel I'm like well they're gonna have towels I don't need to take a bloody towel <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0441">see I really don't care what I pack when I'm going to my grandma's house cos I know that she'll pretty much have anything I need so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0441">she's just that type of person what the hell is that?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0439">what the hell is what? <pause dur="short"/> it's a spider</u>
<u n="217" who="S0441">is it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0439">think so</u>
<u n="219" who="S0441">thought it was an ant</u>
<u n="220" who="S0439">oh maybe cos that bin really smells</u>
<u n="221" who="S0441">I know why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0439">I don't know it smelt the other day it was just I I I emptied it I was like <trunc>f</trunc> oh god what is that?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0441">that's only a new thingy though isn't it?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this house is just so warm like</u>
<u n="225" who="S0441">that's probably why just</u>
<u n="226" who="S0439">I'm so confused to why our electricity and gas bill is so expensive</u>
<u n="227" who="S0441">god knows</u>
<u n="228" who="S0439">when we don't even turn like we haven't had the heating on since like</u>
<u n="229" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0439">May <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0441">not even May I'm sure it was like April</u>
<u n="232" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0441">maybe early May perhaps I can't remember now</u>
<u n="234" who="S0439">but no but once <trunc>some</trunc> if someone I assume someone will sign up this weekend for this house then</u>
<u n="235" who="S0441">well we should yeah let's tell them then soon</u>
<u n="236" who="S0439" trans="overlap">we should contact the bill company</u>
<u n="237" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0439">and be like erm we're moving out</u>
<u n="239" who="S0441" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0439">on this date</u>
<u n="241" who="S0441">if we can</u>
<u n="242" who="S0439">if you can just put like organise like a final bill</u>
<u n="243" who="S0441">if we can arrange for them to be able to move in December <unclear>to be fair</unclear></u>
<u n="244" who="S0439">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0441">I want to know what this bloody <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> woman is called er what her email address is I don't wanna email <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0439">yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s shite <pause dur="short"/> why won't she just be fired for being the shittiest estate agent in the world?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0441">she hasn't even got back to me like she didn't even email <trunc>e</trunc>email me back like she's got someone else to ring me</u>
<u n="248" who="S0439">like I genuinely want to just complain about her</u>
<u n="249" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0439">but I actually looked on their website for complaints and you <trunc>c</trunc> I didn't I couldn't find it</u>
<u n="251" who="S0441">that says a lot doesn't it?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know</u>
<u n="253" who="S0441">er let's just see if I've she er emailed me</u>
<u n="254" who="S0439">maybe when you speak to her on the phone just be like can I have your email address? so I can just</u>
<u n="255" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0439">confirm what we said cos I don't really feel safe not confirming things</u>
<u n="257" who="S0441">I don't either</u>
<u n="258" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="259" who="S0441">that's why I wanted her to confirm it with me when on the email <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0439">she's shit</u>
<u n="261" who="S0441">if I save this then that's the number she rang me from</u>
<u n="262" who="S0439">yeah and then if she <trunc>ha</trunc> doesn't call you tomorrow</u>
<u n="263" who="S0441"><unclear/> I'll just ring her</u>
<u n="264" who="S0439">er call then just ring her back and like hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we had some burglars come round last night</u>
<u n="265" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0441">don't</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no offense but that if that girl came in and tried to burgle us</u>
<u n="268" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0439">you'd probably just have to throw some mud at her and she'd go</u>
<u n="270" who="S0441">yeah but she wouldn't do it she'd just be reporting back</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">send the boy round</u>
<u n="272" who="S0441">or her <pause dur="short"/> gang</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">her gang <vocal desc="laugh"/> her gang of thieves and thugs</u>
<u n="274" who="S0441" trans="overlap">she's just she's just like the main woman and she rings up and says I've seen loads of really good stuff in this house that you need to pick up that's what she does</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">but also we know they're not burglars because there isn't even like a sign on the door saying to let like they'd have to like scour websites all day</u>
<u n="276" who="S0441">true</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">looking for people who were just moving out</u>
<u n="278" who="S0441">true</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439">and also why would they ring the estate agent and get like an appointment and stuff? <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's burglary gone too far</u>
<u n="280" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">that's excessive burglary</u>
<u n="282" who="S0441">in fairness burglars could do that anyway couldn't they?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0441">come to like like an arranged letting give false name</u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="286" who="S0441">steal all your stuff and then be done with it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah I wouldn't worry about it too much</u>
<u n="288" who="S0441">we used to do that at uni anyway <pause dur="short"/> go to a house <unclear/> look round</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just rock up</u>
<u n="290" who="S0441">hi guys</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439">how's it going? we're gonna burgle your house</u>
<u n="292" who="S0441"><unclear/> we were actually fighting for a house</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0441">not not literally</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0441">but really nice house and we really wanted it so we literally like we the estate agent actual building was like the other side of <anon type="place"/> so we literally all trudged over there</u>
<u n="297" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="298" who="S0441">like took us ages and as soon as we got there this big group of girls had just got there</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="300" who="S0441">and and and signed it we were just so annoyed</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">do you wanna have a look on the internet and see if the house is listed and how much it's listed for?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh yeah good idea</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I wonder if it's listed for like eight hundred and fifty quid or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0441">that would be lol wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">like</u>
<u n="306" who="S0441">er what are we looking at? Rightmove</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">Rightmove yeah <pause dur="short"/> rightmove dot com <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0441"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">I wonder what photo they probably just used the same photos as last time</u>
<u n="310" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> it's seven seven five</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">oh really? they've put it in the same exactly the same?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0441">there's only one photo oh no there's eight photos yeah seven seven five that's probably why it looks even more</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439" trans="overlap">why haven't they put it back up at eight? <pause dur="short"/> I wonder why they wouldn't put it at eight</u>
<u n="314" who="S0441">dunno <pause dur="short"/> look how nice it looks</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos she definitely could get eight for it</u>
<u n="316" who="S0441">definitely could get eight for it</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439" trans="overlap">er the only reason we <trunc>sugge</trunc> we went in lower cos we were being cheeky</u>
<u n="318" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it looks so nice now</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0441">being so shit</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">let's have a look</u>
<u n="322" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I think that's false advertising <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">that's massively false <trunc>adver</trunc> that looks the kitchen looks amazing</u>
<u n="324" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">and that bedroom looks amazing</u>
<u n="326" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">this is such false advertisement</u>
<u n="328" who="S0441">that's when it was probably like she'd just</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439" trans="overlap">her house yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah her actual house that she <trunc>ca</trunc> like cared about now it's a shit heap</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">that looks actually really nice doesn't it?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we were lured in as well</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">I love how they said oh it looks better now than in the photos</u>
<u n="334" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>what</unclear>? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">like what the fuck are you looking at? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0441">to be fair I I don't like that lounge very much anyway</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">no but still</u>
<u n="338" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's too cluttered</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439">can <unclear>almost</unclear></u>
<u n="340" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I think our lounge looks better</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">yeah I don't like clutter</u>
<u n="342" who="S0441">shit what about the mirror that fell off the wall?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439"><unclear>crap</unclear> should we replace it?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0441">well she didn't say anything about it did she? I mean he didn't</u>
<u n="345" who="S0439">well no he didn't actually that's true he didn't even mention the mirror</u>
<u n="346" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439">should we just not</u>
<u n="348" who="S0441">not mention it</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">mention it? see what happens?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I don't think yeah see what happens I mean if the worst comes to the worst they'll ask us to replace it won't they? but</u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">yeah we could just go go to Home Bargains and get one</u>
<u n="352" who="S0441">just buy buy a mirror <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I can't think of anything else that's broken apart from the fridge really</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439">the fridge we can just sellotape up and say it was shit to begin with</u>
<u n="354" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">because it was shit to begin with like it's an old fridge it's falling apart</u>
<u n="356" who="S0441">and it's got just packed with ice</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439">I wonder why fridges do go icy</u>
<u n="358" who="S0441">I think it's the fact that they can't <pause dur="short"/> I think it's to do with the energy I'm sure</u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">oh is it? oh okay</u>
<u n="360" who="S0441">and that they can't regulate themselves properly cos they're old</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">yep so basically the whole fridge needs to be new</u>
<u n="362" who="S0441">it really does yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">this kitchen yeah it just looks just like all like the doors are slightly falling off and</u>
<u n="364" who="S0441">just peel away it just looks shit</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">it looks so <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>o</trunc> like not ill that's not the right word</u>
<u n="366" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">if it was a person it would look ill</u>
<u n="368" who="S0441">if it was a person it would definitely look ill</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439">it just looks er</u>
<u n="370" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it just looks battered</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439">yeah it looks unloved doesn't it?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0441">yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> that's what I think the risk of having an estate agent is that doesn't <trunc>l</trunc>live near do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0441">cos they actually can't clap eyes on the place it's all very well having that guy to come but <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what what must he be looking for?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">I don't know</u>
<u n="376" who="S0441">like proper proper damage?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">yeah that's what he was like like he was really impressed with the level of <trunc>cle</trunc> like <trunc>cleanline</trunc>cleanliness we had <pause dur="short"/> but he wasn't really like looking at the little things</u>
<u n="378" who="S0441">cos surely if I was a landlady I would want him to look for</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">everything like marks</u>
<u n="380" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I wouldn't I wouldn't be happy like I mean I don't care cos I'm not living you know it's not a family home or I'm not living here for years but I wouldn't be happy with like that level of sort of finish would you?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="382" who="S0441">if this was like a you know long term home <pause dur="short"/> like for example if I I guess they're maybe they're like this is their first home together probably</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439">I think really they need to like just repaint the place</u>
<u n="384" who="S0441">they do <pause dur="short"/> top to bottom</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and just repaint the cupboards cos the cupboards just <unclear>need like</unclear> to be more white they look <unclear>now</unclear> looking like a bit of a weird yellowy mank colour</u>
<u n="386" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439">the flooring needs to just be <pause dur="short"/> I think the flooring's just grim</u>
<u n="388" who="S0441" trans="overlap">ripped up</u>
<u n="389" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0439">thing is we genuinely have like we mop this and every time we mop it it looks grimy</u>
<u n="391" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0439">it's like</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="393" who="S0439">oh that's the problem with like who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0441">my grandad</u>
<u n="395" who="S0439">ah okay</u>
<u n="396" who="S0441">hello</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
