<text id="S9RV">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:24:42</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0266 S0268 S0308 S0309</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Anecdote - being arrested when attempting to sail a boat from Jeddah to Cyprus. Teaching in Saudi Arabia and life there; alcohol in various countries; another sailing anecdote (Involving dental magazines)</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking over a glass of wine</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0266">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Almondsbury, Gloucestershire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0268">
				<exactage>67</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ramsgate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Arabic -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0308">
				<exactage>67</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Manchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>45 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired university lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0309">
				<exactage>76</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>50</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired dental surgeon</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0309">I was assured the boat was in good nick and they had charts and had everything else because because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to him look if you need to get this boat out I've got a friend who's got his yacht masters cos I just passed my yacht masters and and we done quite a lot of sailing anyway and and he'll sail the boat for you mm so having checked that he's got everything I took a fortnight off work</u>
<u n="2" who="S0268">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0309">to sail this help sail this boat with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and a boss bloke and it was fifty foot lovely boat but it hadn't been sailed nothing had been done to it</u>
<u n="4" who="S0268">but how did you get to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0309">erm flew we flew out there he got us a visa and everything</u>
<u n="6" who="S0268">mm very difficult to get a visa</u>
<u n="7" who="S0309">anyway I don't know what pretext we got it on I I went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0268" trans="overlap">mm yeah but you were there anyway</u>
<u n="9" who="S0309">yeah and that was a a real opener actually and I'm not particularly enthralled with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0268">no no no</u>
<u n="11" who="S0309">obviously very rich</u>
<u n="12" who="S0268">right</u>
<u n="13" who="S0309">but a lot of poverty there as well</u>
<u n="14" who="S0268">mm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0309">but the anyway erm we spend three days in <anon type="place"/> and went to have a look at a boat and it was really it was a complete shambles there were no charts no nothing</u>
<u n="16" who="S0308">what sort of boat you talking about?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0309">sailing boat with an engine</u>
<u n="18" who="S0308">right</u>
<u n="19" who="S0309">it's fifty foot long</u>
<u n="20" who="S0308">right</u>
<u n="21" who="S0309">eh</u>
<u n="22" who="S0308">masts?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0309">yes two masts ketch rigged erm <unclear>bow sprit</unclear></u>
<u n="24" who="S0308" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="25" who="S0309">erm eh anyway</u>
<u n="26" who="S0308">what's? wooden hull or?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0309">eh yes yeah it was a Norwegian design</u>
<u n="28" who="S0308" trans="overlap">right mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0309">with a pointed stern fortunately which is quite good in rough seas <unclear/> coming up behind you</u>
<u n="30" who="S0308">was that recently made or?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0309">yes <trunc>he</trunc><trunc>he</trunc>he'd been building itself he bought the hull from somewhere and he was fitting out the inside himself</u>
<u n="32" who="S0308" trans="overlap">mm ah alright okay</u>
<u n="33" who="S0309">and he fitted it all out and this is where this <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> came into the story</u>
<u n="34" who="S0308" trans="overlap">mm right</u>
<u n="35" who="S0309">eh anyway we had to sail this boat out I mean it was a nightmare from start to finish cos you have to go out to <anon type="place"/> go to <anon type="place"/> pick the boat up from <anon type="place"/> and then you had to check out back somewhere else to get the customs clearance but once you've cleared customs there you can't get back in again</u>
<u n="36" who="S0268">right</u>
<u n="37" who="S0309">so we knew we were knackered for going into <anon type="place"/> anywhere if there was any problems</u>
<u n="38" who="S0308">ah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0309">but equally he hadn't got any charts anywhere else</u>
<u n="40" who="S0308">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0309">we had a glorified A A map</u>
<u n="42" who="S0308"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0309">you know of the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0309" trans="overlap">I mean well the <anon type="place"/> is <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>is quite wide and it's quite deep except at the edges you've got coral</u>
<u n="46" who="S0268">mm true</u>
<u n="47" who="S0308" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="48" who="S0309">so if we were in daylight</u>
<u n="49" who="S0308">gosh</u>
<u n="50" who="S0309">yeah we had and of course when we went I forget it was October I think November the prevailing wind is north</u>
<u n="51" who="S0308">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0309">so it's smack down the <anon type="place"/> so we had to tack all the way up</u>
<u n="53" who="S0308">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0268">good lord</u>
<u n="55" who="S0309">the first I mean they were <trunc>ar</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and this bloke were arguing from the from the off and <trunc>the</trunc> but they both retired to their bunks for the first thirty-six hours sea sick</u>
<u n="56" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0309">so I I I I was sailing his boat virtually single handedly tacking up the bloody <anon type="place"/> he'd had a self tacking headsaw which made it a bit easier</u>
<u n="58" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0309">I didn't have to to keep running up the <unclear/> but it's a nightmare cos you've got all these <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> freighters coming down and they don't keep a watch or anything you know</u>
<u n="60" who="S0308">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0309"><unclear>power</unclear> is supposed to give way to sail but they never did so it was it wasn't yeah it was a nightmare but anyway we all got back back together again but then the generator packed in so all the food we got in the freezer went off</u>
<u n="62" who="S0268" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="63" who="S0309">we had to eat it in about two days cook it and ah it was a nightmare</u>
<u n="64" who="S0268">oh god</u>
<u n="65" who="S0309">and and the water pump packed in as well</u>
<u n="66" who="S0308"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so you had no food and no water</u>
<u n="67" who="S0309" trans="overlap">no no fresh water and we couldn't use the engine very much</u>
<u n="68" who="S0268">got fish in the sea</u>
<u n="69" who="S0309">yeah and they argue like in fact they almost came to blows at one time and and the worst</u>
<u n="70" who="S0308" trans="overlap">how many people were on the boat?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0309">three of us</u>
<u n="72" who="S0308">just the three?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0309">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0308">so it was you and those two?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0309">yes and I was trying to keep them apart and they were arguing about this bloody generator cos the generator belts kept going <pause dur="short"/> anyway we were limping up the <anon type="place"/> and you know you get top of the <anon type="place"/> you got <anon type="place"/> to the right and you've got the <anon type="place"/> up to the left</u>
<u n="76" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0309">so we were we could see that because we did that bit in daylight</u>
<u n="78" who="S0308">oh right</u>
<u n="79" who="S0309"><unclear>we had</unclear> a rough idea by direct reckoning where we were</u>
<u n="80" who="S0308" trans="overlap">so so did you go left or right?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0309">well we went left you see to start with but then the the wind blew up and there was a tremendous storm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0308"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0309">and it and there's oil rigs up there</u>
<u n="84" who="S0308">oh my god</u>
<u n="85" who="S0309">and there's islands and things but they're not really marked and we didn't have a thing any er</u>
<u n="86" who="S0308">charts charts</u>
<u n="87" who="S0309">any charts so we're so we're you know no radar nothing like that so we're knackered so the first night in this storm we decided to stay around this oil rig which was <unclear>big flare</unclear> going so we could actually see where we went</u>
<u n="88" who="S0308" trans="overlap">mm good landmark or seamark yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0309" trans="overlap">so we just tacked back and forth all night <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> locked himself in his cabin he basically he was scared and so</u>
<u n="90" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0309">there was this this this American this American chap American chap yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0308" trans="overlap">oh great so we can rely on you <unclear/> can we?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0309">so anyway by morning we could see these huge waves coming down I think you know it's hopeless in a boat we can't go on further like this we've got to go and find shelter so</u>
<u n="94" who="S0308" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0309">we decided to go back down again and go back up the <anon type="place"/> but there's a there's a a a reef at the <trunc>begin</trunc> at the end of the <anon type="place"/> and it's being blocked because in the <anon type="place"/> war they'd sunk boats across there very narrow entrance</u>
<u n="96" who="S0308" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0309">and the engine was on the blink we were <trunc>us</trunc>used practically all our oil anyway we managed to get through there and got up into the <anon type="place"/> so oh god relief cos we were sheltered from the wind and sailing we managed to sail up there a bit and eh eh anyway the engine was really we still had it ticking over to keep us going</u>
<u n="98" who="S0308" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0309">and eh but it was getting really bad and smoke coming out of it and well the heat heat thing was going up</u>
<u n="100" who="S0308"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0309">so so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had come out of his cabin by then but the American chap was a bit gung ho and he said look we're going up here now we're going to have to land he said I'm not going to go I'm not going to put my boat in Arab hands he said I don't trust bloody Arabs</u>
<u n="102" who="S0308">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0309">it'll go we'll take we'll go to Israel</u>
<u n="104" who="S0308">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0309"><anon type="place"/> at the top of <anon type="place"/> there's a tiny little bit of <anon type="place"/> at the top of the <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> five mile stretch which is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0308" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0309">and the rest is <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0308" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0309">and so <trunc>h</trunc><trunc>h</trunc>he was aiming for that without a chart but anyway I'm going to hoist the stars and stripes and he had a bloody great stars and stripes</u>
<u n="110" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0309">it was about the size of that wall there</u>
<u n="112" who="S0268"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0308">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="114" who="S0309">and he hoisted it up the back of the boat which is you never ever do I mean you well you shouldn't anyway but he he <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="115" who="S0266" trans="overlap">what was he on? what was he</u>
<u n="116" who="S0309" trans="overlap">well I don't know I don't know but anyway he did but what we didn't know it was the same time that the <anon type="place"/> had been bombing <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0308"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0309">they had a big bombing campaign <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>in <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god <unclear/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/> flag <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0309" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah exactly well we didn't know this we hadn't got any radio communications you know we hadn't <trunc>cha</trunc> couldn't charge anything up cos we hadn't got a generator with no radio no nothing</u>
<u n="123" who="S0268">can't believe it</u>
<u n="124" who="S0309">so we were limping up and and I said look this engine is really dodgy you know and I was down below deck trying to sort of look at this and nurse it and see if I could find any more oil anywhere to shove in</u>
<u n="125" who="S0308">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0309">and and suddenly they said there's something outside here we can hear noises there's boats around going around us <unclear/> look outside and you could hear this muffled thing and <unclear/> two boats there and suddenly these search lights came on</u>
<u n="127" who="S0268">oh my god</u>
<u n="128" who="S0309">you could see in reflected glare all these blokes with coats on</u>
<u n="129" who="S0308">no</u>
<u n="130" who="S0309">yeah and eh started realised well they spoke English actually very good English <unclear/> all the crew on deck with your hands in the air don't move else you'll be shot</u>
<u n="131" who="S0308" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="132" who="S0309">christ <unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0268"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0309">we're coming alongside nobody move</u>
<u n="135" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0309">so <unclear/> bloke jumps <unclear/> well two or three of them jump bloke puts a gun in my ribs cos I was <trunc>ne</trunc> I'd just come up the companion way</u>
<u n="137" who="S0308">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0309">and said you know what's happening? what are you doing? <unclear/> I said well it's the engine it's on the blink you know what do you mean? I said well <unclear/> I'm an engineer he said show me so we go down below deck and I held the thing up and he had taken his gun out by then and put in back in his holster thank god and he shone a torch down</u>
<u n="139" who="S0268" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0309">he said well look at your sump he said it's full of oil he said your <trunc>sump</trunc>sump seal's gone he said no wonder your engine is on the blink but anyway what <trunc>h</trunc> you're under arrest</u>
<u n="141" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0309">so you know you're not we'll we'll take you in we'll tow you</u>
<u n="143" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0309">where are you from? <anon type="place"/> with the <anon type="place"/> coastguard which is the best news cos they're absolutely fantastic and once he realised that this this <anon type="place"/> bloke was the real problem he was on our side</u>
<u n="145" who="S0268" trans="overlap">right right yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0309">and he was really really quite good he said look I've got to keep you under arrest you're going to be under arrest for thirty-six hours</u>
<u n="147" who="S0308"><unclear/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0309">but after we'd been under arrest for about twenty-four hours and they'd taken our passports off us and everything erm he came back and he said have you got any smarter clothes? I said well yeah we have actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0266">what were you wearing?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0309">we'd been living on we'd been living on <trunc>be</trunc>beans and non alcoholic beer</u>
<u n="152" who="S0308">oh my god</u>
<u n="153" who="S0309" trans="overlap">that was all we all we got green beans and <vocal desc="misc"/> so anyway he said the head of <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> wants wants you to meet him in a in a top hotel in <anon type="place"/> oh right not the <anon type="place"/> just us two</u>
<u n="154" who="S0268" trans="overlap">no? yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0309" trans="overlap">anyway we went to meet this bloke <unclear/> this bloke and it was a fantastic hotel absolutely wonderful and it was really nice he was in his uniform they were all <unclear/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0268" trans="overlap">where was that? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0309"><anon type="place"/> yeah and it turned out he was <unclear/> and he'd just been staying with Prince Charles</u>
<u n="158" who="S0308">oh right</u>
<u n="159" who="S0309">and he'd seen our passports</u>
<u n="160" who="S0308">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0309">from that area</u>
<u n="162" who="S0268">oh I see</u>
<u n="163" who="S0309" trans="overlap">so he was talking about the area to us</u>
<u n="164" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0309">and he'd obviously done background checks on us by that time</u>
<u n="166" who="S0308" trans="overlap">yeah quite thoroughly I would think</u>
<u n="167" who="S0309">and he said look I'm terribly sorry you've been inconvenienced like this you know and <unclear/> blah blah blah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0268" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0309">but he said really you're your engine the boat has had it you're not going to go anywhere</u>
<u n="170" who="S0268"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="171" who="S0309">so</u>
<u n="172" who="S0266">whose boat was it?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0309">well it's this <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0308">I was going to say I bet it was the <anon type="place"/>'s</u>
<u n="175" who="S0309">so he was trying we were trying to <unclear/> that was the thing so anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well you were quite a long way from home</u>
<u n="177" who="S0309">he said we would like we would like you to be guests of the to make up for the all the inconvenience you've had you've been under arrest got to keep you under house guard for another twelve hours but after that we'd like to make up to you and and take you and show you our wonderful country</u>
<u n="178" who="S0308">wow</u>
<u n="179" who="S0309">so we did and we had we went round in the Land Rover they used for the queen</u>
<u n="180" who="S0268">right</u>
<u n="181" who="S0309">we had this officer who'd arrested us who was a lovely chap eh and and eh he took us round yeah he took us round and he took us to</u>
<u n="182" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0309"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0268">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0309">and he took us to eh</u>
<u n="186" who="S0268"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0309"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0268"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0309">and it he was he was wonderful we met all these <unclear/> <anon type="place"/> and <unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0308" trans="overlap">god you lucky thing</u>
<u n="191" who="S0309">and it was absolutely fantastic we had a first class trip</u>
<u n="192" who="S0268" trans="overlap">what a privilege</u>
<u n="193" who="S0309">yeah and it was a lovely chap and he said we got to know him quite well and he said look is eh? do you do you live anywhere near <anon type="place"/>? and we said why and he said well I'm bringing three blokes on a commando course to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0308" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="195" who="S0309">there's a headquarters there for for us coast guards</u>
<u n="196" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0309">are you anywhere? cos we'll be there for a fortnight and we're free on the middle weekend right we'll come and fetch you so we did and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had got one of his partners who was an <anon type="place"/> spoke <anon type="place"/> so we got him along because there were two of them four who couldn't speak any English and he translated</u>
<u n="198" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0309">made a fantastic weekend we took him round the area showed him everything</u>
<u n="200" who="S0308">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0309">and the one bloke he didn't speak English but <trunc>h</trunc><trunc>he</trunc>he was a farmer's son and they grew fruit apples</u>
<u n="202" who="S0308">oh right</u>
<u n="203" who="S0309">well what do you do with the apples? we make fruit juice with them</u>
<u n="204" who="S0308"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0309">we'll show I took I took him down to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="206" who="S0308">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0309">here's what we do with apples</u>
<u n="208" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0309">because we realised they liked a drink but they didn't have a chance of a drink</u>
<u n="210" who="S0308">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0309">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got him on the <trunc>ci</trunc> got them on the cider</u>
<u n="212" who="S0308" trans="overlap">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="213" who="S0309">so they were but they had a wonderful time and we kept in touch over the years</u>
<u n="214" who="S0308" trans="overlap">I'll bet they did god</u>
<u n="215" who="S0268">but you were in a lot of danger then</u>
<u n="216" who="S0309">we were at the time because because it was we were sitting round this table and one of the blokes actually did speak who spoke English so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was asking him <trunc>dire</trunc> she was sitting by him they were all round our table at home</u>
<u n="217" who="S0308" trans="overlap">potentially could've been very risky couldn't it? mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0309">and she says look my husband's been telling me that you know you had a gun on him and you were going to you know</u>
<u n="219" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0309">threaten to shoot you wouldn't have shot would you? he said of course I would've shot him that's my job if he hadn't done what he was told I would've shot him</u>
<u n="221" who="S0308" trans="overlap">laugh oh my god</u>
<u n="222" who="S0309">because you can't mess around when you're in</u>
<u n="223" who="S0308">no no</u>
<u n="224" who="S0309">so she was a bit more respectful after that</u>
<u n="225" who="S0308" trans="overlap">god</u>
<u n="226" who="S0268">but you're also in danger from the elements I mean you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0309" trans="overlap">oh yes yes yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="228" who="S0268">fantastic trip but quite dangerous</u>
<u n="229" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0308" trans="overlap">do you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0266">so what <trunc>happen</trunc> what happened with the boat when you were being shown round did they mend it? how did you get back?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0309" trans="overlap">well <vocal desc="misc"/> no no we left her we had to leave the boat we got the first <trunc>pl</trunc> we got the first flight out we could</u>
<u n="233" who="S0268">what? from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0309">from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0268">from <anon type="place"/> right okay</u>
<u n="236" who="S0309">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0266">so what happened to the boat?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0309">it's still there as far as I know</u>
<u n="239" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="240" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0309">the American came up to me actually and he said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he said he I don't know</u>
<u n="242" who="S0268" trans="overlap">what? the boat's still there and the <anon type="place"/> is still there?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0309">I I I I think I did correspond with him I I think he might have got got it mended and got somebody else to take it round for him but he said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's been a pleasure sailing with you that arsehole <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'll never ever have him near me again</u>
<u n="244" who="S0268" trans="overlap">no no mm how funny</u>
<u n="245" who="S0309">so but erm it was an interesting trip</u>
<u n="246" who="S0268"><unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0266"><unclear/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0309" trans="overlap">but of course we hadn't been in touch we hadn't been in touch cos we I think maybe I did have a mobile phone</u>
<u n="249" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> must have been having kittens</u>
<u n="250" who="S0309">yes yeah because they we couldn't let them know where we were what had happened course we couldn't</u>
<u n="251" who="S0308" trans="overlap">no mobile phones in them days</u>
<u n="252" who="S0309">and I think we we phoned from the airport moments before we got on the plane</u>
<u n="253" who="S0266">she must have wondered what on earth?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0309" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yes I mean she'd been checking through the life insurance and everything</u>
<u n="255" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0309">but no I mean it was an interesting trip but it it it taught me that you know I'm very careful who I sail with these days</u>
<u n="257" who="S0308">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0309">so people say oh come sailing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know</u>
<u n="259" who="S0308">you check them out well friends of ours have just sailed across to <anon type="place"/> in a little four berth boat sailing boat with an <unclear/> not sorry sorry with an <unclear/> er and half way across the engine packed up shorted there was an electrical fault they had no lights sailing across the Atlantic</u>
<u n="260" who="S0309">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0268">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0308">so they had to take it in turns to do listen at night</u>
<u n="263" who="S0309">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0308">to see if they could hear any big birds coming and if they did they had a torch and all they could do was shine the torch on the sail</u>
<u n="265" who="S0309">yeah that's a standard yes yes</u>
<u n="266" who="S0308">and you think but it takes a long time for a boat you know to manoeuvre around a <unclear/> craft like that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0268" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0308"><unclear/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0309" trans="overlap">the trouble is that yeah a lot of them don't keep watch though so you've got to always assume that they</u>
<u n="270" who="S0308" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0266">so what did they think that you were actually doing?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0309">well they thought we were a rear attacking force coming into the thing I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0308" trans="overlap">the <anon type="place"/> are on their way they've sent the <unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yeah no they thought you know because of it all been kicking off with the <anon type="place"/> world <anon type="place"/> was even less diplomatic in those days than it is now</u>
<u n="275" who="S0308">god</u>
<u n="276" who="S0309">so anyway</u>
<u n="277" who="S0268">we're privileged to have you here <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0309"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0266">we love that story don't we?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0268" trans="overlap">oh I like the story because <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0309" trans="overlap">well how did you how did you get on in in <anon type="place"/>? I mean</u>
<u n="282" who="S0268">well it's a difficult country it's a very difficult country</u>
<u n="283" who="S0309" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0268">you know erm I was I was single for a year and then I got married on when I came back and you know it's difficult for a woman you know it's difficult enough for a man but for a woman it's impossible</u>
<u n="285" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yes I mean they don't allow women to drive <unclear/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0266" trans="overlap">you you saw beheadings and things <unclear/> he was walking where were you on your first day? you were walking back to</u>
<u n="287" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0308" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0268" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was outside the mosque on a Friday and I didn't know anything about <anon type="place"/> and they sort of push you to the front and</u>
<u n="290" who="S0309">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0268">this guy comes out all bound up and guy with a big sword and not very nice but you you you know you can't really do anything you just don't know what's going on cos I I was only there like a week and this was the I was just out for a walk and I thought oh well what's going here there's a big fuss you know</u>
<u n="292" who="S0309" trans="overlap">no mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0268">and I was sort of pushed to the front</u>
<u n="294" who="S0309">well I I'd found out about that because you know what's her name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to come and writes poetry in a magazine used to come to church <pause dur="short"/> er lived up on the <anon type="place"/> anyway her they were patients of mine her daughter was at school with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> became an air hostess and she still came back for treatment but she <trunc>ca</trunc> just before I went on this trip and she said oh god I've just been to <anon type="place"/> she said absolutely terrible people told me I've got to go to the marketplace best place to get some gold and things but <unclear>as I was</unclear> there there was a woman who was beheaded</u>
<u n="295" who="S0308">oh</u>
<u n="296" who="S0309">right in front of her she young girl</u>
<u n="297" who="S0268">mm and you see hands sort of dangling you know</u>
<u n="298" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0308">really?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><unclear/> for theft</u>
<u n="302" who="S0309">and she said oh <trunc>je</trunc> it so unsettled me I don't ever want to go there again</u>
<u n="303" who="S0268">yeah you sort of after a while you kind of accept things a bit it's odd isn't it? you know you're there you've got a contract you've got to teach</u>
<u n="304" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><trunc>jes</trunc></u>
<u n="305" who="S0309" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="306" who="S0268">so you stay and you know you just put up with things and it it you know you just choosing after a while not to go to these things you know?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> took me</u>
<u n="308" who="S0268" trans="overlap">erm it's a very odd society very odd society</u>
<u n="309" who="S0309">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> took me to a club the first night we were there we were staying in some expats thing he said come on we're going to the club going to the club you had to go through god knows how many doors and sort of passwords and things to get <unclear>in</unclear> this inner sanctum which is all done in black and white check <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0308" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="311" who="S0309">it was a little bar and they made their own booze and they <trunc>ca</trunc> sadiki is it?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0268">sadiki's my friend I'm I <trunc>suppl</trunc> no I supplied the whole west of <anon type="place"/> with sadiki</u>
<u n="313" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0308" trans="overlap">no sudoku?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0309">did you? well it's bloody awful stuff though they do seven up and sadiki</u>
<u n="316" who="S0268">well it's not too bad if you run it five times</u>
<u n="317" who="S0309"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0268">it's like vodka if you run it three times it's awful cos you can taste the yeast if you run it five times it's like Smirnoff <pause dur="short"/> very dangerous totally refined totally refined</u>
<u n="319" who="S0309" trans="overlap">but all these blokes thought it was wonderful you know they <trunc>s</trunc> they were all there sipping the bloody sadiki and seven up it's like oh my god</u>
<u n="320" who="S0268" trans="overlap">how can you remember sadiki? I mean that's that's</u>
<u n="321" who="S0309">well once you've drunk sadiki you don't <trunc>re</trunc> don't forget it</u>
<u n="322" who="S0268">do you know what it means? sadiki?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0309">no I haven't a clue</u>
<u n="324" who="S0268">it means my friend</u>
<u n="325" who="S0309">oh does it?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0308"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0268">sadiki is friend and sadiki is my I I could've been in prison for years ten years thrown away the key I was in really dangerous situation</u>
<u n="328" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but you could've been</u>
<u n="329" who="S0309" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0308" trans="overlap">it's like it's like that atrocious really?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0268">but you know I was twenty-four twenty-three twenty-four</u>
<u n="332" who="S0309" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0308" trans="overlap">you take the risks don't you?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0268">I took the risk</u>
<u n="335" who="S0308">what's that eh <trunc>ri</trunc> is it <trunc>ri</trunc> recina?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0268">oh that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0309" trans="overlap">oh no recina <unclear/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0308">the Greek wine</u>
<u n="339" who="S0309">that's awful it tastes like paraffin</u>
<u n="340" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0309">you've got this sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0308" trans="overlap">I remember the first night we we we went we arrived in in in <anon type="place"/> and we stayed overnight at this well we slept in the car actually if the truth be known because we weren't sure where we were</u>
<u n="343" who="S0309"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0308">it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0309" trans="overlap">was that before or after you'd been drinking? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0308">that was before believe it or not and then we'd looked in the erm we'd looked in the travel book and it recommended this wonderful place to go and have breakfast and we slept in the car outside this place till it opened up it opened up and we went in and we had breakfast and we thought how would this possibly have got into some guidebook as being recommended for breakfast?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0309" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0308">anyway we had the breakfast it was like got the slices of bread and it was like lard to put on the bread and <unclear/> and we came out I said I can't believe that there's a and we looked at it and went oh god should've been next door</u>
<u n="349" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0308">we were in the wrong place but we then drove through the mountains this is from the sea we went into this little village and as it was dark it was night time and as we drove through the village there were shops with the most bizarre nature it was like ski shops and and we thought why would you have a ski shop in <anon type="place"/>? we just we just been we just been down we just</u>
<u n="351" who="S0266" trans="overlap">whereabouts were you then? <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0308">can't remember where it was it was it was in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0266"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0308">yeah and we we we we got in we got into this little restaurant you know and we said we'd have a bottle of the local wine <vocal desc="laugh"/> we we all took it and we went oh my goodness what is that?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0309">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0308">anyway we eventually acquired a taste as you do and then this other group of four <anon type="place"/> people came in and we just looked at each other and went I wonder if they've had the wine before we just watched them</u>
<u n="357" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yeah it gets better as you drink more</u>
<u n="358" who="S0308">they ordered the local wine they all drink and went oh my goodness what is this? exactly the same as <unclear/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yeah terrible <unclear/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0266">but it's changed now you <trunc>do</trunc> it's quite difficult to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0308">is it? what is</u>
<u n="362" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0266">we had the most amazing erm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0268">is it the wood in the barrels?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it's resonating</u>
<u n="366" who="S0308" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0309" trans="overlap">yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0266" trans="overlap">right exactly exactly</u>
<u n="369" who="S0268">but recently the other last week whenever we were there that white wine <unclear/> was absolutely delicious</u>
<u n="370" who="S0268">yeah it was it was quite smooth one of the wines we had</u>
<u n="371" who="S0309" trans="overlap">right well the cheap wine there was called domestico or something</u>
<u n="372" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0309">but it always put me off it was a bit like domestos so I I <trunc>nev</trunc></u>
<u n="375" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0308" trans="overlap">yeah cleaned the drains with that</u>
<u n="377" who="S0266">that's expensive</u>
<u n="378" who="S0309" trans="overlap">I quite <trunc>li</trunc> I quite like ouzo actually</u>
<u n="379" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0309">but only out in <anon type="place"/> we bought a bottle back and tried to drink it at home and it was terrible</u>
<u n="381" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm no it's horrible sunset ouzos</u>
<u n="382" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> drinks ouzo there but never here</u>
<u n="383" who="S0309" trans="overlap">but sitting out <trunc>th</trunc> yeah same with me</u>
<u n="384" who="S0308" trans="overlap">no but it's</u>
<u n="385" who="S0309" trans="overlap">and what's the <anon type="place"/> stuff? now that is nasty</u>
<u n="386" who="S0308">it's like</u>
<u n="387" who="S0266" trans="overlap">drink?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0309">the the the one on from ouzo <unclear/> their equivalent to</u>
<u n="389" who="S0308" trans="overlap">you'll have a <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0309">of ouzo</u>
<u n="391" who="S0266">yeah I <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0308" trans="overlap">limoncello <unclear/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0309" trans="overlap">I'm trying to think what it's called</u>
<u n="394" who="S0266">erm well eh we had it what was it called? that was served where we were it wasn't ouzo they were serving all the time</u>
<u n="395" who="S0309">it's it's it's it's more potent than ouzo</u>
<u n="396" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0266">oh raki</u>
<u n="399" who="S0309">raki that's it</u>
<u n="400" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh raki yeah that's <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0308"><unclear/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0309" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0266">but there was another one that we were supposed to drink this time I can't remember what it was called</u>
<u n="404" who="S0309">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0266">oh dear</u>
<u n="406" who="S0309">the amazing thing I found with being in in <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> if you if you we sailed quite a bit from <anon type="place"/> and and when they give you the boat you know they say whatever you don't go near any of those <anon type="place"/> islands cos they're bastards and they'll lock you up and you won't and when you go to <anon type="place"/> they say for god's sake don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0309">but they're all lovely people really but as soon as you know</u>
<u n="409" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0308" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0309">and every time we've been there's been an incident and you've got all the <anon type="place"/> navy steaming out all the <anon type="place"/> navy steaming out and how the hell there hasn't been a bust up I don't know</u>
<u n="412" who="S0308" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh my god yeah yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0266">when you say an incident do you mean an incident with you? or just an actual incident</u>
<u n="414" who="S0309" trans="overlap">no no no no no no no somebody somebody's done something and and but I mean there's jet planes jet planes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0268"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="417" who="S0268" trans="overlap">I think you invite trouble <pause dur="short"/> something about the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s there you go there's always an incident <unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0309" trans="overlap">not it's usually I'm better when my wife's there actually it doesn't tend to happen quite so much when she is there</u>
<u n="419" who="S0308" trans="overlap">ah right yeah do you moderate the amount of alcohol <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0309">well no well we we didn't have any in in in <anon type="place"/> but apart from the sadiki because it was you know <trunc>the</trunc>they came and searched the boat</u>
<u n="421" who="S0308" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0309">that was another thing the wind was blowing like hell and we couldn't get out so we we waited and the customs came on board and I'd taken all my dental magazines</u>
<u n="423" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="424" who="S0309">to read</u>
<u n="425" who="S0308">what?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0309">no because because they you know I thought I'm going to be stuck on this boat for you know well I thought look I've got to catch up on some of these things postgraduate stuff and on the one there was an article about syphilis because syphilis can affect the teeth and so on</u>
<u n="427" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> right right</u>
<u n="428" who="S0309">but it but it did have blown up pictures of genitalia because you can get these syphilitic <unclear>shankers</unclear> on</u>
<u n="429" who="S0268" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0308" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="431" who="S0268" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0309">and it just so happened that this bloke comes on board what are those? what are those magazines? dental magazines <unclear/> starts happened to pull open</u>
<u n="433" who="S0308">ah the page</u>
<u n="434" who="S0309">pornographic <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="435" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0309" trans="overlap">out the boat out the boat you know and bloody hammering eventually we got this superior officer came along to arrest me</u>
<u n="437" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well which country were you in now?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0309">it's in it's still in <anon type="place"/> while we were still waiting to get out of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh right oh right yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0309">cos the wind was we we were</u>
<u n="441" who="S0266">the original trip?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0309">yes the original trip yeah yeah and eventually he managed to show him all these dental magazines and that he was a <trunc>den</trunc> you know he could affect teeth</u>
<u n="443" who="S0308">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0309">and they they saw reason really</u>
<u n="445" who="S0268">mm god it's a bit of a stretch though from teeth to genitalia</u>
<u n="446" who="S0308">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0309">yeah no you'd be surprised what affects it what dentists can pick up</u>
<u n="449" who="S0268">really?</u>
<u n="450" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0309">well in more in more ways than one</u>
<u n="452" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="453" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0308">like like that this is this won't hurt but there'll just be a slight prick</u>
<u n="455" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0308" trans="overlap">right okay hey I'm going to have to go</u>
<u n="457" who="S0309">and <trunc>m</trunc> and me</u>
<u n="458" who="S0266">well I'll give you both a lift</u>
<u n="459" who="S0309">oh don't be so silly</u>
<u n="460" who="S0308" trans="overlap">no you won't I've got my car outside</u>
<u n="461" who="S0309">we're alright look</u>
<u n="462" who="S0266">you can't drive after all that wine</u>
<u n="463" who="S0308" trans="overlap">no I'm only going up the hill</u>
<u n="464" who="S0309" trans="overlap">course we can drive good god honestly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0266">no cos if you got your license taken away I'd feel so bad</u>
<u n="466" who="S0308" trans="overlap">fine darling I'm absolutely fine</u>
<u n="467" who="S0309">well you <trunc>ca</trunc> you wouldn't feel too guilty you'd just have to drive me around</u>
<u n="468" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wouldn't let you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wouldn't let you drive with that amount of</u>
<u n="469" who="S0309">look I've only had a couple of glasses of wine crikey</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
