<text id="S9S8">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:45</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0255 S0256</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Ice skating, learning styles, Rainbows, online shopping, women’s clothes sizing, </topics>
		<activity>End of day catch up with daughter</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0255">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Boston, Lincs</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Boston/London/Peterborough</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>account manager - sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0256">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Grantham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Civil servant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0255">are you tired?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0256"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0255">how was this evening?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0256">yeah it was good it was alright we did learn to skate but we had to do the new warm up for the new course so that was interesting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0255">what do you mean? what's the new warm up?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0256">erm the new course skate skate excellence which has taken the place of learn to skate we get to wear these jazzy boot covers and erm we have to do like a warm up with them so they get warmed up for their lesson basically that they have and then they have so much lesson time</u>
<u n="7" who="S0255">so what's the point of the boot covers?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0256">erm they've got like left and right on them and then they've got different colours to correspond with edges and things like that</u>
<u n="9" who="S0255">oh right so as you <trunc>ta</trunc> saying to warm up you sort of say</u>
<u n="10" who="S0256">you go onto your orange edges your yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="12" who="S0256">but it's erm confuses me</u>
<u n="13" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0256">my brain it doesn't work that way so erm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0256">yeah I'm not finding it <vocal desc="laugh"/> the easiest</u>
<u n="17" who="S0255">oh never mind</u>
<u n="18" who="S0256">but er it's okay I'm sure I'll get it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> seems to think I'll get it</u>
<u n="19" who="S0255">yeah you usually do it's just sometimes your brain takes a minute or two longer or a bit longer because of the left right thing as well doesn't it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0256">yeah well they've got L and R on the boots and you have different coloured gloves on each hand for left and right</u>
<u n="21" who="S0255">yeah but left and right doesn't help you cos your brain thinks of left and as being the right one because</u>
<u n="22" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0255">that's the dominant one</u>
<u n="24" who="S0256">I know it just gets easily confused but er it'll be alright I suppose</u>
<u n="25" who="S0255">ah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0256">in the end I just I'm struggling with the idea of colours and doing things like that</u>
<u n="27" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah cos I suppose you just do a certain move without thinking of it as a colour so when you have to think what colour is that move</u>
<u n="28" who="S0256">yeah but it's also just the way that my brain learns things so it</u>
<u n="29" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0256">it erm I learn better from watching and having things broken down slowly</u>
<u n="31" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0256">than having <trunc>t</trunc> if you tell me to go into the tightrope position and then cross my leg and and make the orange edge <trunc>tou</trunc> edges touch</u>
<u n="33" who="S0255">yep</u>
<u n="34" who="S0256">that doesn't make sense to me whereas if you break it down and do the moves slowly and I'll watch it and then I get it and then I can do it</u>
<u n="35" who="S0255">mm so do you think do you find then with the people that are learning it on the learn to skate course do you spot the ones that are struggling and maybe try and show them how to do it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0256" trans="overlap">well we've we've not got any actually doing it at the minute cos we've our level isn't doing it the girls we've got on our level</u>
<u n="37" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0256">aren't actually doing it yet it's the new ones that are coming in that are starting it we just did the warm up with everybody cos they wanted to do it for some reason erm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0256">the problem is though you've gotta stick to the course you can't it's not as as easily adjustable as learn to skate because learn to skate you get told the move</u>
<u n="41" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="42" who="S0256">and then you teach the move the way that you teach it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0256">whereas this is now more you do this with the colours you go onto your orange <trunc>e</trunc> erm orange line and then you go onto your green line and stuff so we'll see I mean I've not actually had</u>
<u n="45" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0256">any experience of anybody learning it yet but we'll see</u>
<u n="47" who="S0255">yeah I suppose cos everybody learns things differently so that actually isn't necessarily gonna cater for everybody</u>
<u n="48" who="S0256">no it's very based for kids and it's</u>
<u n="49" who="S0255">oh</u>
<u n="50" who="S0256">it's been designed by a woman that's got dyslexia so for her it probably makes sense the whole way to learn but for me</u>
<u n="51" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0256">it's my idea of my nightmare way of learning cos I if you just tell me something so just <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="53" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0256">if you taught me how to do a for example er a a crossover and you said you take your left leg you push out you cross your left leg over your right leg</u>
<u n="55" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0256">hold your right leg under and you move it out</u>
<u n="57" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0256">er when I first learned wouldn't wouldn't be able to do it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0255">no cos for me by about the second bit of that being said I'm trying to think well hang on which is my right leg my which the left?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0255">er to to what? but what did you say?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah whereas if I watch it really slow</u>
<u n="63" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0256">then I get it which is</u>
<u n="65" who="S0255">yeah that's what I I tend to learn more like that</u>
<u n="66" who="S0256">yeah I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she didn't realise but it took me a good year to actually figure out what I was doing with my arms in the cool down er at at</u>
<u n="67" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0256">at <anon type="place"/> erm cos we do sort of lemons where you push your legs out and then bring em back together again which is simple</u>
<u n="69" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0256">but we do arms with it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0256">and I couldn't figure out which way I was doing my arms with my legs and it took me a good year to figure out I said most of the time I just waved my arms around</u>
<u n="73" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0256">just sort of bring them round cos er it's like <trunc>br</trunc>bringing them round your your body which I understand but I don't know whether I'm going in or whether I'm going out or</u>
<u n="75" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0256">what I'm doing and <trunc>wh</trunc>when I'm pushing out what I'm doing with my arms took me ages and she said why didn't you say something? I went ah I figured it out</u>
<u n="77" who="S0255">well yeah exactly</u>
<u n="78" who="S0256">just took a while</u>
<u n="79" who="S0255">and if she'd said oh you do this this and this you'd go <trunc>oka</trunc> but that actually wouldn't have made a lot of sense</u>
<u n="80" who="S0256">no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0255">so you just <trunc>w</trunc>wait until your arms were in sync</u>
<u n="82" who="S0256">I struggle with thinking out which way my arms</u>
<u n="83" who="S0255">with what everybody else's arms were doing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0256">yeah my arm which way my arm goes across my body and <trunc>w</trunc> aware of what my legs are doing at the same time</u>
<u n="85" who="S0255"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0256">sorry</u>
<u n="87" who="S0255">oh sorry I'm tired</u>
<u n="88" who="S0256">I'm tired</u>
<u n="89" who="S0255">mm what time are you going into work tomorrow?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0256">haven't decided</u>
<u n="91" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that is such a good thing with your flexitime isn't it?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0256">I know probably like aim for eightish eight half eight</u>
<u n="93" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0256">cos Rainbows start back tomorrow</u>
<u n="95" who="S0255">does it?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0255">erm er you haven't done a planning meeting have you?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0256">nope haven't got anything planned</u>
<u n="99" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have have <vocal desc="laugh"/> have you got any new starters?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0256">no just do a games night tomorrow</u>
<u n="101" who="S0255">yeah and ideas as what you could say to the Rainbows</u>
<u n="102" who="S0256">I've got loads of ideas <unclear>that they like to do</unclear></u>
<u n="103" who="S0255">what what are their favourite things that they like to do</u>
<u n="104" who="S0256">they <unclear>like to do</unclear> baking</u>
<u n="105" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0256">they like baking</u>
<u n="107" who="S0255">yeah well you could have the Great Rainbow Bake Off</u>
<u n="108" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah we'll do something I'll plan something I just haven't got the motivation to do it at the minute</u>
<u n="109" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="110" who="S0256">but</u>
<u n="111" who="S0255">did they come back to you about the accounts?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0256">no I'm still waiting for it back and I need my <trunc>m</trunc>my accounts back cos I need my paying in book back and I need my cheque book back</u>
<u n="113" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0256">so I'm just still waiting on that</u>
<u n="115" who="S0255"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0256">but hey</u>
<u n="117" who="S0255">hey <vocal desc="yawn"/> I've been shopping tonight</u>
<u n="118" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0255">I decided I need to buy some boots for the winter</u>
<u n="120" who="S0256">shopping from the comfort of your own home</u>
<u n="121" who="S0255">well that's how I do all of it now so I decided I need to buy some boots but before I started buying boots I saw there was twenty-five percent off on tops so I had to look at the tops</u>
<u n="122" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0255">because obviously there's twenty-five percent off on the tops er so I found a few tops and then I started thinking about er the boots but actually I want to get some new jeans to go with the boots so then I looked at all the jeans and</u>
<u n="124" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0255">and got some jeans and then I looked at boots and then I thought actually what else do I need? I need underwear so in my saved items</u>
<u n="126" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0255">not that I'm necessarily going to buy all of them cos I think I'm gonna fall off my chair in a minute when I see thirteen items oh it doesn't say total that's probably good actually</u>
<u n="128" who="S0256">bag zero <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0255">yeah no that's it cos er it drops out the bag after about erm after about an hour or something</u>
<u n="130" who="S0256" trans="overlap">stop moving it</u>
<u n="131" who="S0255">sorry see those shirts right</u>
<u n="132" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0255">used to wear those all the time with jeans</u>
<u n="134" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0255">and they're coming back in and this is why they say whatever you have with fashion if it's still good don't throw it away what are you looking at?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0256">I'm adding</u>
<u n="137" who="S0255">oh oh gosh no don't do that that's too scary</u>
<u n="138" who="S0256"><unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0255">so they say don't throw it away cos it'll come back</u>
<u n="140" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0255">it's like now all the bootcut and flare jeans are coming back</u>
<u n="142" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0255">so I'm obviously having to get some of those although I did actually save one real good pair of my bootcut jeans</u>
<u n="144" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0255">so</u>
<u n="146" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0255">I have still got them</u>
<u n="148" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0255">I just need to get the the boots to wear with them</u>
<u n="150" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0255">are you still adding? oh no what? shall I be scared?</u>
<u n="152" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0256">we'll see in a minute I just need to concentrate while I'm adding</u>
<u n="154" who="S0255">one two three four</u>
<u n="155" who="S0256">no <vocal desc="misc"/> don't distract me</u>
<u n="156" who="S0255">thirteen items</u>
<u n="157" who="S0256"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0255">how much?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0256">I'm there and it's three hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="160" who="S0255">ah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0256">erm so three hundred and fifty and then four hundred and twenty-five four hundred and thirty-five hundred and ten what's that? five hundred and ninety-five so let's do six hundred and five six hundred and twenty-seven pounds</u>
<u n="162" who="S0255">and I'm gonna get two of those</u>
<u n="163" who="S0256">six hundred and thirty-seven pounds</u>
<u n="164" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> six hundred and thirty-seven pounds <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0256">so probably a no to all of that</u>
<u n="166" who="S0255">well no well I'll get it and then I'll only keep one pair of boots so I've got three pairs of boots and I'll keep one there's four pairs of jeans and I'll keep one maybe two and I potentially could <trunc>p</trunc> keep all the tops oh this one here look at this this top the T-shirt says vague right? and it says youth is wasted on the young</u>
<u n="167" who="S0256">ha ha ha ha ha ha ha</u>
<u n="168" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I just think that's really funny and then it says here oh no it says here on on on the side bit there erm it says er be yourself everybody else is taken</u>
<u n="169" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0255">I think that's really good</u>
<u n="171" who="S0256">on your boob</u>
<u n="172" who="S0255">yeah on your boob at the side mind you people are gonna come and go what does that say? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0255">and I'll go no</u>
<u n="175" who="S0256">totally unfit</u>
<u n="176" who="S0255">ah it'll be alright so er I'm gonna order these and then they'll come and it'll be cos see like I say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I get free next day delivery so it'll all come well it'll be tomorrow so therefore it'll be what's today? Monday Tuesday Wednesday get it Wednesday and I get free returns so it's just like shopping at home it's like you go and rather than taking in armfuls of clothes to the changing rooms to try everything on I order this this this</u>
<u n="177" who="S0256">yeah but you do actually have to pay for them</u>
<u n="178" who="S0255">order a couple <trunc>o</trunc> no but you take it into the changing rooms try it all on and then decide what you're keeping then go to the till and pay for it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0255">this way this is my shop and I'm looking buying try like trying trying choose choose choose choose different sizes different colours if I think maybe cos the jeans some of them I'm not quite sure exactly what size then they'll all come I'll stand in the bedroom with <trunc>m</trunc> big floor to ceiling mirror things on the wardrobes</u>
<u n="181" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah but you still have to pay for them initially</u>
<u n="182" who="S0255">yeah but if I've got the money in the account</u>
<u n="183" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I know I know I know I know</u>
<u n="184" who="S0255">and then try everything on then send it back free</u>
<u n="185" who="S0256">I haven't sent those jeans back yet</u>
<u n="186" who="S0255">haven't you? you need to do that or else they'll charge them to you well they have done</u>
<u n="187" who="S0256" trans="overlap">it's alright I'll just do an exchange they usually exchange they don't mind how long you have it until you exchange</u>
<u n="188" who="S0255"><vocal desc="yawn"/> I'm sorry</u>
<u n="189" who="S0256">I just I don't know whether to send them back or what to do cos</u>
<u n="190" who="S0255">well do you like them or not?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0256">yeah but they don't fit <unclear>again</unclear></u>
<u n="192" who="S0255">well <vocal desc="laugh"/> well there's no point keeping them then</u>
<u n="193" who="S0256">no they're not far off though but so I can <unclear><trunc>unbu</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="194" who="S0255">so do you think you need to exchange for a bigger size? or you just think hopefully you'll get into them?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0256"><unclear>yeah er maybe</unclear> I don't that's the problem I'm in between sizes at the minute</u>
<u n="196" who="S0255">well exchange for a bigger size if it's too big send it back and then in a few weeks</u>
<u n="197" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0255">order again cos it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0255">if you buy them and keep them think oh I'll have them when I get into them that could be six months before you get down actually just that er cos although you'll lose weight and tone up more the little bit where you need where you need the weight maybe on your stomach or on your hips</u>
<u n="201" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah I know I just annoying cos like I say erm I'm in between two <unclear/> sizes</u>
<u n="202" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0256">so my ones I've got at the minute are too big and fall down but the ones that are smaller er they fit</u>
<u n="204" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0256">but they're just a bit tight on my tummy</u>
<u n="206" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0256">so cos they're low-rise where they sit doesn't look nice</u>
<u n="208" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0256">but I'm in between</u>
<u n="210" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I don't like low-rise cos they tend to</u>
<u n="211" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0255">squeeze in and pop out the bit you don't wanna pop out <vocal desc="laugh"/> over the top of it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0256">I don't mind them</u>
<u n="214" who="S0255">no I like high-<trunc>ri</trunc> high-waisted jeans</u>
<u n="215" who="S0256">when I sit down er they're fine</u>
<u n="216" who="S0255">or the medium-rise ones</u>
<u n="217" who="S0256">I need to get some new leggings as well cos my leggings are too big they're falling down see?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0255">oh yeah well you've so you've definitely lost weight so you should treat yourself to some new clothes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0256"><unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0255">but the trouble is though you you look at the different sizes and you can get a ten a twelve or a fourteen and fit in all of them in different shops</u>
<u n="221" who="S0256">I know</u>
<u n="222" who="S0255">different sizes it's just ridiculous</u>
<u n="223" who="S0256">mm we know my problem with jeans they don't really design them for bums</u>
<u n="224" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="225" who="S0256">jeans are designed for no bums</u>
<u n="226" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0256">because they give you the material for no bums when you've got a bum you get a size that's big enough to fit your bum but falls down</u>
<u n="228" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0256">and then I can't I don't like wearing tight belts so</u>
<u n="230" who="S0255">but it's like you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have got the in between if you could actually share</u>
<u n="231" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0255">make one pair of jeans</u>
<u n="233" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0255">cos she's short with no bum</u>
<u n="235" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0255">and you're tall like long legs with a nice bum</u>
<u n="237" who="S0256">mm yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0255">I must admit I am very lucky with jeans cos I do just have the right shape for them</u>
<u n="239" who="S0256">mm you do just fit into them</u>
<u n="240" who="S0255">I do</u>
<u n="241" who="S0256">that's why I wear jeggings cos jeggings just stretch</u>
<u n="242" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0256">and then I can wear skinny <trunc>j</trunc>jeggings and they look fine try skinny jeans and it won't work cos I can't get em up my leg</u>
<u n="244" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0256">so I just live in jeggings but I'd rather not like in jeggings I'd rather get some jeans but cos they last longer jeggings don't last long</u>
<u n="246" who="S0255">no but they are cheaper than jeans usually aren't they? are they?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0256" trans="overlap">some aren't the ones I got were like about the same price as jeans</u>
<u n="248" who="S0255">oh right <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0256">but they do last they're good quality the ones I got from ASOS they they last quite well but</u>
<u n="250" who="S0255">mm yeah but I can't wear</u>
<u n="251" who="S0256">keep buying them in in the in the like can't remember <trunc>w</trunc>what size it is cos they've changed their sizing <unclear>they've made</unclear> like thirties and or not not</u>
<u n="252" who="S0255">er mm yes I know that but then next to it it does say size ten or something</u>
<u n="253" who="S0256">doesn't on the ones I bought</u>
<u n="254" who="S0255">oh well it has on the ones that I bought</u>
<u n="255" who="S0256">oh cos the ones I bought whatever it was would be</u>
<u n="256" who="S0255" trans="overlap">there's there's some which are size ten to twelve so I thought oh I'll just try those as well</u>
<u n="257" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0255">just in case erm I can't if the ten's no good usually it is</u>
<u n="259" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0255">but then sometimes I'll get ten and I can't get it up my legs</u>
<u n="261" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0255">and you think well I am</u>
<u n="263" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0255">a ten but never mind</u>
<u n="265" who="S0256">I don't even know what size I am any more</u>
<u n="266" who="S0255">no the thing is</u>
<u n="267" who="S0256">not really bothered</u>
<u n="268" who="S0255">it it doesn't matter the size itself doesn't matter and that's the point</u>
<u n="269" who="S0256">it does</u>
<u n="270" who="S0255">but you need to have that as a guide cos you need to try and say I like those in that size please</u>
<u n="271" who="S0256">it does I refuse to buy anything above a fourteen ever</u>
<u n="272" who="S0255">do you?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0256">because I'm not above a fourteen so</u>
<u n="274" who="S0255">well you're not but just if they make something and they decide it's a sixteen</u>
<u n="275" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I just won't buy it</u>
<u n="276" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0256">out of defiance</u>
<u n="278" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0256">it is it's defiance</u>
<u n="280" who="S0255">I'd chop the label out</u>
<u n="281" who="S0256">it it doesn't matter I know what they are</u>
<u n="282" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0256">and er I I don't want to</u>
<u n="284" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="285" who="S0256">cos I'm not a size sixteen so I wouldn't buy a size sixteen</u>
<u n="286" who="S0255">well no you're not a size sixteen</u>
<u n="287" who="S0256">so I wouldn't buy one</u>
<u n="288" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="289" who="S0256">so therefore it's defiance and I will not buy it <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like rebellious</u>
<u n="290" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0256">I'm rebelling against the designer makers</u>
<u n="292" who="S0255"><vocal desc="yawn"/> yeah oh goodness ah oh I'm tired so that's it I think I'm gonna go to bed</u>
<u n="293" who="S0256"><unclear/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0255">are you gonna go to bed? pardon? am I? yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah just don't forget go to bed <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0255">tired being <vocal desc="laugh"/> are you recording still? yes okay</u>
<u n="297" who="S0256"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> snores snores</u>
<u n="301" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0255">snores</u>
<u n="303" who="S0256">snores twenty hours <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0255">turns over coughs</u>
<u n="305" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0255">scratches <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0256">oh dear</u>
<u n="308" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0255">alright</u>
<u n="311" who="S0256">okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0255">okay well I'll see you</u>
<u n="313" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0255">if I don't see you tomorrow evening I will see you</u>
<u n="315" who="S0256">you should no you won't see me in the morning what am I saying? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0255">well you won't see me in the morning but</u>
<u n="317" who="S0256">you'll see me at some point tomorrow evening won't you? because I will come home</u>
<u n="318" who="S0255">yeah and I'll be here er</u>
<u n="319" who="S0256">I'm only eating out for tea</u>
<u n="320" who="S0255">yeah yeah no I'll see you later then</u>
<u n="321" who="S0256">bye</u>
<u n="322" who="S0255">night</u>
<u n="323" who="S0256">look look look look look look</u>
<u n="324" who="S0255">what?</u>
<u n="325" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
