<text id="S9UA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:16:25</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home kitchen, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Swimming, playing with ANON the babysitter, pocket money, seeing ANON’s Travelling Circus, getting a photograph for ANON's Blue Peter Badge, passports, ANON's age, the Chinese eating old eggs</topics>
		<activity>Weekend plans, playing with Pippy and Blue Peter</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0654">shall I tell you how I did that? just a little bit one <vocal desc="misc"/> one <shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0655" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you do this? it just said he do Spinjitzu</u>
<u n="3" who="S0653">could you just sit down?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0654"><shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0653"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0654"><shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0655">there it is</u>
<u n="8" who="S0654"><shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0653"><unclear/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is quite keen on going swimming this weekend <pause dur="short"/> would you like to do that?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0655">depends if I'm tired or not</u>
<u n="11" who="S0653">depends if you are <trunc>ti</trunc> well you are only tired by Sunday</u>
<u n="12" who="S0655">er how do you know?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0654">because you would have to wake up</u>
<u n="14" who="S0653">because I know you very well <pause dur="short"/> that's why</u>
<u n="15" who="S0655">are you going to wake me up? because it depends how and it also depends when you are going to wake me up</u>
<u n="16" who="S0654" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0653">when?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0655">well it depends what time</u>
<u n="19" who="S0653">on Sunday do you mean?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0655">yeah it depends if you wake me if you wake me up very early I won't go swimming</u>
<u n="21" who="S0653">I'm not going to wake you up early on Sunday no we are going to have a nice lie in on Sunday and it ballet is a little bit later isn't it tomorrow?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0655" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="24" who="S0653">is it nine forty-five?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0653">so there will be a mini well not quite a lay in but a little bit less stressful <pause dur="short"/> on a Saturday morning now so that's good <pause dur="short"/> do you think you are going to want another croissant <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0655">mm yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0653">okay <pause dur="short"/> so you were good for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last night?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0655">yep she really enjoyed being with us</u>
<u n="30" who="S0653">she really what?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0655">I think she really enjoyed being with us</u>
<u n="32" who="S0653">ah so what kind of things did you do with her?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0655">we did scramble</u>
<u n="34" who="S0653">you did do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s version of scrabble then?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0654">I wrote hem of the dress although</u>
<u n="37" who="S0653">hem of a dress that's good</u>
<u n="38" who="S0654">and cats</u>
<u n="39" who="S0653">yes <pause dur="short"/> awesome</u>
<u n="40" who="S0654">but then we stopped and I played the piano quietly</u>
<u n="41" who="S0653">I thought you might have played the piano because the chair was in front of it <pause dur="short"/> yeah did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like the piano playing?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0653">yeah and what were you doing at that time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0655">erm probably upstairs playing with Lego</u>
<u n="45" who="S0654">hailstone lightsabers</u>
<u n="46" who="S0655">oh yeah we also had a super a bit of a lightsaber battle <unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0654">and they played and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> played Connect Four she went she read a story</u>
<u n="48" who="S0653">oh which story did you have?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0654">erm Winnie the Witch</u>
<u n="50" who="S0653">the chapter bit book one?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0654">no the big book one</u>
<u n="52" who="S0653">the big book one well that is a chapter book one though</u>
<u n="53" who="S0655">she also read us new tunes I mean just imagine</u>
<u n="54" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh I like that <pause dur="short"/> do you remember when you went to the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s house?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="56" who="S0653">she wrote it do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? you spent the whole kind of time at the bottom of the garden on the hammock I seem to remember and they were stains at the end of the garden you were messing around with them it was nice wasn't it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0654">mum</u>
<u n="59" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="60" who="S0654">can you get the <pause dur="short"/> you choose and just imagine colouring book?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we can't have everything in the world just because you see it on the back of a book you think oh brilliant so if you want to buy that with your pocket money</u>
<u n="62" who="S0654">I do</u>
<u n="63" who="S0653">well we'll have to see if you have got any if you are in profit because you do like to spend don't you?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0654">will you check?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0653">I will check but not at this precise not at this precise moment</u>
<u n="66" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I was suppose to <unclear/> water in there</u>
<u n="67" who="S0653">I I saw you going to put the water in the bin and I just thought mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0655">yeah I was wondering and then I wondered hey what am I doing?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0653">okay I have an update of your pocket money in a while but you've got about thirty pounds <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0655">and <trunc>I</trunc> and I have got about</u>
<u n="71" who="S0654">can I see?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0653">no because I haven't updated it I'll update it tonight</u>
<u n="73" who="S0654">I want to see it I want to see it I want to see it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0653">but I haven't updated it since the nineteenth of December so there's about two more weekends there you go here <pause dur="short"/> no no no there's none there's none in there this is all so I don't put it in there any more because actually when we are out and about that's when you both need it so it's easier for I mean if you want us to put it in the</u>
<u n="75" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I just want <pause dur="short"/> I want to get some I wanted it in there mum</u>
<u n="76" who="S0653">yeah I know but then when we are out alright well if you prefer</u>
<u n="77" who="S0654">because I want to get a <trunc>b</trunc> because I have because I have purses and bags</u>
<u n="78" who="S0653">okay well I get paid on Monday so I will take out well I'll do it over the weekend I'll take out the correct amount of money and then we will put it in there what are you doing? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0655" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> can I have some more water please mum?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0653">are you clapping your hands as if I'm a servant?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0654">no I'm just humming the theme tune <shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0653">that was nice to see that again last night wasn't it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0654"><shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0653">god it's very windy</u>
<u n="85" who="S0654"><shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0653">yes alright <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> now is there anything else you guys want to do? oh now hang on what I do want to do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I want to go into town and get a photograph of you from a photo booth for two reasons one is for your Brownies book</u>
<u n="87" who="S0655" trans="overlap">oh I know <pause dur="short"/> one is for her Blue Peter badge</u>
<u n="88" who="S0653">and one is for her Blue Peter badge</u>
<u n="89" who="S0655">I'm a genius</u>
<u n="90" who="S0653">you are a genius and this weekend if you want to do your purple badge application I think the thing to do is while we are watching this week's Blue Peter if I download the form because sort of what you've got to do is reflect on the episode that you've just seen so while we are watching it perhaps we could be noting things down that we can write can't we on our application form what do you reckon? does that sound like a good idea?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0653">alright good good good</u>
<u n="93" who="S0654">mummy</u>
<u n="94" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="95" who="S0654">when do you need to have a passport?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0653">when do I need to have what?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0654">when do you need to have a passport?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0653">a passport when you go well when do you think?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0654">when you go on holiday</u>
<u n="100" who="S0655"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you've got a passport</u>
<u n="101" who="S0654">I'm worried I might not be able to go because that says age six but I'm seven</u>
<u n="102" who="S0653"><trunc>wh</trunc> to go where?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0654">we've already been to Spain with my passport</u>
<u n="104" who="S0653">yes so passport you need if you are going to a foreign country</u>
<u n="105" who="S0655">like Jupiter</u>
<u n="106" who="S0653">no not like Jupiter</u>
<u n="107" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> because that's a foreign</u>
<u n="108" who="S0653">I'd be very impressed if you get to Jupiter <unclear>uni</unclear> yeah so a foreign country so you used one for the first time last year because uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> paid for your guys to go to Spain</u>
<u n="109" who="S0655" trans="overlap">in a car? <pause dur="short"/> in a car or aeroplane <pause dur="short"/> hey <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> remember when that erm person was holding the microphone erm up with like all those allergies and then the owl <vocal desc="misc"/> and landed on it and she went <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0654">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0655">yeah and <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> again <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0654"><vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0653">what are you worrying about with passports?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0655">it's all that stuff</u>
<u n="115" who="S0654">now I'm aged seven and that says aged six</u>
<u n="116" who="S0653">what does? what says aged six?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0654">my passport</u>
<u n="118" who="S0653">oh does it?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0654">yeah it was the summer time we went to Spain</u>
<u n="120" who="S0653">does it say your age or does it say your date of birth?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0654">I think it's date of birth</u>
<u n="122" who="S0653">yes it says your date of birth my love</u>
<u n="123" who="S0655">and also <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> dad needs to get a <trunc>pass</trunc> I think dad needed to get a new passport</u>
<u n="124" who="S0653">as well</u>
<u n="125" who="S0654">yeah because he had a passport</u>
<u n="126" who="S0653">I probably oh no I renewed mine two years ago but for a while I hadn't I didn't have a passport for about <trunc>t</trunc> a valid passport for two years</u>
<u n="127" who="S0655">what's a valid?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0653">one is one that's current that you can use so mine had become out of date because we hadn't been anywhere but it didn't matter because I wasn't going anywhere on holiday however passports are very important for jobs and things because they are our way of proving who you are it's probably well they either <trunc>li</trunc> people like to see your birth certificate or and your driving licence and your passport but the passport is the best one because they are quite actually hard to get you prove that you <trunc>des</trunc> live here for permanently and all that so actually when I was getting teaching work I had to it was very difficult to not to try and prove who I was without my passport so that's why I renewed my passport so I still haven't been abroad I haven't used my passport</u>
<u n="129" who="S0655">a lot</u>
<u n="130" who="S0653">for holiday purposes but I <trunc>have</trunc> no I haven't been abroad for</u>
<u n="131" who="S0655">hundreds of years</u>
<u n="132" who="S0653">not hundreds of years</u>
<u n="133" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0653">for about eleven years</u>
<u n="135" who="S0655">woah one hundred and eleven wait one hundred and ten</u>
<u n="136" who="S0653">a hundred and <trunc>ele</trunc> eleven years is how old am I then?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0655">one one one <pause dur="short"/> one one you are one million one thousand one hundred and <unclear>a million</unclear> and eleven</u>
<u n="138" who="S0654">you're old <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's how old you are</u>
<u n="139" who="S0653">do you want anything else to eat for for your breakfast? some apple?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0654">is it eleven thousand years old?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0655">no thank you</u>
<u n="142" who="S0654">is it eleven thousand years old?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0653">what how old I am?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0655">no firstly I would like to eat</u>
<u n="145" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="146" who="S0653">well if you could eat something that was just a number I would be very impressed</u>
<u n="147" who="S0655">just a number</u>
<u n="148" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0655">I mean is it that years old?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0653">you know that Chinese people bury their eggs and make them rotten and they eat them</u>
<u n="151" who="S0655">why?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0653">it's a delicacy so they eat like a hundred-year-old eggs they do I don't think I'd like it</u>
<u n="153" who="S0655">I've eaten the Wok and Grill scrambled eggs is that a hundred years old?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0654">no because that <trunc>wa</trunc></u>
<u n="155" who="S0653">that was freshly done that day</u>
<u n="156" who="S0654">because the Wok and Grill don't do that because they know everyone is not Chinese so if we do that then they might not come to our place so let's do it today</u>
<u n="157" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0654">not a hundred years ago because I'm not sure the Wok and Grill was here one hundred years ago</u>
<u n="159" who="S0653">I don't think it was</u>
<u n="160" who="S0655">hopefully they haven't buried any eggs in case</u>
<u n="161" who="S0653">I don't know I don't know if modern Chinese people still do it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0655"><shift new="singing"/> LYRICS <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0653">I could imagine that the egg would not taste very nice at all what are you doing?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0655">she's not doing anything</u>
<u n="165" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0653">mm I don't believe that for one moment</u>
<u n="167" who="S0655"><vocal desc="misc"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0653">right if you've finished can you go and could you put your plates in the dishwasher please? and go and brush your teeth <pause dur="short"/> now</u>
<u n="170" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0653">thank you very much</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
