<text id="S9VA">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:32:33</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-08</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0170</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Learning how to drive, jobs, racism and homophobia, teaching, mobile phones, siblings</topics>
		<activity>Friends (ex-colleagues) chatting after lunch.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring,  anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0170">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stourbridge, West Midlands</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Beginner; Polish -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">drop off</u>
<u n="2" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">so how long did it take you to learn how to drive and be confident knowing that what you were doing was coming automatically and?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> before I passed my test I took nineteen lessons</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">nineteen?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0170">but</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">but did you have practice at?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0170">but that was because I failed four</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">no you see I'm thinking of having at least twenty <pause dur="short"/> but I don't think I'm gonna get any practice outside of the lessons <pause dur="short"/> that's why um</u>
<u n="10" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">did you?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0170">yeah my <trunc>dr</trunc> my dad um took me to Wales</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0170">so that was quite quite good</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">what you drove?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0170">yeah but me and my dad had loads of arguments <pause dur="short"/> when he was</u>
<u n="17" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0170">he was teaching me to drive <pause dur="short"/> I mean we didn't go out very often to be honest <pause dur="short"/> just before my second test cos I was a bit sick and tired of failing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">how many times did you take your test?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0170">five <pause dur="short"/> but I passed on the fifth time <pause dur="short"/> because I got so nervous</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0170">on my test <pause dur="short"/> I mean one um examiner told me okay we're gonna stop the car <pause dur="short"/> please relax <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like this <pause dur="short"/> my leg <pause dur="short"/> because I failed the first one</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0170">the next one is <trunc>m</trunc> you know you get more nervous</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">you feel the pressure's on and</u>
<u n="26" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then each one then became okay I've got to pass this time <pause dur="short"/> I've got to pass this <pause dur="short"/> And my driving instructor said after the you know first one what happened? You know you <trunc>sh</trunc> you you should have passed <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then you start saying well we'll just have a lesson before each test now <pause dur="short"/> After which it's we'll just have one lesson before and try and get some practice <pause dur="short"/> because I'm I'm wasting your money <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">but did you feel quite confident when you were actually driving without the</u>
<u n="28" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">in the lesson and stuff?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0170">I'm the same with exams and that</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0170">I get really stressed <pause dur="short"/> my sister had to run out of an exam one time because she just threw up</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> this is gorgeous</u>
<u n="36" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> it is nice</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">absolutely lovely <pause dur="short"/> the lime tastes really fresh and</u>
<u n="38" who="S0170">I like things like that <pause dur="short"/> I like things that are a bit um <trunc>tar</trunc> tart?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> so how old were you when you learnt how to drive?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> when I was had my birthday when I turned nineteen <pause dur="short"/> or was it eighteen? I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> no I passed my test when I was nineteen</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">and did you start driving straight away after your test? Did you have a car?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well my dad took no I got my instructor to give me a motorway lesson</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0170">and then I just yep I drove <pause dur="short"/> I was driving on the roads but I wouldn't go on the motorway without a lesson</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0170">so he took me</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">that's a good idea <pause dur="short"/> and did you feel quite confident quite quickly?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0170">yeah I felt confident before I even passed because I knew that I could drive</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0170">and my driving instructor was really nice <pause dur="short"/> he was sort of saying you can drive <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> do not come back to me this time and tell me you've failed again <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think that's one thing I've maybe got going in my favour being older and learning to drive is that you know I don't get so stressed in in tests and stuff now <pause dur="short"/> I can</u>
<u n="54" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">control my nerves a lot better but</u>
<u n="56" who="S0170">I still do for interviews</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0170">that's one thing I hate <pause dur="short"/> because you're selling yourself aren't you really</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0170">you've really gotta <pause dur="short"/> and then if you don't get it it's such a it's a personal thing <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I take it as just like <pause dur="short"/> oh why didn't I</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> and it feels like such a waste of time because it takes so long to prepare for an interview and</u>
<u n="62" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018">write the application form and</u>
<u n="64" who="S0170">especially for a good job</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> do they still exist?</u>
<u n="66" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0170">if I'm being like honest I want something you know over twenty really <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to go for something that's less than that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="69" who="S0170">if I'm going back full time and paying for nursery fees</u>
<u n="70" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0170">I don't  I don't  want less <pause dur="short"/> and I want to you know <trunc>h</trunc> have some  have some  money and</u>
<u n="72" who="S0018">are you still thinking about doing a PGCE primary?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0170">at the moment no</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0170">no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">he's too little</u>
<u n="77" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I'm not sure if I want to work with little kids to be honest</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Why don't you get a job um as a teaching assistant? And help you make up your mind</u>
<u n="79" who="S0170">it'd be good but um it's like about fifteen thousand</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018">I've seen some that pay up to eighteen</u>
<u n="81" who="S0170">have you?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yep and you get all the holidays</u>
<u n="83" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">and you don't have to plan or anything</u>
<u n="85" who="S0170">this is true <pause dur="short"/> that would be good if I could get something for about you know about eighteen</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0170">that'd be great</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">yeah but I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> I think I mean cos I'm I've only got one salary coming in <vocal desc="laugh"/> although not at the moment <pause dur="short"/> um I was just thinking that it it's under twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> it's not a living wage</u>
<u n="89" who="S0170">it's not really</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018">you can't afford to to live pay rent let alone saving for a mortgage on anything below that</u>
<u n="91" who="S0170">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> and we have had I mean you've got more experience than me but we have had you know they're not it's not a job teaching English is not a job that you just go in into work and just do <pause dur="short"/> it's I think it and it gives you a lot of good er life experience as well with people <pause dur="short"/> how to deal with people <pause dur="short"/> how to manage situations <pause dur="short"/> cos you know I've had racism in the classroom</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0170">I've had sexism <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the classroom <pause dur="short"/> especially with some of the people from from um usually from Iraq or Iran can be very racist</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0170">I had one Iranian guy do not sit me next to that nigger</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="97" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> and I was like excuse me? He said I have people like that cleaning my house back in my country <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> So what did I do?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">sat him next to it <trunc>o</trunc></u>
<u n="99" who="S0170">between the two</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0170">guys from Africa</u>
<u n="102" who="S0018">how did he cope?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0170">he didn't say anything <pause dur="short"/> cos I said if you say anything else like that again you're not gonna be on this course</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">did he get on with them?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0170">yeah he was fine after that <pause dur="short"/> he expected me to agree with him <pause dur="short"/> and when he saw my reaction was like of horror rather than <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh yeah you're right <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">I was surprised how racist the Chinese students were against Indian people</u>
<u n="107" who="S0170">oh yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0018">I mean really really surprised</u>
<u n="109" who="S0170">yeah and I find if the Chinese girl were to have a a black boyfriend they would be you know ashamed the family be very</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018">what a shame <pause dur="short"/> yeah like no I think you're right <pause dur="short"/> I mean er the teaching <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot of different skills that you're pulling together all the time</u>
<u n="111" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018">and even like things like project management <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's no actual projects involved per se but you're still managing <pause dur="short"/> like every class is a project to be managed like</u>
<u n="113" who="S0170">definitely</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">over the course of the  of the  the academic year or how long the course runs for</u>
<u n="115" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> you can communicate with people from all walks of life <pause dur="short"/> um and bring them together <pause dur="short"/> cos there can be conflicts in the classroom between certain individuals <pause dur="short"/> and you have to try and sort it out</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0170">I had one class of they were all  they were all  Muslim men but they were from <trunc>var</trunc> different countries but with one Christian guy who was from Eritrea</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> oh I never knew how to pronounce that</u>
<u n="119" who="S0170">and um</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">I've only ever seen it written down <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0170">well I think yeah Eritrea <pause dur="short"/> they er I think that's how you say it <pause dur="short"/> and um anyway this Eritrean guy was um saying that he wasn't gonna get married just yet <pause dur="short"/> and he was twenty-four twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> and the other  the other  guys were all no there was two Somali guys who were saying to him you must get married now  you must get married now  <pause dur="short"/> and um he's like well no I haven't got a job now and I don't want to get married until I can provide for my family <pause dur="short"/> and the one Somali guy was saying to him no you must get married it doesn't matter in this country <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You don't need to have a job <pause dur="short"/> you don't need to worry about that <pause dur="short"/> um Allah will provide <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="122" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0170">and it really it just started into a big argument between everyone in the class because</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018">did it generate a lot of English though?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0170">it did yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">perfect <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0170">no it was great <pause dur="short"/> I mean that class they cos they were all from different countries <pause dur="short"/> there were two guys from the same country and they were both Somalian</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0170">but the other guys was like Eritrean Iranian guy from Yemen um Iranian guy <pause dur="short"/> yeah there was all different countries and an Iraqi guy <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>i</trunc> they had to speak English together <pause dur="short"/> I think some of them spoke Arabic <pause dur="short"/> they you know <trunc>w</trunc> not everyone</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0170">so</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">that was their only common language <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="133" who="S0170">but it <trunc>w</trunc> it <trunc>m</trunc> all men together was just such hard work <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0170">like cos the <trunc>sum</trunc> the summer school and I was like thinking after the first week oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> maybe would have been better if they'd had a a male teacher <pause dur="short"/> But no they were alright about that <pause dur="short"/> except for one guy who was a bit disrespectful to me <pause dur="short"/> quite often actually</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0170">the other guys were like <vocal desc="laugh"/> no don't do that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">oh good <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah sometimes it's it's <trunc>e</trunc> less contentious to just let them sort it out themselves <pause dur="short"/> I had um a class of nineteen-year-olds <pause dur="short"/> one of which was er very very very heavily into the Opus Dei Church in Spain which</u>
<u n="139" who="S0170">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">are very religious Catholic order I think <pause dur="short"/> and her family she had about seven brothers and sisters cos they believe in having numerous er children cos that gives better better gifts to God or something I don't know</u>
<u n="141" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">and they were all going on a march in Madrid that weekend</u>
<u n="143" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018">against gay marriage <pause dur="short"/> because gay marriage was just about to be legalized in Spain</u>
<u n="145" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018">and there was a a girl in class who was a lesbian <pause dur="short"/> and quite openly so <pause dur="short"/> and she came to class with three of her friends from school <pause dur="short"/> so it was like to her it was</u>
<u n="147" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">you know a really open issue <pause dur="short"/> she was really you know very happy talking about it or what not <pause dur="short"/> but because she'd heard that um this other girl's family were going to the er the march she just um unsigned herself from the class <pause dur="short"/> she she stopped coming <pause dur="short"/> and the first day that she didn't come they had a huge argument about how</u>
<u n="149" who="S0170">the class did?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">like her three friends against this girl <pause dur="short"/> the Opus Dei girl <pause dur="short"/> and the worst thing about it was that she'd just been indoctrinated <pause dur="short"/> she'd just been brainwashed</u>
<u n="153" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018">into having this opinion <pause dur="short"/> a really intelligent girl <pause dur="short"/> without having any logical <trunc>ar</trunc> logic whatsoever behind her arguments <pause dur="short"/> and these three girls just picked her apart totally <pause dur="short"/> and I I kind of felt I had to mediate in a way to make sure that she didn't feel that she was being picked on because there were more people that were completely against her opinion than shared it</u>
<u n="155" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018">but I just took a bit of a backseat and just let them debate it because I I thought it was important for this Opus Dei girl to realize that her beliefs were unfounded</u>
<u n="157" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018">and that you know kind of a jury of her peers was <trunc>l</trunc> leading her to realize</u>
<u n="159" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0018">that her beliefs were unfounded <pause dur="short"/> and that maybe she should apply a bit of logic and not</u>
<u n="161" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018">just blindly follow something that someone else is telling her to do</u>
<u n="163" who="S0170">it's it's so a shame like especially people who are from countries that um like in Somalia they're they are mainly Muslim but a lot of them have never read the Quran and they believe what they're told by their imams <pause dur="short"/> because the imam knows <trunc>th</trunc> well they believe that he's knows the Quran and he's read it <pause dur="short"/> so they just follow what he says without ever having read it <pause dur="short"/> without ever</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018">right so it's</u>
<u n="165" who="S0170">like a dog</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">his interpretation</u>
<u n="167" who="S0170">is a dirty animal that you can't have a dog <pause dur="short"/> and some of the things they believe <pause dur="short"/> one student adamantly believed that if he wrote in the Quran and closed it when he opened on the same page it would be gone</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0170">and he would be damned because it's you know it's the Quran and you should never do it anyway <pause dur="short"/> but I said but how okay why don't you try it and see? and he said well no no no no I could never do that because you know if if I do I'll die sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And he really really</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">didn't you offer to try yourself? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I can do it <pause dur="short"/> don't worry <unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0170">I was tempted to but I thought no I'm gonna get in trouble if I took it too far <pause dur="short"/> but what some people have been led to believe is amazing <pause dur="short"/> cos they've just been told it their whole lives</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">and how they don't then question it when they <trunc>ha</trunc> you know er develop rational thought processes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you're teaching people to learn to read for the first time <pause dur="short"/> who've never <vocal desc="laugh"/> learnt in their own language</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">I just wondered whether there might be too many brightness coming through for him</u>
<u n="175" who="S0170">to keep him to make him sleep <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0018">no whether it was er disturbing him <pause dur="short"/> he seems to like it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0170">he likes things over his face <pause dur="short"/> he plays a little bit like wuh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0018">shall I leave it there?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0170">I don't yeah I think he's alright actually</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">shall I uncover his mouth a bit though? <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's a bit worrying <pause dur="short"/> whoop <pause dur="short"/> peek-a-boo</u>
<u n="181" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">yeah but also set up the situation in which there can be dialogue between people who've got different opinions</u>
<u n="183" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and this is like a very transferable skill as my sister said <pause dur="short"/> I was like</u>
<u n="184" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's true</u>
<u n="186" who="S0170">my <trunc>sis</trunc> she's very good at this um interview talk</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="188" who="S0170">especially in banks and that <pause dur="short"/> they have to you</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0170">have to know all the er lingo</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0170">you know like all these transferable skills and</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">I suppose all the stakeholders as much as possible la la la la la <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0170">I'm actually gonna help her have a go at my <pause dur="short"/> oh I might do it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">let's do some more <pause dur="short"/> we <trunc>ju</trunc> we should just finish it I think</u>
<u n="196" who="S0170">it's gotta be eaten today</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">yes well if it has to be eaten today we should really eat it today shouldn't we <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0170">we must</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> it's actually quite light as well <pause dur="short"/> I thought it would</u>
<u n="200" who="S0170">it is</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">be really filling but</u>
<u n="202" who="S0170">shall I just scoop it out?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">go for it <pause dur="short"/> sorry what were you saying about your sister?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0170">I'd scoop yours but I've eaten from mine</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">Don't worry <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0170">um <pause dur="short"/> er she's gonna help me with my CV <pause dur="short"/> um like a generic one that I can use and just adapt a little bit <pause dur="short"/> cos it's one of those things that if it's my own I'm terrible at it <pause dur="short"/> if it's someone else's I can</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="208" who="S0170">I can  help them <pause dur="short"/> but with mine I won't be happy with it and I'll change it and I'll change it and I'll change it and <pause dur="short"/> so she's gonna help me and have a look</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0170">objectively at it <pause dur="short"/> cos otherwise</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018">no it's good to show <trunc>you</trunc> as many people as possible your CV</u>
<u n="212" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">to get good advice from as many people as as possible</u>
<u n="214" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but what what we have from teaching I think it can be the skills that you use could be very useful for many</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0170">different kinds of jobs</u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">we've got planning skills <pause dur="short"/> organization skills <pause dur="short"/> presentation skills</u>
<u n="218" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">prioritizing <pause dur="short"/> multi-tasking</u>
<u n="220" who="S0170">mhm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">and if you say this <pause dur="short"/> oh he's pulled it off</u>
<u n="222" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> who's a clever boy? Aren't you</u>
<u n="225" who="S0170">I found this really good website <pause dur="short"/> um I can't remember if it was Bristol University? And it actually goes through all the different skills that you can have as a a job-hunter</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0170">um like er things like problem solving <pause dur="short"/> numeracy <pause dur="short"/> self organization <pause dur="short"/> which wouldn't to me <pause dur="short"/> they're more skills as opposed to experience of what you've done</u>
<u n="228" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0170">and when I wrote my CV I found it quite difficult to to name my skills <pause dur="short"/> so it was really good having that list in front of me going oh yeah I have <trunc>g</trunc> I have got most of these skills</u>
<u n="230" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0170">I just never had never thought about it in in that way <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know if I can remember which one which <pause dur="short"/> I'll find the webpage and send it to you if you want</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> thanks <pause dur="short"/> cos that's another thing I hate doing <pause dur="short"/> I hate writing application letters <pause dur="short"/> I don't like changing my CV <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd rather just keep it how it is</u>
<u n="233" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0018">it's just making myself sit down and do it really <pause dur="short"/> it's not so bad when you do it</u>
<u n="235" who="S0170">hm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0018">it's the thought of I think it's the whole job-hunting thing really that's putting me off looking at my CV and looking at stuff</u>
<u n="237" who="S0170">just sounded like  sounded like  he said his daddy's name then</u>
<u n="238" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0170"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Little sound and that ah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0170">he's quite cheeky</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">that sounded quite odd <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0170">he's loving that <pause dur="short"/> aren't you <pause dur="short"/> ask daddy to put a hole in the roof</u>
<u n="244" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">I wonder  I wonder  whether we'll have a good summer this year</u>
<u n="246" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">then he can play in the garden <pause dur="short"/> have you got a little garden?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> I think maybe it's cos we've got</u>
<u n="250" who="S0170">I think he's okay <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna start grumbling a little bit <pause dur="short"/> usually means he's gonna he's getting tired and hopefully he'll just</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">oop <pause dur="short"/> oop <pause dur="short"/> shall we just turn you round? Give you something else to look at <pause dur="short"/> here we are <pause dur="short"/> ooo <pause dur="short"/> ooo <pause dur="short"/> ooo</u>
<u n="252" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/> He likes you</u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">do you want to see mummy? Let's turn you round so you can see mummy <pause dur="short"/> woo</u>
<u n="254" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">ah that smile</u>
<u n="256" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0170">I do it's you I think he really likes you <pause dur="short"/> cos he <trunc>loo</trunc> he's not so</u>
<u n="258" who="S0018">the feeling's mutual <pause dur="short"/> you're my mate <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh he's such a cutie <pause dur="short"/> oh oh oh <pause dur="short"/> we're here  we're here  Actually if I sit here</u>
<u n="259" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0018">he can see both of us then <pause dur="short"/> and if we pretend we're talking to you you can feel included</u>
<u n="261" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0018">can't you? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> then we get smiles</u>
<u n="263" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">so has your sister already started applying for jobs or?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0170">er yeah <pause dur="short"/> she has already applied for a couple <pause dur="short"/> she'll just have to wait</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0170">to hear back <pause dur="short"/> but she's away at the moment so <pause dur="short"/> mind you I've seen jobs that and they're saying closing date April and I'm thinking well if I desperately needed a job <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a long way away</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">yeah I think most places that've got human resources departments</u>
<u n="270" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">they usually advertise the job for about a month</u>
<u n="272" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018">before the closing date</u>
<u n="274" who="S0170">but this was <unclear/> I saw this job</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0170">and the closing date was April <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking something like the tenth of April <pause dur="short"/> they're planning in advance</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">that is forward planning</u>
<u n="278" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018">isn't it <pause dur="short"/> what was that for?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0170">I think it's that job I said about <pause dur="short"/> the um going round to the different centres and checking their the way they do the exams <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> cool <pause dur="short"/> who was that working for?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0170">oh</u>
<u n="283" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0170">edexcel</u>
<u n="285" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0170">edexcel</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018">well maybe you should check out um the different exam boards' websites and see if there's any others that have got</u>
<u n="288" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0018">something <pause dur="short"/> then again if you've got maternity benefits until May</u>
<u n="290" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> the only thing's like it's not very much money <pause dur="short"/> it's like if I got something a few weeks if I could get something like a month before that I don't mind too much <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family are coming over in April hm over Easter</u>
<u n="291" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="292" who="S0170">so I really would like to not be starting a new job when they come <pause dur="short"/> cos that wouldn't really <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="293" who="S0018">my you wolfed that down quickly</u>
<u n="294" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0170"><unclear/> I'm eating for two</u>
<u n="296" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0170">that's my excuse</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't got that excuse <pause dur="short"/> damn <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0170">ah you're ever so tired aren't you</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">are you thinking of having another one?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to <trunc>ha</trunc> him to have a brother or sister <pause dur="short"/> I mean he has a brother and a sister but Orla's fifteen <pause dur="short"/> there's too much of a age gap between them <pause dur="short"/> she's not really interested in him at all</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="303" who="S0170">she's more interested in her friends and that now</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">would you  would you  like to wait and have another one or?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0170">no</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">or have one</u>
<u n="307" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think two years maybe</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0170"><trunc>M</trunc> maximum probably because I'm not not a spring chicken</u>
<u n="310" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0170">I I don't want to be <trunc>o</trunc> really forty or <trunc>o</trunc> well no forty would be okay but forty-five or something I don't want to</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0170">anyway um</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="315" who="S0170">oh dear</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">sleepy sleepy <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Hm <pause dur="short"/> so welcome to my new smartphone</u>
<u n="317" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0170">Samsung <pause dur="short"/> they're supposed to be good</u>
<u n="319" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0018">well this was the cheapest one on the market <pause dur="short"/> um it took me about half an hour to work out how to turn it on</u>
<u n="322" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0170">and the thing is the the batteries go so quickly in it <pause dur="short"/> these ones these phones that do everything</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018">they do</u>
<u n="325" who="S0170">you have to recharge</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0170">them like every day where I used to like couple of days you could use it without charging it</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">well my other phone you know this one</u>
<u n="329" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">my brick from the nineteen seventies I'd like charge it up once a week?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">Cos I'd only ever use it for text messaging and receiving some calls <pause dur="short"/> but yeah this one's all singing all dancing <pause dur="short"/> wants to be juiced every night</u>
<u n="333" who="S0170">but those are better than the iPhones <pause dur="short"/> I've heard a lot of bad things about iPhones to be honest</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">I can't get with the whole i phenomenon</u>
<u n="335" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018">it I had iTunes <pause dur="short"/> I had a little iPod Nano and the interface of the program that you have to work through to get any songs onto your iPod</u>
<u n="337" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">was just so it just wasn't logical</u>
<u n="339" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">and it really annoyed me that you couldn't just use it as a like a hard disk external disk drive</u>
<u n="341" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">and just you know copy and paste over digital music tracks</u>
<u n="343" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">Cos I had to <trunc>c</trunc> um convert all of the MP3 files</u>
<u n="345" who="S0170">oh yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">into</u>
<u n="347" who="S0170">yeah things like that drive me insane</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">but I've heard that the iPhone is similar <pause dur="short"/> that you anything that you've need to put on it it has to go through particular channels</u>
<u n="349" who="S0170">it has to be like from Apple doesn't it more or less and a way for them to make more money</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0170">Cos unless you get it from the Apple Store or whatever then like you say you have to convert the things and do you have to pay to do <trunc>p</trunc> you <trunc>hav</trunc> if you put it through this process does it cost you to do it or?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so but</u>
<u n="353" who="S0170">hm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">it costs you in time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> when I bought mine and the guy I said oh you know like apps and that how do I put these I've heard that you put like different apps on your phone <pause dur="short"/> he said you have to go to the yours is an Android phone <pause dur="short"/> I'm like <vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="356" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0170">who the hell is this guy?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">I will exterminate</u>
<u n="359" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">I am an Android phone</u>
<u n="361" who="S0170">and you have to go to the Android Market and I was just what?</u>
<u n="362" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0170">what's an Android Market? Where's the Android Market?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">were you picturing the <anon type="place"/> with everybody walking round with little</u>
<u n="365" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">little green men</u>
<u n="367" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0170">oh so okay <pause dur="short"/> I pretended I I understood what he was talking about <pause dur="short"/> then I'm like going home <unclear/> what's the Android Market? What does it do?</u>
<u n="369" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0170">is it a shop you have to go to?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> They do like using all these er outer space references</u>
<u n="372" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0018">for telephones don't they</u>
<u n="374" who="S0170">yours is Android isn't it</u>
<u n="375" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he</u>
<u n="376" who="S0170">all of</u>
<u n="377" who="S0018">he <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="378" who="S0170">all of them are</u>
<u n="379" who="S0018">he offered me a choice between Android and Symbian <pause dur="short"/> and I had no idea what he was talking about</u>
<u n="380" who="S0170">I hadn't heard Symbian <pause dur="short"/> what's that?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0018">I think it's just a different operating system</u>
<u n="382" who="S0170">oh</u>
<u n="383" who="S0018">I think Nokia phones work a lot with it</u>
<u n="384" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0018">but um I have no idea pff no idea <pause dur="short"/> I mean I couldn't even work out how to turn it on <vocal desc="laugh"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but no they're quite cunning <pause dur="short"/> apart from having to charge them up every every night</u>
<u n="386" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0018">oh look the Android <trunc>Marke</trunc> the Android Market</u>
<u n="388" who="S0170">yay</u>
<u n="389" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">but then again I can you know I've got all these fancy functions but to find really <trunc>f</trunc> what I would say is basic stuff like alarm clock</u>
<u n="391" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">er call log see who you've your missed calls are from <pause dur="short"/> they're just not obvious at all</u>
<u n="393" who="S0170">oh I've got the call log from when I first had the phone and I don't know how to you know can delete in sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how to delete that <pause dur="short"/> I've got saved messages I don't know how to mm you know when you've written a message but you've not had time to send it so it's</u>
<u n="394" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0170">saved as draft <pause dur="short"/> but <vocal desc="laugh"/> can I find my draft messages? I have no idea where they are <pause dur="short"/> it's they're in their phone somewhere but <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0018">what kind of phone is yours?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0170">it's a HTC <pause dur="short"/> it's on my over there</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">who have you contracted? Who have you?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0170">oh Orange</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">yeah I've got Orange too</u>
<u n="401" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um but it's just really funny because it says save this draft <pause dur="short"/> I was like well that's it then <pause dur="short"/> it's gone</u>
<u n="402" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0018">it's saved somewhere</u>
<u n="404" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0018">I can't work out how to stop a call <pause dur="short"/> because when I'm speaking to someone on the phone</u>
<u n="406" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0018">the um screensaver comes in and it's just black</u>
<u n="408" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0018">and so when I finish the call</u>
<u n="410" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0018">the screen is black <pause dur="short"/> and I press that to reactivate the screen</u>
<u n="412" who="S0170">mhm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018">and it's just the main menu and there's nothing there about ending</u>
<u n="414" who="S0170">can you just press</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">the call</u>
<u n="416" who="S0170">the screen <pause dur="short"/> but it means the other person probably finished it already haven't they?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">I don't know but like</u>
<u n="418" who="S0170">yeah I think you just touch the screen</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">when you phone someone and they've got answerphone on and you leave a message</u>
<u n="420" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">and they can't put the phone down <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0170">if you just touch the screen</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018">then</u>
<u n="424" who="S0170">and then it should come up like</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0170">and</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> it's obviously too smart for me</u>
<u n="428" who="S0170">two minutes and he's gone</u>
<u n="429" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="430" who="S0170">I knew he would but <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was really desperate <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="432" who="S0170">determined not desperate <pause dur="short"/> determined that no I'm not going to do it but it's just so easy</u>
<u n="433" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0170">to do it like that <pause dur="short"/> but sometimes it's just makes life easier</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> oh well it makes for a less stressed happy mummy</u>
<u n="436" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">that's probably important</u>
<u n="438" who="S0170">mm yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0018">is there something in breast milk that's like a</u>
<u n="440" who="S0170">apparently when you breastfeed you release hormones that er make it easier for you to fall back to fall asleep</u>
<u n="441" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="442" who="S0170">I don't know if that's passed on to him</u>
<u n="443" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="444" who="S0170">but for him it um breastfeeding is just very relaxing for him and makes him feel safe</u>
<u n="445" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0170">so he feels safe to be able to fall asleep</u>
<u n="447" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0170">and um it lowers the heartbeat <pause dur="short"/> it um and when they're stressed destresses him</u>
<u n="449" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0170">so it's a wonderful thing</u>
<u n="451" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0170">but I think bottle er does the same <pause dur="short"/> if they're used to bottle feeding that makes them feel because they're with you and next to you and you're holding them and feeding them</u>
<u n="453" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0170">they get the same feeling</u>
<u n="455" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0170">but then they can use a dummy <pause dur="short"/> cos if they usually only take a bottle they'll usually take a dummy</u>
<u n="457" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0170">so</u>
<u n="459" who="S0018">and he's out like a light</u>
<u n="460" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0170">and as heavy as <unclear/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0018">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0170">actually I need to weigh him to find out <pause dur="short"/> er you can book to go to baby clinic and you book when you've when you feel like it <pause dur="short"/> if you want to know if he's growing okay <pause dur="short"/> you can book like every week but they probably wouldn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> wouldn't be too happy if you went every week <pause dur="short"/> but you can book when you want</u>
<u n="465" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0170">so if you're worried <pause dur="short"/> like maybe I'm not making enough breast milk and I think he's not put on weight</u>
<u n="467" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0170">so you can just go they'll check and make they <trunc>ch</trunc> chart the growth</u>
<u n="469" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0170">and he'll on the larger side <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Is his dad quite?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> he's quite chunky I suppose <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> not that</u>
<u n="473" who="S0018">Cos you were huge when you were pregnant weren't you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0170">now I know why</u>
<u n="475" who="S0018">er I wish I'd married a smaller man <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0170">Cos I'd say usually like the baby is doesn't usually get um even if you're a smaller person then usually the baby won't grow above a certain weight cos it's you know it's</u>
<u n="477" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0170">too to be able to to come out <pause dur="short"/> but he wouldn't have been able to <pause dur="short"/> er the surgeon was saying who did the caesarean said he wasn't coming out by himself</u>
<u n="479" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">the door's not big enough</u>
<u n="481" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0170">maybe I'll have a nice little girl next <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Little <pause dur="short"/> please</u>
<u n="485" who="S0170">just like her mum <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">make her little <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah that would be nice <pause dur="short"/> have a girl and a boy</u>
<u n="487" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that'd be nice</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">big brother</u>
<u n="489" who="S0170">are your brothers older or younger than you?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">three years older <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0170">do are you close?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> we we share the same sense of humour and we can</u>
<u n="493" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">banter</u>
<u n="495" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">we're not close but um</u>
<u n="497" who="S0170">I think that with my brother and sister we definitely have the same sense of humour</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="499" who="S0170">they get you more than than other <trunc>peop</trunc> that would sense of humour way</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0170">kinda like say things and it's just</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Have you got a brother as well?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="505" who="S0170">I'm the <trunc>ol</trunc> I'm the oldest</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018">are you?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got one</u>
<u n="508" who="S0018">I'm the youngest</u>
<u n="509" who="S0170">one brother and one sister</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0170">my sister's the middle one and my brother's the youngest <pause dur="short"/> so he's spoilt</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">is he? Oh my brother was a tyrant when I was growing up <pause dur="short"/> he was a right bully <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0170">was he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">that's why I was thinking don't turn into a bully <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Where does he live?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">Australia <pause dur="short"/> so yeah he's</u>
<u n="517" who="S0170">do you think you would be close closer emotionally if he lived closer or you just think</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">um</u>
<u n="519" who="S0170">it would be the same?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">probably we'd probably see each other more <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but we don't tolerate each other as much as I do my friends for example</u>
<u n="521" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">er <trunc>h</trunc> that's the thing I think I probably wouldn't be friends with my brother if</u>
<u n="523" who="S0170">he wasn't</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">he wasn't my brother</u>
<u n="525" who="S0170">I wouldn't be friends with my brother <vocal desc="laugh"/> if he wasn't my brother</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">we're completely different <pause dur="short"/> um and our relationship with our parents as well <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm a lot more respectful as my <trunc>par</trunc> of my parents as individuals</u>
<u n="527" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">and more I'm more placid and more peace-loving <pause dur="short"/> my brother's a bit of a stirrer</u>
<u n="529" who="S0170">ah okay</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">he's a he always provokes arguments and <trunc>dis</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
</body>
</text>
