<text id="S9VB">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:52</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Manchester</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics> Communication in languages, phone number/calls, medical bills/ hospitals, public transport/ walking, photocopying, printing, areas/ places, seatbelts/ car crashes, </topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on the way to pick up granddad at the hospital</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421"><pause dur="short"/> I was like he was cos he was saying it back to me in the English and I was like do you want me to say it in English? I was like <trunc>wh</trunc>why do you <trunc>wa</trunc>? like saying it in <anon type="place"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">he maybe just wanted to check that he had it correct and <unclear/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and then and then he kept saying say it again like after I'd said like two numbers and then he was like oh I thought there was a one and I like 0 seven it starts with 0 seven <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0423">are you sure you said it right in <anon type="place"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">of course I did <pause dur="short"/> I'm like the numbers of course I said the numbers right and I said them clearly as well and right and he just he was just like <trunc>on</trunc>one and I was like zero doesn't sound anything like one</u>
<u n="6" who="S0423">is that what you said back to him?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421">no but that's what I was thinking <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0423">why didn't you just look at your phone when he was on the phone?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">because it doesn't come <trunc>u</trunc> it was coming up like plus four four or something I don't know</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0421">but on yours it didn't</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423">you could've just put mine on loudspeaker and looked at the number it would've been on the screen</u>
<u n="13" who="S0421">yeah but he's he was using his credit and I could tell that he was like he was like what?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421">what is it? cos I called you on my phone out of the packet and he was like what is it? tell me so I was like I'll call you back</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's why he didn't understand why cos he was anxious about</u>
<u n="17" who="S0421">no no because then I rang him back</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423">oh right oh yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0421">cos I was like I can't I don't know what this number is so I was like I'll ring you back <pause dur="short"/> do you know what? I bet I bet what he was doing now that I think about it was that he was saying it back in English because as I was telling him he was telling the person who was writing his number down cos he needed to give it to them so I bet he was talking to me and as I was saying zero and then they were probably writing it down at like as he was saying in <trunc>en</trunc></u>
<u n="20" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah he was probably having a three way conversation <unclear/> that's why he got confused <pause dur="short"/> cos he's probably said it to them he came back to you and then they repeat back to him then he's probably</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0423">then they've said the wrong one so then he's asking you then well was it this <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> but yeah I hope he doesn't have to pay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0423">no no the woman she just the second one she knows what she's doing</u>
<u n="25" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423">she's an administrator not a receptionist so the woman <unclear/> in the room</u>
<u n="27" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0423">she just said erm she explained and <unclear/> oh I've got the card so that's all I need</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0423">then it said oh I'll have your passport as well just as an extra and that was it she said right she didn't even say don't worry no never mentioned it</u>
<u n="31" who="S0421" trans="overlap">anything about money <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0423">no <unclear/> you know that other one <unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0421" trans="overlap">otherwise yeah otherwise she would have said like oh we need this they like there's going to be a payment or whatever but</u>
<u n="34" who="S0423">yeah there was no mention of I need this cos you have to pay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0423">cos you just wouldn't say that you'd just say have you got it? if you're saying no I've got nothing</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0423">say well if you can't get that you'll have to pay</u>
<u n="39" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423">whereas this receptionist saying oh this is very expensive this thing you know? we can't just do it for anyone and if we did that everyone's going to be coming over</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> you know? just <pause dur="short"/> and obviously your grandad is probably getting worried now <unclear/> literally it could be thousands of pounds</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah because they right they got that <pause dur="short"/> they got that letter and erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">well in the letter it's not clear as well</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423">cos it doesn't say if you're a visitor and you're in the EU it says if you're not a resident</u>
<u n="47" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423">and you can't prove you're a resident you might have to pay</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0423">so that's not very helpful either</u>
<u n="51" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423">it's only when I started thinking well <unclear/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah because cos grandma and grandad were going to buy something but they're not now because they're waiting to see if they have to pay anything</u>
<u n="54" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0421">I don't know what it was they wanted to buy but they were going to buy something but now they're like no no cos we might have to pay</u>
<u n="56" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well you know? I wouldn't stop them buying it cos if there is a bill they they're not going to be able to pay it I think it's going to be I think it would cost a lot of money that</u>
<u n="57" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0423">for <trunc>a</trunc>all the visits to the hospital for the I think it it's probably a surgical procedure that it's classed as <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0423">and they don't very expensive to have anything kind of surgery I know it's not surgery but it's classed surgical</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> then you know if he did have to pay he'd be back doing referring it to his the health people of his country and let them</u>
<u n="63" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423">do it but he wouldn't have to pay cos</u>
<u n="65" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423">cos he didn't say anything and he has the card you know? there's health restrictions on that card the reason they have it is because then they can contact the the right country and the right department that deals with</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423">their citizens and they could claim that money back that they need to claim can't they?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0423">I mean they may not even do it that way they might do it say at the end of the year and get a feel for <anon type="place"/> say <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah like this many people</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">they may have done so many English people</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and that'll that'll kind of counter out so much of the bill won't it?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">well I would imagine there'd be probably more over here than English over there but</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0423">plus I <trunc>th</trunc> I think they've probably got a certain agreement because there'd be a bit of an imbalance in what that would cost in <anon type="place"/> to what it would cost over here</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">it's a bit unfair if they even have to pay the whole English price for it</u>
<u n="81" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">just shows you if you're going to a non EU country it's worse <unclear/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423"><unclear/> health insurance there's that plus <pause dur="short"/> cos you do I read anyway <trunc>st</trunc>stories where people say they've been in the hospital and in certain countries they won't see them until they get their credit card out and pay</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">I don't think they'd ever do that in this country they'd always treat you if you're really ill</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423">they will make sure you're you know? you're treated <unclear/> afterwards</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah what it is is that erm I think if you have a bill of over a thousand pounds there they won't let you back into their country</u>
<u n="90" who="S0423">oh it said that on the letter <unclear/> then you they'll consider not letting you back in</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they would treat you</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421">but you probably wouldn't be able to come again until you paid it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0423">I mean cos doctors they wouldn't refuse they take a an oath in this country don't they?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423">to treat anyone that needs medical assistance</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421" trans="overlap">to like erm do anything possible to like save the most lives</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0421">but yeah like you were saying in America the ambulance won't come for you if you've not got health insurance</u>
<u n="100" who="S0423">yeah it's hard to imagine anyone who's involved in the medical profession not helping somebody who needs <unclear>a bit of</unclear> assistance and I think doctors probably would it's all these people in between <unclear/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah well they like they would but then if like they help them then like who's going to pay for that?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like if you're on a plane and somebody's ill they say oh if you're travelling say oh is there a doctor around? or an emergency</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423">the doctor doesn't say well yeah I'm a doctor but I'm not treating him until after he gives me some cash</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0423">they pay they treat people don't they?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423">they try to erm do what they can for them obviously if it's not urgent then they they probably won't they'd say well go and see a doctor</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421">yeah if it's like ah I've had this ache in my eye <unclear/> like for the past month <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0423">yeah I imagine any anywhere you would think in the world that if somebody was there was an emergency then they would treat them wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421">yeah but if like say if you were like on a plane though and someone was choking like they would help them <trunc>a</trunc> or if like but if they had something that required medication like obviously they wouldn't have it with them so they wouldn't be able to</u>
<u n="112" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah there's limitations</u>
<u n="113" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0423">we're not far off now</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0423">not too bad is it? <pause dur="short"/> your grandad <unclear>and the er</unclear> for a taxi it's probably even twenty-five pound at least</u>
<u n="117" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">or he could be spending two hours to get to get over on public transport</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421">he wouldn't use public transport do you know what he did though right? cos he went to <anon type="place"/> to get that photocopier</u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0421"><trunc>ph</trunc> that thing photocopied and he went to the bus stop and erm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I was going to say he didn't get a taxi to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0421">no and no buses were coming</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0421">erm they were all going to <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="126" who="S0423" trans="overlap">did he walk?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0421">yeah walked it took him an hour and he walked</u>
<u n="128" who="S0423">yeah it's it's only a few miles isn't it? it's not very far so</u>
<u n="129" who="S0421"><vocal desc="misc"/> are you <trunc>ma</trunc>? is that like a reasonable thing? like I was like what? he walked?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0423">well yeah <unclear>right now</unclear> to <anon type="place"/> you're not that far <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0421">it's because there's not a straight bus going to <anon type="place"/> from</u>
<u n="132" who="S0423">oh really?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0421">yeah you have to change</u>
<u n="134" who="S0423">well he <trunc>co</trunc> you'd think he would have walked towards <anon type="place"/> and then picked up the bus on the way wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0421">well like he kept looking to see the other bus that come past him but it didn't</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/> I suppose it I suppose he must be feeling fit enough to do that if you're ill you wouldn't do that I don't suppose <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0421">yeah but erm I don't know because <trunc>i</trunc> he was like they couldn't see a bus so he had to walk and I was just like should have just gone to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0423">yeah well yeah <unclear/> why? why go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0421">he said he knows <anon type="place"/> a bit better than <anon type="place"/> but he could've gone to <anon type="place"/> I was just like <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos I was like why is he gone so long? cos then when he came back he was like oh yeah I found one really quick like somewhere to photocopy and oh and it's cos he walked that's why he was gone most of the day</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and how did he know where to find one?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421">he was just looking in everywhere yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0423">could've just went to the library</u>
<u n="145" who="S0421">which one?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0423">well there's one in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is there? maybe he's he</u>
<u n="148" who="S0423" trans="overlap">just you would've thought there'd be one don't know if there's one in <anon type="place"/> but you would've thought there'd be one closer than that but maybe not</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421">well because I I asked at the post office cos I asked the post office and I said do you know where I could find somewhere to photocopy?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="151" who="S0421">and she was like oh there's not really anywhere that does it now there might be a computer shop in <anon type="place"/> that does it</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421">and I was like I said that to him but he didn't want to cos he thought if he goes to <anon type="place"/> and it's not there then there</u>
<u n="154" who="S0423">he could've <unclear/> to <anon type="place"/> rather than <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0421">then there's not <trunc>mu</trunc> there's not many places in <anon type="place"/> er</u>
<u n="156" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0421">well it's the same thing</u>
<u n="158" who="S0423">it's completely different one has a D on the end and the other doesn't</u>
<u n="159" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0423">and there's a big difference in the places</u>
<u n="161" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0423">one's a big <trunc>ci</trunc> one of the biggest cities in the country</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so cos it was <anon type="place"/> is a small place so he was like oh I won't go there I'll go to <anon type="place"/> instead</u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/> yeah they used to it used to be good for photocopies cos they used to have them in all the newsagents didn't they? two P or five P</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah they've got in <anon type="place"/> they've got a <trunc>photocop</trunc> well they used to when we were there they had a photocopying one for the newsagents</u>
<u n="166" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah used to see them in most ah newsagents they must have stopped doing it they mustn't be doing so good</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421">people mustn't need it really</u>
<u n="168" who="S0423">yeah it's not a thing thing people need very commonly is it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="170" who="S0423">no <pause dur="short"/> it's a handy thing when they were in the shops <unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0421">yeah I mean you've not even got a printer</u>
<u n="172" who="S0423">erm no <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> I know I should get one but I I mean I don't need it that often and when I do I can always get stuff printed off in the library</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I suppose it might be quite dear for you to run a printer and if you're like never really</u>
<u n="174" who="S0423">yeah well no the only reason I'd get it is oh I want to start doing photos on it and printing them off and</u>
<u n="175" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh you'd get a photographic printer or photographic paper</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah that's the only one I'd get but yeah the that for a normal one it's not worth it I may as well just go to the erm library on the occasion I need it</u>
<u n="177" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0423">I want to be in the left lane I think <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0421">where is this?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0423">this is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0421">is it?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0423">don't you know <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423">you've been to <anon type="place"/> haven't you?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know of course I have but I don't recognise it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">this is a new development all this is quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423">and they have a cinema and restaurants and</u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423">so you wouldn't recognise this bit this is all new</u>
<u n="191" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but like I don't even recognise <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0423">I would've thought maybe <anon type="place"/> you might <anon type="place"/>'s changed a little bit since last time since they had the tram in made some changes</u>
<u n="193" who="S0421">I I recognise the bowling thing but other than that</u>
<u n="194" who="S0423">yeah it looks erm a bit of a mess <anon type="place"/> at the moment really erm but I think they're starting they're going to start doing something similar to that you know? a a shopping thing with shops and cinema and stuff like that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0423">so it will improve in the next few years <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> right we're just round it's just up the road from here it is <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0421">so why is it called <anon type="place"/>? this thing</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423">no it's it's not <anon type="place"/> hospital it's <anon type="place"/> old road it's on</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423">so that's where this is <anon type="place"/> so it's only up the road from <anon type="place"/> but this is <anon type="place"/> old road</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="202" who="S0423">if you go straight up that road it will lead straight to <anon type="place"/> eventually</u>
<u n="203" who="S0421">cos I was saying to grandad and he was like even after cos I was like no erm it's in <anon type="place"/> and he's like no no it's in <anon type="place"/> it says it's in <anon type="place"/> on <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="204" who="S0423">that's what he said to me coming here</u>
<u n="205" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0423">and I said no cos I had the thing here that said oh it's <anon type="place"/> road but he says no no</u>
<u n="207" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0423">it's <anon type="place"/> and I though oh right well I've I'll we'll soon find out</u>
<u n="209" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0423">cos we're going to be in the wrong place</u>
<u n="211" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0423">but it did it said cos I looked it up as well on the on online</u>
<u n="213" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0423">and it's <anon type="place"/> old road <anon type="place"/> so I don't know why your grandad is thinking <anon type="place"/> old road</u>
<u n="215" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I <trunc>kn</trunc> I <trunc>kn</trunc> I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> and he looked at it he read it to me and he was like see?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0423" trans="overlap">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0421">and he was like yeah and he was like looking at it and he was like yeah see it is <anon type="place"/> road in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0423">but did you then look at what he was reading?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no I <trunc>di</trunc> I didn't look</u>
<u n="220" who="S0423">oh okay</u>
<u n="221" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos he he had it and I was like oh right I was like <pause dur="short"/> and he was like mm was like I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0423">unless that was directions from somewhere cos there is a <anon type="place"/> old road</u>
<u n="223" who="S0421">yeah and he's like oh it doesn't matter cos if you put it in the sat nav it'll take you there and I was like yeah but but it would be good to know if you're going to <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0423">yeah cos that's what your mam said at first said it's <anon type="place"/> I said oh I <unclear/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos that's what grandad came home saying</u>
<u n="226" who="S0423">oh right but he even said it today</u>
<u n="227" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no one no one no one yeah I know and then after cos you'd looked at it and said</u>
<u n="228" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and then he gave me and I said it's <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not <anon type="place"/> and I said oh I'll take them anyway cos it's hard to get to from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0423">so</u>
<u n="231" who="S0421">but erm yeah like I even after you told us it was <anon type="place"/> and I was saying to him no no and he was like no cos I</u>
<u n="232" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0421">but you know before you'd looked at it we'd not looked at it and he just came home saying <anon type="place"/> and we were like oh right</u>
<u n="234" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right right</u>
<u n="235" who="S0421">and then he's still saying <trunc>wr</trunc> I don't know</u>
<u n="236" who="S0423">and then when we got on this road</u>
<u n="237" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0423">there's a sign saying <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0423">and he said see <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="241" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0423">yeah I just</u>
<u n="243" who="S0421">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0423" trans="overlap">gave up at that point</u>
<u n="245" who="S0421">sometimes you have to yeah they're a bit like that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0423">well here's a sign you can see it see the sign <anon type="place"/> this way</u>
<u n="247" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0423">so he must be thinking I was right it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0423">there's a sign we're going to <anon type="place"/> now but it it's up the road just outside <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah sometimes like I'm talking to them like either one of them and then they say things and I'm just like okay yes now next bit I'm <trunc>exp</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I'm too hot what am I doing with this coat on?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0421">I know I took mine off I was sensible <pause dur="short"/> even though it cost me a couple of seconds without my seatbelt on</u>
<u n="254" who="S0423">that's dangerous behaviour that is surprised at you</u>
<u n="255" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos in those couple of seconds someone was going to crash into us</u>
<u n="256" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it takes a millisecond you don't know what was going on behind you do you?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0423">some idiot all of a sudden before you know it he's in the back of you and then you'll be through the front window</u>
<u n="259" who="S0421">yeah although no cos the airbags are coming</u>
<u n="260" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> you could have black eyes and bruises from the airbag</u>
<u n="261" who="S0421">but yeah I would it I would anyway if I had my seatbelt on but yeah generally it's a good idea to wear a seatbelt</u>
<u n="262" who="S0423">you know I'm surprised listening to you defending taking it off</u>
<u n="263" who="S0421">I mean it's not the worst thing but like I I'm sure there was one person who got like strangled by their seatbelt</u>
<u n="264" who="S0423">it might have been a child and they weren't wearing a seat</u>
<u n="265" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0423">I think we're here now</u>
<u n="267" who="S0421">although on children in general it can be quite dangerous to have a seatbelt cos it can <trunc>crus</trunc>crush like your ribs and stuff</u>
<u n="268" who="S0423">yeah but it's not as dangerous as not having one</u>
<u n="269" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0423">you'd rather have crushed ribs can you imagine the damage of going through that windscreen? you'd be travelling at the same time as like the same speed as the car when you hit it</u>
<u n="271" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0423">so the car stops and if the belt doesn't stop you you're doing the same speed as the car</u>
<u n="273" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0423">you know what? I think I should've turned right back there <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0421">you know you know like if there's airbags can you go through the windscreen?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0423">not if they if they work <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah if they yeah yeah but I suppose like you would be bashed like back and forth wouldn't you? cos if you didn't have your seatbelt so</u>
<u n="278" who="S0423">oh you mean if you didn't have it would the airbags work?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0423">well well you know your momentum could possibly because you're going along at a bigger speed</u>
<u n="281" who="S0421" trans="overlap">go through the yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0423">they're they're designed really to have it on with a</u>
<u n="283" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0423">seatbelt on so you you might end up you could possibly end up bursting the <pause dur="short"/> the <unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0421" trans="overlap">do they have flour in them?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0423">no there is kind of a powder</u>
<u n="287" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0423">it's probably an explosive powder isn't it?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right great</u>
<u n="290" who="S0423">well that's cos they <trunc>i</trunc>it needs an explosion to to kind of get them open instantly doesn't it?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0421" trans="overlap">ah did you know flour is explosive?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0423">is it?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like what when you mix it with something?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0421">no when you throw it in the air like if you yeah if you I'm not sure what it is exactly but if you throw it in the air like if you burst a bag of flour</u>
<u n="296" who="S0423">oh no it is still further up I thought I should have turned further back I recognise this inn we're nearly there now if you do what?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0421" trans="overlap">if you if you burst a bag of flour and it's all in the air and there's like a a flame it'll all explode</u>
<u n="298" who="S0423">oh right if you if you have a very high flame on you?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0421" trans="overlap">there'll be an explosion not a high one you could</u>
<u n="300" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="301" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like you could do it with the stove on probably</u>
<u n="302" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="303" who="S0421">if it was close enough</u>
<u n="304" who="S0423">yeah that all like it's it means it's combustible is it?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0421">well highly combustible</u>
<u n="306" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="307" who="S0421">it is quite a <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0423">there it is do you want to phone your grandad? tell him we're at the entrance then?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0423">erm ask him</u>
<u n="311" who="S0421">I don't know what entrance it is though oh I'll just say we're at the yeah I'll know what I'll say yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just say which car park is? <trunc>sho</trunc>should we meet him in <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0421" trans="overlap">okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
