<text id="S9WP">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:19</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0081 S0090</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Student accomodation, Salford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics> Things I do not like</topics>
		<activity>Colleagues Complaining about Things they do not Like</activity>
		<conv_type>Complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0081">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Manchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North West</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years, 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Security Officer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0090">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Manchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North West</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Atherton, Somerset</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Resident Life Support Officer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0081">so what don't you like about this job?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0090">the hours <pause dur="short"/> the shifts <pause dur="short"/> working overnight <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> the rain <pause dur="short"/> it's raining <pause dur="short"/> what about you? </u>
<u n="3" who="S0081">but you stay inside all the time it's raining</u>
<u n="4" who="S0090">no but when it's raining you can guarantee you've got to be outside most of the shift <pause dur="short"/> like somebody will cut their finger or drink too much alcohol or I don't know go crazy <pause dur="short"/> what don't you like about your job?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0081">em <pause dur="short"/> I don't have a company I work for <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> I get on alright with most of the guards <pause dur="short"/> can be a bit trying sometimes but <pause dur="short"/> that's with all people <pause dur="short"/> em the students can be a pain</u>
<u n="6" who="S0090">true <pause dur="short"/> I didn't mention the students <pause dur="short"/> but they can be</u>
<u n="7" who="S0081">that's cos you're being diplomatic</u>
<u n="8" who="S0090">no but sometimes they're alright <pause dur="short"/> like they're more alright than not usually</u>
<u n="9" who="S0081">yeah there are some nice ones yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0090">em <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> still doesn't stop me hating the shifts</u>
<u n="11" who="S0081">shifts I'm not too bad about nights <pause dur="short"/> not too bad <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't mind a few weekends off but it's just one of those</u>
<u n="12" who="S0090">I get a week a weekend off every four weeks so it's not too bad <pause dur="short"/> but I always hate the fact that everybody else seems to be working when I'm off</u>
<u n="13" who="S0081">always the way</u>
<u n="14" who="S0090">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0081">I can't remember the last time I've been out</u>
<u n="16" who="S0090">so what do you hate about the students then?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0081">em they're goby mouthed <pause dur="short"/> em the lack of respect <pause dur="short"/> em their reluctance to just do a simple task like signing this visitors in <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> mainly being mouthy an unpleasant sometimes</u>
<u n="18" who="S0090">are they the kind of things that annoy you about normal people as well? Like the general public</u>
<u n="19" who="S0081">yeah but the students as well I don't like them lying to me</u>
<u n="20" who="S0090">right</u>
<u n="21" who="S0081">I find lying very disrespectful and I don't do it to them so don't be doing it to me</u>
<u n="22" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hate liars as well <pause dur="short"/> like obvious liars as well that you're just like why are you saying that? When it's clearly not true?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0081">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they don't seem to realise that you've been here like a couple of years and you've heard all these lies over and over and over again <pause dur="short"/> you're not the first so</u>
<u n="24" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not clever <pause dur="short"/> not inventive at all <pause dur="short"/> sometimes if it's a bit of a more of an inventive lie I think that's quite funny really <pause dur="short"/> so what do you hate in general? Like what would be your most hated thing like out of work</u>
<u n="25" who="S0081">out of work <pause dur="short"/> em mainly just stupid people</u>
<u n="26" who="S0090">I hate stupid people too</u>
<u n="27" who="S0081">I don't pay fools <pause dur="short"/> I don't suffer fools</u>
<u n="28" who="S0090">I hate my neighbours <pause dur="short"/> every single one of them</u>
<u n="29" who="S0081">should move</u>
<u n="30" who="S0090">I would do if I could afford it <pause dur="short"/> absolutely every one of them <pause dur="short"/> especially the guy that got speed bump put put in the road the other day</u>
<u n="31" who="S0081">he got them put it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0090">well I don't know if it's him but em he mentioned it at the residents meeting <pause dur="short"/> that's how weird my neighbours are <pause dur="short"/> and all of a sudden we've got three speed bumps to get out the road <pause dur="short"/> it's like about a hundred meters <pause dur="short"/> it's only a cul-de-sac <pause dur="short"/> you can <unclear/> bumps <pause dur="short"/> so I hate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at number four <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know where number four is</u>
<u n="33" who="S0081">I'm going to say it's near the beginning of the close</u>
<u n="34" who="S0090">yeah I've never see number four <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I still hate him <pause dur="short"/> I hate quite a lot of people <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a people person you see</u>
<u n="35" who="S0081">so what do you do <unclear/>? Are they retiling it or are they just going to have that one tile that's <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0090">why what are they doing?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0081">have you not seen it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0090">no</u>
<u n="39" who="S0081">well you know as you go in? And you've got the girls on the right and you had that like kiosk thing</u>
<u n="40" who="S0090">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0081">that's all gone <pause dur="short"/> the girls all the toilets have been ripped out <pause dur="short"/> em I think they're going to retile it but Rob was saying the he doesn't reckon they are <pause dur="short"/> cos I've seen packs of tiles in there so I assumed they were going to retile it and then do the same to the boys <pause dur="short"/> so I didn't see the point of it <pause dur="short"/> it's only what? Another two years on the site?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0090">yeah I would say there's no point in doing anything to the Pav <pause dur="short"/> only like maybe like a lick of paint for when the parents come</u>
<u n="43" who="S0081">plus they're only students <pause dur="short"/> hardly any of them use it so</u>
<u n="44" who="S0090">no it's only when we have the Pav parties isn't it? And then</u>
<u n="45" who="S0081">in fact they're the ones who make a mess in the place anyway so</u>
<u n="46" who="S0090">yeah usually sick in there and stuff and we get</u>
<u n="47" who="S0081">plus plus the mainly the lads though <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what they do <pause dur="short"/> some of them can't even flush the toilet <pause dur="short"/> it's sad</u>
<u n="48" who="S0090">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> it's cos a lot of the time they don't live in the real world that's what it is</u>
<u n="49" who="S0081">maybe they get mummy and daddy to push the toilet for them</u>
<u n="50" who="S0090">I think my brothers would if they could <pause dur="short"/> I always think my brothers are kind of almost like the students are here you know that that come in the first year and like mum and dad do everything for them <pause dur="short"/> only they're older <pause dur="short"/> so it's worse</u>
<u n="51" who="S0081">I don't even like <pause dur="short"/> I don't like getting molly cuddled by my mother <unclear/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0090">I never did cos I was the oldest so I really didn't get much choice</u>
<u n="53" who="S0081">ah I'm the youngest <pause dur="short"/> and the only boy</u>
<u n="54" who="S0090" trans="overlap">spoilt <pause dur="short"/> and the only boy <pause dur="short"/> bet you're well spoilt</u>
<u n="55" who="S0081">by my ma yeah I'd say I was <pause dur="short"/> I'd say she pampers me too much</u>
<u n="56" who="S0090">how many sisters you got?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0081">three <pause dur="short"/> all older <pause dur="short"/> all uglier</u>
<u n="58" who="S0090">I'm obviously the most beautiful one of the four of us <pause dur="short"/> not really <pause dur="short"/> but the boys do get treated lot better than the girls I think <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know that's because they're the two youngest</u>
<u n="59" who="S0081">I read em girls get on better with their mums though than lads <pause dur="short"/> they seem to have some sort of connection</u>
<u n="60" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think my mum realised how lucky she was to have daughters until we both moved out <pause dur="short"/> and now I think she wants us to move back in but I'm a bit too old for that really <pause dur="short"/> although I'd love to <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="61" who="S0081">you'd have to take your boyfriend with you wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I could leave him at mine <pause dur="short"/> move out without him</u>
<u n="63" who="S0081">do that then</u>
<u n="64" who="S0090">what just leave him to his own devices? Wouldn't have a house to go back to if I wanted to</u>
<u n="65" who="S0081">have you noticed that twenty minutes drags</u>
<u n="66" who="S0090">not before <pause dur="short"/> you never realised how boring I am before either <pause dur="short"/> it's just like <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe anybody speaks to me <pause dur="short"/> sometimes <pause dur="short"/> it's awful <pause dur="short"/> trying to think of other things I hate <pause dur="short"/> don't like dogs <pause dur="short"/> don't like dogs barking <pause dur="short"/> don't like the sun</u>
<u n="67" who="S0081">I love the sun</u>
<u n="68" who="S0090">do you?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0081">more sun is what we need</u>
<u n="70" who="S0090">we don't last week was too much</u>
<u n="71" who="S0081">no I get depressed if I don't get sun</u>
<u n="72" who="S0090">ah have you got that SAD thing?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0081">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0090">I've got the opposite of that I don't think it's been discovered yet but I definitely have got the opposite</u>
<u n="75" who="S0081">well <unclear/> she just made it up <pause dur="short"/> right I'll just <unclear/> forward</u>
<u n="76" who="S0090">didn't make it up <pause dur="short"/> I could say that SAD's made up <pause dur="short"/> but they have light boxes and everything of it don't they? So</u>
<u n="77" who="S0081">I don't get them <pause dur="short"/> you got a light switch and <unclear/> you need a light box</u>
<u n="78" who="S0090">sit in front of a light</u>
<u n="79" who="S0081">it's still an artificial light at the end of the day</u>
<u n="80" who="S0090">true</u>
<u n="81" who="S0081">the sight of the sun <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>bri</trunc> well brings me joy <pause dur="short"/> where a light that simulates sunlight is excuse me is just a light simulating sunlight</u>
<u n="82" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> apparently it does make people feel better <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="83" who="S0081">get out more that's what I say <pause dur="short"/> or move to somewhere where it's sunny all the time</u>
<u n="84" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah no I couldn't cope <pause dur="short"/> it's cos I'm too fair <pause dur="short"/> the sun doesn't like me and I don't like it</u>
<u n="85" who="S0081">sun doesn't like me <pause dur="short"/> always burns me <pause dur="short"/> I'm pretty fair</u>
<u n="86" who="S0090">yeah but</u>
<u n="87" who="S0081">I don't even tan <pause dur="short"/> never gone brown in my life</u>
<u n="88" who="S0090">no I don't tan <pause dur="short"/> I just look like one big freckle <pause dur="short"/> or one big rash depending on what it decides <pause dur="short"/> what else don't <pause dur="short"/> what else don't you like? I think I'm really miserable so you've got to</u>
<u n="89" who="S0081">I like everything I'm such an outgoing loving person <pause dur="short"/> always got a smile on my face</u>
<u n="90" who="S0090">there must be something you really don't like</u>
<u n="91" who="S0081">em</u>
<u n="92" who="S0090">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> scousers or something</u>
<u n="93" who="S0081">I've never had a problem with scousers <pause dur="short"/> I mean gads can get a bit annoying sometimes but I've never really had anything against scousers <pause dur="short"/> just the goby ones the braggers <pause dur="short"/> which that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is but</u>
<u n="94" who="S0090">it's his age as well</u>
<u n="95" who="S0081">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but he's still a bragger</u>
<u n="96" who="S0090">can't believe you don't like not like anything</u>
<u n="97" who="S0081">there's loads of things I don't like</u>
<u n="98" who="S0090">go on</u>
<u n="99" who="S0081">I don't like peppers</u>
<u n="100" who="S0090">do you not? That's weird</u>
<u n="101" who="S0081">can't stand it <pause dur="short"/> the devil's fruit</u>
<u n="102" who="S0090">all colours of peppers?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0081">Don't like spicy food <pause dur="short"/> don't like <pause dur="short"/> I don't like certain nationalities of people</u>
<u n="104" who="S0090">that's em</u>
<u n="105" who="S0081">no I don't like the jocks let's face it <pause dur="short"/> they don't like me I don't like them</u>
<u n="106" who="S0090">I like people in the north-west and that's almost it <pause dur="short"/> it's that kind of thing</u>
<u n="107" who="S0081">even some of those can be annoying</u>
<u n="108" who="S0090">yeah true <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a people person <pause dur="short"/> is that it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0081">em <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a big fan of R and B cos I don't see it as rhythm and blues <pause dur="short"/> maybe rhythm but there's no blues there <pause dur="short"/> you can't be singing the blues if some girl's going at you cos you've been cheating on her <pause dur="short"/> that is not the blues that's just being cut out for being a naughty boy</u>
<u n="110" who="S0090">I don't like R and B either <pause dur="short"/> I don't like anything by Lady Gaga cos she's a nutter <pause dur="short"/> she's not even that good <pause dur="short"/> what about when you're driving what do you hate when you're driving?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0081">other drivers full stop</u>
<u n="112" who="S0090">other drivers <pause dur="short"/> any drivers in particular? Probably drivers that are like me</u>
<u n="113" who="S0081">just anyone who's on the road in front of me <pause dur="short"/> why is he just get out my way and I'll be fucking sweet <pause dur="short"/> I hate when people at traffic lights the light turns it's like these ones you know on Popper Park?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0090">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0081">right? They're only green for like seconds and I mean literally seconds</u>
<u n="116" who="S0090">yeah they are they're not very long are they?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0081">right? And people are just sat there dozying <pause dur="short"/> like there's about five cars length from the car in front of them pulled away and the they decide to pull away <pause dur="short"/> so I might squeeze through but there's like five other people who could have got through who didn't get through just cos they're dozy and can't pay attention</u>
<u n="118" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I had an accident once because the person in front of me didn't set off as quick as I thought he should of and I ran into the back of him <pause dur="short"/> so I think technically I was in the right even though it went down as my fault cos I hit him <pause dur="short"/> well he should have been paying attention</u>
<u n="119" who="S0081">I would have hit him in the face <pause dur="short"/> soon as he got out the car <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0090">it was  it was  a BSM one a school of motoring thing <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't like a learner so <pause dur="short"/> he still can't be forgiven <pause dur="short"/> and it was rush hour so you've got to be in a rush</u>
<u n="121" who="S0081">yeah what what's that about let's go ad take somebody em on their first driving lesson right in the middle of rush hour</u>
<u n="122" who="S0090">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I hate learner drivers <pause dur="short"/> they've just opened like the new like driving test thing near my house like just round the corner <pause dur="short"/> so it's full of learners all the time just like swarming <pause dur="short"/> sometimes you can be behind about three or four of them</u>
<u n="123" who="S0081">see I don't actually mind learner drivers <pause dur="short"/> I just don't like their instructors taking them out at stupid o'clock in the <trunc>after</trunc> or evening <pause dur="short"/> when people are trying to get home through rush hour traffic <pause dur="short"/> which they're already stressed they've had a long day at work they don't want to</u>
<u n="124" who="S0090">Don't want to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0081">Don't want to be sat in a car They certainly don't want to be sat behind somebody at a traffic lights who stalls their car like three or four times <pause dur="short"/> because some instructor decides oh let's go out on a rush hour and get you all stressed</u>
<u n="126" who="S0090">shouldn't really go out in rush hour until they're like almost ready for the test</u>
<u n="127" who="S0081">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0090">when they're like almost like a normal driver</u>
<u n="129" who="S0081">or if that's the only time they can do it take them down quiet roads don't take them down the busiest roads you can find</u>
<u n="130" who="S0090">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hated learning to drive as well <pause dur="short"/> that's another thing I hated <pause dur="short"/> cos I found it really difficult cos I'm not a natural driver <pause dur="short"/> I hate driving</u>
<u n="131" who="S0081">never looked forward to mine <pause dur="short"/> it was coming up to like you know this day and it was like oh got twenty minutes more <trunc>twent</trunc> didn't like that <pause dur="short"/> but as soon as I got in the car I was happy as Larry <pause dur="short"/> then again I had a really fit instructor</u>
<u n="132" who="S0090">did you choose her because of that?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0081">no <pause dur="short"/> she's not chose me more than anything <pause dur="short"/> no just the luck of the draw</u>
<u n="134" who="S0090">my driving instructor wasn't fit <pause dur="short"/> he was the dad of one of my friends from high school <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> is that? What else I don't like? I don't like sand <pause dur="short"/> I don't like beaches <pause dur="short"/> I'm really miserable aren't I?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0081">I like sand I like snow I like beaches I like mountains</u>
<u n="136" who="S0090">I like mountains and waterfalls and like countryside things</u>
<u n="137" who="S0081">I don't really like cities though</u>
<u n="138" who="S0090">no I don't like cities I don't like <unclear/> like I don't like London <pause dur="short"/> surprise surprise I don't like something</u>
<u n="139" who="S0081">nobody likes London up north</u>
<u n="140" who="S0090">no <pause dur="short"/> it's too busy and it's really dirty and people are rude <pause dur="short"/> it's really expensive <pause dur="short"/> and it just feels rubbish <pause dur="short"/> proper manky</u>
<u n="141" who="S0081">I think it is quite manky</u>
<u n="142" who="S0090">I'd much prefer being like countryside way <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="143" who="S0090">see that's what I like about Manchester <pause dur="short"/> you got a little bit of the city and then you've got the countryside right on the doorstep <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to go far <pause dur="short"/> or you can just look outside the actual city boundaries and pretty much any</u>
<u n="144" who="S0081">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what I like about where I live cos it's nearer to Bolton but like really near the west Pennine moors <pause dur="short"/> like there's all like farm fields up next to my housing estate and stuff <pause dur="short"/> so it's a lot nicer <pause dur="short"/> but I'm definite close to the motorway <pause dur="short"/> to get to like the seaside and stuff</u>
<u n="145" who="S0090">see that's what I think you should do with <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> have a big ocean and Manchester's got a beach seaside <pause dur="short"/> just go go up like towards that Busby way and you get to the top there and then like <anon type="place"/> where all that would be just stop it all flooding nice big  sea <pause dur="short"/> we'd have a beach and everything would be great</u>
<u n="146" who="S0081">who was it that said was it Ian Brown? Did he say that the only thing missing from Manchester is a beach <pause dur="short"/> so like like bomb Liverpool or something so the</u>
<u n="147" who="S0090">Liverpool is a bit too far away <pause dur="short"/> I think he was just being anti-scouser there <pause dur="short"/> I say just flood <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> a lot easier</u>
<u n="148" who="S0081">I'm half from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> my dad's from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0090">yeah but you're from over that way somewhere aren't you? Quay it wouldn't affect you flooding the quays</u>
<u n="150" who="S0081">yeah I don't live in <anon type="place"/> now cos my mum doesn't live in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> she's s snob</u>
<u n="151" who="S0090">plus the bit which would be flooded s only like where the Lowry is and all you know media city <pause dur="short"/> they're not important <pause dur="short"/> and the houses which are there are just full of scumbags so that's not important <pause dur="short"/> you don't even have to tell them we're flooding it just</u>
<u n="152" who="S0081">just get rid of them through</u>
<u n="153" who="S0090">brick them in and flood the place</u>
<u n="154" who="S0081">what <unclear/> are the nice places I think <pause dur="short"/> it's really close to get to like north Wales and stuff like that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0090"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="156" who="S0081">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0090">not that there's anything in <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="158" who="S0081">no but I like <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> they've got at the end of the pier they've got like this amusement thing that's like all the amusements and you <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> and thingy <pause dur="short"/> you get <unclear/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0090">no but it's all tokens now <pause dur="short"/> you can't just pay <pause dur="short"/> you got to buy all these tokens just to go on all the rides</u>
<u n="160" who="S0081">yeah but they're old pennies so it's the whole feel of it <pause dur="short"/> like being kind of I don't know Victorian or whatever</u>
<u n="161" who="S0090">they're not old pennies <pause dur="short"/> they're just tokens last time I went</u>
<u n="162" who="S0081">the one at the end of the peer?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0090">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0081">they were pennies last time I went like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0090">when was that?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0081">not long ago <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> last year</u>
<u n="167" who="S0090">I've been last year and it was tokens</u>
<u n="168" who="S0081">I think they were pennies <pause dur="short"/> old pennies</u>
<u n="169" who="S0090">I didn't get any so I wouldn't know <pause dur="short"/> he just said oh you've got to get tokens so I said ooh sod that <pause dur="short"/> but it's the same at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you can't just you used to be able to go and pay just for one particular ride now it's all tokens and <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0081">I've been to the on the rides at <anon type="place"/> for ages <pause dur="short"/> about eight years</u>
<u n="171" who="S0090">yeah I fell out of them when they got rid of the <unclear/> and put in the em some stupid fan <unclear/> yeah some Viking ride</u>
<u n="172" who="S0081">is that that <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0090">yeah <anon type="place"/> something like that</u>
<u n="174" who="S0081">I went on that <pause dur="short"/> the boat sank <pause dur="short"/> not cos I was in it <pause dur="short"/> it just sank anyway</u>
<u n="175" who="S0090">we went on it and it was like everyone was buying all those you know rain things to keep you dry <pause dur="short"/> me and my mate just went on there <pause dur="short"/> we go a little bit wet <pause dur="short"/> so all we did was went to the pub which is right next to it and sat in the sun and dried off <pause dur="short"/> instead of paying two pound for a piece of plastic that you can get in Benidorm or something for thirty P</u>
<u n="176" who="S0081">yeah see when I went with my sister it was raining all day anyway <pause dur="short"/> so we were absolutely soaking <pause dur="short"/> so sinking on the <anon type="place"/> ride wasn't any different <pause dur="short"/> but the queues were deal quick <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> went on</u>
<u n="177" who="S0090">that suddenly reminds me of that the ride <pause dur="short"/> it's the <trunc>Ma</trunc> Mouse <pause dur="short"/> which was basically you just got on this like boat sort of thing and it just went around on a track inside these caves</u>
<u n="178" who="S0081">oh yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0090">I've only been on it once and not great</u>
<u n="180" who="S0081">it was just a boat wasn't it? Wasn't anything exciting <pause dur="short"/> no I used to  I used to  really like the log flute and the big one <pause dur="short"/> and the mouse one</u>
<u n="181" who="S0090">bad mouse</u>
<u n="182" who="S0081">I never felt safe on it though</u>
<u n="183" who="S0090">what the mad mouse?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0081">no</u>
<u n="185" who="S0090">no? People have died on that</u>
<u n="186" who="S0081">have they?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0090">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0081">oh I didn't know that</u>
<u n="189" who="S0090">it's only like rickety wooden things and before health and safety became a big issue yeah <pause dur="short"/> people used to come that</u>
<u n="190" who="S0081">I didn't know that <pause dur="short"/> is the Grand National still there?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0090">I used to like that <pause dur="short"/> I like the big big one <pause dur="short"/> whatever it's called <pause dur="short"/> is it called the big one?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0081">we used to call it Pepsi Max big lift</u>
<u n="193" who="S0090">oh yeah they didn't they?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0081">t's alright <pause dur="short"/> I've never been on the front and that's where you want to be really on the form</u>
<u n="195" who="S0090">I think I'll <unclear/> on one like that</u>
<u n="196" who="S0081">I think that's still there <pause dur="short"/> but the <trunc>wo</trunc> the woman who eh thingy she's sold it now the one who used to own it</u>
<u n="197" who="S0090">oh has she <pause dur="short"/> cos it was family <unclear/> a family owned thing</u>
<u n="198" who="S0081">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0090"><unclear/> she died <pause dur="short"/> she was very old</u>
<u n="200" who="S0081">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0090">I was there once and seeing her in a big Rolls Royce</u>
<u n="202" who="S0081">it's the only thing worth going to in Blackpool really</u>
<u n="203" who="S0090">there's the tower</u>
<u n="204" who="S0081">I've never been up the tower</u>
<u n="205" who="S0090">should do it's good</u>
<u n="206" who="S0081">is it? Oh and the lights the lights are good</u>
<u n="207" who="S0090">well they don't have the circus there anymore</u>
<u n="208" who="S0081">no</u>
<u n="209" who="S0090">by the tower which is a shame</u>
</body>
</text>
