<text id="S9WZ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:11:18</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0517 S0558</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Family home, Fradley)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>House auction and improvements, friends’ lives, Holland, sister and baby, mice in the house, work experience</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting over coffee.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0517">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sutton Coldfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Self employed - marketing &amp; Proofing services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- working knowledge; German -- Working knowledge</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0558">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Sales Rep/ Lunchtime Supervisor</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0517">so I wanted to know what's happening next door did it not get sold at the auction?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="3" who="S0517">cos I see there's a big auction sign back up</u>
<u n="4" who="S0558">yeah so it didn't go the best the guide price was one sixty-seven</u>
<u n="5" who="S0517">yes which you said was way too much didn't you?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0558" trans="overlap">ridiculous</u>
<u n="7" who="S0517">bit of land that size?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0558">so somebody had obviously made an offer that was the last bid price which</u>
<u n="9" who="S0517">oh oh</u>
<u n="10" who="S0558" trans="overlap">they didn't accept erm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0517">oh well you er <trunc>t</trunc> can they not just put a reserve price on where it has to be</u>
<u n="12" who="S0558">I think it was guide price one six seven</u>
<u n="13" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0558">so er so but that was I suppose it's a guide price isn't it? but they've put it up haven't they for two hundred thousand</u>
<u n="15" who="S0517">oh god</u>
<u n="16" who="S0558" trans="overlap">which is ridiculous I mean for christ's sake</u>
<u n="17" who="S0517" trans="overlap">did anybody bid do you know? did you go? cos you were talking about going</u>
<u n="18" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well there there was a price of one seven on the on the information if you go online</u>
<u n="19" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0558">and look I think there's a price of one seventy-seven</u>
<u n="21" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0558">so erm obviously they didn't accept that so it's at that was over at <anon type="place"/> auction's I mean why would you go all the way</u>
<u n="23" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0558" trans="overlap">to <anon type="place"/> auction do you think?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0517">it was December wasn't it?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0558" trans="overlap">don't know</u>
<u n="27" who="S0517">cos I remember you said you were thinking of</u>
<u n="28" who="S0558">yeah yeah we were thinking of</u>
<u n="29" who="S0517">going along yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0558">this one as at Derby</u>
<u n="31" who="S0517">oh when's the next one then?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0558">twenty-third of February I think</u>
<u n="33" who="S0517">I wonder how long they'll like hang on before they accept a</u>
<u n="34" who="S0558">well I don't know I don't know</u>
<u n="35" who="S0517">gosh</u>
<u n="36" who="S0558">because they've only got twelve months left of the planning permission</u>
<u n="37" who="S0517">right so somebody's got to</u>
<u n="38" who="S0558" trans="overlap">because it expires</u>
<u n="39" who="S0517">buy it and build it and get sorted and</u>
<u n="40" who="S0558">and er yeah within that twelve months otherwise they've got to start again I mean if you if you were buying it for the plot and the location and all the rest of it to be honest I don't think the fact that plans were about to expire would</u>
<u n="41" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="42" who="S0558">overly concern me because it's highly unlikely they're gonna say no next time round when permission has been given</u>
<u n="43" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0558">so that wouldn't concern me too much erm but it is obviously something that <trunc>nee</trunc> you know it's gotta be in your thought process hasn't it really?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0517">you wouldn't just buy that</u>
<u n="46" who="S0558">just</u>
<u n="47" who="S0517">you wouldn't just buy that without intending to buy would <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>b</trunc> er build you'd just</u>
<u n="48" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh no no you'd only buy it with the intent to build but it wouldn't be too much if</u>
<u n="49" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="50" who="S0558">the existing plans</u>
<u n="51" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="52" who="S0558">had expired</u>
<u n="53" who="S0517">but it's still a lot isn't it? cos even when you've built your house on that</u>
<u n="54" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="55" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I mean it's such a small plot you're not gonna get a massive amount of money you're not gonna get the return I wouldn't have thought</u>
<u n="56" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="57" who="S0517">and I don't know how much it costs</u>
<u n="58" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="59" who="S0517">to build a house but</u>
<u n="60" who="S0558">I think you're talking fifty fifty-sixty thousand pounds to build a house</u>
<u n="61" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to build it but then you've got to kit it out</u>
<u n="62" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0517">I mean that you'll</u>
<u n="64" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0517">you'll double that again won't you by the time</u>
<u n="66" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0517">you've put in your kitchen and your bathroom or your furniture so I just don't see how</u>
<u n="68" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and there's a lot of</u>
<u n="69" who="S0517">they're gonna get the</u>
<u n="70" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="71" who="S0517" trans="overlap">return on it</u>
<u n="72" who="S0558">there's a lot of work involved because they've got to lower the land haven't they?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0517" trans="overlap">lower it yes yeah all those conditions well got to</u>
<u n="74" who="S0558">lower the land</u>
<u n="75" who="S0517">oh so the next one's February</u>
<u n="76" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0517">wait and see then</u>
<u n="78" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I think it's the twenty-third of Feb so we'll have to see go online just after and see if it's sold</u>
<u n="79" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0558">or whatever</u>
<u n="81" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh is that what you did last time?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0558">yeah if yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="84" who="S0558">just go on and it it it gives you information of all the plots that are available or were available and</u>
<u n="85" who="S0517">oh right</u>
<u n="86" who="S0558">and you know so you can</u>
<u n="87" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and what they went for?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0558">go on and have a look yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="90" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="92" who="S0558">yeah I know and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she <trunc>frighte</trunc> well frightened the life you know when somebody takes the wind out of your sails and you're like</u>
<u n="93" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0558">I phoned her up the other day and erm I said to her erm I texted to say I'll phone you tomorrow blah so I phoned she phoned me up half an hour before I was going to phone her and said er oh I'm only phoning you to tell you I've come home but I've gotta go straight back out I won't be here at half two erm I'll catch are you in tonight? I said no I think it was something Avon or something I said I'll speak to you tomorrow so she said I've got loads to tell you</u>
<u n="95" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0558">so she phoned me the following day and I I was doing like a couple of hours of admin but I shortly before that I text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to say I'd sent her an email and she wanted to discuss it I was working from home and the phone rang and I thought it might be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> anyway it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I said oh I said I'm just sort of midway through my admin can I call you back in half an hour when I've finished because otherwise</u>
<u n="97" who="S0517">you won't get it done</u>
<u n="98" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I'm <unclear/> and that's gonna be the</u>
<u n="99" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0558">go yeah yeah yeah no problem she said and er I said no actually oh no said yeah no problem but I'm going out</u>
<u n="101" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="102" who="S0558">make it tonight</u>
<u n="103" who="S0517">who'd have thought it was that difficult to arrange a phone conversation?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I know she said make it tonight and I said we're doing Avon tonight I said</u>
<u n="105" who="S0517">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="106" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so erm it'll have to be tomorrow so I puts the phone I down I thought gonna have to phone her now and I cos it's not gonna happen so I phoned her back and I said right okay I've clocked off let's talk now and I'll return to that</u>
<u n="107" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0558">afterwards I said so what have you got to tell me then? she went I'm having a baby</u>
<u n="109" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with the grown up children?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0558">and I went</u>
<u n="111" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no way</u>
<u n="112" who="S0558">what? and she went I'm having a baby and I went but well ah you're fostering</u>
<u n="113" who="S0517">oh is she?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she went no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0517">adopting?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I'm having a baby and I went</u>
<u n="117" who="S0517">a puppy</u>
<u n="118" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well your baby? and she went yeah and I went well how? so she starts laughing <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I went you're not you're winding me up aren't you? you're winding me up and she went no I'm not having a baby really and I went oh my god</u>
<u n="119" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh my goodness what a relief</u>
<u n="120" who="S0558">I said where's that come from? so she starts laughing she said oh I have got something to tell you she said I've been avoid talking to you</u>
<u n="121" who="S0517" trans="overlap">a <trunc>gran</trunc> a <trunc>grand</trunc> a <trunc>grand</trunc></u>
<u n="122" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="123" who="S0517" trans="overlap">child no?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0558">I said that grandchild I said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they're having a baby? she went no and er cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend and they've been together a while and she practically lives there</u>
<u n="125" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="126" who="S0558">she said no no no she said I'm playing you up and er I said to her er well what's this you've got to tell me then? she said well I've been avoiding talking to you she said because I wouldn't be able to talk to you and not tell you I went go on then tell me she said I'm moving to <anon type="place"/> and I went</u>
<u n="127" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> up here?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0558">yeah I went why?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0517" trans="overlap">from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0558">yeah I said why? I said has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> been made redundant? cos you know he's part of this big</u>
<u n="131" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0558"><anon type="place"/> she said no she said what it is she said I haven't wanted to tell you she said because we said a few years ago we were moving to <anon type="place"/> and then we didn't</u>
<u n="133" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0558">she said erm what it is is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they've put out voluntary redundancies and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s requested it but they've</u>
<u n="135" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how old is he?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is same age as us I think he might be a year</u>
<u n="137" who="S0517">late</u>
<u n="138" who="S0558">a year or two</u>
<u n="139" who="S0517" trans="overlap">late fifties or</u>
<u n="140" who="S0558">older than</u>
<u n="141" who="S0517" trans="overlap">er sort of forties fifty oh</u>
<u n="142" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no yeah year or two older than me</u>
<u n="143" who="S0517" trans="overlap">gosh <vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0558">a year older maybe I dunno one or two erm so he's requested voluntary redundancy and they've said no you know they <trunc>d</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="145" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="146" who="S0558">he's too important to lose type of thing but erm whilst he'd put in for this request he's been putting the feelers out and he's been offered a job working at the company in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0558">it's a family business the guy who one of the family members works there but the guy who is kind of like manager of the of the depot branch wherever it is company used to work with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="150" who="S0558">so this guy approached <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and said look I wanna sort of like take a sort of you know a bit of a <trunc>s</trunc> a step out and</u>
<u n="151" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0558">go just a couple of days a week and be like the chief exec so I'm kind of overseeing it all but I'm only coming in one or two days a week so I need someone to run the company and you're my man I want you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so he's like oh oh all this and that so anyway he's accepted it</u>
<u n="153" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0558">erm they're happy to wait you know however long it takes if it's six eight twelve months they'll assist him with the move although they haven't actually said financially</u>
<u n="155" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="156" who="S0558">it may just be impatience you know</u>
<u n="157" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0558">well however long it takes blah I don't know</u>
<u n="159" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0558">erm so the only thing is is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't want to come which you can understand cos they're established in <anon type="place"/> aren't they?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at erm university still? no she's finished</u>
<u n="162" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no she's finished uni erm she hasn't got herself a proper job yet but she's doing a sports massage course now</u>
<u n="163" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="164" who="S0558">and</u>
<u n="165" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and has she got a boyfriend?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0558">no she hasn't had a boyfriend</u>
<u n="167" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a girlfriend</u>
<u n="168" who="S0558">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a girlfriend</u>
<u n="169" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah I can understand why they wouldn't want to</u>
<u n="170" who="S0558">yeah they used to go they used to go to school together and I think it was when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in his second year at uni through social media and everything</u>
<u n="171" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0558">they you know they managed to meet up</u>
<u n="173" who="S0517" trans="overlap">got back in touch yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0558">got in touch all that sort of thing and they've been together ever since so and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> practically lives there you know shame for her poor mum <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said</u>
<u n="175" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the</u>
<u n="176" who="S0558">I keep inviting her mum to tea cos I feel awful</u>
<u n="177" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did she say</u>
<u n="178" who="S0558" trans="overlap">cos she's here all the time and since they've finished university cos she used to just on the holiday she'd spend all her time with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at their house</u>
<u n="179" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0558">and hardly see her mum and like you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0517" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0558">now that they've actually finished she's she's doing the same again she's I said so has she as good as moved in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? she went well yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="184" who="S0558">and I mean oh god how much her mum feel? she must</u>
<u n="185" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is her mum on her own?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0558">still I still keep inviting her for tea erm no got she's got a son who lives at home</u>
<u n="187" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0558">but she's divorced</u>
<u n="189" who="S0517">right oh gosh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum and dad split up so erm so yeah I mean they're close</u>
<u n="191" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0558">they're close you know and they meet for coffee and that sort of thing</u>
<u n="193" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but</u>
<u n="194" who="S0558">but she's kind of living</u>
<u n="195" who="S0517" trans="overlap">not the same so oh so they they're gonna stay</u>
<u n="196" who="S0558">so</u>
<u n="197" who="S0517">so where will they live?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't wanna come so what they're going to do they're really really hoping <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets redundancy</u>
<u n="199" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0558">because with the money they can pay off the uni debts and not the kids' uni debts the uni debts <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have incurred</u>
<u n="201" who="S0517" trans="overlap">have they still got those?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0558">through supporting them</u>
<u n="203" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0558">I mean they've been running <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s car for her haven't they?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0558">putting petrol in it all the time three hundred and fifty pound a month no three hundred pound a month to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> three hundred and fifty pound a month to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0517">yeah it's a lot</u>
<u n="208" who="S0558">extra year for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so they have incurred over the time</u>
<u n="209" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0558">like you know debt so they wanna pay that off and they want to give a deposit for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> officially in name to have a house</u>
<u n="211" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0558">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will live there as well</u>
<u n="213" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="214" who="S0558">now I don't know but I just think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s making a mistake</u>
<u n="215" who="S0517">I'd give them separate amounts to use as a</u>
<u n="216" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0517">deposit towards their own houses</u>
<u n="218" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0517">cos otherwise that's just gonna get messy down the line isn't it?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0558" trans="overlap">it's gonna get messy isn't it? cos she said if they decide to go their separate ways then they can sort it then cos I said so what's gonna happen? is is it like that you'll give them the deposit but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's up to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then to to fund the mortgage? and she said yeah I said and the the bills et cetera are cut three ways? and she said yeah she said and then if they wanna go their own ways then they sort it</u>
<u n="221" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0558">but I'm thinking to myself gonna be awfully young to potentially have to be buying out like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0517">the other one and</u>
<u n="224" who="S0558" trans="overlap">seventy thousand pounds or whatever</u>
<u n="225" who="S0517"><vocal desc="sigh"/> absolutely and then there's all that</u>
<u n="226" who="S0558">and there's</u>
<u n="227" who="S0517">so they'd have to choose together which house they're going to buy</u>
<u n="228" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0517">decide how they want to decorate it I mean that's a married couple thing that's not a brother and sister thing</u>
<u n="230" who="S0558">exactly</u>
<u n="231" who="S0517">and and the brother's girlfriend</u>
<u n="232" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="233" who="S0517">I mean that's just not</u>
<u n="234" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said what if sort of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos of being <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend and all the rest of it starts sort like just being as she would in any house but like doing things for her and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0517" trans="overlap">things yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0558">and all the rest of it? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to be kind of a a <trunc>sp</trunc></u>
<u n="237" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the spare part</u>
<u n="238" who="S0558">the spare part</u>
<u n="239" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0558">I said it's not gonna work</u>
<u n="241" who="S0517">no and the next thing you know</u>
<u n="242" who="S0558" trans="overlap">it's not gonna work</u>
<u n="243" who="S0517">she'll fall pregnant and it'll be a disaster</u>
<u n="244" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0517">no I wouldn't</u>
<u n="246" who="S0558">no no no</u>
<u n="247" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do it that way either but erm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no no I need to speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about this I need to say look I'd give this some <trunc>th</trunc>thought it's not gonna work <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0517">no I mean absolutely give them both money that they can put towards a deposit</u>
<u n="250" who="S0558" trans="overlap">they would be better off they would be better off I'm gonna say to her you would be better off putting whatever money you're gonna give them to one side yeah but split it in half</u>
<u n="251" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0558"><trunc>wherev</trunc> if you're gonna give them ten grand or a deposit for a house that's <trunc>fif</trunc> five grand each short term they rent something until they are</u>
<u n="253" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0558" trans="overlap">in a position</u>
<u n="255" who="S0517">to buy</u>
<u n="256" who="S0558">to buy</u>
<u n="257" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to say <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and then they've got five grand towards their deposit then</u>
<u n="259" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0558">but</u>
<u n="261" who="S0517">cos you need a huge deposit these days don't you?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0558">yes is it like fifteen grand?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0517">oh I know</u>
<u n="264" who="S0558">but then she said which I think is oh she said I think what we're gonna do to start with for the first couple of years so that at the end of each month they don't feel like depressed cos they've got no money we're gonna go on an interest only mortgage</u>
<u n="265" who="S0517">oh no</u>
<u n="266" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="267" who="S0517">can you still get those?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0558"><vocal desc="cough"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said she'll be</u>
<u n="269" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I didn't think you</u>
<u n="270" who="S0558">they'll be lucky if they get one now</u>
<u n="271" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I didn't think they were still I didn't think they were still an option because they caused so many problems didn't they? people couldn't</u>
<u n="272" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0517">get to the end and couldn't afford the</u>
<u n="274" who="S0558">see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't know I've not looked into them but</u>
<u n="276" who="S0558">when when they moved to the house they're in in Wales</u>
<u n="277" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0558">they went on an interest-only because it was a bit more than they could afford but erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her sister lives in a huge house in <anon type="place"/> and erm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh that's why <anon type="place"/> cos her sister's there?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0558">well yeah and I'm down the road</u>
<u n="281" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she's not been very well of late <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's suffered quite with depression quite</u>
<u n="283" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh has she?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0558" trans="overlap">of late cos I said well why <anon type="place"/> if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s working in <anon type="place"/>? there's some beautiful villages <vocal desc="cough"/> I said I wouldn't live in <anon type="place"/> itself</u>
<u n="285" who="S0517">oh no</u>
<u n="286" who="S0558" trans="overlap">it's vile I said but closer to <anon type="place"/> there are some nice villages</u>
<u n="287" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0558">about and that I said but then I suppose you're kind of gonna be on your own</u>
<u n="289" who="S0517">I suppose <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> cos it's that much further north than us</u>
<u n="290" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0517">it's only gonna be half an hour isn't it?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0517" trans="overlap">forty minutes something like</u>
<u n="294" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah it's not hard</u>
<u n="295" who="S0517">so it's not</u>
<u n="296" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="297" who="S0517">that's not a bad journey</u>
<u n="298" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0517">and if her sister's there like you're saying and you're only</u>
<u n="300" who="S0558" trans="overlap">sister's there</u>
<u n="301" who="S0517">ten minutes this way</u>
<u n="302" who="S0558">at least she's got a little bit of <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="303" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0558">support not that she'll need support cos she got no kids any <trunc>m</trunc> but in the way they're relations</u>
<u n="305" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well I know but then she won't know anyone will she so it's quite a bit thing still to move area and</u>
<u n="306" who="S0558">it's still quite a big thing</u>
<u n="307" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos without the kids there you don't there's your</u>
<u n="308" who="S0558">you don't get to meet people</u>
<u n="309" who="S0517" trans="overlap">your link to to make to make friends isn't it?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0558">and she can't be reliant on me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0517">no no</u>
<u n="312" who="S0558" trans="overlap">cos we've still got kids and are running here there and everywhere</u>
<u n="313" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0558">and</u>
<u n="315" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0558" trans="overlap">we're at a different stage</u>
<u n="317" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0558" trans="overlap">of live aren't we? so she can't think oh I'll move there because</u>
<u n="319" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0558">I can see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> twice a week and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0517">no no</u>
<u n="322" who="S0558" trans="overlap">twice a week and that'll fill my week cos that's not gonna happen</u>
<u n="323" who="S0517">will she get a job?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0558">probably she'll</u>
<u n="325" who="S0517">so that that'll help</u>
<u n="326" who="S0558" trans="overlap">look for a job</u>
<u n="327" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah she'll look for a job</u>
<u n="329" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="330" who="S0558" trans="overlap">cos she's looking in Wales and she's just not having much luck just wanting a job</u>
<u n="331" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I imagine the job market's not great there though is it?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0558">no ideally she wants something erm because of the operation on her hips on her hip</u>
<u n="333" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0558">erm she can't the the job she's come from was you know when you go into like Debenhams and stock up the jewellery or you know wherever and do</u>
<u n="335" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0558" trans="overlap">do the jewellery top up and that was an awful lot of work on her knees</u>
<u n="337" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="338" who="S0558">coding and you know <trunc>re</trunc></u>
<u n="339" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0558">rehanging</u>
<u n="341" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh that's no good</u>
<u n="342" who="S0558">different things you know so that's absolutely no good for her she can't do that and it involved a lot of driving which if she sits for any major length of time she has terrible problems with her hip</u>
<u n="343" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0558">so erm she got a little bit of restriction really she can't sort of sit for too long she's better off</u>
<u n="345" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="346" who="S0558" trans="overlap">being a little bit mobile</u>
<u n="347" who="S0517">yes well</u>
<u n="348" who="S0558">she's just looking for something part time</u>
<u n="349" who="S0517" trans="overlap">part time</u>
<u n="350" who="S0558">really</u>
<u n="351" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they're the hard ones cos everyone wants that don't they?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0517" trans="overlap">have you heard how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s getting on with her job?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0558">no I haven't no</u>
<u n="355" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos she was very pleased to get it wasn't she?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0517" trans="overlap">hers is part time but yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0517">everybody wants the part time jobs don't they?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0517">our age <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0558">our age</u>
<u n="363" who="S0517">can't be doing full <trunc>ti</trunc></u>
<u n="364" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="365" who="S0517">somebody asked me the other day would I ever go back to full-time work who was it? thought it was the boys when we were chatting I said god no</u>
<u n="366" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="367" who="S0517">haven't done full-time work <trunc>sin</trunc> well since since before I had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0558">how many hours would you say you do a week?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0517">now?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0517">erm <pause dur="short"/> maybe twenty that's not many is it? at the minute</u>
<u n="372" who="S0558">it's enough</u>
<u n="373" who="S0517">it's enough because of all the other stuff the unpaid stuff the taxiing</u>
<u n="374" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0517">toing and froing the cooking the shopping the cleaning I mean I do all of that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't really do he does the shopping sometimes but I try not to let him as you know</u>
<u n="376" who="S0558">oh no he spends too much</u>
<u n="377" who="S0517" trans="overlap">too expensive when he goes erm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0558">far too much</u>
<u n="379" who="S0517">so yeah but it's enough it's enough</u>
<u n="380" who="S0558">so where were you Friday night then?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0517">Friday night?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0558">where were you?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh did you go to erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0558">oh is that where you where then?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I wasn't there where were you?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0558">I was at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and pops</u>
<u n="387" who="S0517">oh I wasn't invited</u>
<u n="388" who="S0558">and as</u>
<u n="389" who="S0517" trans="overlap">obviously</u>
<u n="390" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was erm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0517">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were at our house weren't they?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yes so where were you?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0517">ordering a pizza <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I went to <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in a play</u>
<u n="394" who="S0558">oh was she?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0517">called Daisy Pulls it Off which was good actually</u>
<u n="396" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="397" who="S0517">we enjoyed it</u>
<u n="398" who="S0558">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I bet they're having an evening out together</u>
<u n="399" who="S0517">out together yeah no we went to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="401" who="S0517">because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> invited me to her</u>
<u n="402" who="S0558">yes she invited</u>
<u n="403" who="S0517">Neal's Yard party</u>
<u n="404" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0517">and I said no I can't we're going to the <anon type="place"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming round</u>
<u n="406" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0517">I said have you now?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0558">yeah cos I</u>
<u n="409" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the minute we go out literally the minute we go out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0558">oh really?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0517">they don't</u>
<u n="412" who="S0558">oh oh well it's planned</u>
<u n="413" who="S0517">oh yes</u>
<u n="414" who="S0558" trans="overlap">it was planned cos as soon as they came in from school because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were gonna be here cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had invited we were out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0517">yes I know</u>
<u n="416" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear>it was a lovely</unclear> meal</u>
<u n="417" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I've seen those two since actually and she said you had a nice time</u>
<u n="418" who="S0558">and he had invited <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="419" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="420" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0558">and is said oh well we don't go out very often on our own</u>
<u n="423" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="424" who="S0558">and they're not gonna know anybody you know what I mean so although I said it was really lovely of you to include them but no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0517">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0517">don't want them to come no</u>
<u n="428" who="S0558">erm and erm so the plan was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were gonna stop in and have a pizza delivered and all this and that so they come I'm sitting here I'd just literally finished work at ten to four cos I've got a new system now tell you about that so I was just sitting here with a cup of tea thinking oh be here three minutes even just three minutes' peace would be nice and they appeared and it was always <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to go down to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s tonight I said that's alright and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh will <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> be okay on her own? I said yeah yeah she's fine as long as there's no candles other than what's safely in them pots lit</u>
<u n="429" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0558">she'll be fine so they're laughing you know and erm and I'm sitting here I'm thinking oh haven't gotta cook tonight oh my god what shall I do with myself? you know when you think <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0558">yeah and I had a thought so I said next time they appeared I said mm I said I don't want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> having pizzas delivered with nobody else in the house I know nobody else I know they're not gonna know nobody else is in the house but if they genuinely said could I use your loo</u>
<u n="433" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0558">it would put <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in a difficult position do you know what I mean? and she might go oh yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0558">and then they realise oh</u>
<u n="437" who="S0517">she's on her own</u>
<u n="438" who="S0558" trans="overlap">young girl and</u>
<u n="439" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0558">I said you know I'm not even I'm not even gonna put her in that position</u>
<u n="441" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0558">so said right I'm not so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes told you so they'd obviously already</u>
<u n="443" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh they'd discussed it</u>
<u n="444" who="S0558">discussed this</u>
<u n="445" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="446" who="S0558">so I said either you order your pizza to be sure it's here before <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> leaves</u>
<u n="447" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0558">or the pizza gets ordered with the boys and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> whizzes it up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'll do that I'll whizz up on my bike and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going oh it will have slid and it'll be flat and</u>
<u n="449" who="S0517">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0558">and it'll be this</u>
<u n="451" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0558">and they're going no way <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it'll just be flat in the bottom of the bag I said but either way sort it because you're not having a delivery pizza a pizza delivered</u>
<u n="453" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0558">blah so <pause dur="short"/> drops her up at the gym comes back she's in the shower right I'll order my pizza now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said okay and just as we were going out there was a car on the corner and I I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as as we got in the car I saw lights and I said oh with a bit of luck</u>
<u n="455" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="456" who="S0558">that's the pizza</u>
<u n="457" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the pizza</u>
<u n="458" who="S0558">so we went to the bottom of the drive and looked he said no somebody's parked up so as we were passing saw this cap and it was a girl she was doing this I said are you delivering a pizza? she went yeah I went oh it's just there and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as luck happened it was a girl anyway</u>
<u n="459" who="S0517">yes yeah <unclear>but you don't know do you?</unclear></u>
<u n="460" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said blimey though fancy sending a young girl out</u>
<u n="461" who="S0517" trans="overlap">girl out I know</u>
<u n="462" who="S0558" trans="overlap">on her own</u>
<u n="463" who="S0517">well</u>
<u n="464" who="S0558" trans="overlap">you never know</u>
<u n="465" who="S0517">she must want that job yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0558">he said I suppose they think of <anon type="place"/> respectable area she'll be safe there</u>
<u n="467" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah but she could be <trunc>any</trunc></u>
<u n="468" who="S0558">you know</u>
<u n="469" who="S0517">she could get anything on her round</u>
<u n="470" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you don't know do you?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0558">so erm so yeah that was sorted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had her pizza and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came round to you</u>
<u n="473" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh well they didn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't tell me cos I had got them out that he didn't tell me till we were going out that they were coming round even and I had got them out it when I'm in Tesco's like on a cos I knew we were going out and we'd be rushed I bought them you know one of those ones they make those huge ones that they make on that</u>
<u n="474" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0517">on that pizza counter?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0517">so I'd got them one of those for the boys to share so and and actually I'd bought it with the shopping last week so it had been in the freezer so I'd got it out that morning and I'd said to him you can have this tonight because we're we're going out</u>
<u n="478" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0517">and er so that was that so they <trunc>c</trunc> they didn't get home from tennis <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> picks them up and they get got in at quarter to seven and I'd put the pizza in the oven and we were going out at seven and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh by the way erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and erm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are coming round I said oh are they? I said oh okay and off we went so it wasn't until we got back and er we got we well we weren't late the thing finished at ten we were home you know before half ten</u>
<u n="482" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0517">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh they've <trunc>g</trunc> said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ordered pizza I said did they? and cos the boys those pizzas that you get in Tesco's</u>
<u n="484" who="S0558" trans="overlap">huge</u>
<u n="485" who="S0517" trans="overlap">are huge so they hadn't actually managed to eat all of that said they ordered a they ordered a pizza and they and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like it's great though mum cos they didn't eat it all there's some left in the fridge for breakfast <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0517">I said well why didn't they take it with them it's theirs? no they didn't want it but of course</u>
<u n="488" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0517">he loves cold pizza for breakfast sadly</u>
<u n="490" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="491" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0558"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0517">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was off an all-day hockey thing and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had coaching <trunc>th</trunc>they were they sorted</u>
<u n="494" who="S0558" trans="overlap">sorted</u>
<u n="495" who="S0517">cos they had their lunch there as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> breakfast lunch</u>
<u n="497" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0517">and then then the pizza was gone</u>
<u n="500" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="501" who="S0517">but no they didn't tell they didn't even tell me that they were coming round but so obviously they had it planned that they were going to be ordering pizza but</u>
<u n="502" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never said a word</u>
<u n="504" who="S0558">never said</u>
<u n="505" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but he knew from the morning that I'd got this pizza that</u>
<u n="506" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0517" trans="overlap">out of the freezer so it had to be cooked</u>
<u n="508" who="S0558">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said cos cos I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0517" trans="overlap">sneaky aren't they?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0558">I said do you do you want to invite anybody round? and like and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know do you want to you know whatever watch a movie and <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said no like you know we're going down to yours <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="513" who="S0517">no I think they just played on the Playstation I don't think they did much did they?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0558">no it was the week before sorry I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you want anybody come round where were we? and I said do you wanna invite anybody <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? oh when we went to the skate <unclear/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0517">oh to the scout meal</u>
<u n="516" who="S0558">the scout meal</u>
<u n="517" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was it any good? was it alright?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0558">yeah it was okay actually</u>
<u n="519" who="S0517">oh good</u>
<u n="520" who="S0558">I was I was sitting next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wife?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0558" trans="overlap">there was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that side yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0558">and then opposite there was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she did some toddlers for a little while</u>
<u n="525" who="S0517">oh I might know her by sight I can't</u>
<u n="526" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0517">I don't know the name</u>
<u n="528" who="S0558">they've got erm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was one of the ones that run it wasn't he?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="532" who="S0558">that's it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yes I know him</u>
<u n="534" who="S0558">they live yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so I was sort of opposite them</u>
<u n="537" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="538" who="S0558">so it was quite to chat with him</u>
<u n="539" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0558">but it's difficult it's a long table twenty</u>
<u n="541" who="S0517" trans="overlap">were you <unclear/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0517">yeah yeah it is difficult you can only really talk to the people</u>
<u n="544" who="S0558" trans="overlap">thirty-two people <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right by you</u>
<u n="546" who="S0558" trans="overlap">were there but they were down the other end so I didn't speak to them</u>
<u n="547" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="548" who="S0558" trans="overlap">erm it's difficult isn't it?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0558">but er but no it was nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0517">have you now?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0558" trans="overlap">mm yeah weekend</u>
<u n="553" who="S0517">yeah this weekend</u>
<u n="554" who="S0558">we're out Saturday night</u>
<u n="555" who="S0517">where are you going Saturday?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0558" trans="overlap">erm for a meal with like er one of them erm <anon type="place"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum and dad</u>
<u n="557" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="558" who="S0558">and I don't know whether <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are gonna be there I don't know whether they're available Saturday night</u>
<u n="559" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="560" who="S0558">but that'll be an early one we're meeting at half six</u>
<u n="561" who="S0517">we're out Saturday actually</u>
<u n="562" who="S0558">are you?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0517" trans="overlap">we're having an early meal too it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday on Saturday</u>
<u n="564" who="S0558">oh is it the big one?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="566" who="S0558">er oh is that not</u>
<u n="567" who="S0517">er</u>
<u n="568" who="S0558">what how old is she?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0517">she <trunc>m</trunc> made me stop and think then how old am I? no she's gonna be forty-nine</u>
<u n="570" who="S0558">oh it's next year the big one</u>
<u n="571" who="S0517">it's next year yes</u>
<u n="572" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0517">and she's going to be forty-nine so erm so we're going to a restaurant near to where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> live</u>
<u n="574" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0517">and they're coming with the baby so that's why we're going early half past six so that that we can then</u>
<u n="576" who="S0558" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0517">go back to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and go cos apparently he's going to bed at around eight o'clock now</u>
<u n="578" who="S0558">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling me about erm Saturday she was looking after him <unclear>five hours</unclear></u>
<u n="579" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes I went I went over there for an hour</u>
<u n="580" who="S0558" trans="overlap">did you go? she said to me <trunc>d</trunc> did I want to pop over and I said oh we've got erm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well if I'd have realised I could have taken you</u>
<u n="582" who="S0558">well I said we've got a twenty-first birthday party in <anon type="place"/> we were going out at like</u>
<u n="583" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="584" who="S0558">six o'clock and</u>
<u n="585" who="S0517" trans="overlap">earlyish</u>
<u n="586" who="S0558">and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to the gym on the morning</u>
<u n="587" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yeah you should <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="588" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and had went and had a coffee with dad</u>
<u n="589" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah but no she was there all afternoon they were at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0517">so I went over for an hour called in at mum's and then went</u>
<u n="592" who="S0558" trans="overlap">cos she said have you have you met him yet? and I said no I said</u>
<u n="593" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="594" who="S0558">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the new year I said cos you know what it's like get all your friends and your family and after a bit you think I just wanna be left alone</u>
<u n="595" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0558">you know</u>
<u n="597" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0558">with my little family unit I said so I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the New Year I'll have to meet him</u>
<u n="599" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="600" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0517">she's babysitting again on Thursday I think</u>
<u n="602" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh I was gonna say she made me laugh cos she said I've got him for five hours she said and she's started starting to reduce his sleep in the day so he sleeps better at night</u>
<u n="603" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="604" who="S0558">she said and she <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s told me all this and that she said and I said sorry five hours? my rules</u>
<u n="605" who="S0517">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0558">me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my rules forget that my rules <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0517">honestly</u>
<u n="608" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="609" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I got there and she was like oh thank goodness cos she was stood up she went my back's killing me she was holding him</u>
<u n="610" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="611" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I said what's the matter? she said oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told me I was wait till three o'clock until he had his bottle but I caved in at quarter past two but now he hasn't drunk it all and he doesn't want it and she'd managed to go out with the dog as well they'd been out for a walk and</u>
<u n="612" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yes she said we were gonna go out</u>
<u n="613" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and she was <unclear/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0558">oh was she quite stressed by the end it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she was just shattered really so I just</u>
<u n="616" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="617" who="S0517" trans="overlap">held him for a bit and he's as good as cold he did sound tired we couldn't decide he kept doing like it sounded like a little tired cry but then he lay on his mat and he was quite happy then he'd have a little I don't know I don't know but he was happy</u>
<u n="618" who="S0558">but he</u>
<u n="619" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but it was just funny</u>
<u n="620" who="S0558">he will be getting to the stage now you know where he knows it's not his mum</u>
<u n="621" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="622" who="S0558">you know</u>
<u n="623" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but he's <trunc>se</trunc> he's seen that much of nanny <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0558"><trunc>ye</trunc> well yes</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="625" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="626" who="S0517">nanny <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0558">every day</u>
<u n="628" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she's always there so you know she's like a second mother to him honestly</u>
<u n="629" who="S0558">ah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0517">so funny but he was cute but yeah so they're they're coming out with us so it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday on Saturday so we're out Saturday night</u>
<u n="631" who="S0558">oh that'll be nice</u>
<u n="632" who="S0517">mm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are off to Thailand so they won't be going</u>
<u n="633" who="S0558">are they?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0517">on Friday</u>
<u n="635" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0517">for a fortnight's holiday</u>
<u n="637" who="S0558">oh how lovely</u>
<u n="638" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm she got the job in the <anon type="place"/> did I did you know</u>
<u n="639" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="640" who="S0517">she was going for one?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0558">she at <anon type="place"/> store manager</u>
<u n="642" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0517">in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0558">wow</u>
<u n="645" who="S0517">and I think that was the one she had originally wanted but it wasn't available yet you know when she first applied?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0517">so they'd put her in <anon type="place"/> and said you know when it comes available apply for it but it had to be applied for but she did she went she got the interview she's got that so</u>
<u n="648" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well done</u>
<u n="649" who="S0517">yeah so she's started in <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="650" who="S0558">so how does she travel there car or</u>
<u n="651" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she's getting the train</u>
<u n="652" who="S0558">the train</u>
<u n="653" who="S0517">apparently it's saving her money</u>
<u n="654" who="S0558">it's cheaper on the train yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0517">yeah and you know she was using the toll road cos it was taking her a while to get to the <anon type="place"/> one so</u>
<u n="656" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="657" who="S0517">yeah so she's very happy</u>
<u n="658" who="S0558">oh bless her</u>
<u n="659" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and she's got her holiday and they go I think it's Friday this week off to Thailand for a fortnight I know</u>
<u n="660" who="S0558">how lovely</u>
<u n="661" who="S0517">so yes so it'll just be the eight of us us four <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but he won't be eating</u>
<u n="662" who="S0558">no he'll be on his little chair <unclear/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos she's put him on a little bit of formula milk and erm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0558">oh this is it</u>
<u n="665" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0558">he didn't want <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0517">didn't want the <trunc>br</trunc> he doesn't want the breast milk any more <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0558">doesn't want the</u>
<u n="669" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told me I said <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0517">she's producing that much I know and he spat it out I said oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="672" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0517">not having that now too watery don't want that</u>
<u n="674" who="S0558">oh I know it's like</u>
<u n="675" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I was laughing</u>
<u n="676" who="S0558"><trunc>wa</trunc> it like water</u>
<u n="677" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but they've got this they've got this fancy bottle making thing</u>
<u n="678" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0517">has she told you about it?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0558">she did tell me</u>
<u n="681" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0558">I said my how technology moves on</u>
<u n="683" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know cos they're not allowed to make them up in the morning and keep them for twenty-four hours that's not allowed any more</u>
<u n="684" who="S0558">well I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0517">it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="686" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I breastfed both of mine for a year I said and in the company of friends I used to see them with the bottles washing them out and putting the and I used to think to myself how time consuming all I do is unclip</u>
<u n="687" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0558">get my boob out sorted</u>
<u n="689" who="S0517" trans="overlap">out and there you go</u>
<u n="690" who="S0558">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0558">and I used to watch you know bottles</u>
<u n="693" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0558">and scoops and shake and</u>
<u n="695" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0558">and I used to think oh my god what a faff</u>
<u n="697" who="S0517">well I bottle fed mine but you just get used to it don't you? it's what you know</u>
<u n="698" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="699" who="S0517">I can't remember why she said actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had put him on a bit of formula I can't remember there must have been a reason cos she was producing that much milk anyway</u>
<u n="700" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0517">apparently he's spitting it out now</u>
<u n="702" who="S0558">spitting it out now</u>
<u n="703" who="S0517">the breast milk</u>
<u n="704" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I can't say I blame him it's like it is like water</u>
<u n="705" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's watery yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0558">very watery</u>
<u n="707" who="S0517">so anyway he was very happy though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0558">bless him so will she stop now do you think?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0517">I don't know</u>
<u n="710" who="S0558">she</u>
<u n="711" who="S0517">cos I didn't actually see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was out for lunch until the cinema so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0558">no oh</u>
<u n="713" who="S0517">I know it's nice isn't it? when I had mine I didn't have anyone to babysit cos we didn't live <trunc>n</trunc> by anyone</u>
<u n="714" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="715" who="S0517">we never did that yeah we never had that luxury</u>
<u n="716" who="S0558">I I never did</u>
<u n="717" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos if they came to see us</u>
<u n="718" who="S0558" trans="overlap">even though</u>
<u n="719" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they were coming to see us</u>
<u n="720" who="S0558">yeah I never did even though cos like mum was sort of starting to get poorly</u>
<u n="721" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0558">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I certainly wouldn't leave them with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum and dad</u>
<u n="723" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0558">oh god no</u>
<u n="725" who="S0517">I see I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from the gym she said er how what hours does she work? cos she always seems to be in the gym</u>
<u n="726" who="S0558">I think she only works two days a week</u>
<u n="727" who="S0517">oh does she?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I'm not sure what hours she does but I think she does two days and then sometimes she'll do some private physio on a Monday or I think that</u>
<u n="729" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh is she a physio?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0558">well she's not a qualified physio she's just one of them assistants you know</u>
<u n="731" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="732" who="S0558">like an <trunc>assis</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="733" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="734" who="S0558">she's not</u>
<u n="735" who="S0517">I didn't really know what she did</u>
<u n="736" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she's done no exams or qualified</u>
<u n="737" who="S0517">oh right</u>
<u n="738" who="S0558" trans="overlap">but she works at <anon type="place"/> hospital</u>
<u n="739" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="740" who="S0558">so like you know if erm simple basic exercises you know</u>
<u n="741" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="742" who="S0558">to get people back home or they've</u>
<u n="743" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="744" who="S0558" trans="overlap">had an injury</u>
<u n="745" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="746" who="S0558">just that sort of thing she does</u>
<u n="747" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I didn't know anyway she always seems to be in the gym</u>
<u n="748" who="S0558">yeah yeah she goes out most nights I think to there</u>
<u n="749" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0558">and I think do you never spend any time with your family?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0517">I think sometimes she goes twice a day</u>
<u n="752" who="S0558">yeah I wouldn't be surprised</u>
<u n="753" who="S0517">because I went to a class yesterday morning that I haven't been to for quite a long time and sometimes I go on a Monday night and I <trunc>th</trunc> and I was there in the morning and there she was and I'm thinking I'm sure I see you on a Monday night so obviously</u>
<u n="754" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0517">for me it was either or er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0517">but I thought it wouldn't surprise me actually if she goes back</u>
<u n="758" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no and when erm when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was talking about their <trunc>dr</trunc> cos they've moved house</u>
<u n="759" who="S0517">oh have they?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0558">their sort of drive situation <vocal desc="cough"/> you can sort of pull one on and sort of swing it round and park the other one here but then of course that one can't get off</u>
<u n="761" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="762" who="S0558">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> parks it it's across the road in a side street</u>
<u n="763" who="S0517">oh what so that she can go in and out?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0558">cos he said oh most nights <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is out you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is off to the gym and I think</u>
<u n="765" who="S0517">cos he's a member there but he doesn't seem to go half as often does he?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0558">I don't think he goes as much as</u>
<u n="767" who="S0517">no mm no</u>
<u n="768" who="S0558" trans="overlap">anyway she is</u>
<u n="769" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is is</u>
<u n="770" who="S0558" trans="overlap">obsessed by it</u>
<u n="771" who="S0517">yeah yeah very much so</u>
<u n="772" who="S0558">you know</u>
<u n="773" who="S0517">very much so but anyway I mean it pays off she's got an amazing figure</u>
<u n="774" who="S0558">yeah but</u>
<u n="775" who="S0517">but yeah it's a lot of hours</u>
<u n="776" who="S0558">she don't eat</u>
<u n="777" who="S0517">oh doesn't she?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she hardly eats no even the girls are turning out the same now picky you know</u>
<u n="779" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh that's not good is it?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0558">oh no she don't she hardly eats</u>
<u n="783" who="S0517">oh well that makes sense then</u>
<u n="784" who="S0558">yeah no I've never seen her tuck into a good meal</u>
<u n="785" who="S0517">oh <trunc>rea</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="786" who="S0558">never no no never</u>
<u n="787" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="788" who="S0558">it's you know bitty like a little bit of this and a little bit of that and</u>
<u n="789" who="S0517">oh god</u>
<u n="790" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="791" who="S0517">drive me mad that would</u>
<u n="792" who="S0558">oh god no god no no it's not no no</u>
<u n="793" who="S0517">we had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for tea the other night the new <trunc>girlfrie</trunc> well she's not that new is she now?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0558">what's she like?</u>
<u n="795" who="S0517">well she's nice</u>
<u n="796" who="S0558">is she nice?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me yeah she's got a lot more about her than the first one</u>
<u n="798" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I said that's no way to talk about</u>
<u n="800" who="S0558" trans="overlap">a lot more about her</u>
<u n="801" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's no way to talk about your brother's girlfriend</u>
<u n="802" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="803" who="S0517">er no she was <trunc>n</trunc> she was nice she was very chatty you know she was happy to talk to me she was very erm dunno she did seem a little bit besotted with him I thought really?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0558">oh really?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0517">well she like she knew his</u>
<u n="806" who="S0558" trans="overlap">what just looking at him or</u>
<u n="807" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well just I don't know she she knew his timetable better than he did which I thought was a bit</u>
<u n="808" who="S0558">are they in</u>
<u n="809" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="810" who="S0558" trans="overlap">the same classes? no?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0517" trans="overlap">only for science only for science like she was saying you know the following day she said well I've got this and you've got that and I cos he you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll still get to Wednesday and ask me which week we're on</u>
<u n="812" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0517">are we on week A or week B? I say I don't know</u>
<u n="814" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="815" who="S0517">but you know he's a bit like that but she said no you've got this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she knew the rooms he was in and everything I thought blimey</u>
<u n="816" who="S0558">it's cos she's meeting him when he comes out isn't it?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0517">I think it must be and erm I'd had a I can't even remember what it was we'd had a text from the school about something that was going on <pause dur="short"/> was it a careers fair or something? anyway I said to them what's this text? I don't understand this text from the school and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went oh I don't know never heard of it and she went <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they talked to us about that in assembly this morning <vocal desc="laugh"/> I said oh that sounds about right but I don't know she just was really I mean she was very nice but she did seem to like know his life better than he did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0558">oh bless</u>
<u n="819" who="S0517">I said to him have you planned ahead <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos you do know you're missing Valentine's Day? he said oh oh and that's about it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0517">it's as far as we've got mm</u>
<u n="822" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0517">cos you won't be here have you told her?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="825" who="S0517">have you told her you're going away? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="826" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0517">but yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0558">so what why did the other relationship finish?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0517">I don't know he never really said</u>
<u n="830" who="S0558">and did this one</u>
<u n="831" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I mean it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't it that told us that the word</u>
<u n="832" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0517">word on the bus was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was cheating on her <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0558">oh I was gonna say yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0517">I don't know he never said</u>
<u n="836" who="S0558" trans="overlap">the word wasn't it that</u>
<u n="837" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he just said to me no we didn't see each other mum he doesn't see much of any cos he's so busy</u>
<u n="838" who="S0558" trans="overlap">he likes the girls then does he our <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he seems to and <trunc>the</trunc> they seem to like him <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so yes yes bit of a worry that according to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's forever chatting to other girls <pause dur="short"/> according to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Mr know it all there yeah he's on he's on the text or he's on Snapchat to all he's on this and that to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and so and so or you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I think that's the way they are now</u>
<u n="841" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0558">to be fair I think</u>
<u n="843" who="S0517" trans="overlap">all <unclear/> chat</u>
<u n="844" who="S0558">opposite opposite erm gender</u>
<u n="845" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="846" who="S0558" trans="overlap">you know is the norm now isn't it as friends whereas in our day if you spoke to a boy it was like is that your boyfriend?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0517">what was it he said to me this morning?</u>
<u n="848" who="S0558" trans="overlap">whereas I think the opposite sex now</u>
<u n="849" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I tell you what changing times what was it he said to me this morning? <pause dur="short"/> I oh that <vocal desc="laugh"/> his hair he'd he'd had a disaster with his hair literally he was supposed to be going out the door and he said oh mum look what I've done to my hair I said oh just wet it pat it it's all sticking up he said oh that's it that's it I'm having a bad hair day I've gotta end it all I said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't be so ridiculous you sound like a girl talking about a bad hair day and he just said to me did I not tell you mum? I'm a boy trapped in no I'm a girl trapped in a boy's body</u>
<u n="850" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="851" who="S0517">I said no you didn't mention it I thought</u>
<u n="852" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="853" who="S0517">you know what <trunc>li</trunc> er when we were what? fourteen you just wouldn't have entertained the idea that that thought wouldn't come into your head but this is what</u>
<u n="854" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they hear about and talk about all the time</u>
<u n="856" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0517" trans="overlap">isn't it?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0558">and it's yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and he's going did I not tell you mum?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0517">I'm a <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0517">I'm a which way <trunc>rou</trunc> I keep having to think</u>
<u n="864" who="S0558" trans="overlap">girl</u>
<u n="865" who="S0517">I'm a girl trapped in a boy's</u>
<u n="866" who="S0558" trans="overlap">trapped a boy's</u>
<u n="867" who="S0517" trans="overlap">body I said oh I said well now we'll see how that turns out then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0517">and off he went with his hair sticking out everywhere</u>
<u n="870" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0558">oh bless him</u>
<u n="873" who="S0517">but yeah you just can't <trunc>im</trunc> you know you think oh god that's what they're</u>
<u n="874" who="S0558">it's it's like erm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0517" trans="overlap">dealing with all the time isn't it?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0558" trans="overlap">it in our days at school you know if somebody wore glasses or braces you you know it you know there would have been that mimicking and taking the mickey</u>
<u n="877" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="878" who="S0558">wouldn't there? but no now they go for like coloured <trunc>tra</trunc> jazzier the better and</u>
<u n="879" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yeah no no that's right no no that's just that's perfectly okay but</u>
<u n="880" who="S0558" trans="overlap">very different</u>
<u n="881" who="S0517">but you know</u>
<u n="882" who="S0558" trans="overlap">isn't it?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0517">that I think they're sort of taught that aren't they? it's okay</u>
<u n="884" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="885" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to be whoever you are</u>
<u n="886" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0517" trans="overlap">which is a good thing I'm not saying it's a bad thing at all it's just that it just you know just sounded weird coming from him</u>
<u n="888" who="S0558">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like that time you know I've told ages ago when he they were obviously doing about self-harming in school and he said oh I'm just going to have to start self-harming now mum <trunc>li</trunc> yeah yeah alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="891" who="S0517">off he goes and kicks his football but you know they</u>
<u n="892" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0517">they obviously have to talk about all this stuff don't they?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0558" trans="overlap">they do because it self-harming is really quite</u>
<u n="895" who="S0517">oh popular for want</u>
<u n="896" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0517">of a better word <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0558"><trunc>pop</trunc>popular yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know it's not really word is it?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="901" who="S0517">but it's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0517">what is the word?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0517">prevalent I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> but anyway</u>
<u n="906" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="907" who="S0517">not popular but</u>
<u n="908" who="S0558">scary</u>
<u n="909" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="910" who="S0558">it's scary</u>
<u n="911" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0558">I mean you know in our day if you'd have been seen to be self-harming you'd have had an appointment with the psyche wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0517">well you were</u>
<u n="914" who="S0558" trans="overlap">you'd be going to see the you know</u>
<u n="915" who="S0517">well you would</u>
<u n="916" who="S0558" trans="overlap">the psychopathic nurse because</u>
<u n="917" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well when I</u>
<u n="918" who="S0558" trans="overlap">they'd think you were</u>
<u n="919" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is how old we are <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when I was that age you had a school nurse</u>
<u n="920" who="S0558">you did</u>
<u n="921" who="S0517">we had a <trunc>sch</trunc> we had a nurse</u>
<u n="922" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she was there all day every day and you went to the if you weren't well</u>
<u n="924" who="S0558">yeah you went to the school nurse</u>
<u n="925" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you want to the nurse's room she had a little like <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was like cupboard really</u>
<u n="926" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="927" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but we did we had a school nurse but yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="928" who="S0558" trans="overlap">just trying to think whether we did at <anon type="place"/> do you know I don't it wasn't as posh at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="929" who="S0517" trans="overlap">were you not as posh as <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="930" who="S0558">I don't think we had a nurse there</u>
<u n="931" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0558">all day every day <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0517">well she always I mean I didn't go but like if somebody was ill</u>
<u n="934" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="935" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they were sent there so assumed she was there</u>
<u n="936" who="S0558">I tell you what they had at <anon type="place"/> college when I went to <anon type="place"/> college after I'd vacated my sixth sixth</u>
<u n="937" who="S0517">sixth former</u>
<u n="938" who="S0558">lower sixth</u>
<u n="939" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0558">yeah former yeah oh it's not for me move on so I went to college and they had erm like a counsellor</u>
<u n="941" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="942" who="S0558">had like a lady that was a she was lovely she did one of our lectures I think as I remember but anyway she used to have her own little office and when she wasn't lecturing erm she was sort of an open door if anybody had got any problems</u>
<u n="943" who="S0517" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="944" who="S0558">or issues</u>
<u n="945" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="946" who="S0558">and I suppose you are of an age there aren't you where oh well I don't know were drugs as</u>
<u n="947" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0558">big?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0558">you know where the I don't know erm for whatever reason but I always remember she was a lovely lovely lady she was but she was permanently onsite and</u>
<u n="951" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="952" who="S0558">and she had this little office</u>
<u n="953" who="S0517" trans="overlap">had a little</u>
<u n="954" who="S0558">at the end of the corridor</u>
<u n="955" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="958" who="S0558">she was lovely</u>
<u n="959" who="S0517">but anyway I don't actually think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a girl trapped in a boy's body</u>
<u n="960" who="S0558">no not <unclear/></u>
<u n="961" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I've never seen more of a boy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0558">no no if he was bringing a lot of male friends home then you know you'd have reason to be concerned but no I don't think you're gonna have any worries there</u>
<u n="963" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="964" who="S0558">oh bless them bless them <pause dur="short"/> it makes you wonder doesn't it?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="966" who="S0558">how they're gonna turn out what jobs they're gonna be doing you know</u>
<u n="967" who="S0517">oh goodness knows have you did I ask you about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s work experience? have I asked you that?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="969" who="S0517">because you know they have to do it don't they in <trunc>Ju</trunc> in this year?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0558">yes cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been talking about sort of possibilities</u>
<u n="971" who="S0517">what does he <trunc>wh</trunc>what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't really know</u>
<u n="972" who="S0558">see the problem is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't really know what they wanna do for a living</u>
<u n="973" who="S0517" trans="overlap">what he wants to know so it's hard to know isn't it?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0558">so I think we've just got to look upon this work experience of just putting them in a working day</u>
<u n="975" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos I did work experience and I had a boring week well because you're sixteen and they don't give you anything to do do they?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0558">no no</u>
<u n="977" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you just sit there</u>
<u n="978" who="S0558">yeah but I think just exposing them to er strange people people they don't know</u>
<u n="979" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah I suppose so</u>
<u n="980" who="S0558">all that</u>
<u n="981" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and being able to get on with it yeah</u>
<u n="982" who="S0558" trans="overlap">even yeah</u>
<u n="983" who="S0517">I suppose so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0558">is part of it</u>
<u n="985" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="987" who="S0517">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has <trunc>arra</trunc> if he wanted to he could go and work on one of his sites</u>
<u n="988" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="989" who="S0517">for a week</u>
<u n="990" who="S0558">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="991" who="S0517">and he has <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="992" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> could go as well</u>
<u n="993" who="S0517">yeah he has asked the manager of <anon type="place"/> if he could would he mind having <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>sha</trunc> not shadowing him for a week cos he wouldn't he'd put him in with different</u>
<u n="994" who="S0558">put him in yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0517" trans="overlap">people each day</u>
<u n="996" who="S0558">that's very</u>
<u n="997" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so he could do that</u>
<u n="998" who="S0558" trans="overlap">good idea I've said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about <pause dur="short"/> potentially obviously the hospice I don't know what he'd do</u>
<u n="999" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0558">erm <pause dur="short"/> he couldn't go with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because of the nature of the work</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and he would just end up end sitting there all day</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0558" trans="overlap">doing nothing <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0517">it is hard to know isn't it?</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0558">you know when you think who <trunc>cou</trunc> who do you know who's in business that he could ask</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well we were trying to think of we were <trunc>tr</trunc> we were going along all those lines</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0517">all of our friends and their occupations and some were do you fancy this do you fancy that? but no no well what does that involve?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0517">doesn't really know what the involve so</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0558">no I said you could go and stop at auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s for a week and do some work with uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but that's not going to develop him as a person is it?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0517">no no</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0558">and that's what he needs</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0517">it's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <vocal desc="laugh"/> can I not follow you mum? you just sit at home all day</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0558">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1017" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no you can't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0558">cos I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you wouldn't be able to come out with me again because you're not you wouldn't be able to I don't know</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no I don't know</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0558" trans="overlap">he's actually he's older than sixteen so he's old enough to play</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0517">yeah so yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0558">so whether he's find it really boring</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0517">no this is it you want them to have a little go at doing something they might possibly</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0517">enjoy don't you?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0558">I said you could always go over to school as a last resort</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0517">to school?</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0558">yeah over there</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0517">oh really? oh</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0558">as a last resort</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wouldn't fancy that</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0558">erm</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well we'll see maybe he will go to one of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s holiday parks for a week I don't know</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0558">god he'd love that</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0517">he probably would could run the erm <pause dur="short"/> what's the thing in trees? the high ropes</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0558">probably wouldn't let him</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0517">no they wouldn't</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0558" trans="overlap">cos of the insurance</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0517">they wouldn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is in Holland today and yesterday</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0558">what's he doing in Holland?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0517" trans="overlap">in Holland that man</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0558">why's he gone there?</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0517">he's looking at water parks they're going with his boss</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh they're having one in</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they're going to put in a water park in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1046" who="S0558">yeah he was saying that</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0517">so that's where he is he's gone on a little</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so they've gone to have a look</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0517">two day jolly in Holland or I say it's a jolly it's a</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0558" trans="overlap">told you he's got a nice job</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0517">yeah he was up at half past four yesterday morning and he'll get back about half nine tonight and then he's off to Windsor tomorrow <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it's not much of a jolly it's quite a tiring two days</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0517">long two days but anyway said he's had a good day yesterday he facetimed me</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0558">so they've been to look at some in situ?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to meet the manufacturer</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0517">cos that's I think that's the manufacturer they they'll want to use I don't really know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I wasn't listening that much</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0558" trans="overlap">there'll be coffee and biscuits</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and the manager'll be sucking up to them</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they were going off to a</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0558" trans="overlap">like you wouldn't believe</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0517">steakhouse last night and</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0558" trans="overlap">of course they'll be wined and dined</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0558">and</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0517">yeah yeah yeah yeah anyway Holland</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0558">very nice</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0558">and there's you running around taxi servicing</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know taxi service</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0558">every night now though every night</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0517">yes welcome to my world</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0558">actually <vocal desc="cough"/> I dropped <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to the gym last night erm at eight o'clock and I was thinking about going but it's a bit busy in there on a Wednesday and I thought oh I dunno if I can be bothered erm so I dropped <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had got a meeting here with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> re explorers</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0517">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0558">so I text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on the off chance</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0558">T</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0558">and I said I've just dropped <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to the gym got an hour are you free for coffee? but she text back that would be lovely but she'd only just got in and she'd got to sort out</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0517" trans="overlap">at eight o'clock?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0558">erm no she hadn't she'd got in at seven</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0558">and she was having <trunc>t</trunc> she didn't get home till seven and she was er but I spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at school today I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I said how are you sweetheart? I'm alright thank you and I said erm I said oh I text your mummy last night she said oh I know she said you know she was busy doing things</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0558">and that I said oh it <trunc>was</trunc>wasn't planned anyway I said</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0517">it was on the off chance</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so you know I understand that erm and erm I said to her I said I said how are you how is your mummy managing to get to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to <trunc>sch</trunc> the bus</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0517">to school er to the train station?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0558">yeah that's it</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0558">and she said oh she said well sometimes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> comes over</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0517">oh does he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and I said oh does he? she said yeah I cos I said oh does mummy take her? she said yeah but sometimes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll prop pop across to help</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0558">I said oh I said and what about the night times? how are you getting on of a night time after school until mummy gets home? I said cos she doesn't get home till late does she? she said no she said daddy looks after us</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0558">she said but he's she said it's a bit of a nuisance though you know</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1102" who="S0558">cos obviously she's heard this she said if it's a bit of a nuisance I think nuisance was the word but a you know a a negative comment because he has to come to <anon type="place"/> go erm he he has to come from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> then back to <anon type="place"/> and back to <anon type="place"/> so that would be obviously coming to pick the two of them up taking them home going out to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up and coming back to the house isn't it?</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh so he looks after them at his</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0558" trans="overlap">he must</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0517"><trunc>h</trunc> oh okay</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0558" trans="overlap">at their I said I said well do you go back to daddy's or does</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0558" trans="overlap">he come to yours? and she said no he comes to their house</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0517">oh I see</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0517">right so</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0558">so</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0517"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1114" who="S0558">so</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to the house then <anon type="place"/> to get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you mean?</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0558">yeah so</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and then back again and back again</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0558" trans="overlap">from <anon type="place"/> from</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0558">where he's living</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0558">to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0558" trans="overlap">then to go back to their house and then has them when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> needs picking up</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know cos it's mad isn't it?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1127" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos that half the reason they moved house was so that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wouldn't have free reign to but he er but if he's doing the childcare</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0558">he's doing all that</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0517">he's got to er <vocal desc="misc"/> gosh</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0558">so now he's in that house sort of</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so now she's got</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0558" trans="overlap">every night</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0517">two exes running round after her gotta hand it to her I mean you know she's she she juggles that well two exes and they're both one of them has not got any relationship to the children but still helping out and paying for the roof</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0558" trans="overlap">has has been part of their lives for how long now?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0517" trans="overlap">seven years yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0558">seven years</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0517">paying for the roof over their heads and still helping out gotta hand it to her she does do that well</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0558">yeah but does she sleep at night?</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0517">er no I don't think she does</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0558" trans="overlap">using and abusing people makes you wonder doesn't it? makes you wonder</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0517">oh dear dear dear</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I saw her walking up from school this morning when I went to get my nails done walking with Treacle on her phone</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0558">she was going to work because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she made me laugh she said oh I do <trunc>chauf</trunc> chauffeur service now I said do you? she said yeah she said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is coming to have her nails done erm but because her car's in for service I'm going to pick her up at twelve o'clock</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1146" who="S0558">going to pick her up at twelve o'clock and then I assume she's got a <trunc>d</trunc> so I think she's kind of coming in her lunch hour</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0517" trans="overlap">where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s only in <anon type="place"/> isn't she?</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0517">so where was she picking her up from?</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0558">I think she must be on <anon type="place"/> avenue this week</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0517">no cos that office isn't there</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh no in <anon type="place"/> is it I who does she work for?</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0517"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1154" who="S0558">have they still got a</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh they've got <trunc>ano</trunc></u>
<u n="1156" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> depot or something?</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0517">yes they do still have a <anon type="place"/> depot</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0558">she's picking her up from there</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0517">oh right</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0558">and then she must be having her nails done in her lunch hour</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0517">and taking her back?</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0558">and then taking her back cos she did say to me in the past sometimes erm</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0517">gosh</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll dash out in her lunch break mm</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's the problem she does everything at a hundred miles an hour</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I wonder if she still gets up at the crack of dawn every morning and goes running</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0517">I don't know cos I don't know is she happy to leave the girls with nobody in the house? whereas obviously before <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would have been in the house wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0558" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0517">so I don't know I haven't asked her actually if she's still running but</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0558">but I said we'll have to erm organise for us all to get together</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0558">just haven't had a free</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0517">no you've been out every weekend</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0558" trans="overlap">every weekend and we're out this Saturday we're out next Saturday we're doing our planned Christmas walk in the Peak District</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0517">who?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0558" trans="overlap">with dad us four and dad</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0517">oh well that'll be nice</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0558" trans="overlap">which is what we planned to do</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0558" trans="overlap">over the Christmas period but it was raining so we did a plan B which was a trip to Ikea</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0517"><trunc>ri</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1182" who="S0558">cos dad <trunc>wa</trunc></u>
<u n="1183" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0558">dad had</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I know dad had commented on the replacing his office his chair at his</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0558" trans="overlap">desk like and he'd said he liked ours and we said well we got it from Ikea blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay yeah they do do good stuff</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so as it was raining we said shall we do the plan B and go to Ikea?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0517" trans="overlap">ah so you're going</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0558">so erm</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0517" trans="overlap">next weekend?</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0558">so next Saturday we're doing that</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0517">and the weekend after it's half-term and we are away</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0558">yes you're going away</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0517" trans="overlap">come round quick hasn't it?</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0558">yeah I know cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said about that potentially for you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to come round I said that's what I'd got in my head but they're away on holiday</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0558">they're going skiing so yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was telling <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0558">skiing and skiing holiday and things Friday night</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0517">has he</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0558" trans="overlap">was yeah</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0517">has he booked his skiing lesson yet? I haven't asked him</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0558">I don't know actually I forgot about that yeah his</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0517">I've booked mine</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0558" trans="overlap">fifties plus</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0517">fifties plus</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0558" trans="overlap">skiing lesson</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0558">bless him</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0517">I've booked mine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh can I come and watch? I said no you cannot it's not a spectator sport <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0558">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got no intention of doing any skiing has she?</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no she hasn't</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0558">she'll just go to the spa</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0558">so I'm sure you'll join her a day or two</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0517" trans="overlap">at some point yeah I've <trunc>d</trunc> I wouldn't do it for a week though</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0558">the spa?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0517">yeah I think she'll get bored</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I've told her this but she said oh I'm just gonna take lots of books oh I'll have a glass of wine and a book I'll be happy and go in the spa and which is fine but you know it's one thing doing it in the sun isn't it</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0517">but not indoors for a <trunc>w</trunc> I I anyway</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0558">she said she's confident enough to get in a taxi and go down to town on her own</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0517">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0558">she said</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0558">I feel confident enough she said I've got enough lingo to</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0558">to sort of not be too exposed as a</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah no she could do that</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0558" trans="overlap">a traveller you know</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's a good point</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0558">so she said she'll do that</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but erm</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0558">and go and have a wander round town</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0558" trans="overlap">is the town is it a big town?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0517">I've no idea <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1244" who="S0558">have you never been down to the town?</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no idea</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0558">well when you've gone then</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's never been there this is a <trunc>diff</trunc> totally different place we're flying to a different airport</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0558">oh <trunc>rea</trunc></u>
<u n="1249" who="S0517" trans="overlap">we're in the mountains</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh well no ours is a</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I assumed this was</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no hers is a beach hers is a beach holiday</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0517" trans="overlap">hers is on the sea this is in the mountains obviously we're going skiing</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0517">erm</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no it's no we're flying to a different airport and erm</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's a three hour <trunc>tr</trunc> no totally different area so I've no idea what it's</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0558">so just</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0517" trans="overlap">gonna be like</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0558" trans="overlap">or well they'll be in Thailand won't they? or just coming back from</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0517">erm</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0558" trans="overlap">that'll be a nice break for them all won't it?</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0558">cos</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0558" trans="overlap">just as they come back they'll have the week</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0558">to the house</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0558">to themselves</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0517">that's right</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0558">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said so is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> kind of living there? she went well yeah and I went and are you okay with that? and she went well I've gotta be haven't I? and it I didn't like to say well no actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you don't have to be</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you don't have to no</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0558">but I thought we were in a really busy pub</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0558" trans="overlap">you could barely hear do you know what I mean? but I wanted to say well well actually no if you're not happy with it you don't have to put up with it</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0517">no but she does I mean in fairness I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s quite a lot too</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0558">does she?</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0558">where does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> live?</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0517"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1288" who="S0558">so how did they meet? was it work or</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0517">it wasn't work I can't remember now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you know I can't remember was it through a friend of a through a friend of <trunc>fr</trunc> I don't know</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0517">I don't know</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0558">they're quite keen on each other</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0517">seem to be I mean it's been going on a while hasn't it now?</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0558" trans="overlap">a while hasn't it? are they they were together before how long were they together before <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wedding?</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0517">well</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0558" trans="overlap">cos he's been travelling hadn't and he</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they'd only just got together when she <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went off to Australia do you remember?</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0558">that's right</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0517">they hadn't really spent any time together because <trunc>h</trunc> they'd sort of got together but then he'd gone off travelling so they spent all that time skyping or on Facetime</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0517">and then she went off to <trunc>Aus</trunc> to Australia then that didn't work out</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0558" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0517">so she ended up</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0558" trans="overlap">going</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0517">visiting him in China didn't she?</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0558">that's right she did yeah</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so that was I think that was just the year before wedding</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0558">that's right</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0517">so when was the wedding?</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0558">and then she came back</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0517">she came back and then he surprised her for the wedding</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and then he came back for the wedding didn't he?</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0517">yeah and it they'll they'll they'll have been married two years this <trunc>Ap</trunc> this May</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0558">gosh</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0517">so</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0558">hasn't time gone?</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0517">I know so I suppose about three three years they've been together haven't they? three and a half years</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0517">yes cos they'd got together in the summer before the wedding so</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0558">so I wonder if they'll sort of look at perhaps getting somewhere to live together or</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0517">well I don't know I think that was maybe the hope <unclear/></u>
<u n="1322" who="S0558" trans="overlap">has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a good job? is he settled in work and that?</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0517">he's self-employed he's erm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0558">is it with his leggings or something?</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he's importing these leggings but he's doing very well at it cos apparently he's given up his job at <anon type="place"/> now he had a job at the phone shop</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0517">just I think that was only part time but just as a like a regular thing but his his leggings business is doing very well he's VAT registered now so he's got a high whatever you have to have as turnover</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0558" trans="overlap">what's so special about these leggings?</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0517">I don't know I think it's just quantity rather that quality to be honest <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1330" who="S0558" trans="overlap">have you had any?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0517">no I'm not a leggings wearer</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0558" trans="overlap">who's he selling to?</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0517">he sells them on Ebay</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0558">oh just on Ebay?</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0517" trans="overlap">apparently if you put them up in put put it up it comes up</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0558">he's the top one</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0517">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0558" trans="overlap">what just put leggings?</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0517">do you know I don't know I've never done but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said he you know he's got a good ranking on the internet he just he just er sells them on the internet so basically imports them in cheap from China and just sells them off on Ebay and his his turnover's huge</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0558">really?</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0517">and he's VAT registered now but he looking at doing some some other business but he he hasn't told us what it is yet <pause dur="short"/> but anyway so</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so he's a bit of an entrepreneur</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0517">he is a bit of an entrepreneur I know he's been in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about patenting something but again don't know what</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0558">don't know</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0517">he's keeping it all a bit close to the chest at the moment erm</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0558">what's his family? what's their background?</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0517">erm he's got a sister his mum and dad are are divorced but they're er fairly recently I think did they split up while he was travelling? so <pause dur="short"/> I think last Christmas cos obviously two Christmases ago he was away for Christmas but then last Christmas not the one just gone but the one before he came to us on Christmas day in the afternoon to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and he was a little bit subdued I think and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said afterwards I think he's just feeling it cos this'll be the first Christmas his mum and dad have been separated</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0558" trans="overlap">separated</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0517">that he's been there for and she said I think he was a bit conscious that he'd come out to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and his sister had gone to her boyfriend's leaving the mum by herself so he didn't say long he was only there</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0517">an hour and then he went I don't can't even remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> may have gone back with him but er yeah so so I don't I don't know whether she's got another boyfriend or anything yet I haven't heard but so he just lives with his mum</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0558">how old's his mum do you know?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0517">I think she's about our age</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0558">yeah is she? mm</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0517">same sort of age</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0558">mm mm</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0517">but it was funny cos not long after they had been together I must have told you that story she erm she was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like getting to know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and asking what about her parents</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0558" trans="overlap">her mum?</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0517">yeah the <trunc>m</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was asking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about her parents and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was just saying what they did and like the mum went <vocal desc="gasp"/> that man that does <anon type="place"/> oh that lovely man? oh I'd give him my last penny oh</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0558">oh that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and she's <trunc>si</trunc> he'd signed her up and er she'd said</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> I'd give that man all my money that</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0558">ah</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0517" trans="overlap">what a lovely man and er and she knew</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0517" trans="overlap">exactly who <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad was just from erm</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0558">yeah from yes I remember that</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1374" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1376" who="S0558">oh bless</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0517">so that was funny</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0558">oh I know I was telling <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> Friday night he charms the ladies</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0558">she said does he? and is said oh yes I've heard it firsthand <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said and you want to see their eyes sparkling when they talk about him she went <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're going to have to tell me about this</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I can imagine it's like yes his charm's long since worn off on my sister</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0558"><trunc>ye</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1383" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0558">and er what was she said? oh she said they can have him she said er</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1386" who="S0558">she said er I wouldn't be without him she said but you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1387" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that sounds about right</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she's doing her</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0558" trans="overlap">do you want another drink <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0517">I will do in a minute <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's doing her bedroom up but she talks about it as my bedroom and I pulled her up on this on Saturday</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1393" who="S0517">I said your bedroom? well you know what I mean I let him in</u>
<u n="1394" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1395" who="S0517">told him to decorate my bedroom and my en suite she said I don't let him in the en suite well he goes in to clean it she said but he doesn't use it</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1397" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> lazy cow</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I erm</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1400" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on Friday night we were coming out and I said oh god I said I said you're so much alike you pair I said your mannerisms and everything</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0517">who?</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0558">you two</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0517">me and her?</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0558">oh god yes I said</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0558" trans="overlap">you're so much alike you pair I said er as soon as I arrived you said something to me I said and it like talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0517">oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1408" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and erm even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he said my god he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are so alike</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really? oh</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0558" trans="overlap">their mannerisms and</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0517" trans="overlap">don't say that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1412" who="S0558" trans="overlap">how you speak how you speak</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0517" trans="overlap">don't say that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1414" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah how you speak god you are you're so alike</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh no and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps telling me that I sound like you sound just like nanny then mum said oh don't say that it's it's the way you go you know you know</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he said oh you do you sound just like nanny oh no</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0517">before</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0558" trans="overlap">when's your mum due back? must be soon</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0517">erm <pause dur="short"/> the did she say the fourth the fourth or the fifth? I couldn't <trunc>remem</trunc> I can't remember whether she's leaving</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0558">six weeks she went for didn't she?</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0517"><trunc>si</trunc></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0558">was it six or</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well <trunc>n</trunc> it was longer actually she went on the ninth of December</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0558">oh gosh yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to the fifth of February</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0558">yes the</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's fifty-nine days and I know that because <vocal desc="laugh"/> she wanted to go for longer but her house insurance was invalid <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1430" who="S0558">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0517" trans="overlap">if she stayed longer that sixty days</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0517">consecutively away</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I'm surprised <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> haven't gone and lived there as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did that time</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's just a bit out it was a bit out of the way for <pause dur="short"/> I can't even remember why <pause dur="short"/> but actually no they didn't I don't think they were even asked cos you know there was all that</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0517">so with mum and anyway no but erm</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0558" trans="overlap">it's better now though isn't it?</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0517">oh yeah it is better but he he's er</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0558">yeah do you</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but no</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0558" trans="overlap">still think there'll always be a little bit of a <pause dur="short"/> air now?</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah but I think that's just my mother now getting a bit old and a bit</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0558">mm cantankerous</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0517" trans="overlap">turning into my nan yeah I do actually</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0517">without dad being here to <pause dur="short"/> cos I think she probably always had that tendency to go a bit you know funny</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0517">but dad would never let her do it</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0517">but of course he's been gone what?</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0517">six years now</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0558">six years</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0517">so I think that's likely to be just</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0517">one of those but erm</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0558">er a sort of a <pause dur="short"/> her own true expressions if you like</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0517">well yes</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0558" trans="overlap">being allowed to</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah she's got nobody sort of monitoring it</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah nobody sort of</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0517" trans="overlap">or or saying</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0558">toe the line in</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0517" trans="overlap">having a word yeah</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0517">oi watch it you</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> type of thing</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah watch what you're saying there yeah</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos er obviously he was totally <trunc>diff</trunc> anyway so no they are alright but yeah she's due back it's either the fifth or the fourth Thursday Friday I can't remember whether she said she was leaving New Zealand</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0558">you haven't gotta pick her then?</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no no no</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1475" who="S0517">but I did say I'm put her some erm</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0558">I know she's got the taxi</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0517">she's got the taxi</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I'm only joking</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0517">I did say I put some</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1481" who="S0517">some food in the fridge and turned the fridge on cos she turned her fridge off</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0517">I know why would you do that?</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0517">but she said there's nothing in it</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0558">yeah but</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so she turned it off with the door open</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0558">oh so so</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so it's all you know</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0558">been cleaned and everything</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>ye</trunc> oh of course the whole place is spotless</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0558" trans="overlap">have you been over to check?</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0517">yes a few times</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0517">you need to come over actually</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1497" who="S0517">well I wasn't sure if she had a mouse</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0517">I know I know</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear>I saw</unclear> a mouse <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1501" who="S0517">oh well I didn't see a mouse but</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1503" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's got she's got this huge cupboard in the hall and there's a oh I don't know some sort of funny pipe thing in there I'm not even sure where from and she'd it had had a little drip so she'd left it with some newspaper down so one of my jobs was to check that</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0517">it wasn't dripping or if it was she said it was really really tiny so it was nothing bad's gonna happen but obviously if that paper got damp</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0558" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0517">change it this was one of my jobs anyway at the front of that cupboard she's got a Tupperware with her birdseed in cos you know what she's like</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0517">for feeding the birds and the lady in the flat behind was coming in to fill up all mother's birdfeeders</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0517">so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1512" who="S0558">bless</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0517">so she had the seed in a Tupperware but then she'd bought in a big bag in bulk because it was</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0517">on offer and that's just in like a like</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0558">like the hessian type plastic</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0517" trans="overlap">like plastic like not even <trunc>he</trunc> yeah just plastic bag really</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0517">and there was a bit of there <trunc>wa</trunc> there was that was inside a carrier bag and the carrier was a bit erm shredded and inside the bag of seeds was the bits of carrier bag and I put my hand at the back to check that the paper wasn't damp and the paper the newspaper was a bit shredded and I thought</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0558">it's gonna living in the bag of seed</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0517" trans="overlap">there's gonna be a mouse so I wasn't sure there were no droppings anywhere and she had a stack of newspaper should I have needed it that wasn't touched</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0517">and she also had some toilet roll in there that was in a in a like a pack of nine or whatever unopened but that hadn't been touched either so I just wasn't sure anyway I came away but a couple of days later I went back with a tin to put the the <trunc>s</trunc> the seed</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0558" trans="overlap">the bag yeah</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0517">that was just in a carrier bag inside the tin</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0517">and I thought okay I'll I'll put that in there the other big of seeds in a in a Tupperware so you know no there's no other food no other food anywhere and I did go back and and it was just that it was as I had left it so part of me thinks maybe a mouse came thought mm seed isn't for me and hasn't bothered coming back</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and went</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0517">cos I don't know do mice eat seeds? I mean it's birdseed</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0558">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0517">do they? but it was alright I cleaned it up</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1535" who="S0517">I cleaned it all up and I've put into the tin and and that was Saturday and I haven't been back since but I sent her a a just an email saying no you haven't got a mouse mum don't worry about it it's fine</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0558">well I I</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0517">so</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0558">I got some bird food once can't remember what container it was in now but I took the lid off and there were two little mice going</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1540" who="S0558">in the shed we used to get them regular in the shed</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0558">you know cos these</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0558">I think they used to get they used to come into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cage I think</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0558">and you know</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0517">when we had our playhouse and first started putting seed out there was a</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0517">there was a mouse under the <unclear>glass</unclear> so I was oh I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't want that just</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0558">alright</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0517">oh I know they are</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I know they're vermin and spread disease but they're they're got you know they've got to live</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but anyway so I'm just keeping an eye on that</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0517">I'm just keeping an eye on that</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah cos it what where why would you need toilet roll or paper if you've got seed to sleep amongst and just</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0517">well it's probably in the tin now then yeah who knows? anyway it didn't appear to be I didn't see it</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0558">did you empty the bag into the tin?</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0517">no I just lifted the bag up and put it</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0558">and put it in?</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0517" trans="overlap">put the lid on suffocated it if it's in there</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh it's so it'll be dead now anyway if it was in there</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't think well no I would have seen it wouldn't I if it was in the bag? wouldn't I?</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0558">is it a clear bag?</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0558">oh so it's not one of them</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's a clear bag</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0558">big ones like I get?</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no it's about it's about this big</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0558">oh I yeah oh</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but it's clear</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0558">oh and there was no visible hole?</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0517">well it was open the bag was open</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0517">at the top so and there was a bit of shredded carrier bag inside it was obviously it she'd obviously had bought the bag</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0558" trans="overlap">see but he might have got in</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and it was inside the carrier bag</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0558" trans="overlap">and he can't get out so he might have died anyway might have got in</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0558">and can't get out</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0517">so eventually some</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0558" trans="overlap">even before you put it in the tin</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so eventually when somebody scoops</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0558">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0517">they might get a</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0517">anyway</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0517">I don't know but</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0558" trans="overlap">let your mum sort it yeah</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0517">there was no <trunc>dr</trunc> there was no erm droppings or anything</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0558">cos we were walking erm we were walking out once if you go onto the canal and do a left and go round them woodlands and there was this big erm big bin and we thought what's that? so we had a look at it was</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0558">all seed for birds and that and there was a couple of dead mice in there that had obviously got in but they couldn't</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh couldn't get out well maybe I have trapped it but anyway anyway I don't know I'll send <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> round if there's a mouse</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0558">yes and pops</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0517">yeah and pops he got the first mouse</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0517">that there was ever that I must have told you that story where my mum when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was first seeing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so how long ago is that now? how <trunc>l</trunc> they've been married twenty-six twenty-seven years gotta be you know thirty years ago and I still lived at home and we had a dog and mum said that there was a mouse under the sink where she kept the dog biscuits</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0517">did I tell you?</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0517">and erm and so I think she'd put a mouse trap in there right at like teatime or something thinking that maybe the next it came out at night and maybe the next morning she was all psyched up for it the next morning well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came to visit <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was about oh probably about eight o'clock cos that was in the days when he was on <anon type="place"/> and he'd come from Cubs</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0558">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0517">so he came round and er he stood in the kitchen eating a piece of toast cos you know my mother liked to make him a piece of toast after he'd done his Cub duties</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0558">ah</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0517">and er the dog was there <trunc>sh</trunc> so she went in the cupboard to get a biscuit for the dog and there was a mouse in the mousetrap and she just squealed I've never heard her scream so much and you know how she like <vocal desc="laugh"/> she just literally she just slammed the cupboard door she ran</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1609" who="S0517">from the kitchen out through the kitchen all down the hall and collapsed in a heap by the front door</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1611" who="S0517">she just collapsed in a heap going oh my god there was a mouse there was a mouse <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1612" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1613" who="S0517">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was just stood at the sink and I can still see him now just munching on his toast finished his mouthful and he went so do you want me to move than for you then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1615" who="S0517">and he's still eating his toast and she was just in a heap squealing in the hall</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0558">oh my goodness me</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it was the <trunc>fu</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> so he said I'll just finish my toast</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1619" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he opens it up and he goes oh yeah caught a mouse</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1621" who="S0517">she said I wasn't expecting to find it till the morning I was ready for it tomorrow morning I wasn't ready for it tonight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1622" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0517">she'd only just put that trap in there</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1625" who="S0517">oh it was just so funny the way he just like</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0558">oh dead calm</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0517" trans="overlap">watched her go calmly</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1629" who="S0517">carried on eating and he said do you want me to move that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1631" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1632" who="S0558">he is dead calm though isn't he?</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0517">she <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1634" who="S0558">good lad that</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0517">she was and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were just wetting ourselves laughing at her</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0558">oh god</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but er no I'd have been the same if I'd have opened the door but it was just</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so funny just she I've never seen her run so quick</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0558">it is scary particularly when you're not expecting</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0517" trans="overlap">when you're not expecting it she just ran so fast</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0517">and fell in a heap</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1646" who="S0558">well no they're not very nice they're not very nice <vocal desc="laugh"/> we had a mouse in the back room once</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0517">we had one in our lounge</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0558">yeah and that</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0517" trans="overlap">in fact didn't I come up to you and borrow your traps? didn't we come up here?</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0558" trans="overlap">did you? did I yeah I think you did yeah I think you might have done</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0517">that was a few years ago now</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0517">somebody had left I think it was it was er just after Christmas</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear>the front door was open yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="1655" who="S0517">well it was just after Christmas and there was <trunc>cho</trunc> they really like chocolate don't they?</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0517">it turned out there was a load of chocolate and wrappers behind the settee I imagine <vocal desc="laugh"/> one of the boys had you know</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0517">Christmas it gets everywhere doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0558">oh it does</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>ye</trunc>yeah we had a mouse cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1662" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0517">didn't believe me till he saw it with his own eyes</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0517">I was hopping around the furniture screaming</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1667" who="S0517">yeah I didn't like it</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0517">he was just laughing at me I said no no no no I'm not stopping with a mouse in the house <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1670" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0517">just have visions of it running over you in your bed <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1672" who="S0558">oh I know spiders I don't like</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0517">oh no</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0558">don't like the thought of spiders</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0558" trans="overlap">walking over me</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0558">when I'm asleep</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0558">oh no I can't</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s rubbish with spiders is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> any good?</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0558">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <trunc>ok</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s brilliant she'll just pick them up in her hand</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is very good</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have woken him up before now <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's gone to bed</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and you woke him up?</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0517">he's gone to bed and I went into my bathroom and of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not there is he? and I was <vocal desc="gasp"/> there was this huge spider so I told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's as bad as me he was screaming and hopping so we woke <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0517">I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I can't I can't go to sleep I can't rest there's a</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no no I couldn't no</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0517" trans="overlap">there's a spider in my en suite</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0558">no no</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so we literally we woke him</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0558">I won't if it was in the same room I can't no</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we woke him up to move it</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0558">oh bless him</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know the poor lad</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1699" who="S0517">and he was quite calm about it</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0517">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s rubbish he's like a big girl honestly</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0517">he squeals <vocal desc="laugh"/> of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> being <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know what it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> he'd put it put a glass over it and <unclear/> was carrying and dropped it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1704" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1705" who="S0517">and ended up <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos he</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> dropped it</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0517">he's so clumsy so and he was doing it for us so we can't moan <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1708" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1709" who="S0517">but he's so clumsy he dropped it so he starts you know running <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1710" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1711" who="S0517">so he's like with the glass and then he managed to chop a leg off</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0558">oh no</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know it was awful</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the whole thing was very inhumane but</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it was very it was all so of course then we're having a go at him oh look what you've done to that spider <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1718" who="S0558">you've chopped and then he puts him in the <trunc>c</trunc> freezing cold I suppose</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0517">and he puts him out in the freezing and he goes so what? you've woken me up <vocal desc="laugh"/> now you're having a go at me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1720" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1721" who="S0517">well next time I'm not gonna do it mm you know</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1723" who="S0517">well thank you thank you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for getting up and doing this</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0517">but really <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going he's so clumsy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1726" who="S0558">oh dear me how funny</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0517">I don't know</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0558">funny isn't he? oh dear I need a wee <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1729" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0558">am I alright?</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0517">alright I'll stop</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0558" trans="overlap">do you need to just carry on I'll shout</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0517" trans="overlap">are you gonna have another no don't are you gonna have another cup of tea?</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
