<text id="SA6K">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:44:15</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0262 S0301 S0304</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At the family home in Harston, Cambridgeshire.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Discussing a film we’d been to see at the cinema, a recent debate held In Cambridge about how to teach history, politicians, discussion about the current national curriculum in England, talking about one’s education at school. Talking about how to organise Higher Education degrees, and linked to industry based experience.</topics>
		<activity>A family having dinner together.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0301">
				<exactage>73</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Reading</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0304">
				<exactage>44</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ayr</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>advertising director</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_1</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0301">that we we are culturally all Europeans</u>
<u n="3" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0301">you know the fact that he could play that on the piano and she could sing it</u>
<u n="5" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0301">was the same piece of classical music</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">did you know what it was?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0301">no I don't actually know what it was a er <pause dur="short"/> I think it was probably something by Schumann but I but I couldn't actually quite place it</u>
<u n="9" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0301">but but it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0262" trans="overlap">how much it kind of really meant something to her as well it was just you know incredible</u>
<u n="12" who="S0301" trans="overlap">well to him you know he was saying you know sorting through the music and saying oh gosh you know erm this this this this brings me back to <unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can play this one yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0301">and it and you know and <trunc>h</trunc> and here they were erm absolutely sworn dreadful enemies but but sharing the same culture it was that was the last sort of bizarre thing I suppose about fighting the Germans</u>
<u n="15" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it it would be I suppose even</u>
<u n="17" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh look at that</u>
<u n="18" who="S0301">erm I mean <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc>even closer in the case of the British because we're geographically closer to them</u>
<u n="19" who="S0262">yeah yeah I know what you mean I mean I mean I thought that was quite a poignant part of the film erm yeah it was er definitely the sort of more human side</u>
<u n="20" who="S0301">yes</u>
<u n="21" who="S0262">but erm my god eight weeks in the army and that was it you know</u>
<u n="22" who="S0301">yeah and I don't I don't think that would have I don't think that that would would have happened but apart from anything else was taken was taken bloody you know a week to get across the Atlantic for starters</u>
<u n="23" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0301" trans="overlap">and another week to get out into into Europe wherever they were <trunc>vir</trunc>virtually into into Germany and</u>
<u n="25" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0301"><unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0262">that bit's a little bit farfetched</u>
<u n="28" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0262">but made for a good story though I suppose in a way it's an analogy isn't it? it's like you're fresh off the boat whether you've had training or not you know and you're trying to get into a an already very formed erm bonded</u>
<u n="30" who="S0304" trans="overlap">tight-knit group</u>
<u n="31" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="33" who="S0304">kind of like a family</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah and nothing is more tight-knit than a tank crew</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262">but in a way I didn't think they were really really nasty to him</u>
<u n="37" who="S0304">what?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0262">in in a sense it was kind of well portrayed it was that you know levels of kind of nastiness and things like that doesn't really come into it it was kind of like you need to understand you need to kill people <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0304">cos our lives and everybody else's depends on it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262" trans="overlap">cos yeah exactly</u>
<u n="41" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/> absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0304">that's you know <unclear/> bits that dad's sort of mention goes with it as you know part of your training you know we're all civilians we're all taught that you know thou shalt not kill and if you do you go to jail for plenty of years</u>
<u n="43" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0304">and you know it's not a natural thing for people to do and if you are going to do it you need a bit of training to get you there</u>
<u n="45" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0304">or it would be at least and not just killing people but when the shit goes down so to speak once you know the the fire's on</u>
<u n="47" who="S0262" trans="overlap">or you would have thought</u>
<u n="48" who="S0304"><unclear/> you're fucking terrified you're scared witless</u>
<u n="49" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0304">and that's the bit where your training just you know don't even think about what you're doing you just do your training</u>
<u n="51" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>that's it</unclear> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0304">that kind of helps you get <unclear/> through it</u>
<u n="53" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0304">yeah just become the the all all <unclear/> you know get into it that will kind of get you through as well as</u>
<u n="55" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0304">you know trusting the people are a bit more wise or more experienced than you you can't <unclear/> what possibly might be going on</u>
<u n="57" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0304">he didn't have any of that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0262">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> pretty good job actually considering</u>
<u n="60" who="S0304">I mean the fact that I was actually quite impressed is without any training he knew how to load and unload thirty calibre machine gun in front of him</u>
<u n="61" who="S0301">yeah well I suppose they sort of showed him maybe</u>
<u n="62" who="S0304">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0301">the way they showed him how to use the grease gun as it's called like submachine gun erm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0304" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0301">the touch I liked was that Brad Pitt had this captured German erm <foreign lang="ger">Sturmgewehr</foreign> rifle which was the first of the assault rifles that the Germans <trunc>invo</trunc> invented I mean everybody postwar you know the grandson of it is the SA eighty and the M sixteen er and they were prized you know if you could get one they they were they were worth having and he obviously had got one from somewhere</u>
<u n="67" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0304">I'm <unclear/> sorry can we can I with the sort of lids yeah <unclear/> throw them over here and I'll put them in a bag and then put it back on the floor</u>
<u n="69" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yes yeah that's <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<event desc="sound of movement"/>
<u n="71" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0301">you must <unclear/> you need some</u>
<u n="73" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> little bit of kind of a third of each <trunc>pe</trunc>people's rice</u>
<u n="74" who="S0301" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="75" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0301">yeah I'd be interested to know exactly where it was in the English Midlands that that all took place</u>
<u n="77" who="S0262">yeah I'm trying to think of I haven't heard of a massive film studio there</u>
<u n="78" who="S0304">it's it's not really a studio</u>
<u n="79" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh really it's more like a land?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0304" trans="overlap">it's it's it's just an area of little land that they filmed to do all the Band of Brothers stuff</u>
<u n="81" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0301">they shut off <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0304" trans="overlap">so you know they made up sets yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so the towns stuff would've been done you know in a studio</u>
<u n="85" who="S0304" trans="overlap">then Private Ryan because it was Tom Hanks again came again erm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0304">and then you know they used it so all those things like all the uniforms all the it's all been made I've seen there was a picture of it in The Sunday Times around a couple of months ago</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0304">of the armoury of all this fake kind of stuff that they have left over</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0304">which you know people are using all around the globe to make sort of movies</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0304">so they're constantly <unclear/> it out</u>
<u n="94" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0304">you know even as much as Peep Show did a bit there's one of the episodes where</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0304">you know fat guy John Mitchell goes out with a guy who who finds out that he's actually a racist it's they were going to so even they a little show like Peep Show used bits of the material</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0304">and all the re-enactment stuff you know when you see a bit of history they tell the story on on discovery and then they have real people sort of walking around with stuff almost to sort of highlight the points <unclear/> they will pay for it</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0304">so whoever's <unclear/> made all this stuff</u>
<u n="103" who="S0262">it's a costume department <unclear/> each warehouse</u>
<u n="104" who="S0304" trans="overlap">yeah so <unclear/> Star Wars cos that doesn't get used <unclear/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0301">no</u>
<u n="107" who="S0304"><unclear/> stormtrooper not a great deal of call but if you've got a whole load of you know sort of military outfits or GIs and for the German army <foreign lang="ger">Wehrmacht</foreign> and the SS and some equipment and</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm have you heard of the TV programme? the children's TV programme which is like lives erm history erm sort of children? erm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0304" trans="overlap">you talking about the Horrible Histories?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0262">Horrible Histories <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s uncle produces that and erm or he <trunc>dir</trunc> has directed episodes of it erm and you're right and you know you look at the little segments of history that they do within one episode I actually quite enjoy watching it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0304">I think it's much as for adults as it is for kids</u>
<u n="113" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0304">I think it's hilarious</u>
<u n="115" who="S0262">but they <trunc>ha</trunc> like talking about costume it's like right just for about two minutes they've gone to re-enactment of they've gone to such an extent of you know erm really trying to make it as authentic as possible you know in the sense of but I mean they really try</u>
<u n="116" who="S0304">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and I and I could see you know the same costume wise they just bowl up to this lot and go can we have this that and the other? and they go yeah sure you can we've got it we've got it in stacks you know in shitloads so but Horrible Histories is great I think you're right it is just as much for adults <pause dur="short"/> have you seen it dad?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0301">no I haven't</u>
<u n="119" who="S0304"><unclear>spawned</unclear> all the books as well</u>
<u n="120" who="S0262" trans="overlap">about half an hour mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0304">it's massive it's a massive phenomenon now <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="122" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0301">but there there are cabinets who are very large who specialise in this</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0301">erm I went to a talk once by a guy who was <pause dur="short"/> the the cameraman erm for who was the guy? erm Paths of Glory</u>
<u n="126" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0304">Kubrick</u>
<u n="128" who="S0301">Kubrick Stanley Kubrick <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I love I love that film</u>
<u n="130" who="S0304" trans="overlap">over money wasn't it?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0301">yeah well no it was about working conditions</u>
<u n="132" who="S0304">oh right</u>
<u n="133" who="S0301">Kubrick was a monster</u>
<u n="134" who="S0262">mm but boy did he make good films <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah but <unclear/> but but one of the things this guy guy also did was he organised the battle scenes for The Charge of the Light Brigade</u>
<u n="136" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he enjoyed conflict</u>
<u n="137" who="S0301">and he got the Turkish army to provide lots of guys who could ride horses</u>
<u n="138" who="S0304">you mean all the extras?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0301">yeah the extras and he was able to outfit them all in the in the British uniforms because there was no no special effects</u>
<u n="140" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0301">you know?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0301">there was a cavalry regiment of four hundred guys or four hundred horses</u>
<u n="144" who="S0262" trans="overlap">just as is yeah yeah and that's what's really impressive</u>
<u n="145" who="S0301">and they were all dressed in the in the right uniforms</u>
<u n="146" who="S0262">yeah all charging</u>
<u n="147" who="S0301" trans="overlap">and he was telling us all charging and he said I was able to go to this firm in London</u>
<u n="148" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm and get everyone <unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0301">you want four hundred cavalry uniforms of the Crimean period</u>
<u n="150" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <trunc>no</trunc>none of this CGI business every single bloody extra had to have a you know uniform costume yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0301" trans="overlap">no well <unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0262">and a and a horse yeah was amazing</u>
<u n="153" who="S0304">well better <unclear/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh it's good <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0304">you know that book you were touching the Horrible Histories? if you get a chance to see one</u>
<u n="156" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0304">we'll record one</u>
<u n="158" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's very well done</u>
<u n="159" who="S0301" trans="overlap">they're good are they?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0262">oh they're really</u>
<u n="161" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah cos they're incredibly well written</u>
<u n="162" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0301">but they're they're actually acted by <trunc>pr</trunc> you know named adult <trunc>com</trunc>comedian or or proper straight actors erm blend of who you know forget it's a kids' show do a proper job</u>
<u n="164" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0262">no it's very well done</u>
<u n="166" who="S0304">and and if they call all the sort of you know <unclear/> Horrible Histories you can sort of hear it you know what happened to you in? well what was the plague like? or you know if you were the two princes in the tower what would life have been like?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0304">if you were well if you were in a trench what would it</u>
<u n="169" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but it's not just one theme throughout the episode it's actually cut up to</u>
<u n="170" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> beautifully yeah no oh</u>
<u n="172" who="S0262">you know right we'll jump from <trunc>ro</trunc> the Romans you know Julius Caesar <vocal desc="misc"/> <unclear/> then we'll do a bit of World War Two then we'll go <unclear/> so it's <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>it's never boring for the kids because they're just picking up <unclear/> I guess bits of information but then they'll reinforce it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0304" trans="overlap">it's a study aid you're not going to be able to pass an A level off the back of it</u>
<u n="174" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah you're not no but it's enough to get you interested in history I think and <unclear/> you went to a lecture didn't you about how to teach? well the curriculum was about how to include history in <unclear/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah since last Monday it was part of the <anon type="place"/> festival ideas and erm it around about it was chaired by a fella called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is a <anon type="place"/> historian who's written who's written extensively about the the Third Reich in fact <pause dur="short"/> but what they were they what they were talking about and he had a panel he had erm <pause dur="short"/> he had a woman who is a who has taught history in a secondary modern in in London for about fifteen years was really quite left and very much anti Michael Goves unlike <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's quite pro Michael she tells me</u>
<u n="176" who="S0262" trans="overlap">now see Michael Goves who's he?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0301">Michael Goves</u>
<u n="178" who="S0262">Goves yeah who's</u>
<u n="179" who="S0304" trans="overlap">Gove</u>
<u n="180" who="S0262" trans="overlap">Gove</u>
<u n="181" who="S0301" trans="overlap">he he was the secretary of state for education</u>
<u n="182" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he was?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0304">yeah but he became so contentious that these erm all parties have done this now apart from the erm UKIP they've all hired all the experts from the States who've got various people elected so Bush's campaign manager</u>
<u n="184" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><trunc>u</trunc>UKIP what's UKIP?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0304">the the Nigel Farage fascist party</u>
<u n="186" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear/>party oh right okay right</u>
<u n="187" who="S0304">so the Lib Dems Conservative Labour proponents of Obama or Bush all they've all hired have you ever seen The West Wing?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0304">you know the guys who get people elected and <unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm hm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0304">they don't just do presidents they do senators and cos there's lots of elections and <unclear/> those experts</u>
<u n="192" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay mm hm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0304"><unclear/> how divisive Gove was and turned round to Cameron and said with him you just can't win an election which I I I am I am kind of with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on this I sort of think that he was given almost back to this is the way school should be taught it should be interesting but it should be numbers it shouldn't be all the airy-fairy every kid is kind of right you're making a contribution even if you're a thick idiot well played for turning up and spelling</u>
<u n="194" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so he was really out on his own then on that one</u>
<u n="195" who="S0304"><trunc>he</trunc>he used <unclear/> teachers and people started hammering him <trunc>head</trunc><trunc>headmas</trunc></u>
<u n="196" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0304">in the same way who anyone who touches the NHS will get a nurse and a doctor and a midwife having having a moan</u>
<u n="198" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0304">most parents though generally seemed to quite like <unclear/> I liked what he was doing but <unclear/> erm party secretary he's they have you know</u>
<u n="200" who="S0262">so</u>
<u n="201" who="S0304">so he's got sort of he got a sort he's got a sort of important job but not the he's not the secretary of <trunc>edu</trunc></u>
<u n="202" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but not really in in the thick of it so to speak yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0304">which is well I I think it was a bit of a cowardice act I think he should've been allowed to continue and I think that should be part of the manifesto of the Conservatives</u>
<u n="204" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so was that Cameron's decision to shift him aside?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0304" trans="overlap">ultimately yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0301">mm yes</u>
<u n="207" who="S0262">okay because he was getting so much flak</u>
<u n="208" who="S0301" trans="overlap">but I mean he was he was being told that this guy was a liability as well that's basically why</u>
<u n="209" who="S0304" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="210" who="S0262">all because of what he was saying about education or other things too?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/> history</u>
<u n="212" who="S0262">god</u>
<u n="213" who="S0301">and the teaching of history</u>
<u n="214" who="S0262">and this actually had such a a negative effect? just goes to show how political education is isn't it?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely no absolutely that's absolutely right</u>
<u n="216" who="S0262">so anyway he's not but that that you were saying about the lecture that he was actually</u>
<u n="217" who="S0301">well it was more of a discussion actually</u>
<u n="218" who="S0262" trans="overlap">debate yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0301">they also had a Conservative MP who was Conservative MP for part of <anon type="place"/> and he'd read history at <anon type="place"/> so he had a sort of Conservative slant on them but I guy who actually knew what he was talking about cos he'd read history at <anon type="place"/> sort of thing erm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0304">so when parents are talking to you about their schools and their issues and stuff they kind of know what they're talking about cos they've got a bit of personal experience</u>
<u n="221" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0304">then I'm quite good at history I went to <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0262" trans="overlap">though when he went to school <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's quite a long time ago <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0301">but my ah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was also out of luck with with Goves because he said what you're actually trying to do why do you do history <unclear>at all</unclear>? what's the aim of studying history? so the aim of studying history is is is to teach analysis that's actually what it's all about and I the problems that I had about Goves was he <trunc>wa</trunc> he didn't teach analysis he he he want</u>
<u n="225" who="S0262" trans="overlap">wanted facts</u>
<u n="226" who="S0301">he wanted to be based entirely on the facts</u>
<u n="227" who="S0262">yeah the <unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0304" trans="overlap">but but again I think that's slightly disingenuous because I I I agree with you</u>
<u n="229" who="S0301">well with him I'm only repeating what he said</u>
<u n="230" who="S0304" trans="overlap">no no but I but I think what Gove was trying to do is but if you don't have then again I I look at philosophy <unclear/> philosophy <unclear/> you still have to go out and get a job and pay a mortgage and stuff <unclear/> unless you want to be a philosopher</u>
<u n="231" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0304">but again it's a bit like law people that do law don't necessarily go into law it's about analysis</u>
<u n="233" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0304">but unless you know the basics</u>
<u n="235" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0304">you can't perform analysis</u>
<u n="237" who="S0301">no</u>
<u n="238" who="S0304">so what he was what Gove was trying to say was up until a certain point you need to know the facts and then as you start getting into maybe sort of thirteen fourteen start going to GCSE and on</u>
<u n="239" who="S0301" trans="overlap">no no no he</u>
<u n="240" who="S0304">then you start laying more analysis and interpretation on it but you can't do that at sort of seven or twelve if you don't know the facts to start with</u>
<u n="241" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0301">no you're absolutely right I don't think there's any disagreement about that at all</u>
<u n="243" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0301">and that the the the rather left-wing woman who actually teaches history she she actually put up <trunc>wa</trunc> you know she said this is typical of what I teach and and it is exactly as per the national curriculum and it was the question was Europe erm in nineteen <trunc>f</trunc> pre the First World War was divided into two armed camps the <trunc>trip</trunc><trunc>tri</trunc>triple alliance and the <foreign lang="fre">entente cordiale</foreign> erm but I think the question was <pause dur="short"/> the comment on how these the interaction between these two armed camps led to the First World War that's actually quite a difficult and broad question I I was quite impressed I thought you know cor if you got sort of eh you got kids that are answering that</u>
<u n="245" who="S0262" trans="overlap">this isn't A level history this is actually GCSE history</u>
<u n="246" who="S0301">I think this was G yeah she <unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0262" trans="overlap">cos that could sound quite tough for GCSE</u>
<u n="248" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0304" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0301">now I'm not sure if it was A level or whether it was GCSE</u>
<u n="251" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I'd say that was GCSE</u>
<u n="252" who="S0262">really?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0304">yeah you've got you've got two to three years to teach people <trunc>what</trunc><trunc>wha</trunc>what's the answer to that?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0262">but I think that's the thing that you were saying the other night was trying to squeeze in what? one hour a week is it? to <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0301" trans="overlap">well she said that this was the real one <unclear/> way if they're real problems I only <unclear>get</unclear> an hour a week</u>
<u n="256" who="S0262">I think that might be quite difficult to get your kids to answer that type of question <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> in one hour a week</u>
<u n="257" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><trunc>biz</trunc>bizarrely that would be the sort of thing that Gove I think would be trying to argue against is you know things like history things like languages you need more time on the syllabus and and less pottery and less this and less</u>
<u n="258" who="S0301">well</u>
<u n="259" who="S0262">but apparently the hours that are soaked up on curriculum is actually maths still maths and well more so maths and English just to try to get them to literacy rate numeracy and you know an academic literacy</u>
<u n="260" who="S0304">see that's that's one of the things I've always found slightly funny about the argument is but isn't part of your job as a teacher to make sure that they've already got that?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0262">yeah yeah well you have to develop it that's right and you can develop it in other subjects</u>
<u n="262" who="S0304" trans="overlap">is is is <unclear/> we have to concentrate on otherwise we'd miss all the targets and figures isn't isn't <unclear/> hang on a sec maybe we need to be better at delivering this so that we can still do four hours of geography four hours of history six hours of another language with French</u>
<u n="263" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah well can't can't couldn't numeracy be taught in geography? like work out the G you know the like history you think about the numbers how many people died?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0304" trans="overlap">ah I</u>
<u n="265" who="S0262">so how many you know people were left? and think about you know academic history you still have to write an essay answer to your to your exam question you can do that in history you can do that in geography</u>
<u n="266" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I think it's absolutely fascinating</u>
<u n="267" who="S0262">you can do that in any subject</u>
<u n="268" who="S0304"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> turned around and went I don't actually understand why we taught subjects why aren't they things? <trunc>wh</trunc><trunc>wh</trunc>why isn't this all holistic?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah why don't we just <trunc>de</trunc>develop analytics?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0304">yeah but <unclear/> bits of French bits of German bits of bits of everything should be worked out in pillars and you should be taught across them so you get the skills across all them</u>
<u n="271" who="S0262" trans="overlap">or you know? <trunc>de</trunc>develop creativity yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0304">you wouldn't just need a geography lesson</u>
<u n="273" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0304">when you see geography in isolation and not realise oh there's bits of trigonometry that we did here</u>
<u n="275" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0304">will actually help when you do a survey for oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah well you're right in French say <foreign lang="fre">combien</foreign> and then you could ask them right so think about how much is it? does it sound like in French and then work out the number and then try and give <trunc>yo</trunc> give an answer so you at least know what you're getting back in your euros or whatever it is</u>
<u n="278" who="S0304" trans="overlap">you could be trying bits of</u>
<u n="279" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0304">do you remember the Eddie Izzard <unclear/> routine I'm sure I showed both of you where you know he knows certain bits he learned at school like he knows <foreign lang="fre">la plume de ma tante</foreign> he knows <foreign lang="fre">singe</foreign> he knows <foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0262" trans="overlap">laugh</u>
<u n="282" who="S0304">and he's going how do I chat a French girl up unless literally the cheeky monkey is on a bicycle and he's going round he's now <foreign lang="fre">au revoir</foreign> <foreign lang="fre">au revoir</foreign> <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0304">ah <unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he's he's got it in one</u>
<u n="286" who="S0304">yeah you teach a bit of maybe you teach a bit of the war and and <unclear/> how do they make stuff with jam? and how do they come up with the uniforms? and do the fake passes?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0304">and what French German would you need to try and get home again? make the whole thing <trunc>fuck</trunc> but link it</u>
<u n="289" who="S0262">but even just put a timescale on it you know <trunc>his</trunc>history put it on a continuum do you know what fifty years ago looked like? and they'd all sit there going no</u>
<u n="290" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> so kids go <unclear/> what French would I use to get home and not give myself away?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0262">right let's go back ten years twenty thirty just to even have a sense of what those timescales mean in time and that includes your working outs and things like what was the population size of the UK twenty years ago? <trunc>ho</trunc>how much was it in <trunc>fif</trunc> <trunc>c</trunc> fifty years can you give me the number? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0304">show them certain <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you know it's like it's not rocket science really but they can't seem to get away as you say from the subject-based curriculum</u>
<u n="294" who="S0304">and also it's it's very it's very wordy erm <unclear/> lucky enough <unclear/> and then dad got to hear me unfortunately on a Friday night once or twice bang on about <unclear/> we had the <unclear/> we have government contracts at <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> we managed to get the the erm the education guys to give us a course that we could get involved and <unclear/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0304">and you spend a bit of time with the teachers <unclear/> every and then again look I'll I'll <unclear/> that picture paints a thousand words</u>
<u n="297" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0304">and I know how my presentations work when I look at other peoples and mine's mostly images and I do all the talking</u>
<u n="299" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0304">cos that's where they go they'll see the images and go away and then end up being oh yeah I get what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s painting pictures for me</u>
<u n="301" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0304">some people will go away and it's like fifty bullet points and you got a hundred slides</u>
<u n="303" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0301">death by <unclear/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0304">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0304">but but there's bit of teachers stand up and they're all they talk a lot or it's read the book</u>
<u n="308" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0304"><unclear/> more visuals I mean you mentioned <anon type="place"/> earlier</u>
<u n="310" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0304">you know where is <anon type="place"/>? we were having that conversation</u>
<u n="312" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0304">I like <unclear/> people you know that's the rallying call when they were out hunting cos that was the <unclear/> they went from Hampton Court to go hunting <unclear/> forest it was woodland stags? what?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm mm mm wouldn't that be nice to know? if you if you're a kid and you're walking down Oxford Street and you go ah actually I can <trunc>pictor</trunc>pictorially think about this as a different landscape</u>
<u n="315" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I I think people sort of paint it and then turn London back through the ages do you remember erm? <unclear/> dad would definitely have seen this erm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0304">it was probably the first kind of interesting version of Orson Wells's Time Machine</u>
<u n="318" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0304">where he sort of sits in it and I mean it's quite a colour it's about the sixties and he presses the levers and does the little dials and you see him kind of zoom through London</u>
<u n="320" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah sort of whizzing by yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0304" trans="overlap">and all the factories and the windows and everything changes I've seen a version of that taking it through London all the way back to Soho and and <unclear/> people hunting</u>
<u n="323" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0304">but again <trunc>al</trunc>almost half an hour of that is <unclear/> standing up doing hour upon hour of teachers going this is Soho it was woods</u>
<u n="325" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0304">and kids sit there going I don't know if I've ever seen a wood I <trunc>li</trunc> I'm an inner city Birmingham kid</u>
<u n="327" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0304">what's a wood? and what's a wood in London?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0304">hunting? well what's what's that?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0304">how do you hunt a stag? why would you hunt? you know <trunc>it</trunc>it's it's too many words it's not enough images that's actually how the brain works</u>
<u n="335" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0262">but then the literacy there is that you know I suppose <trunc>e</trunc>erm it's really hard because they really do you have to use words to write their exam you know they can't paint a picture to express their understanding of <unclear/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0304" trans="overlap">look in the <trunc>mou</trunc> and even then I quite like the French schooling but I've seen enough French schools that do <unclear/> movies <unclear/> everyone sits in you must have done this in class you get Shakespeare and go right start reading right <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> your turn and everyone just sits there kind of bored reading without understanding it you're not bringing it alive</u>
<u n="339" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0304">I just think there's a lot of wasted time in class of people going through here's here's how we now teach it and kids don't get it</u>
<u n="341" who="S0262">I completely agree with you</u>
<u n="342" who="S0301">yeah <unclear/> I'm sure you're right</u>
<u n="343" who="S0262">so what was the outcome do you think though of the debate? was it still sort of open ended and <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I <trunc>th</trunc> I <trunc>th</trunc> there's no easy answers really is there?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0301">well there's no easy answers I I think well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> summed it up he said that probably when in his summing up he said probably most people now don't realise that originally the erm the history <trunc>nat</trunc><trunc>na</trunc>national curriculum was actually designed quite a long time ago over forty years ago</u>
<u n="346" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0301">by a group of experts by a group of historians and erm <pause dur="short"/> when it was presented it was signed off by Maggie Thatcher actually in her first erm in her first years of office she didn't like it but she said well you guys are the experts I'll sign it off</u>
<u n="348" who="S0262">because <trunc>s</trunc> her subjects at school when she was an education it weren't history it was it was geography and home economics</u>
<u n="349" who="S0304" trans="overlap">no <unclear/> chemist</u>
<u n="350" who="S0301" trans="overlap">no no she was a chemist</u>
<u n="351" who="S0262">was there chemistry?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0301">chemistry and law</u>
<u n="353" who="S0304">yeah mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0262">I remember reading about her that you know as a teacher you have like <unclear/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0304" trans="overlap">did you just say home economics?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0262">as a you know the certificate to teach training <unclear/> she had geography as her main subject if you look down and you drop down to the other subjects that she actually had to pass specialism in terms of you know I don't know why they did it like that</u>
<u n="357" who="S0304" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0262">you <trunc>w</trunc> you weren't just a geography specialist you had to</u>
<u n="359" who="S0304">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0262">you can see it but I think as well that she was she was chemistry but she had she had these other things</u>
<u n="361" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I feel kind of sexist she had to have home economics <unclear/> blokes had to have home economics</u>
<u n="362" who="S0262">that she had to do as well</u>
<u n="363" who="S0304">right <unclear/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so chemistry was her great passion I think but you're right she was a <unclear/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0262">chemistry teacher</u>
<u n="367" who="S0301">and <unclear/> yeah well she was <unclear/> oh no she wasn't she never she never did chemistry no Maggie never taught chemistry</u>
<u n="368" who="S0304" trans="overlap">she never taught straight into politics</u>
<u n="369" who="S0301">she well no she she worked as a chemist she worked in <unclear/> no as a chemist yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0301">she worked in you know</u>
<u n="372" who="S0304">ICI or something was it?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0301">yeah she worked on on the flavours of ice cream is what she actually worked on</u>
<u n="374" who="S0304">oh my god every time you eat vanilla or chocolate ice cream or Neapolitan that's Maggie</u>
<u n="375" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0262">but but I mean though she put <unclear/> something I read that she really got through to the you know teachers' unions and what not about we have to do this differently I remember that she had a great argument for I'm just trying to think of what it was now maybe it was bringing in a wider curriculum but anyway what was the point that you were saying? that she didn't like about history</u>
<u n="377" who="S0301" trans="overlap">erm that that you know erm what what so what what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said was he said that this was actually an attack on on something that we've had for a very long time and basically were quite satisfied with erm and you know and and Goves in he said in his view picked us not because he wanted to pick on the teachers or anything or pick on <trunc>hist</trunc>history establishment Goves picked this because it was all about establishing his position within the Conservative Party</u>
<u n="378" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0301">erm on the right wing of the Conservative Party he said that that was his take on the whole business and in the end he said yes we've made some changes and there's nothing wrong with changes but basically it's the status quo we we we actually he said common sense won we we won and there haven't been that many changes and we're all pretty well happy with it apart from the woman who said I I can I can fit the curriculum in an hour a week and I think we all believed her actually</u>
<u n="380" who="S0262">yeah but you know the thing I'll come back round to again is that the examining boards erm <pause dur="short"/> teachers can choose which exams their students can take</u>
<u n="381" who="S0301">yeah which which which board they take</u>
<u n="382" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so actually so which is a syllabus it's not a curriculum it's a syllabus</u>
<u n="383" who="S0304" trans="overlap">which they use for their examination</u>
<u n="384" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I always used to wonder</u>
<u n="386" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so for example at GCSE level I never learnt about World War One and World War Two anything like that I learnt all about the Tudors Lancashire Yorkshire you know? War of the Roses and a shitload about the suffragettes</u>
<u n="387" who="S0301">yeah cos girls would be interested in suffragettes</u>
<u n="388" who="S0262">presumably</u>
<u n="389" who="S0301">what what <trunc>wh</trunc> they would</u>
<u n="390" who="S0262">but I actually wasn't</u>
<u n="391" who="S0301">oh dear <unclear/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0262">erm so I would have preferred to have had more of a world view of history</u>
<u n="393" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0262">cos when you're talking to people when you're travelling yeah you can talk about suffragettes but not every person <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the country knows what I'm talking about so yeah if they <unclear/> talked about World War One World War Two we would basically have some kind of you know conversation about something or you know? any kind of war would be kind of useful we just didn't do war just girls <unclear>school</unclear> ancient war</u>
<u n="395" who="S0304" trans="overlap">did ancient war War of the Roses romantic war</u>
<u n="396" who="S0301">yeah well I I</u>
<u n="397" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and love in terms of the Tudors and you know the Stuarts and oh my god the <trunc>i</trunc> the ins and outs of who was sleeping with who and blah blah blah you know it's like right great thank you that's real useful</u>
<u n="398" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah but what <anon type="place"/> would argue you see that that doesn't make any difference that really if what you're teaching is analysis erm there's no reason why you can't learn analysis from whatever particular era eh period you're doing erm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0304" trans="overlap">you see and I might suddenly disagree that the bigger the fee the bigger the <unclear/> you're talking about</u>
<u n="400" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah it helps yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0304">the deeper the grey cells have to work</u>
<u n="402" who="S0301">well that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0304" trans="overlap">because I have a certain argument about brain circuitry</u>
<u n="404" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0304">I don't believe in god or anything I believe it's all brain <unclear/> <trunc>chemi</trunc>chemicals</u>
<u n="406" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0304">so it took to to the harder you go the more brain cells you're making which means in life kind of the smarter not more intelligent but the smarter you are if you're only looking at something that's kind of two-dimensional versus twelve</u>
<u n="408" who="S0301">yes</u>
<u n="409" who="S0304">it's like okay well can you play chess? well that's one thing can you do a Rubik's Cube? okay can you do a six-sided Rubik's Cube?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0301">anyone want any more beer?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0262">yeah I'll have a beer thanks</u>
<u n="413" who="S0304" trans="overlap">alright</u>
<u n="414" who="S0262">but the <trunc>suffrage</trunc> as you say the suffragettes you know vis-a-vis like a World War like complexities of that you're right because students who <unclear/> normally kids are quite curious <pause dur="short"/> eh when they're they need to have it broken up but at least there's something big enough to be curious about so if they're not really interested in that bit they might be interested in the politics of war they might be interested in the kind of like the actual strategic parts of war least it's big enough for somebody to attach a little bit of interest and curiosity to whereas I found that history for me was quite sliced and <unclear/> up already it was like you can only really move between this bit and that bit and I was like well if not actually interested in that bit it's not making it exciting for me I'm not curious enough to ask any more questions I now know that I know I just have to copy and just write what I see on the board that's not analytical that's just how good you are at memorising things and I'm actually not too good at that anyway so they didn't actually teach me that skill <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it didn't really work you know and I just think that was quite a shame really considering how much money you were paying for that education <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0304" trans="overlap">thank you <unclear/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="417" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0304">I mean actually the bit you you raised I remember being at <anon type="place"/> and it being a smallish conversation</u>
<u n="420" who="S0262">thank you</u>
<u n="421" who="S0304">erm but I always used to wonder why parents don't get more interested in it is is cos we were a public school <unclear/> but you had to do <unclear/> you had to do the <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0304"><unclear/> board</u>
<u n="424" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0304">which everyone kind of knew was as in fact everyone sort of used to talk about well can't we do the AEAEL? the allied and <unclear/> of London <unclear/> associated and and whatever it was board cos everyone seemed to be able to get an A in that</u>
<u n="426" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's the easy one</u>
<u n="427" who="S0304">and it was like all the thickos you knew who didn't get into your school who went to a <unclear/> you know you were at prep school with them</u>
<u n="428" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm <unclear/> or something yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0304">and of all the thickos that didn't get into your school all got As I'm like</u>
<u n="430" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0304">but <trunc>no</trunc>no one apart from no one at work or unis or anyone seems to mark this <unclear/> back where there's different schools</u>
<u n="432" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="433" who="S0304"><unclear/> so if you do the hard one and you get a C that equals twelve points if you do an easy one and get an A actually that's still only ten it doesn't become a point scoring system</u>
<u n="434" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no it doesn't it doesn't</u>
<u n="435" who="S0304">so no one in your twenties and thirties are going to fucking argue the toss</u>
<u n="436" who="S0262" trans="overlap">apart from <anon type="place"/> yeah but <anon type="place"/> is only to get into <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> it's not to get into any other university</u>
<u n="437" who="S0304">but you know</u>
<u n="438" who="S0262">that's got high sort of you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> if you pay all this money why why pay to just do as in be <unclear/> why pay <unclear/> give me the easiest ones cos I want my son at the best uni I can get him in</u>
<u n="440" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0304">or daughter <pause dur="short"/> never understood it</u>
<u n="442" who="S0262">but there's like other courtesies like</u>
<u n="443" who="S0304" trans="overlap">all the parents <unclear>go well</unclear> hang on a sec don't make them do the harder one make them do the most successful one</u>
<u n="444" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so many countries that do that do do national exams every like China I'll just give an example</u>
<u n="445" who="S0304" trans="overlap">there shouldn't be a different <unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0262">and there's what? there's how many thousands of children <unclear/> a year</u>
<u n="447" who="S0304" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0262">suppose they do it out of administration because they couldn't actually go oh look <foreign lang="chi"/> and you blah blah and duh duh duh will add all these different you know syllabi all across the <trunc>c</trunc><trunc>coun</trunc> anyway we have to know who's good we actually have to know who are the top five percent going through into their universities? who are the top ten percent? <vocal desc="misc"/> it's <trunc>str</trunc> it's strategic in a way because at least you actually really know you set it as a national examination <pause dur="short"/> we should bloody well know if they get into a Chinese university they are <unclear/> good and you can put a lot of work onto them cos you know they're good whereas you can't necessarily put a lot of work onto students at in in universities in the UK you really don't know whether they're going to cope you can't actually just land it on their heads <unclear/> intellectually achieve you know?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0304" trans="overlap">the one thing that becomes really interesting with with universities is and and again that you know if <unclear/> can we break all the rules what could you do? one <unclear/> universities is once you go to one it's fixed</u>
<u n="450" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0304">so say for example</u>
<u n="452" who="S0262">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0304" trans="overlap">and this is what the arguments for syllabus is</u>
<u n="454" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0304"><unclear/> say you don't go to <anon type="place"/> when you're doing your course and you haven't gone into <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> well then there there's a certain argument whether people are mature mature let alone intellectual in the way their brain but mature at different levels</u>
<u n="456" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0304">you know <unclear/> everything's got to be set by eighteen which is kind of ridiculous people go away on gap years do stuff come back read stuff and it's fixed</u>
<u n="458" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0304">if you start doing a course at <anon type="place"/> there should be a way of of going actually I'm going to fast track you through this</u>
<u n="460" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0304">and actually <unclear/> you're leaving <anon type="place"/> after the first year and going into <anon type="place"/> second year</u>
<u n="462" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0304">or someone from sorry <anon type="place"/> who's in the first year hasn't quite cut it is now going to <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0304">there needs to be freedom of movement of</u>
<u n="466" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0304">to to understand people <trunc>ma</trunc>matriculate mature and grow up and intellectually <unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0301">can you imagine the academic establishment agreeing to that?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0304"><unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0262">actually yes in a certain way because if you were working for <anon type="place"/> and you knew you were a tier two say you'd send me someone <unclear/> a tier three university but they'd <unclear/> tier three let's say that's a bit lower and you're working at say tier two and you're getting the top of the tier three and you're going great I've got something to work with here I can I know what to put on these students to actually get them to where I want them to be you're probably thinking great I don't have to muck around with all</u>
<u n="472" who="S0301">with the thickos we'll offload the thickos to <anon type="place"/> forever</u>
<u n="473" who="S0304">you're not really doing that from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> but I get where you're coming from</u>
<u n="474" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0304">but but the other thing that makes it interesting is you're now paying you know when when when I talk about this everything is kind of free</u>
<u n="476" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right but I would be fast tracked yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0304">if you're now paying for that degree</u>
<u n="478" who="S0262">if I was really doing very well at university</u>
<u n="479" who="S0304"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0304">rather than going to somewhere like <anon type="place"/> where you'll actually have more time <unclear/> and</u>
<u n="482" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0304">and you're paying the nine K and someone else is paying nine K and isn't getting something out of <anon type="place"/> cos they should swap with you at <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> for my money I deserve better than this</u>
<u n="485" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0304">I need to be looked after properly</u>
<u n="487" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0304">when it was all free now <unclear/> someone's going well <unclear/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's kind of like it</u>
<u n="490" who="S0301" trans="overlap">it was never free was never free <unclear/> you know? free at point of contact yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0304" trans="overlap">you're playing rugby for <anon type="place"/> so that's it you're staying <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well it well it is kind of like a <trunc>sp</trunc>sport in a way isn't it?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><trunc>sho</trunc>should be like should be like almost a sport there should be transfer markets</u>
<u n="494" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> based on merit</u>
<u n="495" who="S0304">based on merit</u>
<u n="496" who="S0262">which is good not based on money</u>
<u n="497" who="S0304">yeah or or the time you did an exam</u>
<u n="498" who="S0262" trans="overlap">because that's what it is based on at the moment <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's based on money or privilege</u>
<u n="499" who="S0304">which even then I still think is weird</u>
<u n="500" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0304">you're I know you're three years younger than me</u>
<u n="502" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0304">but in a sense you're two years</u>
<u n="504" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0304">because you're August versus September</u>
<u n="506" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0304">an accident of birth by days</u>
<u n="509" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0304">you'd be like mum you should have been trying to hang on for another <trunc>tw</trunc>twenty-eight days</u>
<u n="511" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0304">cos it meant different say education wise you know where are you? you know most people have already done their exams before you even get to your birthday</u>
<u n="514" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no that that's a very good point yeah yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0304">so there's you know why isn't it calendar year as well?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0304">why don't you do <unclear/> of people at the top end the first six months and then <unclear/> of people at the second six months</u>
<u n="518" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0304">there's all <trunc>sor</trunc> then again dad's dad's heard me bang on about this here's how I want to change the entire education system</u>
<u n="520" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but no I like the idea of a university thing is that it should be gives gives more scope for merit based erm achievement</u>
<u n="521" who="S0304">and growth at different stages</u>
<u n="522" who="S0262" trans="overlap">about academia yeah yeah it should be</u>
<u n="523" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I mean you <trunc>d</trunc> you done your A levels at seventeen</u>
<u n="524" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah <trunc>al</trunc>also</u>
<u n="525" who="S0304" trans="overlap">you might want to take a gap year you wouldn't go you'd probably someone sitting in your class could be almost a year and a half older than you</u>
<u n="526" who="S0262">and you might like your university like the campus but you might not actually like living in <anon type="place"/> for example so it's not just about based on merit can I achieve to go to <anon type="place"/> or whatever I'd really prefer to go to <anon type="place"/> university cos I quite like the idea of you know going into the hills and <trunc>m</trunc> having a walk or whatever but the idea is that geographical movement and mobility is part of the landscape in Europe at least and there's certainly international students know about that because they're coming in already as internationalism from China and from Vietnam so they already know what it feels like and they might oh I got it wrong I didn't like London I want something smaller but they won't do it because they're locked into the payment scheme it's absolutely you've got to pay up front as an international student</u>
<u n="527" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> transfer too</u>
<u n="530" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0304"><unclear/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0301" trans="overlap">and of course we're taught</u>
<u n="533" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and it costs money</u>
<u n="534" who="S0301">and and and of course you know the universities are earning off these students they don't want to lose them</u>
<u n="535" who="S0262">but it's not a bad idea because they have so many partnerships within the <trunc>ind</trunc> you know the global marketplace</u>
<u n="536" who="S0304" trans="overlap">then again the people I'm really talking about it's it's affecting UK students</u>
<u n="537" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0304">not really international students</u>
<u n="539" who="S0262">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0304">erm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0262">I think yeah I think you're right I think you know</u>
<u n="542" who="S0304" trans="overlap">cos cos the majority have got proper international students who are actually postgrads and you can do that anyway</u>
<u n="543" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0304">the majority of undergraduates are UK based</u>
<u n="545" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and that's more likely when you're going to get wrong</u>
<u n="546" who="S0304">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0262">as in you choose the wrong course or the wrong location or you just simply don't fit in or your <trunc>lic</trunc> lecturers aren't up to the task</u>
<u n="548" who="S0304">or you know the only the only <unclear/> you've got that you've got is you know <trunc>yo</trunc>you're very clever but you were a big fish in a small <trunc>p</trunc> in a small pond</u>
<u n="549" who="S0262" trans="overlap">because you might be very bright you know? yeah nobody notices you</u>
<u n="550" who="S0304">you're getting a first at <anon type="place"/> but <unclear/> you maybe want to get two two at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but they're not challenging you</u>
<u n="552" who="S0304">but if there was that freedom</u>
<u n="553" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0304">you know in a in in a proper meritocracy then you would thrive otherwise it's going to go oh I've got another two years at <anon type="place"/> I know I'm going to get a first here</u>
<u n="555" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0262">so <trunc>wh</trunc> so what you're saying is yeah so what you're saying is year one of your first year at undergrad you could say right everybody</u>
<u n="558" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> so what do you really do to achieve? you don't</u>
<u n="559" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah you are going to have your normal university exams but we're also going to have a look at the top five percent of that cohort</u>
<u n="560" who="S0304" trans="overlap">yeah we're looking statistically across the board</u>
<u n="561" who="S0262">and we're now going to give people an opportunity to see if they can get into the same degree pathway but at a different institution because that's just got that <unclear/> element to it</u>
<u n="562" who="S0304" trans="overlap">cos in a certain sense if you're all UK and and the Scots leave them out because <unclear/> about Scottish universities payment systems so you're all in England stroke Wales</u>
<u n="563" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm hm mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0304">and you're all paying roughly it's nine K to do <unclear/> or six K to do</u>
<u n="565" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0304">it's not another money issue</u>
<u n="567" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0304">and there might be certain people people who go oh but look this guy's going to be an <anon type="place"/> blue can we keep him?</u>
<u n="569" who="UNKMULTI" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0304">well then there's sports sponsorships there's extra things you can do the problem with the other thing I still find funny and <anon type="place"/> used to be quite good at it and still very good at it again to help all of this <trunc>wh</trunc>where is more of business coming into academia to help with this</u>
<u n="571" who="S0262" trans="overlap">wow they are shameless they do fuck all they really don't do anything enough <trunc>at</trunc> I don't think they really don't do enough</u>
<u n="572" who="S0304" trans="overlap">you know we had weird stuff with <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/> but there should be more businesses not just a milk round there should be more businesses helping getting involved and having people do internship and helping qualified people</u>
<u n="573" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0301" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0304">you know is this person talented? could they?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0301">well I I think it <trunc>dif</trunc> that differs from faculty to faculty</u>
<u n="577" who="S0304" trans="overlap">yeah but it but it shouldn't do there should be a there should be a national way of looking at this</u>
<u n="578" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it should do if yeah I agree with you he's <trunc>goi</trunc></u>
<u n="579" who="S0304">and sometimes most of the students don't know faculty <unclear/> until they turn up</u>
<u n="580" who="S0262">yeah they don't even know what the word means</u>
<u n="581" who="S0304" trans="overlap">they'll go oh shit I got lucky <unclear/> sat in a good seat</u>
<u n="582" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="584" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0304">you're sitting in the shit seat</u>
<u n="586" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah exactly yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0301">certainly the engineering faculty here in <anon type="place"/> university I mean they've got from all over the bloody place</u>
<u n="588" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but then cos <trunc>pe</trunc> you know industry is clamouring for their attention</u>
<u n="589" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0262">but I agree with you like if you're paying nine thousand pounds industry has got input into various different universities geographically or sort of strategically or whatever but there are some universities that are just not doing anything about industry input they're not partnering up enough they're not actually having any effect on the syllabus or the learning</u>
<u n="591" who="S0301">no</u>
<u n="592" who="S0262">or the curriculum I should say</u>
<u n="593" who="S0301" trans="overlap">but again I suspect that really would be faculty driven it would surprise me if there was any engineering faculty at any university in the United Kingdom that didn't have a considerable industrial involvement</u>
<u n="594" who="S0262">well engineering aviation anything scientific you know any <trunc>in</trunc>industry</u>
<u n="595" who="S0304" trans="overlap">it's it's slightly easier</u>
<u n="596" who="S0262">but you've got to think about industries in <trunc>hi</trunc> ah hospitality all the different other you know you know <unclear/> that they give yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I I think you'd have very very bright people <unclear/> who do mostly analytical degrees <unclear/> come into advertising</u>
<u n="598" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but financial</u>
<u n="599" who="S0304">most people don't come in cos they did media they come in cos they did you know I look at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as one of my best friends he you know is a <unclear/> at <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> just coming to do to do this</u>
<u n="600" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear/> industry yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0304">and and there's lots of people like this it's not <unclear/> buy another <unclear/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0262">no the acumen</u>
<u n="604" who="S0301" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="605" who="S0304">yeah the amount of kids who come in and go <unclear/> run an account you've got to make this account profitable</u>
<u n="606" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0304">and we don't just do any work we do the work that makes us money cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0301">yes</u>
<u n="609" who="S0304">and then <unclear/> what's that? it's <trunc>sh</trunc> it's so <unclear/> oh there's an engineering firm working with the engineering faculty it's not necessary what I mean</u>
<u n="610" who="S0301">no</u>
<u n="611" who="S0304">there there should be ways that business and <unclear/> comes into all of <unclear>academia</unclear> you all need to learn a bit about business how to run accounts</u>
<u n="612" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0304">you all need to know a bit about you all need to know a bit about human resources if you want to start your own business what do you need to do? and how does it work? If you want to without having to do an MBA to do all of this</u>
<u n="614" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah I think I I I think what you're talking about is professional skills yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0304" trans="overlap">cos this is skills that all of us whatever business you come into whether you're a law or you all need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah you do and industry can input into that</u>
<u n="617" who="S0304" trans="overlap">how to look after staff how to</u>
<u n="618" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0301"><unclear/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0304">and <unclear/> pool it pool the money pool the talent</u>
<u n="621" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah they should they should</u>
<u n="622" who="S0304">there should be like a little business staff college for students</u>
<u n="623" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0301">erm which the French which the French <unclear/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0304" trans="overlap">part of your three years make make it three and a half years and part of six months are spent being a part <unclear/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0301">which the French have got with <foreign lang="fre">École nationale d'administration</foreign></u>
<u n="629" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0301">erm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but then you have to actually go to one of those so you kind of know what you're getting</u>
<u n="632" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0304" trans="overlap">this should be built into your sort of</u>
<u n="634" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah I think it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0301" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="636" who="S0262">so erm there's this idea of erm learn as you earn erm sorry earn as you learn so the idea is that you know you're definitely going to have to pay money for your first degree but you can actually go and do as part of your degree no <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc>it's well thought out normally it's like you know do a bit of first year second year ply it on a bit more and then third year you'll come back into the fold and do exams but the idea is that you'll actually have a portfolio of learning and the industry provides the environment for you to learn and you can actually earn a bit of money so you really might use up all of your holidays it's not just like I'll bum off and go and see if I can find a part-time job this is actually no</u>
<u n="637" who="S0304" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0262">you'll you'll really come here to to do your studies</u>
<u n="639" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0262">but in your free time which isn't your free time this is actually part of your curriculum you are gonna go earn some money with this partnership that we've provided for you you'll come back and tell us what you've learned and we'll look at the whole thing of what you've learnt we'll take your exams we'll take your portfolio your coursework some odd things and that's a broader sort of picture</u>
<u n="641" who="S0301" trans="overlap">well it is I mean it's a bit it's a bit like that year out you did in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="642" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and it helps people to pay their way <pause dur="short"/> and you pay your way cos you know I earned what? ten thousand pounds a year when I was working for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Erasmus</u>
<u n="644" who="S0301">right</u>
<u n="645" who="S0262">which is when you were a student <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0301">that's a lot <unclear/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0304" trans="overlap">plenty <unclear/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well well it wasn't bad I mean I ate out pretty much every single night I mean it wasn't top restaurants but I mean this is like new to me I was like cool but yeah you're right that money I could probably really tucked away and saved and that could've helped me to when I was trying to find a job you know say at the end of my degree and I'd have a little bit of cushioning</u>
<u n="649" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0262">but also I would've made those contacts</u>
<u n="651" who="S0301">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0262">even if I didn't want to go for work to for exactly that company you always network and you find out who else you could go maybe work for and you could interview with them and they'll sort of say yes or no or I'll give you some practice at interviewing it's one thing that they really are bad at</u>
<u n="653" who="S0301">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0262">careers advice at universities no one knows how to interview it seems like no matter what they try</u>
<u n="655" who="S0301" trans="overlap">because the problem is I suspect people who are revising haven't actually worked in industry so</u>
<u n="656" who="S0262">they're very nice people but they're not right on the edge of it</u>
<u n="657" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0262">whereas at least if you're doing these kind of like you know the work experience thing in and out of your curriculum they might actually provide that as a one-day workshop let's all pretend that you're really going to pretend that you're really going to come and look for a job here now when you graduate let's all pretend or let's do it now</u>
<u n="659" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><unclear/> don't pretend get them to do it</u>
<u n="660" who="S0262">yeah let's actually see if you can get in or not yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0304" trans="overlap">set up set up systems do the do the stuff do the <trunc>psych</trunc> do the psychometric testing</u>
<u n="662" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0304">do this testing see how people cope under a bit of stress and a bit of pressure</u>
<u n="664" who="S0262">but you know lots of kids <unclear/> how to write their CV</u>
<u n="665" who="S0304" trans="overlap"><trunc>tal</trunc>talk to <unclear/> I know you all think you know social media because you all use Facebook and Twitter</u>
<u n="666" who="S0301" trans="overlap">that that that would surprise me</u>
<u n="667" who="S0304" trans="overlap">but you you you understand now you're a brand</u>
<u n="668" who="S0262">but it shouldn't be</u>
<u n="669" who="S0304">so so when you're using <trunc>some</trunc> don't do it in the way that when I'm when I'm thinking about hiring you for a job I look you up on the Web I see you're <unclear>bombing</unclear> every photo of the rugby club</u>
<u n="670" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0304">Linkedin is it is how to make yourself private <unclear/> you're a brand</u>
<u n="672" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0304">and the <unclear/> stuff you'd necessarily want people who are going to be prospective employers to see</u>
<u n="674" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0304">have a good time but keep it private set it up that so just giving people straight that you think you know social media I promise you don't cos as soon as you leave university and you go why don't I get a job dad?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0262">yeah well</u>
<u n="677" who="S0304" trans="overlap">and dad doesn't look at your Facebook page cos I don't know I I thought you were quite charming and a good young chap</u>
<u n="678" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0304">why aren't you getting a job? ring me up and I'll go <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not getting a job because do you want me to send you some links?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0301">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well I can tell you I can tell you</u>
<u n="682" who="S0304" trans="overlap">that's not supposed to be one at work because every work practice now has a sort of moral code</u>
<u n="683" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0304">there's an ethical code you have to buy into it we all do</u>
<u n="685" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah but the other thing is they don't know how to write CVs and they actually don't know</u>
<u n="686" who="S0304">mm I'm not I've seen millions of CVs and I'm going to be honest I'm not sure if I know the right CV</u>
<u n="687" who="S0301" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well I do think I think that's that's a problem everybody has but erm</u>
<u n="688" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no but I think it's easier when you're at an <unclear/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0304" trans="overlap">I can tell you stuff not to do I don't know how to make it brilliant</u>
<u n="690" who="S0262" trans="overlap">a CV when you're actually erm just graduating should be one of the easiest CVs to write</u>
<u n="691" who="S0304">oh when you're just graduating?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0262">yeah but they don't</u>
<u n="693" who="S0301"><unclear/> very much to say about <unclear/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah exactly so it's not that difficult <unclear/> blah blah blah</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
