<text id="SABT">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:29:24</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-01-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Masterchef, cooking, Christmas food, school dinners</topics>
		<activity>Talking about Masterchef, cooking, Christmas food, school dinners.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">okay <pause dur="short"/> was that upstairs?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">it was the fire alarm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whose it was</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll check I've this thing working <pause dur="short"/> I think that's okay</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">well the fire alarm's got a heat sensor so it's not really the smoke</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">which we know cos we filled the house with smoke recently</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">and it didn't set the alarm off</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm surprised that you would think it would be smoke</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">erm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">I think <pause dur="short"/> like it doesn't make sense that it just to be</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's maybe partly like serious smoke <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">like maybe like proper</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037">ah like black smoke not like bit of chicken that you've left on a bit long</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">death smoke <pause dur="short"/> yeah rather than just like a bit of sausage or something but</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">er what's on the TV tonight then?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">erm I think is MasterChef not on? Because it's not on on a Friday because like prime time television's on on a Friday</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">er I don't normally watch it on Friday I don't think</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh is it? No it's not on <pause dur="short"/> it's like erm like good things are supposed to be on the Friday</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it  but it  is on quite a few days <pause dur="short"/> it's on like</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">mm mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">it's on like Monday Tuesday or Wednesday or something isn't it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">because it was like before it was the erm the real ones <pause dur="short"/> like the real chefs <pause dur="short"/> the last series <pause dur="short"/> but this time it's  like the  like the like normal people <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right yeah so it's just like oh yeah the the general public</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037">but like they've totally changed the form haven't they because like do you remember when it was Lloyd Grossman? And it was just like three people standing behind like some plywood</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I remember those ones <pause dur="short"/> I remember the Lloyd Grossman ones with the er the black <pause dur="short"/> it was quite black <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">the the set?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">the the the set was sort of dark and like</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">I remember the music</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">the kitchens were the the kitchens were they had little kitchens arranged in a sort of a <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> there was four of them or something and they were arranged in a sort of square or something</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no wasn't there three of them? Oh yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">they used to sort of walk around erm in the blackness sort of going from the kitchen to little kitchen to little kitchen and er</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">he's funny <pause dur="short"/> because wasn't he a chef before Lloyd Grossman?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">I don't know</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037"><unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">he makes  he makes  the sauces doesn't he? He makes the</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">well did you hear about that sauce though like? One of his sauces like <pause dur="short"/> did they kill somebody or?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">honestly</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">so no no look <pause dur="short"/> if if I heard you correctly you said one of his sauces cooking sauces killed somebody</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I'm I'm not telling <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it definitely killed them but like</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115">you mean that someone died eating the the sauce yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> it didn't like just like choke on it <pause dur="short"/> it had something horrible in it like I don't know <pause dur="short"/> like campylobacter or some really horrible</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">yeah like salmonella or something</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">I don't know I'll have to google it <pause dur="short"/> it had like</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">so someone  so someone  died at one of his <pause dur="short"/> er what he do like a Italian or tomato sauce</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">I don't know like</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">and someone ate that and and died of and er</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think it was pasta sauces <pause dur="short"/> but they all had to be recalled <pause dur="short"/> there was like a massive product recall <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought I just thought about</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he'd have to do  he'd have to do  where they'd have to be destroyed so he'd have to lots of mini impressions of himself being burnt so it would be quite</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">like like a pyre of Lloyd Grossman sauces</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">it it will be quite upsetting erm to see all those mini mes being sort of burnt</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well but I'm sure it I'm sure it's Lloyd Grossman <pause dur="short"/> maybe I've got that completely wrong <pause dur="short"/> it's probably slanderous</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">one of something like that yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">anyway but yeah I think Masterchef's on</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">erm <pause dur="short"/> that's a risk <pause dur="short"/> that's cool</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">but the thing is though unless</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115" trans="overlap">er <unclear/> different now isn't it because we've had so much more cooking programmes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">that kind of explosion of cooking recently</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh good them them horrible baker boys <pause dur="short"/> oh they're so annoying <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I can watch them</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I've seen them <pause dur="short"/> they're er</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">they're so annoying</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">they're sort of two little Gordon Ramseys or something</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">no they're not even like that <pause dur="short"/> they're just so like public school <pause dur="short"/> and like oh the first one to make the most tasty chapatti wins <pause dur="short"/> what ho <pause dur="short"/> it's like don't you think it's really annoying?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">I think it's quite fake <pause dur="short"/> it looks quite like they're pretending to be like very competitive <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and they're living this like they in this idyllic place where just like he's the butcher and I'm the baker and my other sister's the candlestick maker or something <pause dur="short"/> it's just stupid <pause dur="short"/> that might be a lie</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well they're  they're living  they're living the <pause dur="short"/> I know well they're supposed to live in in two shops next door to each other <pause dur="short"/> one of them one of them is a butcher and then one of them is a baker and then</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I think it's just bull <pause dur="short"/> well I think it's just made up <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a set <pause dur="short"/> I think they're just actors <pause dur="short"/> it's all a lie</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037">anyway what I was saying originally</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well yeah it does look  a bit  a bit fake actually yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">what I was saying before about MasterChef was like <pause dur="short"/> did you see? I think  I think I think  originally it was like erm in Australia they changed the format and made it really like <event desc="sound of fire"/> with flames and like chop you know really dramatic and like making people cry and shouting at them <pause dur="short"/> and so over here they changed the format because if you remember a few series ago like Greg Wallace and Jonty Rhodes weren't even like</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">his his name for the record is John Torode</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">no it's not it's Jonty <pause dur="short"/> anyway like no because  a few  a few series ago it was like erm just normal like hello Mary what are you cooking? and now it's like <event desc="sound of fire"/> the contestants will never survive <pause dur="short"/> it's like</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115">yeah it's more like er something that would have Arnold Schwarzenegger rather than like than sort of Fanny Craddock or whatever</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like yeah it's like action cooking <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">mind you <pause dur="short"/> she is she's a bit scary a little bit</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037" trans="overlap">with the eyebrows <pause dur="short"/> did you see  did you see  her eyebrows?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">yeah I mean I I think  I think I think  she could take on Schwarzenegger like</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what was her helper? What was her little called again?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> er Oddjob?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think it was Oddjob</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know like er</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">he was like her sort of obedient husband and she used to like shout at him and stuff <pause dur="short"/> have you ever seen it? It's sometimes on like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's that's disturbing actually</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">I don't really see it because we haven't got a <unclear/> at home</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">you don't  you don't  have a like a box set of a</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">no but there's all those food channels like we haven't got them <pause dur="short"/> just because we've got Freeview</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">oh yeah well there's that American one isn't there when he he his his purpose is to sort of eat as much as he can before he sort of dies</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037" trans="overlap">man Versus Food?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">oh he's a pig him</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">he he sort of he has a show called the America's Greediest Person or something and then yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037">man <pause dur="short"/> man Versus Food</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> and er mind you some of the things they ate were tasty-looking but they're just very large yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah it always looks tasty but like a tiny plate of it not like seven you know cows in a bap or something</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">he's like a Elvis Elvis burger or something</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's like super chilly <pause dur="short"/> yeah like twenty-five Elvis Elvis burgers and sixteen milkshakes and that <pause dur="short"/> it's like extreme eating but yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">but yeah I think</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">do but now so but you actually like watching erm MasterChef don't you?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's nice</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the new one with yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I like I do like I like sort of erm <pause dur="short"/> although I think like the format like I don't mind a bit of exciting jazzy cooking and all that <pause dur="short"/> like who knows what's going to happen this week? I like I don't really mind that but I think like this time one thing they've changed in this series that's just started is that like the erm the contestants <pause dur="short"/> it feels like so they do the first bit where they've got like the invention thing and they get all different ingredients and they have to make something <pause dur="short"/> and then but then straight away after that I think they've already kicked like one person off <pause dur="short"/> and then straight away after that it's like the bit where they'd have to go in a restaurant <pause dur="short"/> so like the first of all they make beans on toast and then next think they're down like you know The Savoy Hotel like rustling up some <trunc>fr</trunc> foie gras or something <pause dur="short"/> it just seems a bit extreme <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">yeah they it seems extremely hard to to work in that high-pressure environment in in a big you know proper posh restaurant like it seems <pause dur="short"/> there's still a kind of like</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think I wouldn't like <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah when they send it back and it's like that dribble is one millimetre too big and all that</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's I think ex-military chef</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the foam isn't foamy enough</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">but I think it's why I don't think I'd like to be a chef because like erm I don't think I'd like the hours</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">yeah the oh yeah actually because it is a bit sort of well you've got a lunch one that's alright <pause dur="short"/> er er</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">no but you can't just say I'm going to be like a lunchtime chef</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115">you could <pause dur="short"/> do they not have that? Do they not?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's a dinner lady</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115">that I considered being like a chef and I think if I had been a chef I would have wanted to work in during brunch and lunch</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">dinner lady then</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">er supposing so <pause dur="short"/> tuck tuck shop and er</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037"><trunc>D</trunc> <trunc>J</trunc> done it <pause dur="short"/> so like what happens if you're a man and you were a dinner lady? Do you get called like a dinner man?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115">er just chef I think er</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037">well that seems a bit sexist if the dinner ladies are called the dinner ladies</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">yeah well that's just composition really I mean that's what they are isn't it? They're <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> they er he's erm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037" trans="overlap">maybe like with the political correctness maybe they're like dinner persons or something <pause dur="short"/> lunchtime operatives <pause dur="short"/> I bet  I bet</u>
<u n="126" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0037">the lunchtime <pause dur="short"/> lunchtime facilitation operative</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I like operative but the special special operations at lunch or something</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037">lunchtime nourishment facilitator or something</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115">but other that's that's amazing er but I think if you can't do the lunch shift then you've then got to sort of hang around from lunch till like evening</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">but do they not have to prep loads of stuff <pause dur="short"/> like on <trunc>kit</trunc> Gordon Ramsey's thing they have to like shave loads of like carrots and that and otherwise known as peel <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0115"><unclear/> shaved carrots <pause dur="short"/> do they call it shaven when they? It's peeling isn't it?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't think they do <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm just being stupid</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115">not a skinning the carrot or something</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">no but do you know what I mean? They've got to like chop things and like</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah I mean I guess well er they probably have like masses of stuff like frozen as well or or</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115">they have to make it in bulk or something so like a bit pot or something</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do they not like turn their noses up at them kind of things like</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">I well I think they're saying that they might say  they might say  they do but I think they maybe secretly <pause dur="short"/> I think there is a lot of defrosting and microwaving that goes on <pause dur="short"/> behind the scenes</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but sometimes like they must have to half cook like <pause dur="short"/> they must have to like half cook stuff because like otherwise like they wouldn't be able to do stuff would they <pause dur="short"/> some things <pause dur="short"/> some things just take a long time to cook <pause dur="short"/> like if you are slow roasting things they must have to half do them <pause dur="short"/> the same as like when you go out for food <pause dur="short"/> like when you go to Wetherspoon's and you ask for like a roast dinner and it comes after like seven minutes <pause dur="short"/> it's like hmm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">erm those are probably microwaved aren't they</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but not not bad though</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's a bit disturbing really isn't it really when you think about it</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115">what?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037">like radiating your food</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115">oh you mean the science behind microwaving <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037">do you not think?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115">it's just a bit space-agey <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit sort of <unclear/> you know that's has that happening er that shouldn't <trunc>ha</trunc> shouldn't work</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">erm obviously radio waves go through our heads all the time don't they <pause dur="short"/> like when we're on the mobile phone or something but they have different ones</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I mean to purposely do that to eat your dinner seems a bit weird</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115">how they found it out must be quite interesting <pause dur="short"/> must have been having some fun</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037">yeah like accidentally left his sandwich</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115" trans="overlap">er blasting each blasting themselves and various food items with radiation must have had a cracking cracking afternoon erm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037">I don't even miss one like cos obviously we haven't got enough room but I don't even miss it <pause dur="short"/> having not not having a microwave</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115">erm so a microwave yeah it's to do with the er frequency and I think it's to do with the water molecules vibrating or something</u>
<u n="159" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115">erm and there's some stuff you can't put in isn't there <pause dur="short"/> like you can't put metal in <unclear/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah like when you're <pause dur="short"/> I got really like shouted at home when I put like they've got like a plate with like a golden edge or something and I put a dinner in the microwave it was like <event desc="sound of electrical malfunction"/> and I was thinking oh crap like it's killed the microwave but I just killed the plate so</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037">no <unclear/> wasn't impressed but never mind</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115">no she's she's no <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037">but anyway erm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115">and er</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037">but we don't have to watch <trunc>mic</trunc> micro micro chef <pause dur="short"/> micro chef <vocal desc="laugh"/> Maybe that would be a good one <pause dur="short"/> maybe like a MasterChef but</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115" trans="overlap">micro chef <pause dur="short"/> no well we've we've talked so much about him that</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037">maybe they could have like a round where they could only use a microwave like there's no ovens <pause dur="short"/> they just have to microwave everything <pause dur="short"/> that's similar to my other idea that I had before and like you know in MasterChef in the first bit when like they have to choose the food?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">like and they've got like lovely cuts of beef and like shellfish and like lovely hams and that <pause dur="short"/> I'd like it if instead like they had like Quavers some sticks of Twix like er some jam erm maybe some Frazzles a couple of pickled onions</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like a dream like a sort of twenty-<trunc>fo</trunc> like a grocer's shops</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">no but like instead of the fresh ingredients they have to make something out of like some Frazzles a Twix</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah like a newsagent's <pause dur="short"/> so you'd have a newsagent's full of good and you have to go in the newsagent and grab</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah like <pause dur="short"/> that's <pause dur="short"/> some strawberry laces <pause dur="short"/> but newsagents have like milk and that so they'd have to be off</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">is it just like things that survive? Is this like a sort of wartime thing where you can only use things that that are not perishable so</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I haven't thought it through as a concept</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you erm it's just like wartime cooking <pause dur="short"/> so it's like</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037">nothing wrong with a bit of wartime cooking</u>
<u n="180" who="S0115">it's like er corned beef er  things that  things that wash up  on the  on the you'll find on like the beach washed up from like some submarine or something <pause dur="short"/> like a Spam or whatever so</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037">I'm not I'm not have you say anything bad about corned beef I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> don't be horrible <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing wrong with Spam <pause dur="short"/> they wouldn't have any</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115">er no no I like erm er certain types of that sort of meat <trunc>l</trunc> luncheon meat sort of</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">but er</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037">I do corned beef is really nice <pause dur="short"/> but all those old things are coming back though aren't they like erm sweet breads and all that and like</u>
<u n="186" who="S0115">is that that's the pancreas is it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037">it's some sort of horrible disgusting <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know if it was their erm testicles or if it was like</u>
<u n="188" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it's making a comeback is it? <trunc>Pa</trunc> pancreas is back <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037">is it the pancreas? Sweet bread?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think so yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> parson's nose that's some something</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037">horrible piece <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115">er</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037">brains for meat</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">well I think it's good to use to use it you know like</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037">and it's nearly Burns Night</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115">erm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037">it's prime offal eating time</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's it's probably better not to to waste it than let it sort of get go in to sort of unscrupulous dealers and probably <unclear/> again anyway so</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's I'm sure that's what's it like sausages is all just sawdust and like hooves and like you know ears and that isn't it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115">sawdust yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037">well unless you get those really expensive ones</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115">yeah well I mean when we think of something as being tasty that <trunc>mayd</trunc> maybe doesn't correspond with the actual quality of the ingredients</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0115">we may well think that that some like a pizza would be very tasty but whereas in in fact it's just really a kind of low quality dough and like low quality cheese and low quality tomato sauce and stuff and so it's not very good quality but it's tasty but</u>
<u n="205" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah like that pizza we had at  That was horrible <pause dur="short"/> and sometimes if you put salt on things it just makes it taste way nicer than it is anyway</u>
<u n="206" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0037">and like I don't think I could eat like you know erm like a fried <trunc>e</trunc> or even any sort of egg without a nice bit of salt on it</u>
<u n="208" who="S0115">yeah er definitely I think you have to have a little bit of salt with your egg yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort of</u>
<u n="209" who="S0037">oh I really fancy a boiled egg <pause dur="short"/> that's stupid I've just had me tea <pause dur="short"/> and then that enormous piece of cake that I've just scoffed then <pause dur="short"/> what did you think of that cake?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0115">erm yeah I <trunc>l</trunc> I liked that cake though <pause dur="short"/> it had like it was like a sort of well it was a chocolate sponge but it had like a little little like er like a sauce like a chocolate sauce in the middle and that was  that was  pretty good</u>
<u n="211" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't think I did it <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc> <vocal desc="yawn"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I did it any favours by leaving it on the bench like but never mind</u>
<u n="212" who="S0115">hmm mm <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="213" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I came <pause dur="short"/> I woke up this morning and I came</u>
<u n="214" who="S0115">well you matured it <pause dur="short"/> you  you've let it  you've let it age <pause dur="short"/> you've let it breathe</u>
<u n="215" who="S0037">that's that's one theory <pause dur="short"/> I can <pause dur="short"/> I got out of bed this morning and I was like oh I've left the cake on the side <pause dur="short"/> it was all crispy <pause dur="short"/> never mind</u>
<u n="216" who="S0115">well at least it's <trunc>br</trunc> it's breathed you know <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="217" who="S0037">that's one one way of putting it <pause dur="short"/> but never mind</u>
<u n="218" who="S0115">so er what's your favourite thing that you enjoy cooking the most? Like do you enjoy cooking like er bigger dishes? The savoury dishes or like sweet dishes or or like pastry?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I've  I quite  I quite like eating savoury <pause dur="short"/> oh I quite like eating <pause dur="short"/> full <trunc>s</trunc> just stop the sentence there <pause dur="short"/> I quite like eating like cakes and things erm but I think like the thing with only being two of us like if I make a whole cake I'll eat like fifty percent of the whole cake so that's probably not very good for anyone</u>
<u n="220" who="S0115">right so you sort of prefer  more like  more like sensible food more then</u>
<u n="221" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Attem</trunc> yeah I don't really make cakes so I'll then do other than <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know I mean I like cooking so I don't like micro meals or anything <pause dur="short"/> we haven't even got a microwave like I said but erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> er I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I like erm I've been hankering after a leg of lamb for a while haven't I <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got round to that yet <pause dur="short"/> christmas I was overruled <pause dur="short"/> never mind</u>
<u n="222" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you just have that <pause dur="short"/> er oh well we let I think it was the majority er</u>
<u n="223" who="S0037">I know it was a majority vote</u>
<u n="224" who="S0115">my parents requested a turkey with all the trimmings erm which means stuffing er and those little bacon and sausage things which I think are called pig in blankets or something <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="225" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm not even that fond on them</u>
<u n="226" who="S0115">that's the er but we had a  it was a good  it was a good dinner though</u>
<u n="227" who="S0037">ah I don't know though <pause dur="short"/> do you not think turkey's got like a funny taste?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0115">er I think all meat has its own distinct taste <pause dur="short"/> turkey's very healthy</u>
<u n="229" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but I mean <pause dur="short"/> that's not what I said <pause dur="short"/> I didn't say like do you think turkey's got a a flavour on it on its own I meant like do you think it's a bit weird?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0115">erm no I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think the turkey leg I'm not like I don't normally eat as much of that but like that's good for like curries and stuff</u>
<u n="231" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0115">er I like the turkey breast yeah because it's good for you and</u>
<u n="233" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0115">erm yeah turkey's okay I mean</u>
<u n="235" who="S0037">I think it's unnecessary that they cook like the whole turkey</u>
<u n="236" who="S0115">but you're supposed to have like a <pause dur="short"/> well I mean in terms of quantity <pause dur="short"/> in terms of yeah I was going to say <pause dur="short"/> but like traditionally at Christmas like</u>
<u n="237" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it can be a goose <pause dur="short"/> somebody should get goose <pause dur="short"/> or get a goose and put a turkey <trunc>insi</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> put a <trunc>tur</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> which would? Put a goose inside the turkey inside the with a chicken inside that with a</u>
<u n="238" who="S0115">this is the <pause dur="short"/> is that the? The sort of what was it? Er some one of the TV chefs did that didn't they</u>
<u n="239" who="S0037">yeah I think they had it in Aldi though <pause dur="short"/> like a big frozen one</u>
<u n="240" who="S0115">erm they actually <pause dur="short"/> they've they've done it already <pause dur="short"/> so this is like a Russian doll of birds is it?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0037" trans="overlap">cut price <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0115">so you've got like</u>
<u n="243" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like a <trunc>f</trunc> oh I think I had the magazine somewhere about it <pause dur="short"/> the Aldi magazine</u>
<u n="244" who="S0115">erm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0037">it was like a four bird erm four bird roast or something</u>
<u n="246" who="S0115">so what what did it what what was the?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0037">I don't know like a robin inside like a sparrow inside like a crow inside like an owl inside like a chicken or something</u>
<u n="248" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it could  it could  go on indefinitely couldn't it <pause dur="short"/> it should it could sort of keep going couldn't it</u>
<u n="249" who="S0037">Don't know may not be true <pause dur="short"/> er no no I think it was erm what are them little things called? Those little ones?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0115">er Poussin or something</u>
<u n="251" who="S0037">yeah Poussin</u>
<u n="252" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that like is that not a baby or something or?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0037">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> is it? No <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a special</u>
<u n="254" who="S0115" trans="overlap">er wood pigeons are quite small aren't they <pause dur="short"/> they sound small <pause dur="short"/> er yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh maybe it was pigeon <pause dur="short"/> anyway it was one of those inside erm was it inside a <trunc>chi</trunc>? No a chicken must be the third one and duck must be the and sorry and turkey must be the last one <pause dur="short"/> maybe it was a duck <pause dur="short"/> maybe it was a little thingybob inside a duck inside a chicken inside a</u>
<u n="256" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0037">that's nobody needs that many meat <pause dur="short"/> it's a meat</u>
<u n="258" who="S0115">it's that's extravagance <pause dur="short"/> I mean like we have become more like as a nation in terms of cooking <unclear/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but you can get that in Aldi like just as if that was like a normal thing <pause dur="short"/> jam cereal four birds stuffed inside each other <pause dur="short"/> like seems a bit bit far fetched <pause dur="short"/> but it might be nice <pause dur="short"/> I should of got one</u>
<u n="260" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well  it's just the  it's just the sheer thought of er luxury of it I suppose</u>
<u n="261" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><unclear/> But that's Christmas <pause dur="short"/> people go crackers don't they</u>
<u n="262" who="S0115">literally</u>
<u n="263" who="S0037">literally crackers <pause dur="short"/> both senses of the word crackers</u>
<u n="264" who="S0115" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="265" who="S0037">they <pause dur="short"/> what's your favourite Christmas food like? I mean I'm not <trunc>s</trunc> oh I think I would have like <pause dur="short"/> I don't think you can beat a mince pie really</u>
<u n="266" who="S0115">erm there's that yeah there's them</u>
<u n="267" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I like a nice warm mince pie</u>
<u n="268" who="S0115">I like er I like all of it <pause dur="short"/> I like the pudding er Christmas pudding is good</u>
<u n="269" who="S0037" trans="overlap">some mulled wine</u>
<u n="270" who="S0115">er which you pour brandy over and set fire to</u>
<u n="271" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh I don't like Christmas <pause dur="short"/> do you know I think it's too</u>
<u n="272" who="S0115">and er then er you could put some kind of sauce like a rum sauce or like a brandy sauce over it and then that's good</u>
<u n="273" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I think it's just <pause dur="short"/> do you I think it's like fatty? Do you not find like it's like <event desc="sound of clicking"/> on the top of your mouth?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0115">er well the it Christmas pudding yeah it would have that cos it's sort of suet isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I mean it would have depending probably on the temperature that he ate it er <pause dur="short"/> but I think you're supposed to mix it with other stuff <pause dur="short"/> like other <trunc>pr</trunc></u>
<u n="275" who="S0037">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0115">the you know the sauces</u>
<u n="277" who="S0037">the custard</u>
<u n="278" who="S0115">then that would take away the sort of stodginess of it and replace it with a more</u>
<u n="279" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what what if you're eating it with brandy butter you mean? Like that's not going to take away</u>
<u n="280" who="S0115">well not necessarily brandy but you could have like rum sauce or custard or ice cream or</u>
<u n="281" who="S0037">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> maybe ice cream</u>
<u n="282" who="S0115" trans="overlap">some some kind of cream vanilla cream or something but er erm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0037">yeah actually I saw</u>
<u n="284" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you mix it it is really nice <pause dur="short"/> I think like the sort of er Christmas pudding like if you sort of get the custard and sort of like stab it a bit with the spoon then it sort of goes into this kind of mixture which is like half half way pudding and half way custard</u>
<u n="285" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> er well on you know This Morning? You know the <trunc>sh</trunc> erm you know This Morning? The programme? On This Morning anyway I think it was that <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> oh well <pause dur="short"/> they made like erm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0115">that's what did it used to be with like Anne and? No <pause dur="short"/> well that's Good Morning</u>
<u n="287" who="S0037" trans="overlap">er Anne Diamond <pause dur="short"/> that's GMTV</u>
<u n="288" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no Anne and Nick <pause dur="short"/> that that was another the one wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> er  is it  is it the one that used to have Richard and Judy?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0037">no that was <pause dur="short"/> was it?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0115">well did they used to do it or?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0037">oh yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> it's with Phillip well it used to be Phillip and Fern and then it's now it's I think it's the silver fox and Holly</u>
<u n="292" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that a? Phillip and Holly Willoughby</u>
<u n="293" who="S0037">holly Willoughby yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0115">er yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0037" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0115">well I've never seen that with him and her</u>
<u n="297" who="S0037">no well I watched it <pause dur="short"/> was it over Christmas? Anyway they made like a <pause dur="short"/> I feel like I'm being like my nana <pause dur="short"/> like you know when you show up it's like ten thousand story avenues <pause dur="short"/> you're just like oh the other day</u>
<u n="298" who="S0115">yeah I mean well we've being going down a sort of like elderly sort of theme I think <pause dur="short"/> like we're talking about like kitchens and yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0037" trans="overlap">food <pause dur="short"/> well that's why <pause dur="short"/> dinner's at the table I suppose <pause dur="short"/> but anyway erm no what was I saying <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah he he made like erm sorry he made like erm Yorkshire not Yorkshire pudding <pause dur="short"/> christmas pudding ice cream <pause dur="short"/> so like had some Christmas pudding and mixed it with this ice cream mixture and like made an ice cream <pause dur="short"/> that probably was nice</u>
<u n="300" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0037">or was it mince pie ice cream? Either way <pause dur="short"/> maybe he did both <pause dur="short"/> that seemed nice <pause dur="short"/> rather than just like on its own</u>
<u n="302" who="S0115">yeah erm that's that's probably quite quite possibly true yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm that you can sometimes it's better to mix stuff than it is to have it on their own</u>
<u n="303" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is about mince <pause dur="short"/> about Christmas pudding is like it's literally the last thing that you need after a giant giant dinner <pause dur="short"/> do you know what? I'll just have a massive suet pudding <pause dur="short"/> like it seems crazy</u>
<u n="304" who="S0115">hmm <pause dur="short"/> oh well I mean yeah I think that you've got to have a bit of a break after the er the turkey course</u>
<u n="305" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I bit of a snooze</u>
<u n="306" who="S0115">you've got to sort of erm yeah you can't you don't want to <pause dur="short"/> also I've less I find it's better to have less erm like potato and less er er bread or you don't like those sort of starchy things cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but roast potatoes like they're so nice</u>
<u n="308" who="S0115">oh yeah just <pause dur="short"/> but then of course you get the leftovers <pause dur="short"/> you get leftovers for <unclear/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I could happily pass on the mash though <pause dur="short"/> I don't like that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know maybe it's because like you know when you were at school <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if they did this at your school <pause dur="short"/> did did you like have to erm like at my junior school you used to sit on a table with loads of other kids and like they you didn't go up like to a hatch and get your food or anything <pause dur="short"/> they kind of brought it out <pause dur="short"/> and then the oldest kid on the table had to serve it out to all of the other younger kids</u>
<u n="310" who="S0115">oh erm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0037">did you do this?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0115">no er that sounds like the sort of thing that they do it in <trunc>p</trunc> er public <pause dur="short"/> not prison</u>
<u n="313" who="S0037" trans="overlap">did you have packed? Prison?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0115">oh maybe prison <pause dur="short"/> er in private schools isn't it <pause dur="short"/> do they not?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0037">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> well it definitely wasn't a private school <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0115">there was time time on a school trip when I went to boarding school and for a week and I think the the serving was different erm but</u>
<u n="317" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think it was because there wasn't anywhere to <trunc>g</trunc> to go to get the dinner <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? In primary school <pause dur="short"/> it just came out of the kitchen and then into the hall <pause dur="short"/> everyone ate in the hall <pause dur="short"/> did you have like a special dining room?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right I just <pause dur="short"/> it's I've got quite vague memories of that but I think we had like  the er  the er hall  and then  and then you you went up and got your stuff from those dinner ladies that you're you're talking about and then er and erm also like but most people would have er or a packed lunch <pause dur="short"/> or some people had free er dinners as well <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm I had school dinners for a long time anyway and then <pause dur="short"/> so it used to come out in these like metal tray like sort of dishes and if you were like the older kid you got to serve it but if you were the younger kid you just had to like wait until <pause dur="short"/> so the older kid would be like oh what do you want? And you'd say yeah I'll have a bit of everything or whatever it was on the dinner that day <pause dur="short"/> mince or whatever <pause dur="short"/> but with the potatoes it used to be like I could only describe as being ice cream scooped into like portions</u>
<u n="320" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah oh yeah we used to have them sort of ones like the that's old fashioned sort of British erm mashed potatoes <pause dur="short"/> it's like a it's it's like Smash isn't it <pause dur="short"/> it's like erm like that's mixed from a sachet or something <pause dur="short"/> then it it's sort of very very er very like runny isn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was like mashed <trunc>pota</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> a packet <pause dur="short"/> but anyway so then the kids used to be <pause dur="short"/> gloopy <pause dur="short"/> like well these ones used to be like set into like balls</u>
<u n="322" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0037">and then so they'd be like oh do you want potato? And you'd be like yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then the kids the older kid whoever was the server used to like scoop it up and then like whack it down on the plate and go chatty spat and like the potato would be just like splattered all over the plate <pause dur="short"/> it was horrible like <pause dur="short"/> I think that put me off potatoes <pause dur="short"/> like mashed potato forever</u>
<u n="324" who="S0115">yeah you've got  a bit of a  a bit of a disliking to them haven't you so er er</u>
<u n="325" who="S0037">I think that's it I think I'm traumatised by the chatty splats</u>
<u n="326" who="S0115">that is chatty splat <pause dur="short"/> well what does the chatty mean?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0037">potato</u>
<u n="328" who="S0115">oh right I didn't know that <pause dur="short"/> that's not er that's not standard English is it <pause dur="short"/> that chatty</u>
<u n="329" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't  I've never heard it  I've never heard it since</u>
<u n="330" who="S0115">chatty <pause dur="short"/> chatty</u>
<u n="331" who="S0037">I wouldn't be like oh can I have some chatty <pause dur="short"/> like I would never say that <pause dur="short"/> I just I think it was just one of those stupid primary school</u>
<u n="332" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's er it's probably a north eastern words is it?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know I think it was just a stupid primary school thing like</u>
<u n="334" who="S0115">er school dinners are definitely like er I mean  the further back  the further back I try to remember the worse the more disturbing it gets like</u>
<u n="335" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and did you have lemon love pie?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0115">well in my infant school I think I could remember having</u>
<u n="337" who="S0037">lemon love pie</u>
<u n="338" who="S0115">it would sort of smell of beetroot and mushy peas</u>
<u n="339" who="S0037">what the lemon love pie?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0115">no I don't know what that is but I'm saying that the dinning hall you went in I remember the smell it was like mushy peas and beetroot and mashed potato and beef burgers and that</u>
<u n="341" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0115">they'd give you a beef burger but it like didn't have any bread on it <pause dur="short"/> it would just be like a burger on its own</u>
<u n="343" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah I remember <pause dur="short"/> that's horrible and they're really thin and like grey</u>
<u n="344" who="S0115">yeah and they had like bits in them and you thought you know</u>
<u n="345" who="S0037">yeah like sawdust and that like I said</u>
<u n="346" who="S0115">oh er and and then we later found out er that obviously during the eighties there was quite a lot of erm that disease going around <pause dur="short"/> the mad cow disease <pause dur="short"/> and actually that probably would have been you know risky eating those sorts of burgers er in the eighties but er I've survived and I don't think I've experienced any mental er</u>
<u n="347" who="S0037" trans="overlap">when I was at senior school <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> takes ages to come out though doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> not wanting to scare you</u>
<u n="348" who="S0115">yeah yeah I know</u>
<u n="349" who="S0037">so you never know</u>
<u n="350" who="S0115">well erm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0037">do you want to make another cup of tea?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>sh</trunc> er shall we <trunc>s</trunc> have a break?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0037">hmm mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
</body>
</text>
