<text id="SAFZ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:22</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0402 S0405</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Classroom, Upton Court Grammar School</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Careers, Inventions/Patents, China and the growing world, Investment</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about topics that interest us, after school</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0402">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Southall</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>16 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0405">
				<exactage>17</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Slough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Slough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years and 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0405">ah okay let's discuss eh let's discuss our</u>
<u n="2" who="S0402" trans="overlap">life</u>
<u n="3" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0405">yeah no no okay eh other teachers</u>
<u n="5" who="S0402" trans="overlap">you what did you want to be as a child?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0405">a barrister I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no no no no I mean as a child not like as a you weren't born a four-year-old</u>
<u n="8" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm I I I was born and I ah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0402">fine okay watch this right when you were the youngest you know okay obviously football it's football alright obviously</u>
<u n="10" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I didn't care yeah football <unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0405">I didn't I wanted to be eh I didn't want to be I didn't want to be an astronaut or a firefighter or a</u>
<u n="13" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I did no not firefighter I didn't want to be anything where I had to probably die</u>
<u n="14" who="S0405">yeah <trunc>de</trunc> death wasn't something fun</u>
<u n="15" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I I and I and back then I didn't realise that there were so many failed Apollo missions <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0402">before they actually got to space</u>
<u n="18" who="S0405">ah no not Apollo erm <unclear>yeah</unclear> did you understand what death was at a young age?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0402">no cos no one tells you what death is</u>
<u n="20" who="S0405">I know exactly</u>
<u n="21" who="S0402">no one tells you you're going to die in like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0405">we don't have as much of a regard for death as did you ever? oh a swear word</u>
<u n="23" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah you know? you know that everyone grows up at some point yeah?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0402">I'm at that phase where I'm not grown up yet I still want to be something like an astronaut or something</u>
<u n="26" who="S0405">yeah yeah but to become an astronaut that would require</u>
<u n="27" who="S0402">physics degree yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0405">maybe a physics degree but do you think working from an early age? to as as in commit to an <trunc>a</trunc> a career from after eighteen or after twenty-one?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0402">well erm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0405">I don't I don't know</u>
<u n="31" who="S0402" trans="overlap">Neil Neil Armstrong right?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0405">yeah Neil Armstrong</u>
<u n="33" who="S0402" trans="overlap">erm he <trunc>d</trunc> at no point did he want to be a <trunc>s</trunc> a an astronaut</u>
<u n="34" who="S0405">oh yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0402">he flew erm air bombing missions in a in a the Korean War</u>
<u n="36" who="S0405">did he?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0402">yeah he</u>
<u n="38" who="S0405">oh shit</u>
<u n="39" who="S0402">yeah he he he had like a crap load of successful er missions in Korean War</u>
<u n="40" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0402">and after that cos he was so great</u>
<u n="42" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0402">erm that you know the NASA recruited him because he was the best pilot they could find</u>
<u n="44" who="S0405">damn so he he he he but did he have a physics degree before he became a a pilot?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no he he was part of the air force</u>
<u n="46" who="S0405">damn</u>
<u n="47" who="S0402">I guess now you do because if you there's there's a finite <trunc>peo</trunc> amount of people that go like they know how to get people to space now</u>
<u n="48" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0402" trans="overlap">maybe not cos their rocket blew up</u>
<u n="50" who="S0405">they still don't I know that I'm not <unclear/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no no no that was a private company that was a private company</u>
<u n="52" who="S0405">was it really? oh okay</u>
<u n="53" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah NASA know NASA know how to get people to space</u>
<u n="54" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I understand <trunc>NA</trunc>NASA have closed their space project haven't they? their shuttle project?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0402">yeah yeah that's why they need private companies</u>
<u n="56" who="S0405">that's why oh alright investment</u>
<u n="57" who="S0402" trans="overlap">and <unclear/> private companies have re-used</u>
<u n="58" who="S0405" trans="overlap">that's what we should be investing in like er ah I wish I had the statistics on erm on America's use of er <trunc>a</trunc> er military erm as in the amount they spend on military every year it's like eight times more than than China and like Russia combined</u>
<u n="59" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah like you realise they yeah but their military invented duct tape Velcro?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0405">did it?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they did</u>
<u n="62" who="S0405">we invented the jet we gave them the jet after World War Two apparently</u>
<u n="63" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no no no what happened was there was a guy that invented the jet</u>
<u n="64" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0402">and erm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0405">he was British</u>
<u n="67" who="S0402">yeah he was British but er and er this started at like thirty-nine right?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0402">and and he he campaigned for years and years and years trying to get his idea picked up by the military</u>
<u n="70" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0402">it wouldn't have it it wasn't until like after the the er Second World War that that <unclear/> he he went basically went bankrupt</u>
<u n="72" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0402">and then they decided to take his idea</u>
<u n="74" who="S0405">yeah I see well the whole world steals for for everyone's own please</u>
<u n="75" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it's like erm yeah in in king James' time isn't it? monopolies were always people that invented stuff</u>
<u n="76" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0402">I guess that I <unclear/> for me I find that kind of fair</u>
<u n="78" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0402">because if you you were the first person</u>
<u n="80" who="S0405">it's like a patent</u>
<u n="81" who="S0402">yeah no no it's not like a patent because you can you can like patent say you invented the hoover tomorrow yeah?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0402">and the hoover hadn't been invented you invent the hoover you can't patent the hoover</u>
<u n="84" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0402">you can patent the the things that you make the hoover out of and the systems you use</u>
<u n="86" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh right right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0402">but you can't patent the hoover that means that if if if I come tomorrow or the day after and I make a a</u>
<u n="88" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0402">a vacuum</u>
<u n="90" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0402">cleaner and but it uses different parts</u>
<u n="92" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0402"><trunc>it</trunc>it's not it doesn't break the patent</u>
<u n="94" who="S0405">right right right</u>
<u n="95" who="S0402">so <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="96" who="S0405">so it that's an issue with the patent though like</u>
<u n="97" who="S0402">no it's not well because you</u>
<u n="98" who="S0405" trans="overlap">that they're not specific enough or they're not</u>
<u n="99" who="S0402"><trunc>there</trunc>there's two things there's erm what one people believe that if you invent something you've worked hard at it and you should be able to be rewarded in it</u>
<u n="100" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's good yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0402" trans="overlap">so so if you invented the computer say as Alan Turing did in eh World War Two</u>
<u n="102" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0402">he you should have ah undisputed rights to every single computer</u>
<u n="104" who="S0405">yeah okay</u>
<u n="105" who="S0402">and then there's the flip side of that that people say that that's anti-capitalistic whereas that you have a then have a situation where you have a monopoly</u>
<u n="106" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0402">where erm whereby one person controls the complete market share</u>
<u n="108" who="S0405">right right</u>
<u n="109" who="S0402"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah it's it's it's it's eh so it's like but that I think the issue with patents is that they they hinder the progress of anything creative</u>
<u n="111" who="S0402">no patents don't monopolies do</u>
<u n="112" who="S0405" trans="overlap">or <unclear/> no no no</u>
<u n="113" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that's that's that's that was their original argument against monopolies because</u>
<u n="114" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah monopolies yeah okay monopolies existed since seventeen hundreds in</u>
<u n="115" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I mean arguably they still do because</u>
<u n="116" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0402">you have like oil and gas monopolies</u>
<u n="118" who="S0405">right right yeah yeah yeah that that</u>
<u n="119" who="S0402" trans="overlap">in the end big six six energy companies</u>
<u n="120" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0402">it's weird how none of their prices ever drop and they all move it up at the same time</u>
<u n="122" who="S0405">yeah I know I know that's just competition with allies though</u>
<u n="123" who="S0402">yeah <unclear/> no but that is a monopoly though because</u>
<u n="124" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> control yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0402">by by definition if you're controlling market that makes it monopoly</u>
<u n="126" who="S0405">yeah yeah I see that</u>
<u n="127" who="S0402">so that's the <trunc>f</trunc> I I don't know personally I think that people aren't rewarded enough for inventing things and that's why we don't have enough cos cos you could invent something tomorrow and</u>
<u n="128" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0402">you would you could get like <trunc>n</trunc> you would make no money out of it</u>
<u n="130" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0402">and I think <unclear>the inventors</unclear> need to be protected more</u>
<u n="132" who="S0405" trans="overlap">well okay</u>
<u n="133" who="S0402">but on the flip side people that erm eh seek to monopolise a market that can't it's it's like like everything it's nearly impossible to strike up a perfect balance</u>
<u n="134" who="S0405">yeah but just because you invent something</u>
<u n="135" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0405">erm just because eh what was I saying? erm just because you're inventing erm yeah just because you manage to invent something you you said they should be protected more</u>
<u n="137" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0405">doesn't that theoretically mean that in like fifty years or a hundred years or there's going to be a point where it's becoming eh a a a less likely or a smaller chance that you're going to create something then isn't that? I mean isn't that unfair? why don't we reward people for?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no but I know that <unclear/> that is why there is invention because <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>if you you can invent something today</u>
<u n="140" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0402">with a risk of becoming a billionaire or you you can create an amazing product and lose get get absolutely nothing</u>
<u n="142" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0402">whereas <trunc>i</trunc>if you were erm certain</u>
<u n="144" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0402">that you would not get nothing out of inventing something</u>
<u n="146" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0402">more people would you know quit their day job and and pursue you know trying to make something you know <trunc>beli</trunc> unbelievable</u>
<u n="148" who="S0405">and we shouldn't be <unclear>supporting</unclear> that though</u>
<u n="149" who="S0402"><unclear/> must be <unclear>supporting</unclear></u>
<u n="150" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I mean because because <trunc>innovate</trunc><trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>innovation</u>
<u n="151" who="S0402" trans="overlap">cos every right everything</u>
<u n="152" who="S0405">and inventions are so they're so scarce now even in the past they were so scarce</u>
<u n="153" who="S0402" trans="overlap">exactly that's the issue <trunc>th</trunc>they're so scarce <trunc>we</trunc>we're not inspiring enough people to invent</u>
<u n="154" who="S0405" trans="overlap">ah oh no no no no no no I think I think we're over-inspiring I'm saying scarce I'm saying scarce as in it's hard to create something that is original and can be marketed</u>
<u n="155" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I mean you <trunc>re</trunc> you got to realise that the universe you know? ever increasing you know? it's a world of infinite possibilities</u>
<u n="156" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0402"><trunc>I</trunc>I could create you know? a new sandwich tomorrow</u>
<u n="158" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0402"><vocal desc="misc"/> and that would be invention but the point is that you could invent ah ah an infinite amount of things</u>
<u n="160" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0402">but a lot of them don't have <trunc>a</trunc>applications</u>
<u n="162" who="S0405">no</u>
<u n="163" who="S0402">and the the second thing which is an issue you know we're basically talking about is they they're they're not monetarily sustainable</u>
<u n="164" who="S0405">yeah but you don't want to be encouraging people all these people to quit their day jobs for a cause that is very <trunc>un</trunc> it's still very unlikely <unclear/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0402" trans="overlap">right you got alright look at the unemployment yeah?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0402">if more people quit their jobs and went into you're getting more people do the Steve Jobs Steve Wozniak deal or a Bill Gates</u>
<u n="168" who="S0405">that was so rare that's mostly with like innovative speakers</u>
<u n="169" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that's so rare because not not that many people are trying it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0405">no some people how many? <trunc>h</trunc></u>
<u n="171" who="S0402" trans="overlap">you you realise that there's a certain probability something's going to happen</u>
<u n="172" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0402">the more times you you test that</u>
<u n="174" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0402" trans="overlap">the more like the more results you're likely to have</u>
<u n="176" who="S0405">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0402">Steve Jobs and Steve Wozniak yeah?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0402">they set up a business in their garage</u>
<u n="180" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0402">who does that now? who sets up a business in their garage?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0405" trans="overlap">people try people <trunc>tr</trunc> how many stories do we hear of of inventors or people who spend their entire lives trying to follow their dream? whether that's invention whether that's quitting your job to to do something extraordinary</u>
<u n="183" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0405">and yet they can't make money out of it they get no success it's impossible</u>
<u n="185" who="S0402">that's the issue they don't make money out of it we need to help them make financially sustainable</u>
<u n="186" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> like feed them money but at the same time we still need people motivated to work I think people are getting lazier</u>
<u n="187" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah but <unclear/> the easiest way to motivate someone to work is to work for themselves because at the end of the day you're not working for a company</u>
<u n="188" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0402">the profit you make isn't going into the pockets of the person that owns the company if you <trunc>kn</trunc> if you know that the money that you make now is the wage you will take away for the year</u>
<u n="190" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0402">you <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're going to obviously work hard aren't you?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0405">how hard is? yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0402" trans="overlap">because it doesn't matter if the <trunc>bu</trunc> the business starts <trunc>fai</trunc> you're you're the business company you work for they make a a loss this year or they don't make money at all</u>
<u n="194" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0402">because at the end of the day you're still getting paid</u>
<u n="196" who="S0405">but they're going to be making a loss as in how hard is it to be freelance? or or or or self-employed and make money?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0402" trans="overlap">it is hard we we need to help them because</u>
<u n="198" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0402">at the end of the day we we have a you you look at the computing sector or the gaming sector</u>
<u n="200" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0402">erm the movie sector we are miles behind the likes of America and China</u>
<u n="202" who="S0405">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0402" trans="overlap">eh and even India right?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0402">we are miles behind because people don't</u>
<u n="206" who="S0405" trans="overlap">but look what that's resulted in</u>
<u n="207" who="S0402">you know that's not resulted in anything good because at the end of the day you look at it a mountain of things that erm America and China will invent yeah?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0402">they're pushing for why are all the big like mobile <trunc>ph</trunc> why do we not have a big mobile phone making company? because no one because we we <unclear/> we've slipped into the erm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0405" trans="overlap">we</u>
<u n="211" who="S0402">the the way of thinking that well why? why let? why try and work hard and invent something else <unclear/> make our own company?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0402" trans="overlap">it doesn't matter that cos China are going to undercut us and we have America over there we have India with a a <trunc>mass</trunc> population what's the point in trying?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah I mean but you don't want to <trunc>yo</trunc>you still want to look at the way China has increased in its economic growth because of the</u>
<u n="215" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that's the mentality as much as anything else</u>
<u n="216" who="S0405">I think it's as much to do with the work ethic as it is has to do with encouraging people to make inventions and the</u>
<u n="217" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah I know but the the point is that they invested in their people</u>
<u n="218" who="S0405">yeah by forcing them to work by controlling them by giving them hard hours</u>
<u n="219" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I mean yeah I know but <trunc>y</trunc> you think about the amount of freedom they have now compared to fifty years ago yeah? that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="221" who="S0402">obviously they're still it's not perfect you still have a a communist regime and you can't talk out against it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0402">you have the Hong Kong umbrella riots</u>
<u n="224" who="S0405">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0402">but but the point is there's they there's been you've seen a stark amount of investment from erm you know communist regime</u>
<u n="226" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0402">industrialise you know agriculture</u>
<u n="228" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0402">there there's now no more of that as compared to erm we have erm now er a a market where we can start selling people stuff to consumers we can we can you know?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0402">work that way and that's what they try and do they're investing that way that's why their er the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah we do</u>
<u n="233" who="S0402">erm I don't one of the most <vocal desc="laugh"/> one of the most er popular phones right now is the OnePlus One yeah?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> mate yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0402">Chinese company they invent it they make it cheap</u>
<u n="236" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0402">it's all about trying to now change from like industry to try and make stuff that the consumer</u>
<u n="238" who="S0405" trans="overlap">innovative yeah yeah but they do I mean they do that well I guess Japan does it in a similar way but they don't have</u>
<u n="239" who="S0402">well <trunc>j</trunc> no the <vocal desc="misc"/> reason Japan</u>
<u n="240" who="S0405">they're they're just innovative in everything they do</u>
<u n="241" who="S0402">I know but their their issue is that they don't spend enough money</u>
<u n="242" who="S0405">yeah okay but they're they're not in as debt as bloody Britain or America</u>
<u n="243" who="S0402" trans="overlap">like that's why they they no well China are in a massive amount of debt</u>
<u n="244" who="S0405" trans="overlap">or China are</u>
<u n="245" who="S0402">China are in a <trunc>ma</trunc></u>
<u n="246" who="S0405">China's growing though China is sustainable</u>
<u n="247" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah I know that's the difference the China's debt in being investment</u>
<u n="248" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0402">they they unlike us we we we <unclear>plough</unclear> money into the NHS or er we we spend it on benefits China all of China's debt</u>
<u n="250" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0402">has been through erm investing in their er in their country and in their people in their new innovation</u>
<u n="252" who="S0405" trans="overlap">we the NHS is investing in our people maybe not fundamentally or ideologically but healthcare is better erm er school education <unclear>obviously</unclear> that can be argued but we've got we've got a sustainable system</u>
<u n="253" who="S0402" trans="overlap">education is a <trunc>nec</trunc> the the points are these are necessary costs right?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0402">every country will have these costs right?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0402">unless you're America and you try and do an ObamaCare system <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah ObamaCare</u>
<u n="259" who="S0402">okay? but everything will have a set amount of cost what China <trunc>do</trunc> have done well is they've minimised the amount of cost</u>
<u n="260" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0402">that you spend on education and healthcare and they've got the the best that they can possibly get even though they have a billion people</u>
<u n="262" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0402">and it must be hard to <unclear/> healthcare bill budget is going to be pretty high in that</u>
<u n="264" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0402">they've managed to do that whilst also with the surplus money they've had</u>
<u n="266" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0402">they've invested it</u>
<u n="268" who="S0405">they have and they've done that well yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><trunc>a</trunc> I mean if you think about Britain? have Britain invested? they've sold all their gold</u>
<u n="270" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0402">they they wasted the <trunc>in</trunc> eh in the eighties they wasted the North Sea oil</u>
<u n="272" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0402">they <vocal desc="misc"/> they had a they had a a windfall of money with North Sea oil they took the Scottish Scottish oil yeah they have no oil now basically</u>
<u n="274" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0402">and then a massive windfall of millions and they did not invest it correctly</u>
<u n="276" who="S0405">so so you think it's it <unclear/> it should be the government that hold on let's end this conversation erm yeah you think it should be you <trunc>sh</trunc> you <trunc>sho</trunc> you think it should be the government that takes the responsibility</u>
<u n="277" who="S0402">yeah by <unclear/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0405">for yeah yeah that's true alright I got to go yeah?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
