<text id="SAG4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:02:50</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0447 S0448</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Exercise, phones, writing, post, theatre, work, TV, Halloween, food, toilets, ghosts, exams, alcohol, future plans, songs, uni, Manchester, cars, recruitment, sleeping</topics>
		<activity>Partners catching up on their day</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0447">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bridgetown</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Barbados</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Milton Keynes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Professional golfer</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0448">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>High Wycombe</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East England/ Standard English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>High Wycombe</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Currently seeking graduate job</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0448">hello?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0447">hello</u>
<u n="3" who="S0448">oh hi</u>
<u n="4" who="S0447">you alright?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0448">yeah how are you?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0447">yeah not too bad</u>
<u n="7" who="S0448">not too bad</u>
<u n="8" who="S0447">tired</u>
<u n="9" who="S0448">ah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0447">legs hurt</u>
<u n="11" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what did you do?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0447">erm I did some cross trainer</u>
<u n="13" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0447">then I did a two mile run</u>
<u n="15" who="S0448">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0447">and then I did a ten mile bike ride</u>
<u n="17" who="S0448">wow</u>
<u n="18" who="S0447">and then I came back and did some sit-ups</u>
<u n="19" who="S0448">fucking hell</u>
<u n="20" who="S0447">and stuff yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0448">oh I'm so fat</u>
<u n="22" who="S0447">no you're not</u>
<u n="23" who="S0448">I am I really need to get moving</u>
<u n="24" who="S0447">you're not fat</u>
<u n="25" who="S0448">I do need to do something though</u>
<u n="26" who="S0447">what do you need to do?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0448">exercise</u>
<u n="28" who="S0447">well do some then</u>
<u n="29" who="S0448">oh I hate exercise <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0447">well I'm not the greatest fan of it</u>
<u n="31" who="S0448">you've gotta be you have to be</u>
<u n="32" who="S0447">well not really</u>
<u n="33" who="S0448">yeah you actually participate in sport by choice that is someone who gets along with it</u>
<u n="34" who="S0447">mm true</u>
<u n="35" who="S0448">well you can't be an ex-professional footballer and say you don't like exercise oh my god all the fat people would kill you</u>
<u n="36" who="S0447">I don't really like exercise I didn't enjoy the fitness part of it</u>
<u n="37" who="S0448">yeah but still</u>
<u n="38" who="S0447">I just enjoyed the playing football bit</u>
<u n="39" who="S0448">that's still enjoying sport</u>
<u n="40" who="S0447">okay</u>
<u n="41" who="S0448">I haven't got a single thing I enjoy they always said you'll find that one thing and when you connect with it that'll be it and I never found one thing</u>
<u n="42" who="S0447">maybe you'll do like dominoes or something</u>
<u n="43" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that doesn't help</u>
<u n="44" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> extreme dominoes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ultimate domino</u>
<u n="46" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> brilliant maybe I need to get into darts because they're all allowed to be fat</u>
<u n="48" who="S0447">great I've got a darts board in my kitchen that I'm good at darts</u>
<u n="49" who="S0448">I'm not it's the hand-eye thing that I don't have</u>
<u n="50" who="S0447">we we were gonna start a darts team</u>
<u n="51" who="S0448">who?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0447">erm actually like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and a couple of people and actually play in a league and things like that</u>
<u n="53" who="S0448">oh wow</u>
<u n="54" who="S0447">and then realised we're not forty-five years old</u>
<u n="55" who="S0448">well it doesn't stop you all from playing golf</u>
<u n="56" who="S0447">true</u>
<u n="57" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0447">golf's golf's a younger person's game</u>
<u n="59" who="S0448">what? I would say if anything <trunc>go</trunc>golf's the older one</u>
<u n="60" who="S0447">no</u>
<u n="61" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0447">have you seen Rory McIlroy?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0448">have you seen <pause dur="short"/> old man golfer?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0447">no you got a text</u>
<u n="65" who="S0448">I know I <trunc>sh</trunc> I need to I need to put that on mute</u>
<u n="66" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0448">oh why can I never work it out? <pause dur="short"/> oh no I almost muted you then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0447">that would have been an error</u>
<u n="69" who="S0448">it would have been a classic error though</u>
<u n="70" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0448">so</u>
<u n="72" who="S0447" trans="overlap">so so</u>
<u n="73" who="S0448">talk to me</u>
<u n="74" who="S0447">hello <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't how's how's your story finishing?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0448">ah it ended really crap</u>
<u n="76" who="S0447">well I'm sure it'll be fine</u>
<u n="77" who="S0448">no and it's really different to all the other ones like it's way more fictiony than the other ones but oh well</u>
<u n="78" who="S0447">sure it'll be fine don't worry</u>
<u n="79" who="S0448">you can't just always say that I'll be fine cos sometimes I'm not gonna be fine</u>
<u n="80" who="S0447">did this dinner party actually happen?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0448">no</u>
<u n="82" who="S0447">surely it's fiction then isn't it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0448">yeah but I needed a way for her to be talking about it because I read some of the ones where they literally just started listing objects and I thought it was really boring so yolo</u>
<u n="84" who="S0447">okay fair enough</u>
<u n="85" who="S0448">don't even care anymore I just wanna quit</u>
<u n="86" who="S0447"><unclear/> not quit</u>
<u n="87" who="S0448">I want to I hate creative writing I hate it with a passion</u>
<u n="88" who="S0447" trans="overlap">not quitting <pause dur="short"/> not quitting</u>
<u n="89" who="S0448">uh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0447">do not quit</u>
<u n="91" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wanna quit but I can't quit it's too late to quit</u>
<u n="92" who="S0447">yes you couldn't quit <vocal desc="yawn"/> ah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0448">sleepy?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0447" trans="overlap">can't believe you yeah I can't believe you like wasted all your evening</u>
<u n="95" who="S0448">what? I didn't waste it I was brushing up on my trivia</u>
<u n="96" who="S0447">yeah when you knew you needed to finish your story</u>
<u n="97" who="S0448">because I thought that more people were not go basically I checked earlier on and only three people had handed it in and I was like oh cool like half the class are gonna leave it as well so I may as well just leave it cos I need an extra day to finish it and then I went on at ten o'clock just before Never Mind the Buzzcocks and everyone had done it and I was like oh now I'm gonna have to do it now but then I obviously wanted to watch Never Mind the Buzzcocks so I've just done it after</u>
<u n="98" who="S0447">ah <pause dur="short"/> and then trying to push me back <vocal desc="yawn"/> to where I <unclear/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0448">that was your fault though you told me to finish it I was just gonna not hand it in but then you were like you must finish it before ringing me so that's why</u>
<u n="100" who="S0447">yeah but surely that's a good thing</u>
<u n="101" who="S0448">yeah but then you can't blame me for pushing your phone call back to eleven because it would have been at half ten had you not made me be good</u>
<u n="102" who="S0447">well you would have been at at half ten if you had of done it instead of watching Pointless but</u>
<u n="103" who="S0448">yeah but like how can you tell me not to watch Pointless you love Pointless</u>
<u n="104" who="S0447">yeah <unclear/> but still you needed to get that done</u>
<u n="105" who="S0448">well it is done so <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0447">okay</u>
<u n="107" who="S0448"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0447">don't don't do that</u>
<u n="109" who="S0448">why not?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0447">cos I said so</u>
<u n="111" who="S0448">well I don't take no orders from you</u>
<u n="112" who="S0447">ha I'm the boss</u>
<u n="113" who="S0448">boss bitch</u>
<u n="114" who="S0447">yep</u>
<u n="115" who="S0448">my bitch <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0447">interesting</u>
<u n="119" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0447">erm what was I going to say?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0448">I don't know</u>
<u n="122" who="S0447">erm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0448">do you know what I'm gonna say?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0447">no what?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0448">unless did you remember your thing?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0447">did I remember my thing?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0448">well it sounded like you were talking when I was talking then so I thought maybe you'd remembered</u>
<u n="128" who="S0447">oh no no I hadn't</u>
<u n="129" who="S0448">oh well do you know what I'm really pissed off about? do you remember me telling you that my phone synced to Facebook so I had all my Facebook contacts in here</u>
<u n="130" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0448">and it took me ages to work out how to get rid of it and like I <trunc>ke</trunc> I got rid of all the ones I didn't want but I kept the ones that I did want so that people like you could have pictures and today it un-synced itself so I went through all that effort for nothing and now it's gone back to nobody having pictures it's just like a blank man shadow for everyone again so annoyed and</u>
<u n="132" who="S0447">ah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0448">for some reason some of my really important numbers have like disappeared like when I go through my big phonebook list and I scroll down there's no like home saved and my mum's mobile and my nan's nobile nobile? mobile aren't saved in it but then if I go to the phone like the number pad and type it in then it comes up being like do you want to call home? so it's clearly still saved in there it's just disappeared from the list and I'm too retarded to work out how to get it back</u>
<u n="134" who="S0447">shit son</u>
<u n="135" who="S0448">I know so now at the minute I literally just have to like type half the number and then wait for it to auto guess which one it is that's pissing me off</u>
<u n="136" who="S0447">ah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="138" who="S0447">ah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0448">mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0447">well I'm not sure how you fix that to be honest</u>
<u n="141" who="S0448">perhaps I should show you my phone when you next come up</u>
<u n="142" who="S0447">yeah we'll have a look at it next week</u>
<u n="143" who="S0448">yay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0447">you've got two days off now</u>
<u n="145" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="146" who="S0447">ah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0448">well I've got to do stuff on them though</u>
<u n="148" who="S0447">ah what have you got to do?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0448">well <trunc>Tue</trunc> tomorrow I have to basically over the point of these next two days I have to run I have to erm do some more creative writing cos I've got another deadline for Thursday I have to do some seminar work that's in for Friday Wednesday I have to stay in until a package gets delivered because it came today and I wasn't in even though I was only on campus for like two frigging hours they decided to come in those two hours and then they asked me to go and pick it up and I was like no because the er place where you pick it up is at the other end of town up a giant hill so I'm not walking there so I've asked for redelivery for Wednesday and that means I need to stay in like literally all day until they deliver it so I might be housebound depending on when they come er yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0447">oh</u>
<u n="151" who="S0448">and then just all that</u>
<u n="152" who="S0447" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0448">hm?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0447">what are you having delivered?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0448">oh a phone charger <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0447">oh I <unclear>see</unclear></u>
<u n="157" who="S0448" trans="overlap">so I can give the other one back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0447">yeah well fair enough</u>
<u n="159" who="S0448">but yeah erm I was gonna say something but I've forgotten now</u>
<u n="160" who="S0447">oh that's rubbish</u>
<u n="161" who="S0448">well it's your fault you started asking me a question when I was about to finish and then I forgot so now I don't know I forgot because of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0447">I should have let you finish</u>
<u n="163" who="S0448">yeah you should have let me finish</u>
<u n="164" who="S0447">just rude</u>
<u n="165" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm god what was it gonna be about? oh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0447">you were explaining what you were doing</u>
<u n="167" who="S0448">I know I was gonna oh yeah no I was just gonna say like I need to do general like sorting out my future stuff as well</u>
<u n="168" who="S0447">ah fair enough</u>
<u n="169" who="S0448" trans="overlap">erm what else are they gonna say? my mum said that we should wait till next year for The Lion King because she gets this like thing in January which you can get discounts off of erm theatre tickets and she said that's how she got cos you know it was my mum that took me last time</u>
<u n="170" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0448">she said that's how she did it cos otherwise it's like very expensive so she said if we wait until the new year she'll try and get them for us and then we can use her discount yay discount</u>
<u n="172" who="S0447">okay do you want me to let you into a <unclear>little</unclear> secret?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0448">uh what?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0447">I was using that as a cunning ploy to see what theatre shows you'd actually been to in case I got you that for Christmas</u>
<u n="175" who="S0448">oh really? you're too you're too sneaky I can't cope with it</u>
<u n="176" who="S0447">it was good though wasn't it?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0447">rather than just asking you</u>
<u n="179" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0447">see I'm smarter than the average bear</u>
<u n="181" who="S0448">I can't do bear <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't deal with it because I'm like Goldilocks in this sitch</u>
<u n="182" who="S0447">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="183" who="S0448">ah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0447">see how smart I am?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0448">I know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0447">just too good</u>
<u n="187" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0447">anyway</u>
<u n="189" who="S0448">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0447">ah <vocal desc="yawn"/> I've gotta work tomorrow</u>
<u n="191" who="S0448">I know what time at?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0447">half eight</u>
<u n="193" who="S0448">oh yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0447">same as always</u>
<u n="195" who="S0448">just trying to work out the time you need to go to bed at <pause dur="short"/> what time do you need?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0447" trans="overlap">ah don't worry about that</u>
<u n="197" who="S0448">no I will worry because otherwise then you just tell me you're tired all the time and it's not fair because I've got the day off tomorrow so I don't care how long I stay up but if I keep you up for hours then it's naughty because you have to go in tomorrow</u>
<u n="198" who="S0447">well I shall stay up until the same time as I stayed up yesterday</u>
<u n="199" who="S0448">no I'll end it before then cos you're you're tired today</u>
<u n="200" who="S0447">well I was tired yesterday I'm actually not that tired at the minute I just keep yawning</u>
<u n="201" who="S0448">oh have you been napping?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0447" trans="overlap">I had a nap earlier</u>
<u n="203" who="S0448">yeah classic</u>
<u n="204" who="S0447">yeah I told you I was having a nap</u>
<u n="205" who="S0448">I know but like I was busy writing at that time so I wasn't paying much attention to like normally if I'm not doing anything I really notice when you're napping cos I notice that you're not replying but then if I'm busy I don't really notice that you've not replied</u>
<u n="206" who="S0447">yeah and <unclear/> dead annoyed that you didn't reply to me for like nine hours</u>
<u n="207" who="S0448">it wasn't nine hours it was two cos it was an episode of Pointless which is an hour and an episode of The Chase which is an hour</u>
<u n="208" who="S0447">okay</u>
<u n="209" who="S0448">and I told you that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fault your bestie's fault so that's not my fault</u>
<u n="210" who="S0447">I like the way you're blaming him cos you assume that I won't get angry at him</u>
<u n="211" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0448">but it actually was his fault because all I was doing was innocently getting dinner and then as I walked up to take my food upstairs it was already on and he was watching it and I was like oh I've been sucked in and so it was his fault because if he hadn't of been there with it on I wouldn't have been sucked in</u>
<u n="213" who="S0447">okay</u>
<u n="214" who="S0448">yep</u>
<u n="215" who="S0447">I'll let you off you going out tomorrow night?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0448">probably I don't know because basically I finish my antibiotics tomorrow like lunchtime and so I think it's alright to go out because there would have been like a whole like half day but then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm I haven't seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in in a while and he said he has news for me and so he asked if I wanted to go out with him on Wednesday and I don't really wanna do both days so I don't know which one to do at the minute or whether to just try it cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't do tomorrow cos he's got cheerleading and then</u>
<u n="217" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0448">I didn't know whether to try and ask them if they just wanted to do Wednesday instead but they all like Hustle more than going out on a Wednesday so I don't think that'll work so I don't know what I'm doing yet</u>
<u n="219" who="S0447">ah fair enough</u>
<u n="220" who="S0448"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s having a mid-life crisis</u>
<u n="221" who="S0447">why?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0448">he's he's messaging me today been like oh my god I'm so old I don't know where my life is going and I'm gonna die <vocal desc="laugh"/> alone and all stuff like that</u>
<u n="223" who="S0447">so old how old is he?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he's only twenty-one but I suppose that's quite old for us because we're only twenty I know that you're much older but</u>
<u n="225" who="S0447">I'm not much older</u>
<u n="226" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah you're like a hundred <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0447">oi I'm not that old</u>
<u n="228" who="S0448">no you're not</u>
<u n="229" who="S0447">mean</u>
<u n="230" who="S0448">I'm not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0447">you are</u>
<u n="232" who="S0448">I'm not I'm just jokes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0447" trans="overlap">I'm gonna cry now</u>
<u n="234" who="S0448">oh fine</u>
<u n="235" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0447">I'm kidding</u>
<u n="237" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0447">I think I've actually like pulled a muscle in my groin</u>
<u n="239" who="S0448">oh ha ha</u>
<u n="240" who="S0447">no but yeah it's like pains not painful it's just a bit sore feels like it needs to be stretched</u>
<u n="241" who="S0448" trans="overlap">right don't whatever you do don't go tomorrow</u>
<u n="242" who="S0447">no I'm not gonna go tomorrow</u>
<u n="243" who="S0448">good</u>
<u n="244" who="S0447">I go like once every two months</u>
<u n="245" who="S0448">what to the gym?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0447" trans="overlap">my sort of average yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0448">is that why you have so many problems cos you don't go regularly?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0447">probably</u>
<u n="249" who="S0448">probs</u>
<u n="250" who="S0447">I might go on like Wednesday</u>
<u n="251" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0447">or Thursday</u>
<u n="253" who="S0448">Thursday go Thursday</u>
<u n="254" who="S0447">okay yeah I've got an easy  week next week can't wait</u>
<u n="255" who="S0448">a what an Indian week?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0447">yeah Indian week</u>
<u n="257" who="S0448">oh what did you say?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0447">easy week</u>
<u n="259" who="S0448">easy oh yeah because this is your week where you have one day in and then one day off and then one day off or something</u>
<u n="260" who="S0447">like I had one day in the office and that's it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0448">yeah oh yeah cos you do it one day <trunc>aft</trunc> I have got a I have got a you take one day off to revise one day off for your test then one day in the office but that's the day you drive up anyway so that doesn't count like a proper day and then you've got the next two days off and then the weekend and then you have to go back to work boom</u>
<u n="262" who="S0447">well done</u>
<u n="263" who="S0448">I do listen</u>
<u n="264" who="S0447">stalker</u>
<u n="265" who="S0448">no just listener</u>
<u n="266" who="S0447">guess what?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0448">what?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0447">I've got a plan</u>
<u n="269" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0447">I might buy a new TV</u>
<u n="271" who="S0448">oh my god literally why?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0447">because in Argos you can get a fifty inch flat screen TV for three hundred pounds so what I can do is I can buy that app which is like <unclear/> my TV and then just sell that TV <unclear/> and if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> calls me back a hundred pounds</u>
<u n="273" who="S0448">you're insane though you don't need another TV I already thought your old TV was big you don't need another TV</u>
<u n="274" who="S0447">think how good a fifty inch TV <unclear>would be</unclear></u>
<u n="275" who="S0448">your TV's already good</u>
<u n="276" who="S0447">it'll be like the cinema</u>
<u n="277" who="S0448">yeah but your TV's already good and if you did that you'd lose all your desk space</u>
<u n="278" who="S0447">I I'd lose all my what?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0448">your space around where the TV is now you wouldn't have any space because it'd be bigger</u>
<u n="280" who="S0447">yeah I can put it on the wall so then I <unclear/> so now I've got more space yeah that I can put it in the floor so then got more space</u>
<u n="281" who="S0448">well you're obviously gonna like make your own decisions anyway</u>
<u n="282" who="S0447">you've gone really muffled but can't get an actual <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0448">oh a bell I just said you're obviously gonna meet what?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0447">I can hear you now</u>
<u n="285" who="S0448">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="286" who="S0447">yeah sounded like you were talking into a pillow</u>
<u n="287" who="S0448">well I wasn't</u>
<u n="288" who="S0447">okay</u>
<u n="289" who="S0448">you know Hodor remember I told you about Hodor erm from Game of Thrones?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0448">you know he did that DJ set in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0448">now he's coming to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0447">is he?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0448">yeah I'll have to see if I can get you a ticket</u>
<u n="296" who="S0447">I don't still don't know who he is</u>
<u n="297" who="S0448">you're gonna have to fucking learn by next week</u>
<u n="298" who="S0447">by next week? what he's coming up next week?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0448" trans="overlap">he's DJing he's DJing at Halloween that's why I have to try and get you a ticket cos like lol we can't miss Hodor we're gonna have to go out now</u>
<u n="300" who="S0447">ah okay</u>
<u n="301" who="S0448">don't sound so depressed about it it's Hodor he's majestic</u>
<u n="302" who="S0447">I don't even know who he is</u>
<u n="303" who="S0448">I'm gonna make you watch Game of Thrones you absolutely have got to watch Game of Thrones</u>
<u n="304" who="S0447">ah really?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0448">you'll love it I er yes really yes</u>
<u n="306" who="S0447">okay <pause dur="short"/> if I have to watch that you have to do something that you don't wanna do then</u>
<u n="307" who="S0448">ah fine but you should want to watch Game of Thrones cos it is literally amazing right why are you not wanting to watch it? I don't even understand I can't comprehend</u>
<u n="308" who="S0447">I'm not I'm not following the trend</u>
<u n="309" who="S0448">ah but ah stressing me out fine what would I have to do?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0447">I don't know yet I'll <unclear/> and have a think</u>
<u n="311" who="S0448">well I think it's only fair that you pick something I don't wanna do but actually it will benefit my life massively and make me say oh I'm so glad you did that cos that's what's gonna happen when you watch Game of Thrones you're gonna say oh thank you for making me watch that this is amazing</u>
<u n="312" who="S0447">how long is Game of Thrones?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0448">well it's a TV show it's an hour long what do you think?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0447">well I didn't know did I? it could be half an hour</u>
<u n="315" who="S0448">no it's an <trunc>ho</trunc> it's an hour of pure it's an hour of pure brilliance</u>
<u n="316" who="S0447">okay</u>
<u n="317" who="S0448">and then erm obviously like you've gotta you've gotta start from the very beginning so you've gotta start right back from season one you can't be jumping because you need to follow the story oh it's so good though so good</u>
<u n="318" who="S0447">so I've gotta do that for an hour</u>
<u n="319" who="S0448">trust right trust me you need to sit and watch the first erm I don't know couple of episodes of season one and then if you can look me in the eyes and tell me you're not enjoying it I'll let you stop but I know that's not gonna happen cos everyone in their right mind loves Game of Thrones</u>
<u n="320" who="S0447">okay if I do that then you have to come on my football stadium tour with me</u>
<u n="321" who="S0448">fine deal I will do that if you watch Game of Thrones cos I'm telling you you are gonna love it</u>
<u n="322" who="S0447">okay fair enough</u>
<u n="323" who="S0448">yep</u>
<u n="324" who="S0447">we erm we can do that on our day in <anon type="place"/> cos it's in <anon type="place"/> as well</u>
<u n="325" who="S0448">oh</u>
<u n="326" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0448">can we do that after cocktails so that I can get drunk and then not have to pay attention?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0447">no</u>
<u n="329" who="S0448">oh</u>
<u n="330" who="S0447">it's fine you don't have to I'll find someone else</u>
<u n="331" who="S0448">well surely you'd enjoy it more with someone else cos you can you can nudge them be like oh look that's so cool that's where so and so did that and they'll actually be like yeah whereas I'd be like uh when's the food?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0447">there is no food</u>
<u n="333" who="S0448"><trunc>exact</trunc> well no I we'd be getting food after god cookies we need to get Ben's Cookies Ben's Cookies</u>
<u n="334" who="S0447">okay chill out</u>
<u n="335" who="S0448">I am chill I'm just mm this is how I plan I just shout things and hope that someone else has written then down</u>
<u n="336" who="S0447">this is why I'm the planner</u>
<u n="337" who="S0448">you say that but normally I'm the planner so don't be judging like I can't plan you've seen my whiteboard in my room I'm probably the only person who brings a whiteboard to uni so take that</u>
<u n="338" who="S0447">okay I have a whiteboard in my kitchen</u>
<u n="339" who="S0448">is it your personal whiteboard?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0447">no it's not <unclear>mum's</unclear></u>
<u n="341" who="S0448">does it does it come with a pink leopard print pen?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0447">I don't know</u>
<u n="343" who="S0448">does it? does it? does it?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0447">probably</u>
<u n="345" who="S0448">I don't think it does I think I think I've got the better whiteboard</u>
<u n="346" who="S0447">mine's bigger</u>
<u n="347" who="S0448">it's not er size doesn't matter</u>
<u n="348" who="S0447">it it does massively</u>
<u n="349" who="S0448" trans="overlap">no it just matters how you use it and I use my whiteboard quite sufficiently thanks</u>
<u n="350" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you can you can fit more stuff on mine</u>
<u n="351" who="S0448">no you just mine teaches the art of good handwriting cos the smaller you write the more you fit on</u>
<u n="352" who="S0447">yeah but if you write smaller on your and and</u>
<u n="353" who="S0448" trans="overlap">ah da da da da da da da</u>
<u n="354" who="S0447" trans="overlap">and you write smaller on mine you still fit more on mine</u>
<u n="355" who="S0448">mine's pink end of</u>
<u n="356" who="S0447">well I don't know what colour mine is white I think</u>
<u n="357" who="S0448">well that's just</u>
<u n="358" who="S0447"><unclear/> a whiteboard</u>
<u n="359" who="S0448">well that's why mine's infinitely better</u>
<u n="360" who="S0447">okay</u>
<u n="361" who="S0448">my bed's moved way too far away from the wall</u>
<u n="362" who="S0447">ah <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0448" trans="overlap">I reckon I could fit my face down there now</u>
<u n="364" who="S0447">try it</u>
<u n="365" who="S0448">my whole face try it what if I get stuck like when I got stuck in the cupboard in the other room</u>
<u n="366" who="S0447">I was I was thinking more if you do that then all you <unclear/> might <unclear/> might push further out then you <unclear/> down the side <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0448">well</u>
<u n="368" who="S0447"><unclear/> want you to fall</u>
<u n="369" who="S0448">that's not very nice and I'm not going to do it</u>
<u n="370" who="S0447"><unclear/> want you to fall I'm just that was what the picture that was going through my mind</u>
<u n="371" who="S0448">yeah which you were giggling over</u>
<u n="372" who="S0447">ah I'd come and kiss you better</u>
<u n="373" who="S0448">I'd hope so after pushing me down there</u>
<u n="374" who="S0447">woah woah woah I never said I pushed you</u>
<u n="375" who="S0448">well you would have pushed me by by proxy because it was your idea</u>
<u n="376" who="S0447">you'd have probably just fallen down there cos you moved so far to the other side of the bed when we cuddle</u>
<u n="377" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll you'll come up on Wednesday you'll come up on Wednesday and just find me still wedged down there and I've like not moved for over a week oh thank god someone came to help</u>
<u n="378" who="S0447">you'd you'd you'd have moved</u>
<u n="379" who="S0448">how do you know?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0447">cos you'd have needed dinner at some point</u>
<u n="381" who="S0448">and a wee</u>
<u n="382" who="S0447">yeah you should only possibly be in there for an hour at most</u>
<u n="383" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you know I saw an advert today for you know the Tena like piss yourself pants</u>
<u n="384" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0448">they're doing free samples at the minute you can go online and apply for some free samples I was like I should totally do that</u>
<u n="386" who="S0447">yeah you should</u>
<u n="387" who="S0448">I should <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0447">ah we've we've got this erm my boss has got this new thing for his <unclear>field</unclear> but erm it records noises and it's like a motion sensor but it goes motion it like plays out the noises really loud so you've got it in case anyone tries to like break into his field</u>
<u n="389" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0447">it'll be dogs barking that we've recorded this woman screaming and we've put it in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at work's desk so when she opens the drawers there will be this screaming noise coming out of her desk</u>
<u n="391" who="S0448">you guys</u>
<u n="392" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's gonna be funny</u>
<u n="393" who="S0448">you should film like a hidden camera show at your work</u>
<u n="394" who="S0447">it's great <unclear>just</unclear> do that to <unclear>each other</unclear></u>
<u n="395" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0447"><unclear/> they have a ghost at work anyway</u>
<u n="397" who="S0448">a ghost?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0448">what?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0447">cos I keep I've been to the toilet three times in like the last month and</u>
<u n="401" who="S0448" trans="overlap">I thought that was the end of the story <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0447">no</u>
<u n="403" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0447">and the keys for the room next door are normally just left in the door</u>
<u n="405" who="S0448">right</u>
<u n="406" who="S0447">and I can always hear them jangling</u>
<u n="407" who="S0448">are these on windy days or no there's no these are like proper jangling as if you were holding a bunch of keys jangling?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0447">and it's not another person just holding them?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0448">no</u>
<u n="410" who="S0447">no no one says that they've been up and they all swear that they have not been up there</u>
<u n="411" who="S0448">could just be more classic work bants</u>
<u n="412" who="S0447">no one of the girls is proper scared of ghosts and she's like no seriously no one could have been up there I swear on my life</u>
<u n="413" who="S0448">oh okay</u>
<u n="414" who="S0447">I'm like I'm like oh okay we'll I've had it like three times now</u>
<u n="415" who="S0448">maybe this is why you don't wee enough? cos you're just too scared to subconsciously</u>
<u n="416" who="S0447">well yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0448">I'll send you like to Derek Acorah and he'll sort you out</u>
<u n="418" who="S0447">yeah we'll get him in cos it used to be an old dairy our building</u>
<u n="419" who="S0448">oh cheese</u>
<u n="420" who="S0447">er <vocal desc="laugh"/> is that a random statement or</u>
<u n="421" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a declaration of love</u>
<u n="422" who="S0447"><unclear/> did did anyone say cheese?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or is it</u>
<u n="424" who="S0447">erm I don't know</u>
<u n="425" who="S0448">oh okay useless</u>
<u n="426" who="S0447">er yeah well <unclear/> well annoyed earlier</u>
<u n="427" who="S0448">what over your test?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0448">ah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0447">like make sure you read these three areas cos that's what the question's gonna be about <unclear/> the question well that was a complete lie what what</u>
<u n="431" who="S0448">did you say anything about it?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0447">no well whatever at least I've read it</u>
<u n="433" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0447">well I needed to read it anyway before</u>
<u n="435" who="S0448">yeah maybe maybe that was his plan all along</u>
<u n="436" who="S0447">mm I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="437" who="S0448">ah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0447">erm does does anyone at your in your house drink whisky?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0448">erm maybe why?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0447">do they want a bottle of whisky?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0448">are you on about like you found some whisky and no one wants it or you're or you're on about buying it cos</u>
<u n="442" who="S0447">no I won it at in a raffle like a fortified bottle of whisky and I'm never gonna drink it</u>
<u n="443" who="S0448">erm yeah what kind?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0447">Bell's it's like a erm a black labelled one so it's like a special type or something</u>
<u n="445" who="S0448">ah how'd you win it?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0447">it was part of a raffle</u>
<u n="447" who="S0448">yeah but where? what?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0447">at the golf club there was a raffle and then they picked my number out and like won the prize</u>
<u n="449" who="S0448">right cheers for that</u>
<u n="450" who="S0447"><unclear/> that's how you win a raffle you asked how</u>
<u n="451" who="S0448">yeah but I I don't think I mean how I think I meant maybe like where or something like where was the raffle</u>
<u n="452" who="S0447">ah it was at the golf club <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0448">okay thanks</u>
<u n="454" who="S0447">well <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm just saying what you asked for but yeah it's like a a <trunc>s</trunc>special edition one</u>
<u n="455" who="S0448">well I've asked them</u>
<u n="456" who="S0447">right okay cos er yeah they can just have it I don't know anyone that drinks whisky</u>
<u n="457" who="S0448">I'm surprised you don't you're an old man</u>
<u n="458" who="S0447">oi I'm not</u>
<u n="459" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0447">not old <pause dur="long"/> have you been thinking anymore about this thing you've gotta do next year?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0448">what thing?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0447">your P whatever it is</u>
<u n="463" who="S0448">my PGCE?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0447">P yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0448"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0447">okay tell him he can have it</u>
<u n="467" who="S0448">erm yeah PGCE erm <pause dur="short"/> what was I gonna say? yeah I've been looking a little bit erm basically what I'm gonna do is take a year out like when I graduate</u>
<u n="468" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0448">erm use that time to get the experience that you need cos you did I tell you? have I told you already? I can't remember if it was you I was talking to erm that I have to get so many weeks work experience in a school before I can apply</u>
<u n="470" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0448">yeah so I'm gonna use that year out to erm <pause dur="long"/> hang on erm they're messaging me about the whisky</u>
<u n="472" who="S0447">okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="473" who="S0448">erm what was I saying?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0447">talking about having a year out</u>
<u n="475" who="S0448">oh yeah so I'll take a year out use that time to get the experience in the schools that I need and then obviously like work as well erm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0448">I'm hoping to be able to get a job like as either a classroom assistant or a nursery assistant sort of thing cos even though that's not great money like they're the kind of roles that gives me experience whilst paying me and you don't have to like cos you obviously you can't go be like a teaching assistant until you've done a training course but you can be a nursery assistant cos they're not teachers</u>
<u n="478" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0448">do you know what I mean? so I might try and get a job like that and then I was thinking maybe try and like carry on with my tutoring erm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0448">just so that I've got loads of experience working with kids and then at some point I wanna I dunno cos obviously this all depends on how much money I've earnt but I wanna go somewhere like I know I haven't got the job but I still wanna travel even if it's not to America I wanna go somewhere before I start working for good do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0447">oh right</u>
<u n="483" who="S0448">right yeah mm probably not for that long now but</u>
<u n="484" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0448">cos I know a <trunc>loa</trunc>loads of people are like talking about doing Interrailing and stuff and I dunno if I'd wanna do that cos that's like quite expensive for what it is like I've never been really the sort to like wanna backpack and shit cos it's all a bit dirty for me but</u>
<u n="486" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0448">I just wanna do <trunc>s</trunc> ah I just wanna do something even if it's just a holiday I wanna do something before I commit to <vocal desc="sigh"/> a life of teaching <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0447">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0448">and then yeah obviously I'll apply to start a PGCE in the following September and then er that takes just under a year cos you finish in July erm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0448">I've been looking I've been looking at I looked I can't remember if I told no I don't think it was you I was telling you this I looked at <anon type="place"/> and I decided to rule it out because you have to be interviewed to get in there and like interviews at <anon type="place"/> are always like supposed to be really random and I don't do very well in interviews anyway so I thought it's best to go for one where they don't interview me erm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0447">right</u>
<u n="493" who="S0448">so I've been looking at <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> I'd rather go to <anon type="place"/> just cos I don't really like <anon type="place"/> that much I get a bit scared in <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="494" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0448">yeah I mean the <anon type="place"/> one like my mum said she knows someone who's done a PGCE at <anon type="place"/> erm so it can't be that bad and I like the fact they do one cos you know you can do them like for either primary or secondary?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0448">erm like the one at <anon type="place"/> you couldn't like pick which one you wanted to specialise in so I'd have had to do some secondary teaching and I really don't wanna do that whereas the one at <anon type="place"/> like I can pick to specifically do primary and early years and I liked that one cos</u>
<u n="498" who="S0447"><unclear/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0448">I get to do the early years bit as well which is you know like the <trunc>h</trunc> the er before school like you know like two three four-year-olds</u>
<u n="500" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0448">erm so I liked that cos I kinda the like the younger they are the more I prefer it like when I've done my work experience before I've done it in erm I've done work experience in reception year one year two and year five and I definitely preferred working with the little ones erm I'd rather work in a nursery than a school but <trunc>n</trunc>nursery workers get paid less which is why I've gotta do primary school cos</u>
<u n="502" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0448">even though er teaching isn't exactly like gonna pay me that much anyway nursery work is literally like bottom of the barrel stuff so yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0447" trans="overlap">it doesn't pay that badly</u>
<u n="505" who="S0448">it's not bad but it's just not great do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0447">mm it's still probably like twenty-five grand a year</u>
<u n="507" who="S0448">yeah but that's not that much like considering how expensive everything is now it's not er</u>
<u n="508" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0448">it's good but it's not enough to like live on comfortably and do everything I'd wanna do not that teaching really will be either but I don't really have any other options so</u>
<u n="510" who="S0447">mm fair enough what are you planning to do then?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0448">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0447">you said to live comfortably and plan and do what I wanna do</u>
<u n="513" who="S0448">well just like you know like thinking long-term I wanna have children but I don't really wanna be one of those people who does it when they can't afford to look after them</u>
<u n="514" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0448">and I wanna be like my mum's always been really good at taking us on holidays and there's only been like one year I think where she couldn't afford to do it and she makes sure she takes us every year I'd wanna be able to do that because then like I've been so many places I think it's important to keep that up <pause dur="short"/> all really boring stuff like just I'd wanna be able to just not have to worry about bills and yeah I dunno</u>
<u n="516" who="S0447">well fair enough</u>
<u n="517" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0447">well hopefully you won't <trunc>jus</trunc> hopefully it won't just be your money though that you have to live off</u>
<u n="519" who="S0448">no I know it better not be <vocal desc="laugh"/> but</u>
<u n="520" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0448">but I don't wanna I'm never gonna be that sort of person and goes oh it doesn't matter how much I'm earning because you're earning so-and-so amount cos that's not fair like got to be able to contribute and think about worse case scenarios if it does end up being me on my own</u>
<u n="522" who="S0447">and my <unclear/> million pound a year and then you'll be <unclear/> he's earning to much</u>
<u n="523" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I just wouldn't wanna live off it like I still wanna be able to contribute</u>
<u n="524" who="S0447">that's fine then</u>
<u n="525" who="S0448">I'm not a sponger</u>
<u n="526" who="S0447">that's fine we'll split bills down the middle and I'll just keep <unclear/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0448" trans="overlap">you can't I'm just gonna throw this out there if you become a millionaire and I'm still just a teacher we ain't splitting fifty fifty <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0447">what? that's</u>
<u n="529" who="S0448">I'm a frigging teacher you're a millionaire <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0447">you said that you wanted to er you wanted to <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0448" trans="overlap">contribute contribute and I would contribute equally if we were on equal salaries but if we are talking you have literally made millions and I'm making like twenty grand a year that that's just unacceptable <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we can contribute equally</u>
<u n="533" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> cheeky shit</u>
<u n="534" who="S0447">although <trunc>fif</trunc> more like fifty thousand pound a month income</u>
<u n="535" who="S0448" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> and my twenty grand a year</u>
<u n="536" who="S0447">yeah no it will just go into savings</u>
<u n="537" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0447">I'll just spend it it's fine <unclear/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0448" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="540" who="S0447">cos next month I'll get another fifty grand</u>
<u n="541" who="S0448">oh god</u>
<u n="542" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0447">right you're gonna regret saying split it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0448">I didn't say split equally I just wanted you to know I'm not gonna like expect to live off your money however if you were to become a millionaire I would expect to not have to pay half and half <pause dur="short"/> it works both ways if I happen to make it big like not really sure how it's gonna happen at this rate then I wouldn't expect you to pay half and half</u>
<u n="545" who="S0447">okay deal</u>
<u n="546" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="547" who="S0447">well see I think you're you're gonna end up better off in this deal</u>
<u n="548" who="S0448">no</u>
<u n="549" who="S0447">I'm I'm <trunc>dest</trunc> I'm destined to be a millionaire</u>
<u n="550" who="S0448">well that's not my fault</u>
<u n="551" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's weird</u>
<u n="552" who="S0448">what's weird? that I'm so shit compared to you?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0447">no you're not</u>
<u n="554" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0447">I just know it's gonna happen</u>
<u n="556" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0447">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who said it when he was young he he just knew it was gonna happen and the guy who's The Wolf of Wall Street is about</u>
<u n="558" who="S0448">oh for god's sake <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're obsessed with bloody Wolf of Wall Street</u>
<u n="559" who="S0447" trans="overlap">he said exactly the same I'm not I'm just <unclear/> just gonna watch this one the other day and I remembered him saying that it's just like yeah it's it's gonna happen</u>
<u n="560" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0447">it's just when it happens</u>
<u n="562" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll be fine</u>
<u n="563" who="S0447">yeah I know</u>
<u n="564" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0447">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0448">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0447">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0448">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0447">are you seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today? <unclear/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0448">no it was erm this morning on the way to my lecture erm I think cos like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actual <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent a Facebook message asking about erm staples and then cos I'd seen his name I was just like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then just got in my head and I was like no you can't have my trousers on the way to the bus and I was like oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you definitely should have done a story about the phoenix</u>
<u n="572" who="S0448">well I couldn't this time cos it was cos it was non-fiction</u>
<u n="573" who="S0447">you definitely have to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> into one of your stories</u>
<u n="574" who="S0448">okay I will</u>
<u n="575" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0447">and was <unclear/> he have your trousers?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0447"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0448"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0447">thought about sounding like <unclear/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0448">what about it? it's just it's not quite as catchy it hasn't really stayed with me</u>
<u n="583" who="S0447">no need to try and get that into like one of your stories as well but maybe <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has sand in his cracks</u>
<u n="584" who="S0448">I'll tell you why because no one would lend him bloody trousers</u>
<u n="585" who="S0447">well</u>
<u n="586" who="S0448">that sand in that crack is your fault you could have prevented it with a simple pair of orange trousers</u>
<u n="587" who="S0447">I could but do you know what? they're my orange trousers so <unclear>he's</unclear> just merely a mode of transport</u>
<u n="588" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought I was also your companion? make your mind up</u>
<u n="589" who="S0447">now he is but he's mainly a mode of transport</u>
<u n="590" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0447">would like to ride my phoenix down to Tesco</u>
<u n="592" who="S0448">I really really wanted brownies earlier</u>
<u n="593" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that was random <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0448">well it wasn't it wasn't if you followed my brain through its thought process my thought process went oh yeah he went to Tesco to get the cheesecake and then I was like oh desserts I love desserts you know I love desserts and then I was like oh yeah I was craving brownies earlier and that's what I decided to tell you</u>
<u n="595" who="S0447">oh okay</u>
<u n="596" who="S0448">oh really</u>
<u n="597" who="S0447" trans="overlap">I can I can even remember the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going for cheesecake</u>
<u n="598" who="S0448"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0447">you actually remembered what the full story don't you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0448">how can you not remember what you were taking him there for?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0447">oh it was orange cheesecake wasn't it?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0448">you cos you ruined it no one wants orange cheesecake it's all about the vanilla</u>
<u n="603" who="S0447">no no no</u>
<u n="604" who="S0448">it's all about the banana</u>
<u n="605" who="S0447">no it's not</u>
<u n="606" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it definitely is</u>
<u n="607" who="S0447">you if you ever blaspheme like that again</u>
<u n="608" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh by the way you know when we go to <anon type="place"/> which is happening sooner rather than later cos I'm dying for <anon type="place"/> erm I'll have to taste test your cakes first because I remember one of them was a mini banana cake it looked like the exact same colour as some of their other ones I wouldn't want you to die so I'm more than happy to put my life on the line for you there and test your cakes</u>
<u n="609" who="S0447">oh thanks you're such a hero</u>
<u n="610" who="S0448">I know lol I'll be there like eating the chocolate cake like yeah this this could still have banana hidden in it somewhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0448">and went in your mains I'll be like let me check this isn't banana curry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0447">well we can go at Christmas time</u>
<u n="614" who="S0448">eh yes I love <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0447"><unclear/> high pitched</u>
<u n="616" who="S0448">I know I'm sorry it's my <anon type="place"/> excitement coming out I fucking love <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0447">yeah well do you know where we can go at we can go at Christmas <vocal desc="yawn"/> we could we could go in those two days I'm taking off if you wanted?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0448">yeah? well it depends doesn't it cos we could I don't know we'll talk about it when you're up because if you've got like four days off in a row we may as well go somewhere other than <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0448">but we can sort that out when you're up cos it's easier to do it face-to-face cos then we could use my laptop and shit</u>
<u n="621" who="S0447">yeah we can have a laptop become a footballer</u>
<u n="622" who="S0448">no no footballing I told you get out get it out your system before you come up cos you've only got four days here I do not wanna be seen</u>
<u n="623" who="S0447" trans="overlap">I've been trying but it doesn't work on my laptop <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0448">oh no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0447">mm such a let down</u>
<u n="626" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're a let down</u>
<u n="627" who="S0447">it's really frustrating</u>
<u n="628" who="S0448">right I'll make you a deal</u>
<u n="629" who="S0447">what?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0448">you can become a footballer</u>
<u n="631" who="S0447">right</u>
<u n="632" who="S0448">that's not the end of the deal <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't just say right</u>
<u n="633" who="S0447">yeah yeah I <unclear>thought</unclear> deal</u>
<u n="634" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0448">no I was trying to work out I was gonna say you can become a footballer in that hour that I can go on campus on Thursday then I was thinking if you're here I might not go anyway because I've been going and it's bloody pointless because he's one of those ones that literally reads off the slides and I could just print the slides off at home so I don't know whether I'm gonna go or not if I go then you can become a footballer then</u>
<u n="637" who="S0447">okay yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0448">yeah then you can become a footballer in the times I'm in the shower</u>
<u n="639" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0448">and</u>
<u n="641" who="S0447">just on that you need to start taking longer showers</u>
<u n="642" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0447">because you yeah you're starting to smell so I really think you should start taking longer showers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0448">you can also become a footballer when I'm doing my makeup that gives you half an hour of being a footballer</u>
<u n="645" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0448">see look how nice I am to you</u>
<u n="647" who="S0447">I know you're a hero</u>
<u n="648" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0447">this is why I love you</u>
<u n="650" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="651" who="S0447">what?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0448">I said yes</u>
<u n="653" who="S0447">the phone died</u>
<u n="654" who="S0448">it didn't die</u>
<u n="655" who="S0447">the phone died it was like just went silent I had <unclear/> start and the end of the word</u>
<u n="656" who="S0448">well the word was yes er</u>
<u n="657" who="S0447">yeah I know but I heard <trunc>ye</trunc> like that that was it erm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0448">oh</u>
<u n="659" who="S0447">what was that?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I don't know</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="661" who="S0447">you know you said earlier that about the phone contacts going? so <unclear/> a picture</u>
<u n="662" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0447">I still have a picture of you erm it's just a picture of you</u>
<u n="664" who="S0448">oh god well what one?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0447">in a black and white top and a red skirt</u>
<u n="666" who="S0448">eh? <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't remember</u>
<u n="667" who="S0447" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0448">I don't I'm trying to remember what it is and I don't is it one of my profile pictures?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0447">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="670" who="S0448">well that's alright then it won't be an ugly one</u>
<u n="671" who="S0447">that doesn't look ugly</u>
<u n="672" who="S0448">oh yeah some of the ones I left on there when I drunk took you phone a took a load of selfies on it and then forgot until the morning when you were going through them some of those are hideous</u>
<u n="673" who="S0447">mm I deleted some of the blurred ones of me as well</u>
<u n="674" who="S0448">oh you never uploaded the nice ones though you pain</u>
<u n="675" who="S0447">ah well I'll I'll do it</u>
<u n="676" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="677" who="S0447">I'll do it tomorrow</u>
<u n="678" who="S0448">that sounded so convincing I really believed you then</u>
<u n="679" who="S0447">I will do it tomorrow</u>
<u n="680" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="681" who="S0447">erm yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0447">I need to pay for our erm presentation night at the golf club</u>
<u n="684" who="S0448">how much is it?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0447"><unclear/> twenty pound</u>
<u n="686" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="687" who="S0447">why?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0448">well cos obviously I owe you my half don't I?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0447">no don't worry about it you're my guest</u>
<u n="690" who="S0448">oh thanks</u>
<u n="691" who="S0447">that's alright</u>
<u n="692" who="S0448">ye am I right in thinking that's the twenty-second yeah?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0448">sweet I didn't wanna show up like on the wrong weekend like hi</u>
<u n="695" who="S0447"><unclear/> being fine usually you'd just have to come down again <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0448">erm do you wanna come up on the fourteenth? or like obviously a bit before then but cos erm you know you've got a choice of two weekends</u>
<u n="697" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0448">I thought if you came up on that one erm the <anon type="place"/> Christmas market's open then so we could go there cos I've never been there before and <trunc>some</trunc>someone who goes to <anon type="place"/> quite a lot was telling me that it's actually really nice so we should do that yay Christmas</u>
<u n="699" who="S0447">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="700" who="S0448">yay</u>
<u n="701" who="S0447">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="702" who="S0448">yay</u>
<u n="703" who="S0447">are we driving? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="704" who="S0448">huh?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0447">are we driving?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0448">how else are we gonna get there? why?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0447">are we gonna go through <anon type="place"/> again?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no we'll just we'll check the traffic before we go</u>
<u n="709" who="S0447">yeah maybe leave earlier</u>
<u n="710" who="S0448">yeah we well when you come up we don't have to go out erm that much then cos yeah yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0447">cos yeah yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0448">I was just thinking in my head like I was trying I was getting confused I was gonna say we don't have to go out that much that weekend when you're up and then I got confused and thought I was talking about Halloween all of a sudden I was like oh no we'll definitely be going out I remembered I was actually talking about the fourteenth of November which is a completely different time and I was like oh yeah we don't have to go out cos that's why we didn't make out till ages last time cos we were both like sleeping off last the night before</u>
<u n="713" who="S0447">yeah but that time I'll have only travelled up on the Friday night</u>
<u n="714" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0447">and then yeah so I guess we might be going out the Friday night</u>
<u n="716" who="S0448">no and then we can just go to the thing on the Saturday and then potentially go out Saturday night if you wanted to</u>
<u n="717" who="S0447">yeah and then <unclear/> go home Sunday night</u>
<u n="718" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0447">yes?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0448">yah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0447">then the week after you're coming down to me</u>
<u n="722" who="S0448">yep my mum was like laughing being like I bet your car won't make it and I was like thanks for that it bloody needs to</u>
<u n="723" who="S0447">you'll make it <unclear>up</unclear></u>
<u n="724" who="S0448">it needs to I don't have another choice <pause dur="short"/> I need to move it really I haven't moved it since you came up but I don't want to cos I've got the spot right outside my house and when I get that one it's like it's really hard to make myself move especially cos I don't actually need to go anywhere</u>
<u n="725" who="S0447">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0448">but obviously if I leave it too long it'll stop working</u>
<u n="727" who="S0447">maybe you should like drive it round the block</u>
<u n="728" who="S0448">yeah well it's out it's nearly out of petrol like it's on like one-and-a-half bars so I was thinking I could just take it to the petrol station and back again cos that's something to do but it's just the fact that essentially when I move I know I'm going to lose my spot so I keep putting it off and being like I'll go another day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0447">yeah maybe do it like tomorrow during the daytime or something when no one's gonna nick it</u>
<u n="730" who="S0448">yeah maybe if how maybe not tomorrow cos I wasn't really planning on putting clothes on maybe <trunc>Thurs</trunc></u>
<u n="731" who="S0447" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0448">huh?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0447">anytime I'm just saying you could do it during the day</u>
<u n="734" who="S0448">well I might do it Thursday because I'll actually have clothes on Thursday cos I have to go out campus for an hour</u>
<u n="735" who="S0447">yeah do you know do you wanna know a crazy fact?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0448">yeah always</u>
<u n="737" who="S0447">I haven't put fuel in my car since I left you</u>
<u n="738" who="S0448">oh my this just this is just what? insane</u>
<u n="739" who="S0447">I've still got I've still got a quarter of a tank left</u>
<u n="740" who="S0448">I'm so jel</u>
<u n="741" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="743" who="S0447">so good <pause dur="short"/> although I've got to drive to <anon type="place"/> next Tuesday</u>
<u n="744" who="S0448">for your examalam</u>
<u n="745" who="S0447">yeah and them I'm driving to you on the Wednesday</u>
<u n="746" who="S0448">I reckon you'll have to fill up then</u>
<u n="747" who="S0447">yeah I'll I'll probably need to fill it up either tomorrow or Wednesday and then I'll fill up again Wednesday before I come to you</u>
<u n="748" who="S0448">I see</u>
<u n="749" who="S0447">yes</u>
<u n="750" who="S0448">I'm so excited</u>
<u n="751" who="S0447">yeah I reckon it'll take me three-and-a-half hours to get to you</u>
<u n="752" who="S0448">yeah what do you wanna eat?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0447">what do I want to eat?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0447">I dunno anything</u>
<u n="756" who="S0448">oh I hate it when you say anything</u>
<u n="757" who="S0447">pizza</u>
<u n="758" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="759" who="S0447">I won't want anything that's gonna take too much effort cos I'll have just been in I'll have been at work for like ten hours and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0448" trans="overlap">well it doesn't matter how much effort it is cos I'm gonna cook for it cook for you but I don't want to to take too long cos it's gonna be really late and I don't know how you deal with it but if I haven't eaten in hours I I well you've seen me hungry before you know I get all stressy and stuff</u>
<u n="761" who="S0447">yeah yeah pizza'll be fine</u>
<u n="762" who="S0448">okay is there anything else you want me to order?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0447">erm <pause dur="short"/> some soup</u>
<u n="764" who="S0448">oh god okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0447">just order me anything</u>
<u n="766" who="S0448">oh you're so annoying</u>
<u n="767" who="S0447">spicy tomato</u>
<u n="768" who="S0448">yeah I thought so you were obsessing over that probs get you a chicken noodle</u>
<u n="769" who="S0447">yeah just those two'll be fine</u>
<u n="770" who="S0448">ah I'll probably buy myself some cream of tomato and then you'll eat the cream of tomato and then I won't actually get to have any cream of tomato do you remember that?</u>
<u n="771" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0447">it was er it was soup I <unclear/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0447">leave the <unclear>blast</unclear> in the past</u>
<u n="776" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay I'll let you off</u>
<u n="777" who="S0447" trans="overlap">I just wanted a soup</u>
<u n="778" who="S0448">I'll let you off cos you're pretty</u>
<u n="779" who="S0447">ah thanks</u>
<u n="780" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0447">however you rolled me away in bed</u>
<u n="782" who="S0448"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0447">I could I could not let off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0448">what is it gonna take to make you forget that?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0447"><unclear/> like the a lot of vodka</u>
<u n="786" who="S0448">ah okay I can deal with that</u>
<u n="787" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="788" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> honestly</u>
<u n="789" who="S0447">well</u>
<u n="790" who="S0448">it was one time</u>
<u n="791" who="S0447">ah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0447">fine I forgive you</u>
<u n="794" who="S0448">thanks</u>
<u n="795" who="S0447">because you're pretty</u>
<u n="796" who="S0448">yay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="798" who="S0448">oh</u>
<u n="799" who="S0447">yeah it was well <unclear/> phone <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> earlier at work</u>
<u n="800" who="S0448">what happened exactly?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0447">well the phone went so and I answered it and then the the person asked for me</u>
<u n="802" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0447">and said it was a personal call</u>
<u n="804" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0447">so and I <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said erm okay where are you calling from?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0447">so then erm she said where the company was and then she was like oh we don't take personal calls at work and then got into like some mini argument with him about the fact that she wasn't gonna put him through to me</u>
<u n="808" who="S0448">oh really? wow</u>
<u n="809" who="S0447">yeah yeah pretty much she was <trunc>pu</trunc> someone was trying to hire me</u>
<u n="810" who="S0448">would you have wanted to talk to them?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0447">I don't know really</u>
<u n="812" who="S0448">bit cheeky</u>
<u n="813" who="S0447">I know calling me at work and then at least call me at home</u>
<u n="814" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> maybe they it was the only time that they could or something I dunno</u>
<u n="815" who="S0447">yeah or yeah could call me on my mobile or</u>
<u n="816" who="S0448">well</u>
<u n="817" who="S0447">I don't know</u>
<u n="818" who="S0448">at least it's like it's good cos they're gonna be unsettled and be like oh oh they wanted him</u>
<u n="819" who="S0447">yeah it happened a lot last year as well so yeah yeah it's good I guess</u>
<u n="820" who="S0448">it is good I don't know why you keep on going like mm me me me like it's really good</u>
<u n="821" who="S0447">yeah it's good if it means I get paid more</u>
<u n="822" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0447">if I don't get paid more then it's just like bler</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="824" who="S0448">mm</u>
<u n="825" who="S0447">what?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0448">what?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0447">you went mm</u>
<u n="828" who="S0448">yeah cos that's like what you do</u>
<u n="829" who="S0447">I don't</u>
<u n="830" who="S0448">you do</u>
<u n="831" who="S0447">no</u>
<u n="832" who="S0448">you do mm</u>
<u n="833" who="S0447">well</u>
<u n="834" who="S0448">I'm surprised I've only heard you sleep talk that one time</u>
<u n="835" who="S0447">you heard me sleep talk?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0448">yeah remember ages ago like about the second time I'd stayed at your house</u>
<u n="837" who="S0447">I can't remember</u>
<u n="838" who="S0448">we even talked about it cos you you mm</u>
<u n="839" who="S0447">what did I say? oh was it where I thought I was talking to you? I thought I was talking to someone and then</u>
<u n="840" who="S0448">no that was another time that was up here at uni</u>
<u n="841" who="S0447">oh okay</u>
<u n="842" who="S0448">this one</u>
<u n="843" who="S0447" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0448">this one was like you were making weird noises in your sleep you were like mm mm mm mm mm mm mm mm and it was like full sentences but none of them were words it was all like mumbling like that and then in the morning I was like what the hell was that? and then you were like yeah I know and you tried to show me recordings on your sleep talk app but you didn't actually <trunc>s</trunc>seem to have any how can you not remember this?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0447">oh I don't know that was a long time ago</u>
<u n="846" who="S0448">oh yeah like a whole month ago so long ago</u>
<u n="847" who="S0447"><unclear>am I</unclear> ADHD I wonder?</u>
<u n="848" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and you told me that you used to sleepwalk but you're over it now</u>
<u n="849" who="S0447">yeah I haven't done that in years I don't think</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="850" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0447">mm erm yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0448" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0447">I can't remember</u>
<u n="854" who="S0448">oh typical</u>
<u n="855" who="S0447">I dunno I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0448">mm</u>
<u n="857" who="S0447">oh stretch</u>
<u n="858" who="S0448">mm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0447"><unclear/> I put some joggers on cos my room is really cold and now I'm like boiling hot so I'm gonna have to take them off before I go to bed</u>
<u n="860" who="S0448">yeah we should go to bed</u>
<u n="861" who="S0447">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0448">hm?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0447">what time is it?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0448">five five past midnight</u>
<u n="865" who="S0447">mm yeah I'm <unclear/> I might do in a minute</u>
<u n="866" who="S0448">yeah I don't want you to be tired again tomorrow</u>
<u n="867" who="S0447">no</u>
<u n="868" who="S0448">no</u>
<u n="869" who="S0447">I'll remember that <unclear/> today though that was a <unclear/> so I <unclear/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0448">huh? you went really crackly then something about five types of coffee</u>
<u n="871" who="S0447">yeah that's <unclear/> I was alright until I had about five cups of coffee</u>
<u n="872" who="S0448">no again I just got five cups of coffee</u>
<u n="873" who="S0447"><vocal desc="laugh"/> don't worry</u>
<u n="874" who="S0448">ah what? say it like really loud and slow and clear</u>
<u n="875" who="S0447">I was okay today <unclear/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0448" trans="overlap">you were okay today you had five cups of coffee</u>
<u n="877" who="S0447">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> there we go</u>
<u n="878" who="S0448" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0447">alright I think I'm gonna go</u>
<u n="880" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="881" who="S0447">I've got to get up early</u>
<u n="882" who="S0448">I know</u>
<u n="883" who="S0447"><unclear/> but well I'll text you before I go to sleep</u>
<u n="884" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="885" who="S0447">okay night night</u>
<u n="886" who="S0448">bye</u>
<u n="887" who="S0447">bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
