<text id="SAMQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:11:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-09</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0208</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home, Leeds</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Weight, Diet</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing </conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0208">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0202">and all this <trunc>st</trunc> and that so she's told told me all these things about her and stuff like that and it's like oh okay and then <pause dur="short"/> she told me about like her mum and that and basically when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> split up with her ex-girlfriend she'd lost a lot of weight from stress and I mean she was you could see her bones she was she looked ill <pause dur="short"/> erm but her mum thought she looks good like that <pause dur="short"/> and every time like she sees <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's like oh you've put a bit of weight on haven't you? oh like it's just stuff like that</u>
<u n="2" who="S0208">that is awful</u>
<u n="3" who="S0202">and says and she'll say to her stuff like you sure you want to eat that? and like stuff like that</u>
<u n="4" who="S0208">that is atrocious <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean I think that she looks great anyway I think she's got a great body but I think I'll make more of conscious effort to tell her</u>
<u n="5" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0208">cos I've complimented her before and like I genuinely do think she looks nice <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I'm just going to put a film on to load</u>
<u n="7" who="S0202">yeah okay</u>
<u n="8" who="S0208">erm how does Ten Rules for Sleeping Around sound?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0202">yeah whatever yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0208">I'll read it out to you so there's an engaged couple gets some advice on staying together from non-married friends it's okay to sleep around as long as you follow the rules</u>
<u n="11" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0208"><event desc="unintelligible"/> to be funny</u>
<u n="13" who="S0202">yeah okay</u>
<u n="14" who="S0208">yeah?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0202">sounds like a disaster waiting to happen <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll put it on to load but that's really bad for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean bless her</u>
<u n="17" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0208">it's true <pause dur="short"/> what else have you found out?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0202">erm <pause dur="short"/> just about that really like cos <trunc>h</trunc> obviously I have <unclear/> now so she sees it</u>
<u n="20" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0202" trans="overlap">sees it more <pause dur="short"/> and like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0208">does she not like eat properly?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0202">from what <pause dur="long"/> from what I know <pause dur="short"/> from being with her and being friends with her she doesn't eat a lot <pause dur="short"/> but she hasn't <trunc>st</trunc> she hasn't stopped eating I wouldn't not say she was a full anorexic like <event desc="sound of computer"/> but she is she's got an eating disorder she <trunc>m</trunc> she's got some <trunc>se</trunc> sort of eating disorder cos of everything that all the shit that her mum says to her and all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="24" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0202">but like when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told me I was like fucking hell I had no idea</u>
<u n="26" who="S0208">that's so awful to come from your mum as well</u>
<u n="27" who="S0202">mm <pause dur="short"/> like her mum's not skinny either like her mum's a middle aged woman she's carrying a bit of weight around her stomach but she doesn't she's not fat but she's not skinny</u>
<u n="28" who="S0208" trans="overlap">why would you say that to your child though? especially like no matter how old you are</u>
<u n="29" who="S0202">do you wanna grab</u>
<u n="30" who="S0208">it's very you're very impressionable aren't you?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0208">and girls especially are a little bit more what do you want me to grab? the</u>
<u n="33" who="S0202" trans="overlap">er yeah that</u>
<u n="34" who="S0208">erm impressionable especially from your mum like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0202">but like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> never opens her mouth and talks about it like she'll never say</u>
<u n="36" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I bet she doesn't</u>
<u n="37" who="S0202">but like the thing is like I just</u>
<u n="38" who="S0208" trans="overlap">thanks</u>
<u n="39" who="S0202">don't understand her like <pause dur="short"/> she has these emotional blocks up and she makes it so difficult to get close to her and like</u>
<u n="40" who="S0208">thing is she probably doesn't wanna talk about it because she's ashamed at the fact that she lets it get to her but also at the fact that it's her mum <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0202">yeah her life would be easier if she just spoke to people but she doesn't</u>
<u n="42" who="S0208">well maybe we need to approach her more <pause dur="long"/> cos maybe she's too shy or ashamed or whatever to come forwards but <pause dur="short"/> maybe if someone brought it up with her</u>
<u n="43" who="S0202">yeah I'm not bringing that up</u>
<u n="44" who="S0208" trans="overlap">or just said</u>
<u n="45" who="S0202">I don't want <trunc>t</trunc> I don't want to bring that up with her cos like I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was supposed to say anything</u>
<u n="46" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no no but <pause dur="short"/> what I mean is that someone could just mention it would be like <pause dur="short"/> oh you look a bit upset is everything alright? or like if she's eating and we're eating at the same sort of like oh you haven't eaten much is something on your mind?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0208">it's like are you upset about something?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so maybe if you coax it out of her she might be <pause dur="short"/> more inclined to trust people and tell them</u>
<u n="51" who="S0202">mm <pause dur="short"/> but she's so slim like under her she wears baggy clothes a lot so you can't really tell <pause dur="short"/> but like <pause dur="short"/> she's so slim like so skinny you can see her hip bones and everything</u>
<u n="52" who="S0208">she's gotten worse then <pause dur="short"/> cos she wasn't that bad last time I saw her</u>
<u n="53" who="S0202">no <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0208">bless her though that is awful</u>
<u n="55" who="S0202">mm <pause dur="short"/> she does not have a very good relationship with her parents though I don't think like she makes out on the surface everything's all perfect and rosy and she has this perfect life but like her dad's got another girlfriend in Spain</u>
<u n="56" who="S0208">I was gonna say she doesn't see him very often does she?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0202">no cos he works away all the time and then obviously her mum's like that with her <pause dur="short"/> really judgemental and stuff</u>
<u n="58" who="S0208">that's so sad <pause dur="short"/> that's really sad <pause dur="long"/> I can't imagine not being close to my parents <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0202">it would be weird wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0202">I mean I'm not particularly close to my parents but I've got a good relationship with them</u>
<u n="62" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0202">do you know what I mean? like me and my dad don't see each other very often but that's how we both prefer it like</u>
<u n="64" who="S0208">but you still get on when you see each other</u>
<u n="65" who="S0202">yeah as long it's not that we prefer not to see each other it's just that <pause dur="short"/> like he lives far away I'm at uni and we've got other stuff going on like</u>
<u n="66" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the same with my parents I don't see them very often but when we do I know <pause dur="short"/> you know we we get on we have a laugh</u>
<u n="67" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0208">and just knowing that they're there for you for support as well <pause dur="short"/> my mum would never dare say something like that to me</u>
<u n="69" who="S0202">well your mum has her own problems with her weight doesn't she?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0208">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah she does</u>
<u n="71" who="S0202">so I always make a conscious to say to her when I see her like have you lost weight? like I <trunc>obvious</trunc> I genuinely believe that she looks like she's lost weight I don't just say it but I always make a point of like saying to her oh you look really nice today</u>
<u n="72" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0202">like</u>
<u n="74" who="S0208">when I saw her for the first time down at the hospital I could see it but I think that was also due to stress</u>
<u n="75" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0208">she looked I'm not gonna lie and it's not to be nasty but she looked awful when I saw her but that's obviously just the stressful period I could tell she hadn't been sleeping she hadn't been eating properly like she just looked a bit drained</u>
<u n="77" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0208">she looks much better now</u>
<u n="79" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0208">cos I'm not saying this nasty but my mum does genuinely look <trunc>b</trunc>better when she's a bit more</u>
<u n="81" who="S0202">filled out</u>
<u n="82" who="S0208">plump yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0208">it's it's her body type it's how she looks healthy</u>
<u n="85" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0208">just brings life into her <pause dur="short"/> I don't <trunc>h</trunc> know what she's so worried about though because she's not fat she's never been fat</u>
<u n="87" who="S0202">no she's not fat</u>
<u n="88" who="S0208">I remember once when we started doing Wii Fit together at first it was fun <pause dur="short"/> we were both doing it like just to get in shape like we weren't doing it to lose weight <pause dur="short"/> and when they did the testing so it tells you our BMI it said that she was like practically clinically over like obese and I'm just like that's so wrong that's not even slightly accurate because</u>
<u n="89" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0208">you look at her and <pause dur="short"/> she's not fat at all</u>
<u n="91" who="S0202">she's got to be the size she is to carry her breasts</u>
<u n="92" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0202">fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> like most of her weight is her boobs</u>
<u n="94" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="short"/> probably weigh about ten kilos each <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0202">but like she your mum I know it bothers her like cos I've heard you tell me before and I've heard some some of the stuff she says and stuff like that and I'm just like it's and when I know people are like that I always make a conscious effort to tell them like you look really nice today like</u>
<u n="96" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0202">or when I first see them have you have you lost weight? like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has lost so much weight since last time I saw her when I got back from America</u>
<u n="98" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0202">it were the first thing I noticed <pause dur="short"/> but like she's the <trunc>sa</trunc> she's the same she's short so she <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't carry weight as well as someone who would be tall but she probably weighs and is the same size as I am</u>
<u n="100" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0202">but just cos she's short she's more conscious of it</u>
<u n="102" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it looks different</u>
<u n="103" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0208">cos I feel I've gotten much better with mine I mean I haven't had any problems any incidents since I've been here <pause dur="short"/> I think it's as well being out of that stressful environment and I've been at home comfortable I've been absolutely fine</u>
<u n="105" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0208">I haven't had a single problem</u>
<u n="107" who="S0202">good I'm glad that you've told me that</u>
<u n="108" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows kind of but that's only because like the first few weeks when I got back it was really bad like it was really bad and I'd noticed it as well like I'd you could see my ribs and my hips and stuff</u>
<u n="109" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and I was wearing my shorts and I was just getting changed and pulled my top up and <trunc>sh</trunc> I heard her gasp she didn't say anything I just heard her gasp and I put my clothes back on it was only later on when we were a little bit drunk we were out here having a cigarette and she asked me she was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what's happened?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0208">so I had to tell her but I think since then like since I realised and then I actually saw myself I was like oh</u>
<u n="113" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0208">no no it's just not attractive</u>
<u n="115" who="S0202">I'm not really wanting to bring it up with you cos obviously when you told me you were drunk so <pause dur="short"/> and you told me not to say anything</u>
<u n="116" who="S0208">that's the only time I tell I tell anyone</u>
<u n="117" who="S0202">I know but that's why didn't wanna bring it up cos</u>
<u n="118" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0202">I didn't want you to feel embarrassed or</u>
<u n="120" who="S0208">I didn't tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he guessed</u>
<u n="121" who="S0202">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knows your body <trunc>ju</trunc> probably just as well as you do</u>
<u n="122" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he's been really great through all of it he's always helped me so that's like any time I've been drunk and I've been sick it's not for that it's because I've literally been so ill</u>
<u n="123" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0208">and he always has come into the bathroom or shouted at me and be like what the fuck are you doing or something and I'm like it's cos I'm ill like calm down</u>
<u n="125" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0208">but he's been really really good about it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0202">it's not healthy</u>
<u n="128" who="S0208">it's not</u>
<u n="129" who="S0202">and you've got nothing to worry about there's nothing wrong with your body <pause dur="long"/> but <trunc>a</trunc>as many people as you want can say that to you but it doesn't change what you think</u>
<u n="130" who="S0208">exactly</u>
<u n="131" who="S0202">I know that myself</u>
<u n="132" who="S0208">but it doesn't seem to be a problem now I'm hoping that will stay</u>
<u n="133" who="S0202">it'll just be the stressful environment you were in</u>
<u n="134" who="S0208">yeah I think</u>
<u n="135" who="S0202">at uni</u>
<u n="136" who="S0208">I think it was that more than anything and</u>
<u n="137" who="S0202">it'll be a million stuff and</u>
<u n="138" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0202">I'm worried about my mum and her eating habits cos she didn't eat a lot anyway and now she's this has happened with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like</u>
<u n="140" who="S0208">it can either go two ways isn't it people will either stress eat or stress starve</u>
<u n="141" who="S0202">mm <pause dur="long"/> but I hope it doesn't I hope she's not gonna make herself ill</u>
<u n="142" who="S0208">well</u>
<u n="143" who="S0202" trans="overlap">she doesn't eat a lot anyway she</u>
<u n="144" who="S0208" trans="overlap">that's just where you have to come in I guess</u>
<u n="145" who="S0202">like you have one she has one meal a day and she don't even finish her meal like</u>
<u n="146" who="S0208">and without making it into a problem or sounding nasty or anything I think you just have to keep an eye on her</u>
<u n="147" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0208">and make sure that it doesn't become a problem</u>
<u n="149" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0208"><vocal desc="misc"/> sorry</u>
<u n="151" who="S0202">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> that rooster is so weird look at it running around chasing them all</u>
<u n="152" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> come here ladies</u>
<u n="153" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0202">it's such a weird colour it's like brown and then black and white and it ends</u>
<u n="156" who="S0208">oh I'm sweating so much out here</u>
<u n="157" who="S0202">I know it's so hot</u>
<u n="158" who="S0208" trans="overlap">have to go in</u>
<u n="159" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0208">oh</u>
<u n="161" who="S0202">fucking started that one off now</u>
<u n="162" who="S0208">I know <pause dur="short"/> be now for a couple of hours</u>
<u n="163" who="S0202">I hate chickens</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
