<text id="SAT9">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:15</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-31</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Arrangements for the day, exercise, internet, family relationships</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, requesting, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0179">flirted with the er girl with her arm in a sling</u>
<u n="2" who="S0058">oh her</u>
<u n="3" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0058">is she still still arm in sling?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="7" who="S0179">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> she came over to talk to me actually</u>
<u n="8" who="S0058">oh nice <pause dur="short"/> you either look lost and pathetic or she was going to chat you up</u>
<u n="9" who="S0179">I think she was chatting me up</u>
<u n="10" who="S0058">do you reckon?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0058">maybe a bit of both <pause dur="short"/> some girls like that</u>
<u n="13" who="S0179">I was just <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't wasn't <unclear/> I was just looking at something <unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no I know but I was just think of er why she'd come over <pause dur="short"/> some instructors come over cos you look lost and like you need a bit of guidance <pause dur="short"/> sometimes they come over cos it's their job <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0179">well I like to think it was because I looked</u>
<u n="16" who="S0058">I'm sure it was</u>
<u n="17" who="S0179">I just look incredibly fit <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> kings</u>
<u n="19" who="S0179">such an unusual view</u>
<u n="20" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0179">erm right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> okay this afternoon slash evening</u>
<u n="24" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="25" who="S0179">erm do you want to do see if anyone wants to do with anything?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0058">in some ways I wouldn't mind just sort of being in <pause dur="short"/> just us cos we haven't sort of really done that <pause dur="short"/> but I don't mind if you'd like to ask someone</u>
<u n="27" who="S0179">well we haven't seen anyone for <pause dur="short"/> oh Aston Martin</u>
<u n="28" who="S0058" trans="overlap">true <pause dur="short"/> oh nice</u>
<u n="29" who="S0179">relatively kinky <pause dur="short"/> compared to the massive Range Rovers</u>
<u n="30" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0179">there are dotted about <pause dur="short"/> okay you're going there</u>
<u n="32" who="S0058">I can text <unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0179" trans="overlap">there are a lot of XC90s in here</u>
<u n="34" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0179">they've <trunc>re</trunc> slightly released it for two thousand and twelve cos  of a  of a releasing a replacement in about eighteen months</u>
<u n="36" who="S0058">which one sorry the?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0179">xC90</u>
<u n="38" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="39" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0058">wow <pause dur="short"/> so it's going to be very old by the time they actually</u>
<u n="41" who="S0179">it is very old <pause dur="short"/> well it was released in two thousand and three</u>
<u n="42" who="S0058">mhm <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="43" who="S0179">these wheels are severely out of alignment <pause dur="short"/> erm but yes it is <pause dur="short"/> oh that's not going to work</u>
<u n="44" who="S0058">even in your Polo <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> that <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> you've got me quoting Friends now <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> the episodes though <pause dur="short"/> you'll never see Joey in the same light again <pause dur="short"/> I don't know erm we could ask someone round <pause dur="short"/> we could ask see if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <unclear/> want to come round for a drink and something later on</u>
<u n="45" who="S0179">no I was thinking more sort of friends rather than</u>
<u n="46" who="S0058">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> erm well we could ask <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or both</u>
<u n="47" who="S0179">or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> even</u>
<u n="48" who="S0058">or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0179">or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or</u>
<u n="50" who="S0058">true <pause dur="short"/> I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be here <pause dur="short"/> as in he's he's still a Masters student so I don't know</u>
<u n="51" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah but it's a most it is an MPhil which is a kind of Masters</u>
<u n="52" who="S0058">true <pause dur="short"/> I think that because it is taught though</u>
<u n="53" who="S0179">it's not taught is it?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0058">A lot of the MPhils are taught for art <pause dur="long"/> So the you know the ones I was looking at were taught erm <pause dur="long"/> Da da da</u>
<u n="57" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0058">this is the constant angle <pause dur="long"/> I'm not sure that was a recognised pedestrian route there</u>
<u n="59" who="S0179" trans="overlap">can I have my er?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0058">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> is it in here?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="long"/> Nicely timed</u>
<u n="62" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay erm what do you think then? I can give people a text if you want to <pause dur="short"/> erm or we could do that tomorrow night <pause dur="short"/> tonight's easier in the sense people can get buses more easily <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0179">I don't know</u>
<u n="64" who="S0058">what would you like to do?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0179">well not to er be a pain <pause dur="short"/> I would possibly like it if you could get me on <unclear/> tonight</u>
<u n="66" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was going to anyway that's fine</u>
<u n="67" who="S0179">erm <pause dur="short"/> providing we can sort it out time wise I need to talk to Louis at some point this weekend</u>
<u n="68" who="S0058">mhm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0179">but I dunno</u>
<u n="70" who="S0058">yeah well I I was thinking to plan for the next little while erm if we go back erm <trunc>ma</trunc> I mean shall I go straight down to Morrisons and sort of get that done? Or I could <pause dur="short"/> I think I</u>
<u n="71" who="S0179" trans="overlap">erm entirely up to you</u>
<u n="72" who="S0058">yeah I could  I could  get the ironing out of the way I suppose erm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0179">I would really just like to sit down and have some ice</u>
<u n="74" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no definitely I <trunc>wa</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I was going to suggest that you completely sit down with some ice <pause dur="short"/> get it up resting <pause dur="short"/> I'll</u>
<u n="75" who="S0179">no I don't think <unclear/> It's been good to come out for a little bit but I think that I need to sort of</u>
<u n="76" who="S0058" trans="overlap">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow will include less walking</u>
<u n="77" who="S0179">well it was more sort of a wandering around the shops it wasn't hugely healthy</u>
<u n="78" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no tomorrow we'll think of something to do which doesn't involve that</u>
<u n="79" who="S0179"><unclear/> So going round  will probably be a mistake</u>
<u n="80" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> we can get you a like a little er segway to go round on <pause dur="short"/> that would be cool</u>
<u n="81" who="S0179">erm we could hit the gym and do some weights</u>
<u n="82" who="S0058">tonight?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0179">I'm tempted to leave that for tonight cos it is still sort of active and walking round</u>
<u n="84" who="S0058">erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I was going to say I mean <pause dur="short"/> I think if it's a bit sore now maybe the best thing is just to completely rest it for tonight and then tomorrow yeah maybe do some weights which would involve a bit of walking but not</u>
<u n="85" who="S0179">not too much yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0058">not too much <pause dur="short"/> nothing that should be a problem erm but doing it tonight might just be a bit too much <pause dur="short"/> do you think?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it that's the er that's the Iranian restaurant</u>
<u n="88" who="S0058" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yes I've pointed it out to er to Heather <pause dur="short"/> it was good that <pause dur="short"/> I enjoyed that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it did highlight sort of right so this is what you get when you live in a desert <pause dur="short"/> just really a bit uninteresting food</u>
<u n="90" who="S0058">it wasn't uninteresting it just wasn't</u>
<u n="91" who="S0179">I know it was sort of <pause dur="short"/> yeah but you had to <pause dur="short"/> as I have just decided to put it you had to look to find the enjoyment in it</u>
<u n="92" who="S0058" trans="overlap">hmm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0179">it was very subtle</u>
<u n="94" who="S0058">it was <trunc>v</trunc> yeah possibly yeah it was harder work than a curry</u>
<u n="95" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="96" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0179">but you just sort of hit sit back and it hits you</u>
<u n="98" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> whereas that one yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I kind of know what you mean I think <pause dur="short"/> erm it was more about sort of subtle sour and herbs and balances of things</u>
<u n="99" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0058">Cos it was chicken and rice basically <pause dur="short"/> or lamb and rice</u>
<u n="101" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I I have also concluded come to the conclusion that I'm against having sort of the two cooked dishes I had in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I basically I had too much variety</u>
<u n="102" who="S0058">ah right you had a sort of a selection er selection yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah it was sort of eh overwhelmingly rich</u>
<u n="104" who="S0058">right okay <pause dur="short"/> well next time we'll go and have our thing</u>
<u n="105" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's kind of what I wanted to have</u>
<u n="106" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> I just felt like it wouldn't really work one person have a starter and a main course and and you couldn't you can't get it for three cos it's just a fixed size</u>
<u n="107" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0058">Cos you know it's not like it's this price for two it's just this price for all of it and <trunc>y</trunc> however many people you want can eat it sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> erm and it gives us a reason to go back again</u>
<u n="109" who="S0179">this is true</u>
<u n="110" who="S0058">with our voucher <pause dur="short"/> our ten pounds off</u>
<u n="111" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="112" who="S0058">ah that is only on Sunday and Thursday though unfortunately but I might be able to wangle another twenty-five pounds off <pause dur="short"/> if you're on <unclear/> student <unclear/> you should be able to get another twenty-five percent off on which will be nice</u>
<u n="113" who="S0179">indeed</u>
<u n="114" who="S0058">but erm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0179">oh er</u>
<u n="116" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0179">what the fuck are you doing out by yourself?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0058">possibly out with this person <pause dur="short"/> yeah posts <pause dur="short"/> sorry erm cones <pause dur="short"/> he's been out playing something with them <pause dur="short"/> maybe they've had an argument and the boy's stormed off</u>
<u n="119" who="S0179">yeah possibly</u>
<u n="120" who="S0058">that goal was in <pause dur="short"/> it was not in</u>
<u n="121" who="S0179">you're getting drawn into an <trunc>ar</trunc> into a vicious argument which your five year old son <unclear/> which you really need to sort of be a good person</u>
<u n="122" who="S0058" trans="overlap">put your foot <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> in all fairness kids storm off sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I ever did but kids do generally</u>
<u n="123" who="S0179">ow <pause dur="short"/> ow</u>
<u n="124" who="S0058">okay?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0179">oh can you work the clutch for me?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0058">I'm not sure I can chuck <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to get a bit stick</u>
<u n="127" who="S0179">yeah just lean over</u>
<u n="128" who="S0058">and poke it occasionally</u>
<u n="129" who="S0179">the clutch or my leg?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0058">the clutch I was thinking but your leg if that would help <pause dur="short"/> yeah so we'll get back <pause dur="short"/> you don't move for the rest of the night yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll bring you things and then erm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0179">at the moment I'm finding the idea of an automatic unbelievably attractive</u>
<u n="132" who="S0058">oh there's that couple from Cambourne who get <pause dur="short"/> the woman gets on the bus and they're always in the gym in classes and stuff</u>
<u n="133" who="S0179">where?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0058">erm on the <trunc>r</trunc> the <trunc>le</trunc> the right sorry <pause dur="short"/> there's a woman in the black coat and the guy in the brown <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> you do see it's weird cos I I mean I've quite regularly sort of seen people from work around <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> I've see three people from CUP today</u>
<u n="137" who="S0179">my god <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> one week and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this week</u>
<u n="138" who="S0058" trans="overlap">all from customer services <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this week</u>
<u n="142" who="S0058">did you see  Did you see  <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0179">the other week</u>
<u n="144" who="S0058">oh the other week right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0179">that would be a good place to live</u>
<u n="146" who="S0058">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice and handy for pretty much everything</u>
<u n="147" who="S0179">yeah I would be very happy if I lived there <pause dur="short"/> that's nice</u>
<u n="148" who="S0058">yeah it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> planting all these trees <pause dur="short"/> are they new?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0179">yeah look like it</u>
<u n="150" who="S0058">okay so yeah so I'll do the shopping and the ironing in which ever order <pause dur="short"/> I'll work out which I'd rather do <pause dur="short"/> then erm yeah then basically whatever you fancy <pause dur="short"/> I mean I will need to know before oh yeah if I do the ironing first actually cos I will need to know what we're doing other people wise</u>
<u n="151" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's not cool</u>
<u n="152" who="S0058">oh no it's not</u>
<u n="153" who="S0179">park somewhere else</u>
<u n="154" who="S0058">I'm just going to block the road <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="155" who="S0179">or at least if you're going to <pause dur="short"/> get on</u>
<u n="156" who="S0058">yeah exactly no he was er <pause dur="short"/> and presumably there was he his wife was standing behind so she'd obviously stopped and got out</u>
<u n="157" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well but she obviously had had to get out</u>
<u n="158" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> take your time over the process <pause dur="short"/> mm so what do you reckon with regard to other folks?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0179">erm?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0058">I'm happy to do either like I said erm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0179">er in some ways it might be nice to see people erm I'd be more inclined to say sort of ask Billy first</u>
<u n="162" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> I mean yeah I asked him for last week for last Sunday and he couldn't but he did seem sort of oh I'd really like to but so</u>
<u n="163" who="S0179">well I well if you ask him today <pause dur="short"/> if he can't do today he could do tomorrow</u>
<u n="164" who="S0058">yeah okay</u>
<u n="165" who="S0179">presumably</u>
<u n="166" who="S0058">well do you want to do that then?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0179">maybe yeah I think just it might be nice to see him</u>
<u n="168" who="S0058" trans="overlap">maybe? Ah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0179">and possibly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> we'll see <pause dur="short"/> depends what sort of mood he's in</u>
<u n="170" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0179">what's he been doing recently anyway?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? More of the same really I think <pause dur="short"/> as far as I can tell</u>
<u n="173" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0058">I don't think er anything massively surprising <pause dur="short"/> largely watching TV <pause dur="short"/> oh no he said he has been tidying up <pause dur="short"/> very exciting</u>
<u n="175" who="S0179">I'm going to find these next few weeks quite difficult</u>
<u n="176" who="S0058">I know you are chuck <pause dur="short"/> I think the key thing for you is to get loads of exercise <pause dur="short"/> yeah? So as in <trunc>y</trunc> not this week cos of your leg</u>
<u n="177" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="178" who="S0058">yeah I think the key is to make sure that you don't just end up getting bored</u>
<u n="179" who="S0179" trans="overlap">doing nothing <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0058">Cos I think <pause dur="short"/> so you need to do things like swim</u>
<u n="181" who="S0179">I will try swimming <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure that's going to work but <unclear/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh do you think that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? Okay <pause dur="short"/> oh if you give swimming a go and then if not lots of upper body stuff</u>
<u n="183" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I mean have you? Do you want to get in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and just see?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0179">oh I need to do that this weekend anyway when I  when I  get home</u>
<u n="186" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as you say do it when you get in and just see what he says <pause dur="short"/> I mean do you think you might go and just explain that you it <trunc>ha</trunc> it has to be non impact</u>
<u n="187" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0058">Cos he might give you some interesting ideas for things to you know just for some variety</u>
<u n="189" who="S0179">there's not much cardio you can do on upper body <pause dur="short"/> it's just</u>
<u n="190" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0179">I mean there's the hand bike thing</u>
<u n="192" who="S0058">that's true yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it is quite fun and I <trunc>n</trunc> I never use it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0179">well that's cos our gym's got too many good things</u>
<u n="194" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> well it will be a nice opportunity to use that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0058"><unclear/> will be fine <pause dur="short"/> you'll be sitting down</u>
<u n="197" who="S0179">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I mean two weeks isn't too bad but I'm not</u>
<u n="198" who="S0058">the nurse did seem quite sympathetic to that she's sort of erm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0179">doctor? Nurse?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0058">the sorry the doctor in erm well the one who's told you</u>
<u n="201" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she seemed sympathetic to your plight which I thought was nice</u>
<u n="203" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="204" who="S0058">oh and maybe erm go to the cinema next week <pause dur="short"/> I think there was a couple of good things on they wanted to see so one night we'll do that</u>
<u n="205" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> will that be good?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> decent internet will also be good <pause dur="short"/> christ <pause dur="short"/> when are we actually going to get that?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0058">I can er start investigating <pause dur="short"/> writing some stiff letters if you want <pause dur="short"/> try and find out who who to actually get a date from and try and talk to someone</u>
<u n="209" who="S0179">I assume they'd tell us because it would be his chance for him to get more money out of this one wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0058">well yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> I mean it did say March on the website is your thing <pause dur="short"/> which now March is ending so <pause dur="short"/> I assume it's still on the  on the  books and it's just going to happen <pause dur="short"/> it's just delayed because they're not in terribly much of a hurry to connect Caxton but it does seem stupid because they're a lot of people in Cambourne and they'll all sign up because it's dreadful <pause dur="short"/> you know currently so</u>
<u n="211" who="S0179" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well it would improve it even without actually that's an interesting question cos the current exchange is so shit that would the non fibre stuff be any good? Any better than it currently is? And it may not be</u>
<u n="212" who="S0058">non <trunc>fi</trunc> in the sense that?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0179">well cos er</u>
<u n="214" who="S0058">if you didn't change?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0179">so for example my parents before they signed up to fibre they had normal broadband and it was a damn sight better than ours currently is</u>
<u n="216" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> erm I don't actually know whether it would make it any better or not</u>
<u n="217" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0058">I don't really know how it  how it  works</u>
<u n="219" who="S0179">phenomenal fibre speeds are about a hundred times better than what we're currently on as we're on about point four and they're up to forty</u>
<u n="220" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0058">Joy <pause dur="short"/> just imagining forty</u>
<u n="223" who="S0179">four would be an improvement</u>
<u n="224" who="S0058">yeah four would be lovely <pause dur="short"/> can you imagine? Yeah this morning I really fancied just watching a bit of something on the TV you know but it we'll get there <pause dur="short"/> it will happen erm we've signed on the dotted line and stuff so</u>
<u n="225" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0058">well as in it's it's a definite project that's going to go ahead <pause dur="short"/> it's not it has It's just not rumours <pause dur="short"/> erm but it's just when it will happen <pause dur="short"/> I'm you know I don't think</u>
<u n="227" who="S0179" trans="overlap">and where to get the information from <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing</u>
<u n="228" who="S0058">exactly <pause dur="short"/> like I said I mean we went on the website and they had changed it from February so somebody had actually bothered to <pause dur="short"/> something's obviously being done but it's just not March so <pause dur="short"/> erm I mean</u>
<u n="229" who="S0179" trans="overlap">see I have yet to find this website</u>
<u n="230" who="S0058">well we went on it <pause dur="short"/> we were both there and it had the areas</u>
<u n="231" who="S0179">I've well I think I found it once and have been unable to find it since probably</u>
<u n="232" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well what was it? Oh since yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we'll go on again and have another look and if there's a phone number or some kind of contact them I'll contact them on on Monday and just ask what's going on and you know do a bit of shouting <pause dur="short"/> I do a very good complain phone call now <pause dur="short"/> I'm well rehearsed having bought a house from Taylor Wimpy</u>
<u n="233" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0179">ah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0058">it's alright chuck <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0179">no it's not <pause dur="short"/> it hurts</u>
<u n="238" who="S0058">I know but get it go back <pause dur="short"/> put some ice on it <pause dur="short"/> yeah? You'll be back up and going yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not permanent</u>
<u n="239" who="S0179">I know <pause dur="short"/> I want my book</u>
<u n="240" who="S0058">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> well we'll order that today and it will be here on Monday <pause dur="short"/> yeah? Along with your erm new DVD as well <pause dur="short"/> the one you were looking for today</u>
<u n="241" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0058">I love Amazon Prime <pause dur="short"/> my free trial</u>
<u n="243" who="S0179">yes how long does it last for?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0058">thirty days I think it was so I've still got a couple of weeks I think <pause dur="short"/> couple of weeks? Probably <pause dur="short"/> up <trunc>t</trunc> yeah it's still on at the minute <pause dur="short"/> erm I'll go in and confirm that I'm not going to pay anything as well</u>
<u n="245" who="S0179">I thought you already had done</u>
<u n="246" who="S0058">I had but I'll just the check the page again <pause dur="short"/> just <trunc>in</trunc> you know to check there's there's really not a con <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0179">well not that much of a con</u>
<u n="248" who="S0058">not that much of a con yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a pretty clever marketing thing cos I guess a lot of people just really wouldn't be bothered enough to think about doing that and then yeah then you pay for the whole year in one go and then people wouldn't be bothered enough to take it up with Amazon if they didn't want it so they just keep it <pause dur="short"/> and you go ah it's just fifty quid <pause dur="short"/> you know pretty clever <pause dur="short"/> but the benefits really aren't worth it for most people any way</u>
<u n="249" who="S0179">no <pause dur="short"/> I <unclear/> kind of like to do now is to go down to the er sauna and what not</u>
<u n="250" who="S0058">you can if you want to</u>
<u n="251" who="S0179">no it's not worth it</u>
<u n="252" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> we'll keep our eyes open for when they have like cheap days or free days and whatever</u>
<u n="253" who="S0179">well they seem to have gone away from that</u>
<u n="254" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and unfortunately <anon type="place"/> Golf Club won't let us in at all <pause dur="short"/> I really did try and get us a free session but they weren't having it <pause dur="short"/> they weren't buying it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0179">I didn't know that you were selling it</u>
<u n="256" who="S0058">hmm? Nice <pause dur="short"/> I'm always selling it <pause dur="short"/> selling my lies to er to people to try and get free stuff <pause dur="short"/> I love it <pause dur="short"/> however it's my job to  vouchers</u>
<u n="257" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="258" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I think that <trunc>w</trunc> week went quite well considering</u>
<u n="259" who="S0179">it could have been a lot worse</u>
<u n="260" who="S0058">it could have been an awful lot worse <pause dur="short"/> erm it maybe it wasn't you know the best week but nothing really majorly bad happened so</u>
<u n="261" who="S0179">no erm <pause dur="long"/> I mean er <unclear/> observation is that <pause dur="short"/> it would be <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> a good way of putting it erm I think Heather is in some ways quite bipolar</u>
<u n="262" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0179">erm in the sense of I think she behave she's a very different people around for different people</u>
<u n="264" who="S0058">yeah she is <pause dur="short"/> very</u>
<u n="265" who="S0179">and to some extent it might be nicer if <unclear/> if she made an effort to be fun and engaging around you</u>
<u n="266" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I know that she isn't always like that <pause dur="short"/> she can't be because of what her life's like and</u>
<u n="267" who="S0179">but it's just interesting that I mean I think a lot of <pause dur="short"/> a a very good example is her sort of alcohol consumption</u>
<u n="268" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0179">I don't understand how you could drink like a fish in certain situations and then have absolutely nothing in the other</u>
<u n="270" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0179">I it's weird</u>
<u n="272" who="S0058">I agree <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of funny</u>
<u n="273" who="S0179">like last night I was really expecting her to have some wine with dinner</u>
<u n="274" who="S0058">yeah a glass of wine like it's not exactly <pause dur="short"/> but just that kind of prudence <pause dur="short"/> you know not prudence but kind of very erm yeah almost over done sort of temperance</u>
<u n="275" who="S0179">yes exactly <pause dur="short"/> versus</u>
<u n="276" who="S0058"><trunc>Vers</trunc> yeah versus really going out and having like yeah shots with friends from uni <pause dur="short"/> just kind of <pause dur="short"/> I don't know yeah I kind of <pause dur="short"/> I just get the impression that she's a a massive seething ball of nerves and neurosis and when she's with her friends she's kind of yeah more more relaxed and and that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> but maybe it's still there underneath and she's just pretending and it's easier to pretend when she's not with me <pause dur="short"/> and with me she just doesn't worry too much and it's just a massive <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just get the impression that she's on edge a lot of the time</u>
<u n="277" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0058">and she's very easily erm kind of erm angered by people doing stuff and</u>
<u n="279" who="S0179">on like what?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0058">well just like sort of cyclists doing something or pedestrians doing something or erm that kind of thing</u>
<u n="281" who="S0179">really? When was that?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0058" trans="overlap">did you? Yeah like when we cycled into town she was really quite kind of erm on edge about and so you know there's lots of pedestrians just stepped out <trunc>int</trunc> in the road and there's a big long queue of them and I just stopped <pause dur="short"/> didn't worry too much about it <pause dur="short"/> but and she was ringing her bell you know and kind of just and and then yeah and</u>
<u n="283" who="S0179"><unclear/> I saw some road rage cycling yesterday</u>
<u n="284" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0179">as well but er anyway sorry carry on</u>
<u n="286" who="S0058" trans="overlap">and just and like just occasionally this week she sort of I don't know if I've just been moving too slowly or something but she's stormed off <trunc>posi</trunc> you know purposefully <pause dur="short"/> like in Morrisons she was storming off purposefully down an aisle <pause dur="short"/> not knowing where she was going <pause dur="short"/> I'm like it's this way <pause dur="short"/> oh right <pause dur="short"/> and then just going off you know and sort of as if I don't know just yeah being nervous and sort of oh we've got to get there quickly you know <pause dur="short"/> even if she's got no idea where she is or what she's where she's going <pause dur="short"/> just that kind of purposeful stride <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I just get the impression she's really yeah nervous and on edge and worried and she really needs to do something about her fingers</u>
<u n="287" who="S0179" trans="overlap">fingers?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0058">erm she picks the skin on her fingers and it's right back to basically to her knuckles <pause dur="short"/> it's horrible</u>
<u n="289" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0058">it's absolutely disgusting <pause dur="short"/> erm she used to bite her nails and she stopped biting her nails but started picking like the edges around <pause dur="short"/> and yeah the skin's just off <pause dur="short"/> it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> it's absolutely disgusting <pause dur="short"/> and I've said to her your fingers are going to get infected</u>
<u n="291" who="S0179">how did you notice that?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> well she's constantly doing this? And just moving her hands and it really really gets on my nerves because it looks vile <pause dur="short"/> it can't be comfortable for her <pause dur="short"/> her fingers must ache <pause dur="short"/> and I  And I  said they're going to get infected <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> this isn't good <pause dur="short"/> and she said oh I know you know and is bothered <pause dur="short"/> I said have you tried hypnotherapy because genuinely like you need to stop doing it?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0179">erm could you do me a favour?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0179">there's a big rock in the middle of the drive</u>
<u n="296" who="S0058">yeah I see it</u>
<u n="297" who="S0179">whenever we're there you can't get at it</u>
<u n="298" who="S0058">yeah sure I'll I'll go and move it</u>
</body>
</text>
