<text id="SAUJ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:58</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0482 S0483</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Life, family, work</topics>
		<activity>Talking after eating.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0482">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Post Doc Researcher, Health Pyschologist</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Rudimentary; French -- almost  conversational</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0483">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Bromsgrove</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Assessment Manager (Education)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Rudimentary; German -- Rudimentary; Spanish -- Rudimentary</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0483">so erm how were the girls this evening?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0482">fine <pause dur="long"/> yeah they were good actually on good form no tantrums they played well together</u>
<u n="3" who="S0483">excellent makes it easier doesn't it? they're very quiet now as well</u>
<u n="4" who="S0482">yeah I think they're erm right level of tired</u>
<u n="5" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah definitely definitely</u>
<u n="6" who="S0482">how was zumba?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0483">yeah very good did a nice new new dance</u>
<u n="8" who="S0482">yeah?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0483">it was good</u>
<u n="10" who="S0482">what was it to?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0483">er something pop-y maybe I don't know I didn't know the song er <pause dur="long"/> <trunc>ba</trunc> if I had to guess I'd say it was something like Amy Winehouse but I don't don't think it was her <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0482">yeah you'd recognise Amy Winehouse</u>
<u n="13" who="S0483">that no yeah but it was it was that sort of style you know?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0482">right yeah <pause dur="short"/> modern youth music</u>
<u n="15" who="S0483" trans="overlap">modern modern not indie <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0482">no they don't probably do indie tracks do they?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0483">no not really a-ha was as close as we got</u>
<u n="18" who="S0482">to what?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0483" trans="overlap">indie</u>
<u n="20" who="S0482">oh what like what Take on Me?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0483">yeah it was a remix it wasn't it wasn't pretty</u>
<u n="22" who="S0482">no what was the dance like?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0483">er tiring</u>
<u n="24" who="S0482">mm it's kind of the aim</u>
<u n="25" who="S0483">yeah certainly is keeps you fit</u>
<u n="26" who="S0482">good busy still?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah really busy yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0482">how many people are going?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm fifteen</u>
<u n="30" who="S0482">okay that's pretty good</u>
<u n="31" who="S0483">yeah maybe it wasn't that many it was like</u>
<u n="32" who="S0482" trans="overlap">wasn't it like three when you first started?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah yeah it was three I know we were saying erm cos I when when I went yeah er last week erm the space that I went we have at the front had gone and so I just went and stood at the back and everyone was like oh you're at the back I said oh yeah that's fine I said I don't I I don't mind I'm quite happy to go at the back as in the person that was at the front in my space said I don't like going at the front I was like I'll go at the front I mean basically me and er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all go at the front not because we particularly want to go at the front but because we're the only three that used to go so we always had to be at the front there was no back we were the back and the front so anyway but er yeah I think it helps</u>
<u n="34" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah so you got to know you you got to know what you're doing at the front it's easier being at the back if you don't know what you're doing</u>
<u n="35" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah and I think it helps for people at the back to have someone that knows what they're doing at the front because then they can follow cos otherwise you're having to mirror</u>
<u n="36" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah you can copy <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0483">erm and it's it's yep yep yep so did you get did you sort of feel like you caught up on work today or are you still behind?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0482">well I'll always be behind</u>
<u n="39" who="S0483">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="40" who="S0482">erm <pause dur="short"/> no surprisingly productive</u>
<u n="41" who="S0483" trans="overlap">but it felt like you you know you didn't lose a desperate amount of hours today</u>
<u n="42" who="S0482">no no</u>
<u n="43" who="S0483">cos you've gained some at that <unclear/> conference and things</u>
<u n="44" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it was quite productive it was quite productive</u>
<u n="45" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0482">so it wasn't too bad I mean so erm I emailed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh you by the way I've given <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a thirty pound Amazon gift voucher</u>
<u n="47" who="S0483">saw that</u>
<u n="48" who="S0482">oh already?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0483">yeah well cos I was looking at orders cos I'm still checking when this flipping erm vegimals were coming</u>
<u n="50" who="S0482">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0483">flipping eleventh of February it's ridiculous how can it take a month?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0482">eleventh of February</u>
<u n="53" who="S0483">I know exactly eleventh of February I ordered them ages ago so that'll be well over a month</u>
<u n="54" who="S0482" trans="overlap">can you get them can you get them from another buyer?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0483" trans="overlap">paid four pound fifty for the pleasure of that postage</u>
<u n="56" who="S0482">can you get them from another buyer?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0483">erm not not really no I mean it was a you know anyway cos I'd ordered some stuff for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm she's wanted erm she asked if she could have a My Little Pony and we ordered her an Elsa headband and gloves or something</u>
<u n="58" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0483">erm so erm yeah I'd gone to my orders to check what was outstanding and saw that erm there was a thirty pound voucher erm that's good I'm glad you did that</u>
<u n="60" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah I I</u>
<u n="61" who="S0483">bit tight how many hours did she spend?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0482">well I I said on the comment that it was tiny token of appreciation</u>
<u n="63" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah it was a tiny token I'd have gone at least forty</u>
<u n="64" who="S0482">but she said she said in her response erm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0483">is that it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0482">no she she said she made out that it was very she thought it was very generous and</u>
<u n="67" who="S0483">ah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0482">she said I really <trunc>enjo</trunc> you know don't I wouldn't expect anything I didn't do it cos I expected something from it</u>
<u n="69" who="S0483">no of course</u>
<u n="70" who="S0482">I know of course</u>
<u n="71" who="S0483">no of course not cos if you did you'd expect more than that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0482">but I did do it at the time where I asked her another favour</u>
<u n="73" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh no</u>
<u n="74" who="S0482">I asked her about some extracting some data erm and er she's she's already got on to it</u>
<u n="75" who="S0483">oh wow</u>
<u n="76" who="S0482">she you know I <trunc>re</trunc> I was literally sounding her out cos I needed to it's for a conference next month and I don't want to leave it too late cos you know I needed her help for some of it and er yeah she said she said do you know what? I've just started it already</u>
<u n="77" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0482">she said she had a er a spare day this week</u>
<u n="79" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0482">like she was was wondering what to do with so</u>
<u n="81" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0482">I know</u>
<u n="83" who="S0483">oh to be spare spare days</u>
<u n="84" who="S0482">I know</u>
<u n="85" who="S0483">she can come help me decorate</u>
<u n="86" who="S0482">well her <unclear/> just got cancelled or something</u>
<u n="87" who="S0483">yeah well that's good well erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>n</trunc> you were getting her in on publications something were you as well?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0482">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so</u>
<u n="90" who="S0482">she's she's a she's an author on the er on the abstract not that that means very much but she was an author on our paper that we're submitting</u>
<u n="91" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0482">and then she'll be an author on the second paper and then if we do a paper out of this extra little analysis she's doing then you know I don't think there'll be enough data actually to publish it but anyway</u>
<u n="93" who="S0483">well it's a start is the other thing dead in the water? the erm moods thing?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0482">I still need to get data from Australia</u>
<u n="95" who="S0483">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0482">and that said I I have got it on my task list</u>
<u n="97" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0482">I just need to ask <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do it</u>
<u n="99" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0482">but erm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0483">yeah well it's not like you're not busy enough doing other things</u>
<u n="102" who="S0482">no I mean you know actually chatting to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who knows a lot about this sort of stuff he basically he's actually genuinely a he used to work for the British Geological Survey and he genuinely knows about this scale and and a what it means and stuff and he he was he wasn't sort of erm making out like it was a waste of time he was proposing how else to look at it and what other kind of data and whereabouts</u>
<u n="103" who="S0483">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0482">this activity could vary according to <trunc>geogr</trunc>geography so it was quite you know he didn't laugh at me</u>
<u n="105" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah not not dead in the water no no no that's good that's good now</u>
<u n="106" who="S0482">erm and given that he knows the science the real science unlike me</u>
<u n="107" who="S0483" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the erm weather gauge is saying it's not gonna rain so that's interesting</u>
<u n="108" who="S0482">why was something else said?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0483" trans="overlap">it's been quite it's been sort of claiming rain all day well no they've been claiming rain all day and it hasn't and now it's saying not gonna rain</u>
<u n="110" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well it's because of this I'm not surprised the pressure's dropped quite a bit</u>
<u n="111" who="S0483">yeah but I thought</u>
<u n="112" who="S0482">but now it's going back up again so it's gong to decide that that flow's come through already</u>
<u n="113" who="S0483">but I thought the storm was coming I guess the storm's not going to hit us is it? erm erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0482">oh is there a storm on the way?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0483">but yeah oh yeah yeah I told it was I told you the wind was getting up it's the backlash of the er</u>
<u n="116" who="S0482">oh what the US one?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I was talking about weather last time they'll think I'm obsessed erm yeah it's the backlash of the er erm US one</u>
<u n="118" who="S0482">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0483">so erm yeah it's it's you know gonna batter us with rain and stuff</u>
<u n="120" who="S0482">probably not us</u>
<u n="121" who="S0483">no I think it I think it's erm battering <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0482">the waves</u>
<u n="123" who="S0483">it'll fizzle out by the time it gets to us yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0482">oh right I thought it sort of seems quite I mean I I know pressure moves quicker than like wind if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="125" who="S0483">er er</u>
<u n="126" who="S0482">cos it's not it's more complex than that but you still sort of don't expect it to be here already</u>
<u n="127" who="S0483">er</u>
<u n="128" who="S0482">I suppose it is Tuesday tomorrow</u>
<u n="129" who="S0483">I don't know</u>
<u n="130" who="S0482">but you know like if you if you drove across the Channel er across the Atlantic you wouldn't expect to do it in a day and a half would you?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0483" trans="overlap">er no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0482">or maybe you could I don't know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0483">I don't know I don't know I don't know how far it is</u>
<u n="134" who="S0482">two thousand miles?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0483">er well you could certainly do that in a day and a half</u>
<u n="136" who="S0482">two thousand miles</u>
<u n="137" who="S0483">yeah it's like you know you'd be driving all the time wouldn't you? but</u>
<u n="138" who="S0482">well I suppose I mean if you did a hundred miles an hour that would take twenty hours</u>
<u n="139" who="S0483">yeah so two days yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0482">so so I guess eight</u>
<u n="141" who="S0483" trans="overlap">people do it in the States don't they? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did it that time</u>
<u n="142" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0483">erm but anyway wasn't it going into the States that way? so how would it be coming this way as well cos I'm sure the pictures I saw it was hitting the States as if it was going to the left</u>
<u n="144" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no it was coming it was coming away</u>
<u n="145" who="S0483">it was come oh</u>
<u n="146" who="S0482">it was coming no cos it started off like down south</u>
<u n="147" who="S0483">oh</u>
<u n="148" who="S0482">it wasn't coming in off the coast it was coming</u>
<u n="149" who="S0483">oh oh okay</u>
<u n="150" who="S0482">cos there were lots of people who were cos I don't think it was hitting as populated areas as Washington and New York</u>
<u n="151" who="S0483">right</u>
<u n="152" who="S0482">which is why I think erm you know obviously it becomes more newsworthy when it hits</u>
<u n="153" who="S0483">yeah let's see what's</u>
<u n="154" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you know ten million people have <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0483" trans="overlap">let's see what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said in her text and then we'll know it says erm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0482">it's pissing it down</u>
<u n="157" who="S0483"><trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>p</trunc> er no it says oh oh <trunc>wa</trunc> oh blowing up a gale here</u>
<u n="158" who="S0482">yeah well it's quite</u>
<u n="159" who="S0483" trans="overlap">so bit windy <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm well</u>
<u n="160" who="S0482">well if you're in a</u>
<u n="161" who="S0483">yes as I say I mean it's breezy out there but I wouldn't say it was a gale erm how many leeks did you get in there?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0482">three</u>
<u n="163" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0482">four</u>
<u n="165" who="S0483">good <vocal desc="laugh"/> seems to be a week of eating leeks</u>
<u n="166" who="S0482">yeah I know I should've cut the aubergines up a bit more</u>
<u n="167" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no that's fine is there a sauce? <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's exactly the sort of thing</u>
<u n="168" who="S0482" trans="overlap">that's my comment</u>
<u n="169" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I know exactly the sort of thing you'd say to me</u>
<u n="170" who="S0482">well</u>
<u n="171" who="S0483">have you thought about just putting a tin of tomatoes in there? cos like not being funny or anything I quite like a sauce on my pasta</u>
<u n="172" who="S0482">yeah I was thinking about that but then <pause dur="short"/> I'm taking a leaf from your book</u>
<u n="173" who="S0483">you what laziness? <vocal desc="laugh"/> no no I <trunc>do</trunc> no I I would I would personally not put tomato in there</u>
<u n="174" who="S0482">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0483">bucket load of cheesy sauce'd be good <pause dur="short"/> do that another day</u>
<u n="176" who="S0482">yeah I'm just going to have a bit of cheese in there</u>
<u n="177" who="S0483" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> is that is that is that my cheese portion?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it's a bit of <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> do you want some more?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0483">well it doesn't look like loads does it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0482">I'll do some more</u>
<u n="181" who="S0483">yeah if you don't mind</u>
<u n="182" who="S0482">okay <pause dur="short"/> will do <pause dur="short"/> more cheese <pause dur="short"/> coming up <pause dur="long"/> that's probably enough oh go on a bit more <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> bit more that'll do <pause dur="short"/> cheese for everyone <pause dur="long"/> okey dokey check the pasta going well</u>
<u n="183" who="S0483">I've erm <pause dur="short"/> I've left your mother's door open</u>
<u n="184" who="S0482">okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0483">cos she's still miffed that no one's sleeping in her room erm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0482">I felt like that when I was fifteen</u>
<u n="187" who="S0483" trans="overlap">did you do more cheese?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0482">yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> that's obviously weighed it down <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0482" trans="overlap">there's more cheese than you think there</u>
<u n="191" who="S0483">yeah yeah mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0482" trans="overlap">but I mean <pause dur="short"/> that's like a that's almost like a portion of pasta sized cheese</u>
<u n="193" who="S0483" trans="overlap">alright <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0482">if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="195" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> are you going to put it back in the oven so it gets a bit crusty?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0482">I dunno do you think?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0483">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="198" who="S0482">like a proper pasta bake</u>
<u n="199" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0482">do you think it'll fit in there?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0483">no just put it in that tin</u>
<u n="202" who="S0482">do you think?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fucking hell</u>
<u n="204" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0483"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would've been listening to that bit and saying did she say canal? <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh jeez a mess in there isn't it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0483">probably with a cat in the middle of it</u>
<u n="208" who="S0482">it's not too it's superficial</u>
<u n="209" who="S0483">no I know I I did a really good tidy up actually I started binning some plastic tat</u>
<u n="210" who="S0482">I'll tell you what I really really been I think our visit to the showroom this weekend made me think about how the stove will <pause dur="short"/> sort of I I was thinking of it in terms of it being quite local you know the <trunc>at</trunc>atmosphere it would create would be quite local to where it would be</u>
<u n="211" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0482">but now I can sort of really see it being a big part of the downstairs</u>
<u n="213" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0482">so I'm all excited I'll have to make the five year warranty</u>
<u n="215" who="S0483">yeah no it's exciting indeed <pause dur="long"/> pity global warming will mean we won't really need it but</u>
<u n="216" who="S0482">mm <pause dur="long"/> well I don't know when there's a shortage of resources and when Russia stop selling gas to Europe</u>
<u n="217" who="S0483">yeah yeah this is what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying</u>
<u n="218" who="S0482">we run out of North Sea gas</u>
<u n="219" who="S0483">this is what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying don't trust the Russians well not <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0482">well it's a business move</u>
<u n="221" who="S0483" trans="overlap">he's get he's getting he's getting the solar panels as well he's gonna do some deep some sunken water tank or something I dunno</u>
<u n="222" who="S0482">mm?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0483">I've not heard of it myself something about a tank a big tank of water heating solar panel heating a big tank of water</u>
<u n="224" who="S0482">yeah well you it's solar <trunc>he</trunc> solar heating or something where you you remember when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had it in his house?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh right okay watch out for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it's basically where you have use the solar you know <trunc>ra</trunc>radiation to heat up water</u>
<u n="227" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0482">which basically takes the edge off likes warms up your heating water</u>
<u n="229" who="S0483">yes</u>
<u n="230" who="S0482">erm so you have to use up a lot less energy to get it hot</u>
<u n="231" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0482">so say your heating water is by like standard ten degrees</u>
<u n="233" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0482">and you can get it up to about twenty degrees using the solar panels</u>
<u n="235" who="S0483">oh yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0482">you you skip that energy to go from ten to twenty</u>
<u n="237" who="S0483">oh good I doubt <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is managing that in Ireland</u>
<u n="238" who="S0482">I don't think it's been around that much</u>
<u n="239" who="S0483">no I don't</u>
<u n="240" who="S0482">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah I I I think although the wholesale price buy back thing that that oi stop eating the cheese</u>
<u n="241" who="S0483">you were eating the cheese</u>
<u n="242" who="S0482">I know but erm I think the sort of the the amount of money they'd pay for every unit you put back into the gird has although it's gone down a lot the price for solar panels has really come down and I think their efficiency has improved so</u>
<u n="243" who="S0483">I don't know</u>
<u n="244" who="S0482">you know it's still maybe worth looking into solar panels</u>
<u n="245" who="S0483">yeah no but it's just gonna look a bit ugly isn't it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0482">what?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0483">well I don't know because they're going to have to be mounted up on our</u>
<u n="248" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I don't yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="249" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I know it's not like they can go flat on the roof they've got to be mounted up so</u>
<u n="250" who="S0482">on this roof here yeah but you wouldn't be able to see it from anywhere apart form the back</u>
<u n="251" who="S0483">oh you want to put them on that roof well</u>
<u n="252" who="S0482">or where else?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0483">I don't know I didn't really</u>
<u n="254" who="S0482">it's not really I don't think you put them on the top of the house</u>
<u n="255" who="S0483">you you could if they were poked up</u>
<u n="256" who="S0482">yeah but it might be a bit windy</u>
<u n="257" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well the thing is is there is a bit rob-able</u>
<u n="258" who="S0482">that's very true yeah I</u>
<u n="259" who="S0483">I don't think there's a great market in robbing them but they are worth a fair bit of money and you know and if it's a easy place to get them from somebody might want to go for it I don't know</u>
<u n="260" who="S0482">what we</u>
<u n="261" who="S0483">I did ask someone and they said oh you know they're not actually stolen that much cos they're you know there was a reason but I don't know where something's got a value there's risk of robbing isn't there?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0482">yeah I wonder what the black market's like for buying solar panels?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0483" trans="overlap">Ebay Ebay solar panels</u>
<u n="264" who="S0482" trans="overlap">so where did you get your solar panel from? erm a mate gave it to me yeah? it's not stolen is it? no you don't look like the sort of person who'd have solar panels yeah I dunno it's erm well that would that would be the last piece of the puzzle wouldn't it? we've got heating electricity and we'd go off grid</u>
<u n="265" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah but yeah but yeah but that's the thing you can't go off grid can you?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0482" trans="overlap">and not without no? we'd be stuffed for the internet <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0483">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'd be stuffed for a lot of things</u>
<u n="268" who="S0482">get a satellite connection I did look into that in Ireland</u>
<u n="269" who="S0483">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0482">cos it was one of the options but it was going to be too expensive</u>
<u n="271" who="S0483">send up send up your own satellite in a rocket</u>
<u n="272" who="S0482">that's what Google have done isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0483">yeah <trunc>bluet</trunc> we could bluetooth to a satellite black satellite</u>
<u n="274" who="S0482">bluetooth I'm not sure bluetooth would be your <unclear/> of choice</u>
<u n="275" who="S0483">no no what if we had lot if we had a stream of little satellites like a kite</u>
<u n="276" who="S0482">oh yeah that could each like connect to each other</u>
<u n="277" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0482">that'd be good <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0483">be not great connection speed would it really?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0482">generally bit of a shit plan</u>
<u n="281" who="S0483">yeah a little bit shit <pause dur="long"/> is that a child calling again?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0482">mm do you think we'll need a tomato sauce?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0483">erm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0482">cos we've got like half a tin in thingy</u>
<u n="285" who="S0483">no no no no I wouldn't bother no</u>
<u n="286" who="S0482">I would usually I agree but</u>
<u n="287" who="S0483">when's the pasta ready? soon?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0482">it's pretty much there actually</u>
<u n="289" who="S0483">well I mean if it's gonna go in yeah exactly take them</u>
<u n="290" who="S0482" trans="overlap">cos if it's gonna go in the oven then better call it it's probably getting to that stage where it's starting to reduce</u>
<u n="291" who="S0483">yeah yeah what are we what are we er watching tonight?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0482">are you sure putting all that cheese?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0483">oh have you got cheese in there?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0483">oh cheeky</u>
<u n="296" who="S0482">erm are you sure this is going to be good cos of all the cheese and stuff?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yes yes it's gonna be fine erm what are we watching tonight?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0482">erm I dunno we could watch other Mr Robot</u>
<u n="299" who="S0483">oh I'd forgotten about that I might have to write that down otherwise we keep forgetting these things yeah definitely up for that what does that say it's <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I wouldn't mind watching shall we shall we try and watch that Amazing Faces? we never had</u>
<u n="301" who="S0483">oh oh Deutschland do da we've forgotten about</u>
<u n="302" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0483">oh you're not keen are you?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0482">well no we'll try it again</u>
<u n="305" who="S0483">Mr Robot is gonna be <trunc>ava</trunc> for for ages erm I think we need to watch I think we've got to do <unclear/> to do really it was well rated mm you're not keen I'm not I'm not well I don't know what channel was it? was it I T channel four?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0482" trans="overlap">was it? I don't fancy it tonight</u>
<u n="307" who="S0483">no if it's channel four we should get it have it for a while actually I'll check now erm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0482">we'll do an Amazing Spaces</u>
<u n="309" who="S0483">er</u>
<u n="310" who="S0482">come on you enjoy it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0483">erm we'll do a war</u>
<u n="312" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it's easy to do it with dinner actually cos the</u>
<u n="313" who="S0483" trans="overlap">can we do can we do a War and Peace?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0482">erm could do did enjoy it but why don't we do an Amazing Spaces and a Mr Robot?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0483">mm that sounds very much everything you would like erm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0482">alright you you chose what you chose</u>
<u n="317" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no no</u>
<u n="318" who="S0482">no problem</u>
<u n="319" who="S0483">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm oh look there there we go Deutschland eighty-three oops erm so it's still still current <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0482">not <unclear>erased</unclear></u>
<u n="321" who="S0483">er <pause dur="long"/> are we actually? yeah oh I really want to watch watch it we've got tenth of Jan seventeenth of Jan they're only forty-six months long I suppose it's the bloody adverts isn't it? er</u>
<u n="322" who="S0482">what channel is it on?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0483">it's channel four it doesn't I've got no information that it's going at any point</u>
<u n="324" who="S0482">I think the last time we watched it the adverts sort of petered out after about the first advert but</u>
<u n="325" who="S0483">yeah yeah that's true I think</u>
<u n="326" who="S0482">they just expect no one to be watching it</u>
<u n="327" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I'm pretty sure it'll stay for a while okay well now it's on the list we won't forget about it erm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0482">okay this'll be ready in about five minutes</u>
<u n="329" who="S0483">okay</u>
<u n="330" who="S0482">I won't put it in for long so get why don't get Amazing Spaces wracked up cos it's an easy one to to have when we're eating Deutschland whatever isn't good for eating cos of the subtitles you know how I feel about subtitles during meals <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0482">could that sound any more middle class?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well <pause dur="long"/> did you erm are you back on board with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0482">yeah no I did enjoy it <pause dur="long"/> yeah I did enjoy it sorry should I have put that?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0483">no no no did I I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just think realistically in terms of games we're going to play on there it's only really those two I don't think we're gonna <unclear/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I quite like the Resident Evil one that looked quite good</u>
<u n="337" who="S0483" trans="overlap">have we got that?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0482">yes</u>
<u n="339" who="S0483">have we?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0482">yeah apparently it's really good</u>
<u n="341" who="S0483" trans="overlap">who got us that?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0482">your brother</u>
<u n="343" who="S0483">oh did he?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0483">oh right</u>
<u n="346" who="S0482">got us two games</u>
<u n="347" who="S0483">cool</u>
<u n="348" who="S0482">I got his <unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0483">alright well let's do Zelda first then Resident Evil then Zelda again keep us going for a year and a half</u>
<u n="350" who="S0482">what? just the Zelda one?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah probably</u>
<u n="352" who="S0482">by which point the Wii will be in the Victoria and Albert museum</u>
<u n="353" who="S0483">it will god probably yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0482">here we have an ancient games console from the late twenty tens</u>
<u n="355" who="S0483">its wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bought them round two two two thousand and six one was definitely</u>
<u n="356" who="S0482" trans="overlap">sorry twenty hundreds no no actually probably nineties maybe maybe early maybe early noughty er zeroes what every they're called</u>
<u n="357" who="S0483">mm yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0482">noughties? yeah noughties stupid name</u>
<u n="359" who="S0483" trans="overlap">maybe mind you how old's the Playstation now? pretty old what is it? is it?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it's Playstation three</u>
<u n="361" who="S0483" trans="overlap">three yeah but that's pretty old now we had it for our wedding so that's two thousand and four</u>
<u n="362" who="S0482">no that was the Playstation two</u>
<u n="363" who="S0483">oh ah yes ah okay mm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0482"><unclear/> maybe</u>
<u n="365" who="S0483">oh you got it after your PhD completion so</u>
<u n="366" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0483">and it had been out for a while</u>
<u n="368" who="S0482">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a long while probably</u>
<u n="370" who="S0482">we so I don't know ten years? probably ish</u>
<u n="371" who="S0483">keeping up with technology</u>
<u n="372" who="S0482">but yeah I think we got the Playstation two around not far off the time Playstation three came out</u>
<u n="373" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="374" who="S0482">we certainly got we we got a Wii like probably about five years after the Wii the other Wii one came up the good Wii</u>
<u n="375" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah good Wii <vocal desc="laugh"/> is there another Wii then? what's it called? Wii</u>
<u n="376" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah can't remember</u>
<u n="377" who="S0483">play Wii cos you didn't you buy a game for that instead of that?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0482">yeah Wii U</u>
<u n="379" who="S0483">Wii U mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0482">yeah oh I see what they're doing I only I didn't notice that</u>
<u n="381" who="S0483">what?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0482">Wii U</u>
<u n="383" who="S0483">oh</u>
<u n="384" who="S0482">I and you</u>
<u n="385" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0482">I see you</u>
<u n="387" who="S0483"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0482">hey we forgot about that as well</u>
<u n="389" who="S0483">what?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0482">we haven't watched that for a few days</u>
<u n="391" who="S0483">what's that?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0482">House of Cards <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0483">oh House of Cards <vocal desc="laugh"/> I want that cheese properly browned</u>
<u n="394" who="S0482">oh I'll put the grill on then</u>
<u n="395" who="S0483">oh steady on there'll be loads of chicken spitiness coming down</u>
<u n="396" who="S0482">it might smoke a bit</u>
<u n="397" who="S0483">yeah do it good burn some juices off <shift new="singing"/> hey I just met you mm mm mm <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0482">it's starting to smoke</u>
<u n="399" who="S0483">excellent it's a bit like on <unclear/> stove</u>
<u n="400" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> old family recipe</u>
<u n="401" who="S0482"><vocal desc="cough"/> might want to close the door</u>
<u n="402" who="S0483">nothing's coming out yet it wouldn't until you did that I can't believe you're coughing at smoke contained within an oven</u>
<u n="403" who="S0482">I can see smoke it made me cough</u>
<u n="404" who="S0483">it's like it's like the idiots that cough when they see dry ice <vocal desc="laugh"/> that'd be you in a club come on come on mate</u>
<u n="405" who="S0482">well it can make you people look it's the same stuff that's in e-cigarettes and that makes people cough</u>
<u n="406" who="S0483">no <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0482">okay</u>
<u n="408" who="S0483">fine now</u>
<u n="409" who="S0482">smoking is down to zero <pause dur="short"/> it's half hang on is it half eight?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0482">bloody hell</u>
<u n="412" who="S0483">if we want if we want if we want speed cook we call me don't we? if we want decent cook we call you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0482">oh fair enough I'll take that <pause dur="short"/> oh well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not asleep yet</u>
<u n="414" who="S0483">nope</u>
<u n="415" who="S0482">do you want to load up erm Amazing Spaces and get through a few adverts?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0483">well yes I suppose so</u>
<u n="417" who="S0482">I'll stop this <pause dur="long"/> oh</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
