<text id="SAVW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>2:06:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A car journey from Manchester to Cornwall (going on holiday)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Water bottles, pens, journey, lunch/dinner/supper, tea/coffee, Holland and Barrett, Irritable Bowel Syndrome, moving house, cooking, chocolate, manor houses, money, travelling, immigration, Japan, racism, liquorice/medicine, pets, post/delivery, amazon, Jurassic park, DVDS, unpacking, moving house, furniture, cars, delivery, washing machine, counties, Latin, examiners/exams, traffic, cars, inventions, cat flaps, Egyptians, cat in the hat, moomins, Norway, northern lights, taste, languages (Hungarian). </topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on journey to Cornwall (summer holiday)</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing explaining, adecdote telling making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421">I don't know</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">I forget I got that last time didn't I?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0421">yeah I think every time you buy a bottle from these <unclear>like on</unclear> trips they don't fit in your holder</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423">yes it's these seven fifty mils isn't it? I think that's the size</u>
<u n="5" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah cos we always get a big one like oh yes but <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there we are look at that</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0423">a solution</u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">the five hundred mil ones usually fit but <pause dur="short"/> they should really make</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah the normal size yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0421">bigger well though if they made bigger holders then</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423">no this is kind of like</u>
<u n="13" who="S0421" trans="overlap">the five hundred mil wouldn't fit would it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah this is kind of like for a fairly standard bottle these ones these are bit <pause dur="short"/> out of the ordinary size aren't they?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421">oh <pause dur="short"/> the strawberry's nice</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423">is it?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is the</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0421">lemon and lime <vocal desc="laugh"/> nice?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423">yeah I'm glad I got that one than just plain ones <pause dur="short"/> I'll just put that on there on there yeah that'll do no that's a bit <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you just took a picture how many times?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0423" trans="overlap">did a</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421" trans="overlap">have you taken a picture of yourself like that?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't know I'll have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0421" trans="overlap">wow have you got those pens as well?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423">well I must have <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0421">oh yeah we discussed this last time</u>
<u n="28" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421">that we have those</u>
<u n="30" who="S0423" trans="overlap">why did you have?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0421">yeah I bought like a a big pack of them yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="33" who="S0421">although I think yours were slightly different yeah yours was a bit harder <pause dur="short"/> yours is a bit more plasticy but</u>
<u n="34" who="S0423">there</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0423">yours are better quality are they?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421">well they weren't great quality because I bought them really cheap I just thought they were quite comfortable</u>
<u n="38" who="S0423">it's twenty past <unclear>four</unclear></u>
<u n="39" who="S0421">to hold <pause dur="short"/> how long have we been in Sainsbury's?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423">I don't know it wasn't a very good idea was it I suppose? we should have filled this up last night</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421">yeah I was expecting our first stop to be like I dunno like lunch</u>
<u n="42" who="S0423">what what do you mean lunch?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421">well I mean it's like</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423" trans="overlap">now?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421">well no but like having I dunno</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it will be but it won't be but it won't it'll be a late lunch</u>
<u n="47" who="S0421">I know but this was our first stop</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423">might be the time when people have dinner oh right right yeah I think we'll just get straight</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="50" who="S0423">on the way <unclear/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0421" trans="overlap">how how are we going to have lunch when people have dinner?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423">well you can call it dinner if you want <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0423">and then we can have supper later</u>
<u n="55" who="S0421"><trunc>wha</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> as we're eating at the time that have dinner if we're having lunch that we'll be wanting supper what time are we gonna have supper at?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0423">well we on holiday we normally eat a bit later don't we?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0421">yeah but <pause dur="long"/> I never have supper it's a bit outdated now we discussed that in my English language class</u>
<u n="58" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0421">yeah like no one really has supper but</u>
<u n="60" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well you know what? people do but they just don't call it supper</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah well because we were</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos I I <trunc>al</trunc> I always have <trunc>d</trunc> a lot of people well I always have dinner quite late really try and avoid doing that but I tend to you know sit down quite late for dinner and then sometimes if you have an early dinner you may want <pause dur="short"/> you know say you're having a cup of tea or a drink and <trunc>y</trunc>you want what people would probably call a snack</u>
<u n="63" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but in the past they'd call it er supper</u>
<u n="65" who="S0421">yeah well</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like it cos supper was only very light</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421">it was bread and butter</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like a snack really yeah it's not nothing much</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421">because we were reading like a hotel thing and it was like breakfast lunch dinner and supper included and it was like for supper we have on offer bread and butter with some jam or something</u>
<u n="70" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what hotel was that?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0421">in like in the past</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421">like we cos that's what in <trunc>langu</trunc> in English language we did like language change over time</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">and I was thinking my dad has supper <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">I don't really say I'm having supper now although I suppose that's what it is if you it's just it's one of those words probably going out of the</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423" trans="overlap">out of use isn't it?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">yes</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">like when I was a child my mum might say oh I'll I'll get you some er er do you want some supper? like when I was younger it would be used as a word then</u>
<u n="81" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">erm but then people have just stopped <pause dur="short"/> using it I I I've I think <pause dur="short"/> probably because I think people's lifestyles have changed a lot though</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423">everything's around the clock now and they're not as tied to certain times as they used to be and people work lots of shift work and different hours and <pause dur="short"/> erm and I've always never really stuck to a regimented time for eating but some people do don't they? they erm they like to have lunch at around lunchtime dinner around dinner time and and that's where all that's come from I suppose you have particular times for</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">certain things don't you?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423">like if you don't stick to those times I guess the the word <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose people <trunc>st</trunc>still say lunch and dinner don't they?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421">yeah it really confuses though when people</u>
<u n="90" who="S0423" trans="overlap">although they don't say lunch yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yeah when people don't call</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they say dinner and tea</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421">they called it call lunch dinner and I'm like</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0421">why are you having dinner now? and it's like no like er lunch and I'm like oh like it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I I always used to call it that dinner and tea until I went to London and</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421">really?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423">yeah well that's what you say you're from being in the north</u>
<u n="99" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because I've always said lunch and dinner always</u>
<u n="100" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well I suppose I suppose you know</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but I'm not I <trunc>w</trunc> like well I'm I mean I lived in London for like what? five years like</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">yeah so you might have had that expression in you like again I don't know</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">but that is but it's weird though because I've lived up north for like the majority of my life I wouldn't I wouldn't consider the</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah maybe that's what we called it at home when you're in London or</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0423">cos I used to say lunch and dinner er when from <trunc>L</trunc> being in London and working in restaurants</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423">and the main thing is cos I worked in restaurants it's all it's lunch is lunch</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423">cos that's what you're serving and dinner became dinner</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421">yeah in restaurants</u>
<u n="112" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it became that's</u>
<u n="113" who="S0421">it is isn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah it's always lunch and dinner and then it's just what we call it up here erm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="116" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's your dinner and your <trunc>te</trunc> they call it your tea they like it's</u>
<u n="117" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I that always confused me</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421">when I was younger I was like oh well tea?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">yeah I that's well</u>
<u n="121" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it it was er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0423" trans="overlap">when I was a child mum would say come in and get your tea</u>
<u n="123" who="S0421">it was so funny online I saw erm this American person had written online and they were like it was so funny they said I'm so confused about all the British people are so obsessed with tea and I was thinking well okay so like we drink we drink tea but and then like they have they always say oh it's time for tea and they sit down <vocal desc="laugh"/> and they all and I'm thinking I see what they've done here they've obviously been up north and people are like oh it's teatime and they're having as in like tea as in dinner but this American person has heard the word tea and thinking that they're all gonna sit round and have a cup of tea and like have some kind of a weird tea ceremony</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but maybe that's <trunc>wha</trunc> well it could be what they were doing if it's</u>
<u n="125" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't think it <trunc>wa</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0423">you know it might not be how you've imagined it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0421">because they they said it in a kind of like most British people and I'm like I don't know any British people who have tea ceremonies</u>
<u n="128" who="S0423">no but he didn't say it was a ceremony did he?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0421">no they were like they will sit round like it's erm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0423">but that would be like</u>
<u n="131" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a big ritual or something</u>
<u n="132" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well down that could be like in hotels in like London and that they serve</u>
<u n="133" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well you can have high tea <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="134" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><trunc>aft</trunc>afternoon tea and high tea and all that and</u>
<u n="135" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423">so it that is a very kind of old tradition</u>
<u n="137" who="S0421">yeah but</u>
<u n="138" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but normally <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0421" trans="overlap">surely if they'd gone to that they would have known it's a kind of cos like you can go to it but most people go as a kind of novelty it's not something unless they just stumbled into one of those and thought is this what they do every day?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423">yeah it might be just somebody that hasn't got a clue anyway they just</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0423">slagging off the English basically saying you know</u>
<u n="143" who="S0421">they do they do drink tea in America don't they?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0423">yeah I when I was</u>
<u n="145" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there I bought packets of tea and had it but it's just not as common you know</u>
<u n="147" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="148" who="S0423">erm it it's er you don't see you know you you probably get one brand and they'll be a little section on the shelf</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423">whereas you know you if you look over here you have a whole patch</u>
<u n="151" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or you know half an aisle of teas and loads of different like coffee's become popular over here now as well whereas in the past you you'd probably have a couple of brands of coffee</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0423"><vocal desc="cough"/> whereas in other countries <trunc>yo</trunc> the <trunc>em</trunc> there was more of an emphasis on erm coffee rather than tea</u>
<u n="155" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0423">erm and then even in France erm when I was in France there was just one brand Lipton's tea or something that <trunc>w</trunc> that was it so they did have tea but you you can buy it quite limited on <unclear>over there</unclear></u>
<u n="157" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah because</u>
<u n="158" who="S0423">you'd get cos it's just not</u>
<u n="159" who="S0421">when we went to</u>
<u n="160" who="S0423" trans="overlap">as common as <unclear/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0421" trans="overlap">when we went to Hungary and like we went to see one of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends and she brought them tea and they were like oh it's really nice like English tea she brought it over for them</u>
<u n="162" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so they they don't really they don't have it over there</u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">yeah yeah and it is very much associated with you know if you get other <trunc>bran</trunc>brands in other countries they might be kind of an English based brand</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but a bit more obscure</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0423">or saying something to do with English because I guess it's and and I suppose why it's been so become so popular here is because the plantations in India</u>
<u n="169" who="S0421">yeah British empire</u>
<u n="170" who="S0423" trans="overlap">where it was a whole and they they could get it so so cheap it became it just became the drink of everyone you know the</u>
<u n="171" who="S0421">but I don't like it</u>
<u n="172" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the poor for the poor the</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0423">that's cos you weren't really introduced to it when you were younger I think</u>
<u n="175" who="S0421">but I like</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos you always get children</u>
<u n="177" who="S0421" trans="overlap">herbal tea</u>
<u n="178" who="S0423" trans="overlap">when they're really young and they have they have really milky tea</u>
<u n="179" who="S0421">I don't know why</u>
<u n="180" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="181" who="S0421">it's not particularly good for <vocal desc="laugh"/> you</u>
<u n="182" who="S0423">I know it's just what? <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>yo</trunc> it's it's it's just the the drink of <pause dur="short"/> but it's still a very cheap drink isn't it? it's just a drink that everybody would have I <trunc>sup</trunc></u>
<u n="183" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423">I suppose it became so popular but it's the same in Ireland as well as as here it's erm you know tea it's just it's treated just the same or more so you know where it's it's the drink for people in Ireland as well <pause dur="short"/> erm and other countries you you then have to go to maybe say the Asian countries don't you?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">where tea is important like but they drink it differently to us</u>
<u n="187" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423">like in India and China and <pause dur="short"/> er Japan green tea <pause dur="short"/> and er in India I think I saw the documentary they they have chai or something they call it it's really really sweet and really really milky I mean so <pause dur="short"/> it tastes very different to ours but it's probably a bit more in common with ours cos in other countries they don't put milk or</u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">yeah cos I don't put milk in</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423" trans="overlap">sugar in it so obviously</u>
<u n="191" who="S0421" trans="overlap">the one I drink yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0423">no the herbal tea you wouldn't no</u>
<u n="193" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="194" who="S0423">although you'd probably do you sweeten it?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0421">I don't er mum always used to put <trunc>m</trunc> honey in for me</u>
<u n="196" who="S0423">oh I brought some herbal teas in case you cos I know you</u>
<u n="197" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh have you?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423">a cup of tea yeah er</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is it herbal is it tea with added herbs or is it like a herbal infusion?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423">erm I don't know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos you have to be careful because I always look at the ingredients and it has to be a hundred percent the herb but <unclear>if it's got any then I'll</unclear> <unclear/> then</u>
<u n="202" who="S0423">erm well I haven't I've got one of the packets it's all the same brand the Twinings</u>
<u n="203" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="204" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you know Twinings?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0423">so they're in the car <unclear/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they they are a good brand but I think they mix it with well I'll have a look</u>
<u n="208" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do they?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0421">I'll have a look</u>
<u n="210" who="S0423">I don't think it's it's many that do <unclear>I suppose er</unclear></u>
<u n="211" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos I know I I have to buy them in Holland and Barrett</u>
<u n="212" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the herbs well that's it yeah so it's probably not erm well look I mean I've got a few this so <pause dur="short"/> chamomile and peppermint I would imagine peppermint is just peppermint they've <unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah cos I've got peppermint at home but I bought that <trunc>f</trunc> one from Holland and Barrett's and it's like a hundred percent I don't know if that one's organic or if I didn't get the organic one because it was more but yeah erm chamomile can be sometimes mixed</u>
<u n="214" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it it might be their brand because it it's straight off like the supermarket shelf if you want just want purely herbal you have to kind of</u>
<u n="215" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0423">maybe you have to shop around a bit more like you</u>
<u n="217" who="S0421">Holland and Barrett's is just such a good shop <pause dur="long"/> got lots of stuff there that I like</u>
<u n="218" who="S0423">do you not shop around in <trunc>o</trunc>other kind of similar shops?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0421">well I think Holland and Barrett</u>
<u n="220" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that type of thing</u>
<u n="221" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it's a good one cos you can also order online and they have a points system erm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0423">they can be quite dear some of their stuff though I've seen</u>
<u n="223" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but they have good sales sometimes</u>
<u n="224" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah when they have offers on</u>
<u n="225" who="S0421">you can get some of the Holland and Barrett stuff in supermarkets but it was like Holland and Barrett's who <trunc>j</trunc> introduced me to it erm and I saw</u>
<u n="226" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh right</unclear></u>
<u n="227" who="S0421">I saw some Holland and Barrett stuff in TK Maxx like reduced ones</u>
<u n="228" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose erm <pause dur="short"/> if you wanted pure like herbal infusions rather than mixed with tea you could probably look on I bet online you can get something <unclear/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know but who am I buying it from online? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0423">well no you <trunc>ca</trunc> you you can generally you can you know it's reputable company</u>
<u n="231" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah if it is but there's</u>
<u n="232" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0423">and it's just like stuff sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0421" trans="overlap">growing herbs in their garden <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0421">yeah but you can buy loose herbs sometimes at the supermarket as well</u>
<u n="238" who="S0423">yeah but you don't <trunc>oft</trunc> you maybe things like mint but not peppermint</u>
<u n="239" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0423">you you wouldn't really come across chamomile would you?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0421">yeah do you drink peppermint tea? that's supposed to be erm good for irritable bowel syndrome</u>
<u n="242" who="S0423">oh is it?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0421">that's why I got some</u>
<u n="244" who="S0423">yeah I don't I don't drink it often I got some er <pause dur="short"/> as I was coming back when I come back home drinking ordinary tea</u>
<u n="245" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0423">I thought oh I'll get a bit of a mixture so there's one that I I used to drink quite a lot lemon and ginger cos</u>
<u n="247" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I really like ginger</u>
<u n="249" who="S0421">yeah we've got that</u>
<u n="250" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so so and I usually add some honey to it and it's really good if you if I have a cold or something like that and add some lemon extra lemon to it honey and <trunc>s</trunc> erm then I like flavours and that so then I <pause dur="short"/> and no I like peppermint so <pause dur="short"/> when I was working with this Arabic bloke he erm <pause dur="short"/> we went out for a drink and he said oh I'll have a peppermint so I said oh I'll try it used to have it and it was quite common in er <anon type="place"/> er so I quite enjoyed it the peppermint and it's it's good for the digestive system</u>
<u n="251" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0423">isn't it?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that's why it's</u>
<u n="254" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's good for after a meal</u>
<u n="255" who="S0421">it's good for irritable bowel as well</u>
<u n="256" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0421">and it's also a natural antispasmodic</u>
<u n="258" who="S0423">I don't think I generally get spasms <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0421">is er that well that's what my irritable bowel syndrome is</u>
<u n="260" who="S0423">oh is it?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't know if yours is different</u>
<u n="262" who="S0423">oh I don't</u>
<u n="263" who="S0421" trans="overlap">if yours is like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I've never really looked into it was just told like</u>
<u n="265" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="266" who="S0423" trans="overlap">by a doctor once that you've got it and I've never looked up</u>
<u n="267" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no yeah well look my doctor was</u>
<u n="268" who="S0423">what it's about or what it is</u>
<u n="269" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I really liked my doctor in <anon type="place"/> she was really good and she always like explained stuff to me as well</u>
<u n="270" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right I remember you had pains in your stomach didn't you?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0423">last time when we were going to Scotland</u>
<u n="273" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that's what it is</u>
<u n="274" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that time or</u>
<u n="275" who="S0421">no it was in</u>
<u n="276" who="S0423" trans="overlap">was that going to Rome last year?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0421" trans="overlap">Italy yeah and we bought those like antacids but obviously they didn't work</u>
<u n="278" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="279" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but yeah that's what it is it's er</u>
<u n="280" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and I got tablets and they're antispasmodic tablets</u>
<u n="282" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="283" who="S0421">which is what stops it because they're the pain I don't know if it if you're like yours might yours might be caused by food or whatever but the pain</u>
<u n="284" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think it is probably your certain foods yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0421">but the pain's caused by like the the muscles in your stomach like spasm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="287" who="S0421">and which is why it hurts and it it it's it's also caused by like erm I think the gas gets trapped but it's cos of these spasms</u>
<u n="288" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="289" who="S0421" trans="overlap">or something so it might the tablets I was taking they're antispasmodic ones and erm peppermint's a natural antispasmodic and it's quite it I dunno it's not it doesn't work as well as the tablets do but I think it does generally</u>
<u n="290" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it helps to soothe it yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0423">yeah I I'm <pause dur="short"/> pretty good it really erm helps not to have wheat things but then you know I've really cut down on the bread I very rarely have it but then when I do <pause dur="short"/> like now if I've got bread if I go back to eat bread or have much of wheat stuff</u>
<u n="293" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0423" trans="overlap">then you know that you over a few days if I have to buy a lot of that kind of <pause dur="short"/> wheat based food I'll feel like I've been my stomach's kicked it's like a pain like really bloated and it's like a really sore kind of pain</u>
<u n="295" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0423" trans="overlap">not like a pain like a stomach ache</u>
<u n="297" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is that was yours is like?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0421">er mine well cos I remember going to the doctor's and she was like what kind of pain and in er is it? is it? and she gave me a list of all different ones and I'm like well it can be any one of those <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and she's like whereabouts is it? and I'm like well it can be here or it can be here or it can be here and you know like when you go to the doctor's and you've and she just kind of like you feel a bit like I don't really have an answer for you because it like cos it was it can be all sorts of different pain and it can be anywhere</u>
<u n="302" who="S0423">yeah it's hard to describe</u>
<u n="303" who="S0421" trans="overlap">on my stomach it can be anywhere and erm sometimes and I'm like yeah sometimes it's stabbing sometimes it's achy sometimes it's throbbing like I was like it changes</u>
<u n="304" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0421">erm and she was like oh right yeah most people who come in here with irritable bowel like have this similar so then she <pause dur="short"/> like er like pressed on my stomach and stuff and she's like yeah it's probably that if the tablets work then it will be but then if the tablets didn't work then I'd have to come back but the tablets did work</u>
<u n="306" who="S0423">and have you never had to take them again? have you not had a problem since?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0421">er no I've still got some</u>
<u n="308" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but the way I take them is erm like the way she told me to take them is that I don't take them constantly it's like when when it hurts I'll take them for like a couple of days and it'll stop and then it won't hurt again for weeks</u>
<u n="310" who="S0423">oh right that's good news then</u>
<u n="311" who="S0421">erm because on the tablets it says they're not to be taken for a long period of time but I think that's if you're taking them like daily</u>
<u n="312" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a lot</u>
<u n="314" who="S0423">yeah it's not good to be I wouldn't want to be taking medication every day for anything so</u>
<u n="315" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it's erm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0423"><unclear>it's good that yours is that</unclear></u>
<u n="317" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and I looked up online as well and erm it's quite common if you've got it for it to kind of fluctuate and not to have it for ages and then just come on and then some people say the might take them for a week like a few a week or something and then it'll go away again</u>
<u n="318" who="S0423">and</u>
<u n="319" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="320" who="S0423">did she not tell you about food what foods to avoid or anything?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0421">er well</u>
<u n="322" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>what food</unclear></u>
<u n="323" who="S0421" trans="overlap">for everybody is different and</u>
<u n="324" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh right</unclear></u>
<u n="325" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't think mine's food related at all</u>
<u n="326" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="327" who="S0421" trans="overlap">erm because</u>
<u n="328" who="S0423">could it be brought on by stress?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0421">yeah well it's for some people it's like a psychological thing</u>
<u n="330" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="331" who="S0421">er like she didn't offer like what it might have been caused by because as as well since the tablets worked</u>
<u n="332" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0421">erm <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>suppo</trunc> and I said I'd not noticed if it was a certain time of day or after eating or anything</u>
<u n="334" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0421">and some people say that like really random foods like they they make it really bad for them so</u>
<u n="336" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="337" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they don't eat them but I think in general if I'm was gonna avoid something it would be spicy food cos whenever I've eaten anything spicy it's hurt</u>
<u n="338" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0421">but not necessarily like it's not always caused by it's like cos sometimes it would be like caused by whatever I don't know erm or sometimes like fried food I try to avoid like with oil</u>
<u n="340" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0421">and that that's quite a common complaint for most people but then for some people they're like randomly saying like oh yeah I don't eat broccoli or like er lemons <vocal desc="laugh"/> or I dunno like Weetabix because they all like</u>
<u n="342" who="S0423">well people they just have certain foods disagree with them</u>
<u n="343" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like and that's something <unclear>people have to avoid</unclear></u>
<u n="345" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and then other people are like oh no I find that helps me but I can't eat whatever</u>
<u n="346" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0421">but I've not really noticed the food cos sometimes I'll eat something and I'll be like oh I can eat that my stomach didn't hurt afterwards and then I'll eat it again and my stomach'll start hurting and I'll be like so can I eat it or can't I?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and I don't think it's it's it's not food related so</u>
<u n="350" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0421">but some people just get it like it's not no not necessarily like stress or anything some people just have it and then they have it for years and years and years and they don't really know what causes it</u>
<u n="352" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0421">cos there's no abnormalities within the digestive system that would cause it</u>
<u n="354" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0421">which is why they think it might be like some kind of psychological thing but it's not necessarily caused by stress it's like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="356" who="S0423">could be some one of these modern diseases is it?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0421">I don't really know but like no one can really like online on like the NHS and stuff that I look and then I look on forums and stuff where people were talking about it but someone was like yeah I start cos it it's most commonly starts when you're about like I dunno this age if you're gonna have it <pause dur="short"/> or for you</u>
<u n="358" who="S0423" trans="overlap">commonly starts when?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's probably different er like when you're quite young like</u>
<u n="360" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="361" who="S0421">this kind of age</u>
<u n="362" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0421" trans="overlap">when I got it but yours is probably different cos it's like wheat probably yours</u>
<u n="364" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0421">erm and someone said on one of these forums that they they got it when they were quite young I don't know like twenty or something and they've had it for twenty years or something they're like forty now</u>
<u n="366" who="S0423">uhu</u>
<u n="367" who="S0421">and they said it's a real pain <pause dur="short"/> but for some people it's much worse than what I have I'm like I'm really</u>
<u n="368" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0421">I'm really glad that mine's not like that</u>
<u n="370" who="S0423">you er you just have to manage it I suppose I mean for years I tend not to do much about stuff and I've just ignored it and then eventually it becomes so bad that I think I must I need to change things to try to improve this and the the difference it makes when I cut out bread and things like that</u>
<u n="371" who="S0421">some people are <unclear>writing</unclear> on it</u>
<u n="372" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's a massive difference</u>
<u n="373" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because er what I get is like it's not like it's <trunc>ne</trunc> it's never been pain where I've been like ah it's just kind of a bit of a discomfort for me</u>
<u n="374" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well mine's like mine's kind of it's like a er sometimes my ribs and just like an aching as though I were bruised kind of</u>
<u n="375" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0423">that you just don't feel like you say it's very uncomfortable</u>
<u n="377" who="S0421">or like I don't know sometimes it it will be quite like if it's if it's if it's quite bad one day it's never to the extent where I'm kind of like oh I'm gonna stay in bed all day but it will hurt quite a bit</u>
<u n="378" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0421">erm but some people are like yeah some days I'm just in agony and I'm in bed and I thought and these are the people who've kind of gone to the hospital as or for like tests cos obviously it's really bad and they think they're and even the doctors were kind of like oh you know it might not be irritable bowel <trunc>co</trunc> if it's hurting this much and the medication they gave them isn't working and things and er they've had all sorts of tests and scans and everything and <trunc>nothi</trunc> everything's come back that they're all fine so it's just irritable bowel that's what it's got to got to be and they're just sometimes they have to like stay in bed for a day or something</u>
<u n="380" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="381" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and I'm just like well that's unfortunate</u>
<u n="382" who="S0423">so for you it's not that bad is it for us?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0423">when but did you move last year as well while we went on holiday like this? when you</u>
<u n="385" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0423" trans="overlap">back and the house was the house move was done?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0423">well you weren't</u>
<u n="389" who="S0421">I didn't move</u>
<u n="390" who="S0423">you hadn't moved</u>
<u n="391" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0423" trans="overlap">had you that time?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah and I came back</u>
<u n="394" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="395" who="S0421">and I just came back to the other house</u>
<u n="396" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the other house yeah <pause dur="long"/> was it where was that? was it the one in <anon type="place"/> have you been there about a year have you?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0423">doesn't seem that long does it?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0421">yeah it's that one <pause dur="short"/> about a year <pause dur="short"/> cos we moved cos we were in <anon type="place"/> for a year for my first year at college and then we moved back to the <anon type="place"/> one and then now we've sold that one</u>
<u n="400" who="S0423">and has your grandad been over since that move?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="402" who="S0423">he's not been over for a year has he?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0421">no he went home at some point</u>
<u n="404" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="405" who="S0421">no yeah I'm not sure when he came back but you know he's not <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's not been here that long</u>
<u n="406" who="S0423">so your gran will probably go back when the house is done and</u>
<u n="407" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0423">and meanwhile <unclear>will stay</unclear> will she?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0423">so did he like his other presents?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0423">yeah? what else did you get him again?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0421">I got him those truffles the fudge and those chocolate covered almonds</u>
<u n="414" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="415" who="S0421">it's grandma's birthday soon</u>
<u n="416" who="S0423">is it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0421">yeah I might see if there's something for her in Cornwall</u>
<u n="418" who="S0423">are you gonna take her for a curry as well?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0421">no because well by that by the time it's her birthday I don't know mammy could potentially even be in the hospital</u>
<u n="420" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="long"/> cos I'll get them I usually get them a magnet wherever I go but I might see if there's something else that I could get her</u>
<u n="421" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0423">well if your grandad likes fudge and that kind of thing I think it's a it's a Cornish fudge</u>
<u n="423" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I think they have some yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0421">my friend used to go to Devon on her holidays and she always used to bring back this like chocolate fudge</u>
<u n="425" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0421">and it was so nice like I used to I was eating it and I was just like really nice and I wouldn't wanna eat it because I wouldn't know where I couldn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> I couldn't buy it anywhere else <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0423">you could bring back some clotted cream <pause dur="short"/> for your grandma to try <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know if she'd want any <pause dur="short"/> it was funny</u>
<u n="429" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well she bakes plenty of cakes but she doesn't eat them really does she?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0421">yeah it was funny we were at that Indian and she was like how do you think they make this? and I was like erm and mammy's like I I don't think you'll be able to make this at home like</u>
<u n="431" who="S0423">why?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well well she'd have to</u>
<u n="433" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's only lentils</u>
<u n="434" who="S0421">no it was like curry and like and she'd wanna <trunc>ma</trunc> she was like wanting to make all these curries now and like</u>
<u n="435" who="S0423">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0421">erm not it wasn't just lentils you know it was like a lentil curry with chicken and like potatoes and everything</u>
<u n="437" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's easy enough to make curry</u>
<u n="438" who="S0421">I know yeah but would she be able to make that one? because if she where</u>
<u n="439" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well if she looked up a name online and got the recipe</u>
<u n="440" who="S0421" trans="overlap">she <trunc>ha</trunc> she has like this obsession I know but whenever you make it like you'd have to buy all these special Indian spices and everything like</u>
<u n="441" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well <trunc>th</trunc>they're not special you can get spices anywhere can't you?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0421">well not all of them because some of my friends at college</u>
<u n="443" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0421">erm they were cos like they they were I don't know if they were Indian but erm they were from that part of the world and they were saying</u>
<u n="445" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that they go to like the Indian supermarkets and things</u>
<u n="447" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's what I mean yeah while you while you were over here if your grandma wanted any spices there's a big Indian</u>
<u n="448" who="S0421">yeah well we'd have to go there</u>
<u n="449" who="S0423" trans="overlap">supermarket <unclear>in Asda</unclear></u>
<u n="450" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and then like buy them and things</u>
<u n="451" who="S0423">yeah? and?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0421">and it's a bit of a it's like a a big pain isn't it?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's only fifteen minutes down the road</u>
<u n="454" who="S0421">it's not like like you can just go to like Sainsbury's and buy like thyme and stuff</u>
<u n="455" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well Sainsbury's is probably as far as the other place</u>
<u n="456" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0423">so it's a fifteen minute drive</u>
<u n="458" who="S0421">and like she</u>
<u n="459" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and you go in the shop and get what you want</u>
<u n="460" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you'd just buy all this stuff and you just make like one curry with it it's just no</u>
<u n="461" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well no you you'll have the stuff then you can you can do other stuff with it if you have it there</u>
<u n="462" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0423">if she's interested you should get some spices you could bring them back</u>
<u n="464" who="S0421">she just has this obsession with whenever we go anywhere to eat anything or if we buy anything to eat that she's not made she's like I wonder how they make this and she's like looking it up and trying to make it but whenever she makes it it's never the same because</u>
<u n="465" who="S0423">well <trunc>wha</trunc> <trunc>wha</trunc> why what other places?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0421" trans="overlap">anything <trunc>absol</trunc></u>
<u n="467" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I didn't know you took her out to eat much</u>
<u n="468" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well we don't but if we even buy something from the shop</u>
<u n="469" who="S0423">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0421">and we're eating at home she's like I can make this and then the next day she'll be making it and I'm just <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="471" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well I think that's good</u>
<u n="472" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0423">that's really good that she does that</u>
<u n="474" who="S0421">oh I remember er it was something like I don't know we went to McDonald's and I had those like cheese dip things like cheese dippers where you dip it in the sauce and it's like fried cheese and she's like oh I bet I could make these and we went home and we were literally we'd stopped off at McDonald's cos we out and I had</u>
<u n="475" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0421" trans="overlap">these cheese dippers got home and within the next few hours grandma was like in the kitchen</u>
<u n="477" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0421">making <trunc>st</trunc> do you want some <trunc>chee</trunc>? and I'm like I've just eaten them at McDonald's</u>
<u n="479" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0421">I don't want more <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos she's like she</u>
<u n="481" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh so does she like cheese <trunc>d</trunc> erm wrapped in they're coated in breadcrumbs?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0421">yeah like</u>
<u n="483" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and fried</u>
<u n="484" who="S0421">those mozzarella dipper things</u>
<u n="485" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0421">whatever they are erm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0423">yeah it's quite a famous Italian thing only they do their version with the</u>
<u n="488" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0423"><unclear>quite a number</unclear> the Italian <unclear/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it's like anything like absolutely anything if I'm enjoying some kind of food she's like oh I'm going to make this and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says she enjoys</u>
<u n="491" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="492" who="S0421" trans="overlap">she enjoys my cooking as well it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> she wants to beat everybody it's funny <vocal desc="laugh"/> she's like or <trunc>mu</trunc> and mammy bought me a reduced sandwich from the shop once and I I really really like shop bought sandwiches and I was like mm and grandma was like what's in this sandwich to make it so good?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0421">I bet I could make you one of these sandwiches</u>
<u n="495" who="S0423">and what was in it?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0421">I don't know I don't know what it was it was like some kind of</u>
<u n="497" who="S0423" trans="overlap">did she not make you one?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0421">no she didn't in the end because it didn't have like the all the ingredients and everything on cos it was a sandwich so <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> and this cake that we always bought it's called Almondy <pause dur="short"/> and it's</u>
<u n="499" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh is it Hungarian?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0421">no it's from we we always bought it in Aldi</u>
<u n="501" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Lidl's</u>
<u n="502" who="S0421">or Lidl or Aldi and it's from like I dunno Sweden? or like</u>
<u n="503" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="504" who="S0421" trans="overlap">one of these countries and erm it's really nice and we always used to buy it and grandma was like wanting to make it and we were like yeah you can if you want if you can make it because it's probably gonna be nicer if you make it rather than buying it cos it was a frozen one <pause dur="short"/> erm but the recipe for it is like nowhere on the internet everybody's like discussing it like</u>
<u n="505" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="506" who="S0421">how do you think you can make it but it's like a secret recipe?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0423">oh right has she tried?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0421">she didn't in the end but she was going to but then we thought it's probably not gonna we have no idea what's going in it so <vocal desc="laugh"/> it might not be nice</u>
<u n="509" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but your grandma she's good at baking so she would have an idea wouldn't she of</u>
<u n="510" who="S0421">well you see she does she's she has an idea but whenever she does have an idea and she makes it it's usually not as nice it just it just doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> cos she's like I bet I know what's in this but it it's it's not it's not quite right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0423">I think it's time we had some of that chocolate don't you?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> see it's good we bought it</u>
<u n="513" who="S0423">well I wouldn't want it but it's there</u>
<u n="514" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0423">and it keeps looking at me going</u>
<u n="516" who="S0421">Marvellous Creations that ice cream was nice wasn't it? have you eaten it?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0423">thought it was lovely that yeah it was that</u>
<u n="520" who="S0421">do you want a whole row? <pause dur="short"/> oh it's melting <pause dur="short"/> ah ah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0421">well it's a funny shape that's why I couldn't break</u>
<u n="523" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well go on then I'll have that oh I thought you'd give me a whole one</u>
<u n="524" who="S0421">do you want it? there you go</u>
<u n="525" who="S0423">no I'd better not <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a little bit more</u>
<u n="526" who="S0421">but I've bitten it now</u>
<u n="527" who="S0423">oh doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/> well I was gonna <unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0423">it's all over my hand look at it</u>
<u n="530" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> it's all over my this</u>
<u n="531" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's all over the steering wheel</u>
<u n="532" who="S0421" trans="overlap">this <vocal desc="laugh"/> always happens when we go on our holidays it's like get the chocolate and it's all like melting in the glove compartment <pause dur="short"/> and it's not even that warm it's erm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0423">we've only just bought it now</u>
<u n="534" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0423">must have been melting in the shop</u>
<u n="536" who="S0421">they should keep it in the fridge</u>
<u n="537" who="S0423">we'd better eat it all now before it melts some more</u>
<u n="538" who="S0421">yeah I don't think I could eat it all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0423">I need one of these <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/> horse show <pause dur="short"/> great family day out <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> park <anon type="place"/> that's where <anon type="place"/> house is isn't it?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0423">I think so is that where it is?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0421">must be I think it is <anon type="place"/> house</u>
<u n="543" who="S0423" trans="overlap">where the horse show is?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0421">is very nice it's in <anon type="place"/> park</u>
<u n="545" who="S0423">the horse show is?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0421">yeah and I'm guessing that's where <anon type="place"/> house is as well</u>
<u n="547" who="S0423">that's not <anon type="place"/> though it's</u>
<u n="548" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0423">mm?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0421">where?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0421">that's where <anon type="place"/> park is</u>
<u n="553" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="554" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think that's where <anon type="place"/> house is <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0423">no I'm not far from there now</u>
<u n="556" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="557" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0421">yeah <anon type="place"/> house is very nice</u>
<u n="559" who="S0423">erm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0423">I thought you still had the chocolate in your hand I was gonna have a little bit more <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> it's not as nice as <anon type="place"/> house</u>
<u n="562" who="S0421">do you know I was just thinking of <anon type="place"/>? because erm on Facebook it came up that one of my friends from college she was at <anon type="place"/> house</u>
<u n="563" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0421">and I was like I've been to <anon type="place"/> house it was ages ago that we went there</u>
<u n="565" who="S0423">it was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0421">mm <anon type="place"/>'s a a little bit big though</u>
<u n="567" who="S0423">what for your</u>
<u n="568" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0423">just for your living standards?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0421">yeah it's it's a little bit big I think <anon type="place"/> was a bit smaller <pause dur="short"/> it was still big <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0423">yeah I've seen the photos that your mammy took</u>
<u n="572" who="S0421">there's this erm <pause dur="short"/> page on Facebook that I found and it's called Victorian Houses and every day they post like these houses these Victorian houses and I'm like looking at them like oh they're so nice</u>
<u n="573" who="S0423">yeah but it costs a lot of money for the upkeep if you're thinking of buying one</u>
<u n="574" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm some of them aren't that big like they they look affordable <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="576" who="S0421">like you know like not kind of like crazy</u>
<u n="577" who="S0423">not like stately home cost</u>
<u n="578" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah they're like nice they're like big houses but</u>
<u n="579" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0421">like say like not affordable affordable but kind of like within the kind of if you've got a lot of money you could probably buy one</u>
<u n="581" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> right it's a long way in a straight line now</u>
<u n="582" who="S0421">mm I remember when mammy was looking for houses like when we were buying this one and I was sat next to her on my laptop cos she was on hers looking for like houses and I was on mine looking at castles for sale <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like oh</u>
<u n="583" who="S0423" trans="overlap">bet she was surprised at what you were looking at</u>
<u n="584" who="S0421">I was like oh look at this castle that there's for sale in the south of France</u>
<u n="585" who="S0423">they're meant to be a good price in the south of France</u>
<u n="586" who="S0421">yeah the castles in France like there was</u>
<u n="587" who="S0423" trans="overlap">probably be out of mammy's budget though</u>
<u n="588" who="S0421">yeah they're not they're supposed to be er quite they're supposed to be better prices in France for castles than like over here <pause dur="short"/> but there were some really big ones and I was like no that's not affordable but then again for the size of it it was probably a good price but</u>
<u n="589" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0421">I don't really I'm not really in the know <trunc>wha</trunc> of how expensive castles are</u>
<u n="591" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well I think you can get something reasonable prices in Scotland as well you know small ones</u>
<u n="592" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0423">cos some of them are just like a big house in the style of a castle</u>
<u n="594" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0423">you know <pause dur="long"/> I mean the bigger ones again they're like having a big stately home they're <trunc>pr</trunc> very pricey to</u>
<u n="596" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0423">to keep it in good condition and run it it's a</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="598" who="S0421">all that money people used to have</u>
<u n="599" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> well yeah some of these stately homes like Chatsworth house that's why they have to open it up to the public</u>
<u n="600" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos they can't afford to</u>
<u n="602" who="S0421">I can't believe that they</u>
<u n="603" who="S0423" trans="overlap">keep it</u>
<u n="604" who="S0421" trans="overlap">could afford to keep it once though</u>
<u n="605" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's yeah they used to <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose the rich <pause dur="short"/> when you think in Britain you had all the colonies and</u>
<u n="606" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it was a very rich country well I suppose we still are but I think individual wealth was even more so then cos the rich were</u>
<u n="608" who="S0421">oh yeah that</u>
<u n="609" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there was a lot more poor who had nothing <unclear/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the poor were in like the workhouses weren't they?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0423">mm and the rich just had phenomenal wealth didn't they?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0423">they'd have servants they had everything some of those houses <pause dur="long"/> oh traffic <pause dur="short"/> that's one thing I wasn't thinking of traffic <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0421">imagine if you lived in Cornwall and you wanted to go to your holidays to Scotland</u>
<u n="615" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0423">be a long drive wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0421">you'd probably fly wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0421">or you'd have to stop off somewhere for the night</u>
<u n="621" who="S0423">well you could do it in one day</u>
<u n="622" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0423">like couldn't you? you wouldn't have to stop overnight it depends on I mean your grandad drove didn't he? from Slovakia to London</u>
<u n="624" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0423">I don't know if he even stopped</u>
<u n="626" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0423">those houses are nice <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0421">it's cool that isn't it? that you're on the erm if you're on the continent you can just drive to all these different countries</u>
<u n="629" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/> yeah we have to get across the water being an island</u>
<u n="630" who="S0421">although it's just as well really because erm <pause dur="short"/> all the er immigration problems that Calais has <pause dur="short"/> they'd all be coming over to us <vocal desc="laugh"/> if we were attached we'd be like overflowing</u>
<u n="631" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0421">cos Calais is overflowing and France it's like please help us</u>
<u n="633" who="S0423">I don't understand why erm <pause dur="short"/> once they're in France I know quite a lot of <trunc>y</trunc>you hear them interviewed you know these</u>
<u n="634" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0423">the refugees there's a lot of them arriving in Italy isn't there? on boats</u>
<u n="636" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> a lot of them are dying crossing have you seen it on the news?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0421">not recently</u>
<u n="639" who="S0423">oh right have you heard about it though yeah?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0423">it's the big thing at the moment <pause dur="short"/> and quite a lot of them say oh I want to go to England and some there's quite a lot are saying Germany as well</u>
<u n="642" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="643" who="S0423">but I don't understand why erm why do the get to France and want to go to England because</u>
<u n="644" who="S0421">maybe they're</u>
<u n="645" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what's wrong with staying in France?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think maybe the help they get isn't as good</u>
<u n="647" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0421">I don't think they have a</u>
<u n="649" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think that France have a good benefits system don't they?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0421">yeah but I don't know if it's different for the immigrants like for French citizens</u>
<u n="651" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0421">but I don't know if like how they can get citizenship and stuff I think it's quite hard and then until they've got that I don't think they get much help</u>
<u n="653" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0421">cos you like see them like making camps for themselves like in the wilderness or not the <trunc>wildern</trunc> like the</u>
<u n="655" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what Calais? in the wilderness</u>
<u n="656" who="S0421">no in France</u>
<u n="657" who="S0423">I know yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well it's not it's not wilderness but they're like just</u>
<u n="659" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I know you see them</u>
<u n="660" who="S0421" trans="overlap">camping out on their own</u>
<u n="661" who="S0423" trans="overlap">on er just er some rough land</u>
<u n="662" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that that's not used and but it it'll be in the town though on the outskirts</u>
<u n="664" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or something</u>
<u n="666" who="S0421">it's because also we didn't sign that agreement so I mean like if even if we were attached if we'd not</u>
<u n="667" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what agreement?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0421">there was this agreement where erm I don't know what it was called but we learned about it in French and erm all pretty much all of Europe has signed it to say that you can travel</u>
<u n="669" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah well you have free borders yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0423">but <trunc>w</trunc> that's not the reason why they're there though if we'd have signed that then it would be <trunc>eas</trunc> even easier for them to come over wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0421">no like they they they're there because they can't come over because</u>
<u n="673" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we signed it so if we were attached they still wouldn't be able to come over but if we were attached you know if we weren't an island erm then erm</u>
<u n="675" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="676" who="S0421">then they it would probably be easier to get over the border you know what I mean? cos</u>
<u n="677" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0421">here it's like you have to get on a boat and like it's</u>
<u n="679" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0421">er</u>
<u n="681" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well no the agreement I'm thinking of is one where European citizens they don't need a passport do do they? they have freedom of movement</u>
<u n="682" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0423">across borders but we didn't sign up to that we still so that's why when we went to Italy we needed our passport</u>
<u n="684" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0423">erm but other European countries going from <trunc>Euro</trunc> from there around Europe they don't need to show</u>
<u n="686" who="S0421">really? because</u>
<u n="687" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the their passport</u>
<u n="688" who="S0421" trans="overlap">when we were crossing the border I'm not sure where we were I like Slovakia or Hungary or Romania or something like they came round to check passports</u>
<u n="689" who="S0423">well <trunc>th</trunc> maybe they yeah I don't know I don't know how it works well no they've</u>
<u n="690" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh well <trunc>may</trunc>maybe they have to check passports because they don't know where we're from we could have been from England</u>
<u n="691" who="S0423">yeah and I don't I don't know <trunc>whe</trunc>whether they er have signed up to the agreement cos they're quite new aren't they?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0423">Slovakia and Hungary and maybe it's the older ones er maybe western Europe or some <unclear/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> well yeah I don't know we didn't sign something <trunc>t</trunc> oh but maybe that's the reason they can't come over because obviously they won't have passports will they?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0423">well yeah but that won't make a difference though to the immigrants will it?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0421">so that might be the one that's why they can't come</u>
<u n="697" who="S0423">what?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0421">that's why they can't come over because they don't have a passport</u>
<u n="699" who="S0423">well</u>
<u n="700" who="S0421">that might be the agreement that I'm thinking of</u>
<u n="701" who="S0423">well no yeah that's no it's a different thing cos <trunc>immigra</trunc></u>
<u n="702" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="703" who="S0423">immigrants are or asylum seekers they have it's different laws for them isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> but I I think maybe once they're in in Europe say say they arrive in Italy</u>
<u n="704" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0423">and they've been checked and given</u>
<u n="706" who="S0421">yeah they can like travel</u>
<u n="707" who="S0423" trans="overlap">status as asylum seeker they can travel freely</u>
<u n="708" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but not to us</u>
<u n="709" who="S0423">I <trunc>thi</trunc> yeah I think maybe that's cos they have the status from say Italy</u>
<u n="710" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0423">so then they could get across the border to France if they had status but</u>
<u n="712" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but they're like so desperate you wanna see the stuff that people do to try and get over to England like it's not that good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="713" who="S0423">well <pause dur="short"/> you see women and they're carrying babies in those boats and you it's I don't know why it's</u>
<u n="714" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well why is the rest of Europe not good enough? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0423">it's a bit of a risk isn't it to?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0421">well <trunc>co</trunc> like I understand why they'd want to come to Europe</u>
<u n="717" who="S0423">oh you mean when they're trying to get on the lorries and that?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0423">yeah well people have died haven't they?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0423">er</u>
<u n="722" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like <trunc>Eur</trunc> once you're in Europe you're not you're you're okay really like compared to where you were before</u>
<u n="723" who="S0423">well exactly yeah it's er if you're gonna be <unclear/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but like no I wanna go to England</u>
<u n="725" who="S0423">I think for some reason it's just built up some kind of reputation</u>
<u n="726" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0423" trans="overlap">of the countries like it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because everybody always like hears about England like</u>
<u n="729" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0421" trans="overlap">or like go to England and everything'll be alright and then they can't get there and they're like no I must go to England</u>
<u n="731" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0421">in Japan <pause dur="short"/> I think their quota for immigrants that they take on per year is like fourteen asylum seekers</u>
<u n="733" who="S0423">fourteen?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="735" who="S0423">unbelievable isn't it?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0421">something like that</u>
<u n="737" who="S0423">I mean they probably have a well an attitude similar to a lot of people in this country in that well we're an island and</u>
<u n="738" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="739" who="S0423">we're overcrowded and I think</u>
<u n="740" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well I think Japan does have</u>
<u n="741" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Japan it does have a yes</u>
<u n="742" who="S0421" trans="overlap">quite a lot of yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0423">well I mean Japan like this country though there is plenty of space</u>
<u n="744" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it's concentrated in all the cities</u>
<u n="745" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like Tokyo is just like</u>
<u n="747" who="S0423">yeah but they have you know the countryside there's</u>
<u n="748" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0423">you can plenty of space for people but obviously not many people</u>
<u n="750" who="S0421">live there</u>
<u n="751" who="S0423"><trunc>s</trunc> go there it's the same here there's there's if you know look at</u>
<u n="752" who="S0421">yeah all the land</u>
<u n="753" who="S0423">you know the space available there is still plenty but <pause dur="short"/> I guess er there's no work in rural places is there?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0423" trans="overlap">except in the cities and that's like where everyone goes to the city</u>
<u n="756" who="S0421">but yeah it's like in Japan the population's like ninety-nine percent ethnic Japanese</u>
<u n="757" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0421">not many foreign people go over there <pause dur="short"/> to live permanently</u>
<u n="759" who="S0423">it it's it's unusual that isn't it? cos with it being a a a rich successful country</u>
<u n="760" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah maybe it's like the difference in culture though cos it's very hard to integrate yourself</u>
<u n="761" who="S0423">but there are quite a few westerners go and</u>
<u n="762" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0423">live and work over there don't they?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0421">yeah one percent <vocal desc="laugh"/> of their population they probably make up <pause dur="short"/> I mean so yeah that is quite a lot but it's not a massive number</u>
<u n="765" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it they don't really have I mean we've got er <pause dur="short"/> our erm history and so on with with colonising</u>
<u n="766" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we've got links to lots of countries</u>
<u n="768" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0423">that we've started in you know kind of allowed immigrants in for work and so on</u>
<u n="770" who="S0421">yeah that's why yeah</u>
<u n="771" who="S0423">I think Japan hasn't got that kind of history have they?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="773" who="S0423">and I mean it obviously they attract they have <unclear>upped er</unclear> expansion and so on <unclear>but when they</unclear> well it was the second world war not <unclear>the the look of</unclear> kind of integrating those people into their country they wanted to I guess keep separate I wonder if they're much more er <pause dur="short"/> racist over there</u>
<u n="774" who="S0421">they are apparently because well</u>
<u n="775" who="S0423" trans="overlap">maybe they're not if you're in your place you know if you're say a westerner or from another country</u>
<u n="776" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and you're working there but if you try to maybe they don't like you if you erm integrating into their society and way of life</u>
<u n="778" who="S0421">yeah I think if you're yeah if you're kind of like living there I think they don't mind if you're here for like if you're over there for like however many I don't know for like a while like some people go there for a few years or something then go home but erm I think my or someone who I I was speaking to in college I think it was her brother or like her cousin or something her is working in Japan</u>
<u n="779" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0421">and that he said that his experience has been quite like that they were <trunc>s</trunc> he's had quite a lot of racism towards him</u>
<u n="781" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0421">yeah I think he's a he he's <trunc>stud</trunc> he was studying to be erm it's really weird this he's studying to be erm a doctor <pause dur="short"/> over there</u>
<u n="783" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0421">but if he'd if he doesn't get to be a doctor he can use the qualifications he's got and be a lawyer instead <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what it doesn't make sense to be over there studying to be a doctor though why would you?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't know I think he he like learnt Japanese and everything and</u>
<u n="787" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well his Japanese would have to be amazing to be able</u>
<u n="788" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0423" trans="overlap">to be in medical practice wouldn't it? cos when you think of all the medical terminology</u>
<u n="790" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah he must be I don't know why some people want to don't they?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0421">I think he he I think he's like learnt I think he did like quite a lot of it over here but maybe he's just doing some of it in Japan for whatever reason</u>
<u n="793" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0421">I don't know I didn't speak to her that much but yeah that is what she said</u>
<u n="795" who="S0423">mm I saw something on the news erm not long ago they had a Miss Japan some kind of competition</u>
<u n="796" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="797" who="S0423">erm and er it was er the woman who won it her dad was her dad's a black American</u>
<u n="798" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="799" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and like the Japanese and</u>
<u n="800" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there was a big protest about it saying this person can't</u>
<u n="802" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0423">be Miss Japan cos they're not Japanese and saying they're not er but she was brought up in</u>
<u n="804" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0423" trans="overlap">er born</u>
<u n="806" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0423">I I think she might have been born and brought up in Japan and they were <trunc>t</trunc> still saying protesting she's not a Japanese person you know she's a <pause dur="short"/> a half black American</u>
<u n="808" who="S0421">but it's like I think it's just because such a high percentage of their population is Japanese so they're not used to</u>
<u n="809" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0421">like cos over here there's not that much racism <pause dur="short"/> because we're just so like diverse there's all sorts of people over here but er just imagine if like there was just all English people here it would be strange</u>
<u n="811" who="S0423">yeah you'd be going back to what it it was like</u>
<u n="812" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0423">at one stage here</u>
<u n="814" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0423">when immigration was introduced</u>
<u n="816" who="S0421">I mean I don't know how bad it is maybe there's a bit I I don't know but I suppose if it is bad it's not really noticeable because there's not many people to be racist to</u>
<u n="817" who="S0423">mm well like when my auntie come over in the sixties auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0423">do you remember auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="820" who="S0421">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0423">mam said that she came over to work auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm I think she was working in <anon type="place"/> and there used to be crowds of people standing outside saying going back shouting at people there must have been a lot of Irish working in the factory</u>
<u n="822" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0423">go back to Ireland</u>
<u n="824" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0423">so there was a lot of <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc> there's that poster that you used to see in in some like hotels and bed and breakfasts</u>
<u n="826" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah <trunc>n</trunc>no</u>
<u n="827" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no blacks no dogs</u>
<u n="828" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no blacks yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no Irish <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="830" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we did that in er GCSE history</u>
<u n="831" who="S0423">yeah so there was a lot of <trunc>ra</trunc> and there still is erm</u>
<u n="832" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and like how it was like segregated like that you'd have to use separate transport and <pause dur="short"/> shops and things</u>
<u n="833" who="S0423">in this country?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0421">I'm sure there was wasn't there?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="836" who="S0421">was that in America?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no that's America</u>
<u n="838" who="S0421">really? did they not do that over here?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0423">no there was never segregation</u>
<u n="840" who="S0421">was there not? or was it just America?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="843" who="S0423">or South Africa <pause dur="long"/> but there there are still many racist people in this country and still</u>
<u n="844" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah and I think it's got</u>
<u n="845" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's getting very much</u>
<u n="846" who="S0421">it's getting worse at the moment though</u>
<u n="847" who="S0423">well yeah but you don't</u>
<u n="848" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos well</u>
<u n="849" who="S0423" trans="overlap">even when I was at school you'd you'd now you don't it it's very rare</u>
<u n="850" who="S0421">yeah no one says it out loud really</u>
<u n="851" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like well yeah it's very rare and quite shocking when somebody openly says something very racist but when I was even when I was say your age it was openly</u>
<u n="852" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0423">er people would have</u>
<u n="854" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no like</u>
<u n="855" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no qualms about being openly racist</u>
<u n="856" who="S0421">people will say it like</u>
<u n="857" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but now it is</u>
<u n="858" who="S0421" trans="overlap">if if you're sat there</u>
<u n="859" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="860" who="S0421" trans="overlap">with like a couple of people someone might say something like quietly do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they would never say it in front of a group of er like a big group of people</u>
<u n="863" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0421">but like they would say it like if they know you and</u>
<u n="865" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="866" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I'd just kind of be like I never knew you were racist</u>
<u n="867" who="S0423">yeah so it is kept very much underground so there is still a lot of it exists but cos it is er I mean society's changed so much since I was kind of your age with regards er racism and <trunc>sexi</trunc>sexism</u>
<u n="868" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and people are always like</u>
<u n="869" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I'm not I'm not racist but and then they say <trunc>so</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah and they always <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0421">and then they say something and it's like <trunc>th</trunc>that kind of sounds like you might be racist <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0423">well when somebody starts a sentence with that</u>
<u n="874" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0423">you know it generally means well you you're probably about to say something racist anyway</u>
<u n="876" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="877" who="S0423">even though you don't think you are <pause dur="long"/> what shall we have next? a chocolate peanut or a Liquorice Allsort?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0421">oh I don't like Liquorice Allsorts</u>
<u n="879" who="S0423">oh do you not?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so you'll have to eat them all</u>
<u n="881" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh I'll have them</u>
<u n="882" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll have to eat them all no I don't like liquorice I always thought they looked really nice like Dolly Mixtures but then I always ate one and I was disappointed cos it had</u>
<u n="883" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh it's probably cos you were expecting it to be sweet and it has this other flavour</u>
<u n="884" who="S0421">well I just don't like liquorice in general <vocal desc="laugh"/> so <pause dur="short"/> it tastes like cough medicine <pause dur="short"/> I remember</u>
<u n="885" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>it does</unclear></u>
<u n="886" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I was getting some cough medicine once and the person in the shop was like do you like liquorice? cos if you do then you'll really like this and I'm oh no I hate liquorice and she's like oh you're just gonna have to take it then and I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> great <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0423">well most medicines don't taste particularly nice though</u>
<u n="888" who="S0421">Calpol does</u>
<u n="889" who="S0423">well <pause dur="short"/> for babies</u>
<u n="890" who="S0421">I've not had</u>
<u n="891" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="892" who="S0421" trans="overlap">Calpol in years</u>
<u n="893" who="S0423">do you miss the taste? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0421">it was nice but I mean I wouldn't eat it but and that red cough medicine with the teddy bear on it that was nice</u>
<u n="895" who="S0423">yeah I remember there was some medicine you had to take when you were ill and oh it it was absolutely impossible to get you to take it</u>
<u n="896" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0423">you'd scream and be wriggling around and</u>
<u n="898" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0423">moving your head and you just wouldn't take it so we had to go to the doctor and he give us a syringe and we had to put the medicine in the</u>
<u n="900" who="S0421">squirt</u>
<u n="901" who="S0423">syringe and squirt it into your mouth <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0423">so you couldn't er wriggle out but it it's amazing the strength of you when you're a baby</u>
<u n="904" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0423">that you and how much you didn't want this medicine</u>
<u n="906" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="907" who="S0423">you'd just squirm and wriggle</u>
<u n="908" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I mean you couldn't force it down to you on a spoon it just kept getting knocked out of the spoon because of the way you were moving around <pause dur="long"/> pet travel by road and air UK and Europe worldwide</u>
<u n="910" who="S0421">what pets are travelling in there?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0423">must be VIP pets</u>
<u n="912" who="S0421" trans="overlap">animal couriers <pause dur="short"/> is that like are they like delivering animals or are they like <trunc>tr</trunc>?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no they're pets they're people's pets</u>
<u n="914" who="S0421">where are they transporting them though?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0423">well say for instance somebody's coming from another country to relocate they</u>
<u n="916" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="917" who="S0423">they might it might be more comfortable than putting them in a cage or a</u>
<u n="918" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0423">and er</u>
<u n="920" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but they'd have to be in quarantine wouldn't they? if they're coming here</u>
<u n="921" who="S0423">yeah but it's it we I don't know what the agreement is now cos erm it always used to be you'd have to quarantine but I don't know how it works now there is a scheme I don't know whether it's it's when you're taking your pet out and you're bringing them back I don't know if they have to go through that now cos you know they're chipped</u>
<u n="922" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0423">and if they're registered and having injections and stuff and all that</u>
<u n="924" who="S0421">yeah then it should be alright I think</u>
<u n="925" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't know if there's a better way of doing it now</u>
<u n="926" who="S0421">I think if they if it's your pet and you take them out and you're bringing them back in I think it's okay if they've had the necessary injections</u>
<u n="927" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I think if you're bringing them over and they've not been checked and <unclear/></u>
<u n="928" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but if you're like moving from America to here</u>
<u n="929" who="S0423">yeah you probably have to</u>
<u n="930" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and then it's an American animal</u>
<u n="931" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0421">it would have to be quarantined</u>
<u n="933" who="S0423">it's I'm I'm not sure I did hear something about it cos people <trunc>ov</trunc> from over here they're going away to work and pets have to be in quarantine for six months I don't know if they could take it over</u>
<u n="934" who="S0421">yeah you can take over but then</u>
<u n="935" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or drop them off before you come back</u>
<u n="936" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="937" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but it would be six months in quarantine wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0423" trans="overlap">before they're allowed back in <pause dur="long"/> so I'm sure I heard something but I don't know <unclear/> some scheme so you don't have to do that now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="940" who="S0421">did all your new DVDs arrive?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0423">oh yeah they arrived within two days and I thought they'd be usually they're fairly quick on the normal post of with them</u>
<u n="942" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0423">and erm but then you know when it sent me the email cos when I when I said oh normal post they say it's three to five days</u>
<u n="944" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0423">so I thought at the latest it'll be the Saturday before I go away so I'll be okay</u>
<u n="946" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="947" who="S0423">but then it sent the email and it said <trunc>f</trunc> six to eight days</u>
<u n="948" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="949" who="S0423">will be the arrival date and if that's the nearest day</u>
<u n="950" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they usually just say that to just keep themselves save in case the post is late</u>
<u n="951" who="S0423">yeah and then er well I thought it would be Royal Mail but it wasn't so it arrived like two days after I ordered it which was great</u>
<u n="952" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="953" who="S0423">and erm well I got in back in from work I was working in the evening and erm then there was a piece of paper waiting saying you know and I thought oh it must be the from the post office saying it's at the post office</u>
<u n="954" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="S0423">and I picked it up and it's like Amazon courier or something and it's like it's</u>
<u n="956" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0423">and says your your parcel and then it's got options different options</u>
<u n="958" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0423">and it's just written in black bin</u>
<u n="960" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="961" who="S0423">and I thought oh right okay they've put it in the black bin which is where the all the bottles and things are</u>
<u n="962" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="963" who="S0423">so I thought that's not too bad it's out of sight</u>
<u n="964" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it's a good idea yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and it's safe enough and then I went out and it was raining out with a</u>
<u n="966" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="967" who="S0423">light rain and it was on top of the black bin in a cardboard box</u>
<u n="968" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="969" who="S0423">I thought I can't believe they'd just leave it</u>
<u n="970" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0423"><unclear>that was unbelievable</unclear></u>
<u n="972" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they they leave <trunc>i</trunc> they used to leave it in our porch like tucked around the side</u>
<u n="973" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0421">or oh do you know what they did once? it's good it was only books because erm it said where it was and they said over in the in the garden and we had like a big fence and they'd thrown it over the garden fence and it was in the garden</u>
<u n="975" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0421">but did you know that you know cos you can get Amazon Prime and it'll do next day delivery for you if you pay</u>
<u n="977" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0421" trans="overlap">every month? erm you used to have that didn't you? if you live in London and you've got Amazon Prime it'll deliver it in two hours there's an option</u>
<u n="979" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="980" who="S0421" trans="overlap">two hour delivery cos they must have</u>
<u n="981" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you have to pay more for that?</u>
<u n="982" who="S0421">I don't think so oh maybe maybe a bit but they that's what they must have the warehouse there somewhere</u>
<u n="983" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0421">mustn't they?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0423">must be it's er</u>
<u n="986" who="S0421">can you imagine that? two hour delivery like next day delivery is good but if it came in two hours</u>
<u n="987" who="S0423">you could be at home and get your book delivered read it and then say oh I feel I fancy another one</u>
<u n="988" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="989" who="S0423">order another one</u>
<u n="990" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and two hours later it'll be there for you</u>
<u n="992" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's good <pause dur="short"/> efficient</u>
<u n="993" who="S0423">yeah I think I went on that trial</u>
<u n="994" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0423" trans="overlap">to get it all in the stuff in time for Christmas and and I think I nearly forgot to cancel out of it</u>
<u n="996" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0423">I just remembered logged onto it and just cancelled at the last minute before they started charging me</u>
<u n="998" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I was on erm</u>
<u n="999" who="S0423">oh no you know I forgot to cancel</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0421">oh did you?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0423">but they the credit card cos I'm signed on to them with account and that fortunately the credit card they tried to use</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0423">it was er out of date so they couldn't charge me</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0423">so then I just cancelled it so</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0421">I saw something <pause dur="short"/> online about like Amazon Prime for students and I don't know if it's discounted or if it was just like a free trial if you're a student or something but I didn't look at it I think I had to pay something so I was like no</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0421">I won't bother I don't use Amazon as much as I used to</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0423">why not? are you not buying books?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0421">well I haven't been lately but I've been I've been looking and I don't like I used to buy from Amazon themselves but now when I buy a book I buy from like the people who sell through Amazon cos they're cheaper like Amazon is not as <trunc>u</trunc> as cheap as it used to be</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right but you do it on their website</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0423" trans="overlap">type of yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0421">because I remember I used to get like a really big Amazon box just full of all the books</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0421" trans="overlap">from Amazon but now I get separate packages cos I order from separate people</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I <trunc>thou</trunc> I brought loads of DVDs there's big you know those er bag for life things?</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0423">I've got one of those bags full</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1021" who="S0423">although the Laurel and Hardy ones are</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0423" trans="overlap">filling half of that</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0421">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0423">and I I thought I had erm <pause dur="short"/> jurassic Park the second one I'm sure I had</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0421" trans="overlap">do you not?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but I just couldn't find it</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0421">ah</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0423">so I've got one and three but I I don't think <trunc>y</trunc> if you see the first one you don't really</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0423">some of the characters are in they they carry on</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0421" trans="overlap">are the dinosaurs</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0421">do the dinosaurs look real? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1035" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0421">do they?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0423">well the the the ones in the original the kind of it must be animatronics rather than CGI</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0423">I'm not sure I would imagine it would be so they they do look good whereas this last one was a CGI one</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0421" trans="overlap">did you see it online they create a Jurassic Jurassic park once to erm try and do some like <pause dur="short"/> studies or like some experiments on like DNA to create a dinosaur or something? and it like there was an article online and people were commenting like did he not learn anything from his own film? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1041" who="S0423">I don't think you can get DNA from anything would you from a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't know you I I don't think you could no I don't think <trunc>h</trunc>he's doing I think he wants to do it like put more research into like studies about like the bones and everything and like structure and I don't know</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0421">it's probably someone just romanticising it on the internet like they're gonna make a Jurassic park like and it's gonna kill us <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1045" who="S0423">yeah usually as it's on the internet there will be something somebody'll be</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1047" who="S0423">got the wrong end to it you he's probably funding research into a certain aspect or</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0423">you know <pause dur="long"/> but I brought some other some DVDs that I think I brought four and you didn't really want to watch them so</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0423">well I've brought them anyway</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1053" who="S0423">just in case</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0421">I think</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1056" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we could just watch Laurel and Hardy every day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1057" who="S0423">yeah I think we've got more than enough have you brought any?</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0421">no I don't know where they are</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0423">and I've brought some of them that I bought I'm not there is one or two I think you've watched but I'm not sure what you've watched and what you haven't so</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0421">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1061" who="S0423">we'll see they will have a supermarket if you see anything you like that like <pause dur="long"/> a nice thing to watch</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0421">well Laurel and Hardy is just the best so</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0423">I've watched them for a while</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0423">did you bring your one?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0421">I don't know I don't have a clue where do you know how long it took me to find some stuff that I've packed in my suitcase? literally it just I was searching for hours for things don't have a clue where it all is</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0423">so I suppose you can't unpack if your room's not ready yet</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0423">cos maybe by the time you get home it'll all be unpacked will it?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0421">I think some of it will be yeah like yeah most of it will probably it'll be unpacked but I'll probably have to rearrange it all because it'll just be <trunc>pa</trunc></u>
<u n="1071" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you need to get cupboards and wardrobes for your room?</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0421">well <pause dur="short"/> the removal people said my wardrobe wasn't very good quality so they didn't they didn't erm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0423">that's a bit cheeky</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well because we were like why did you not?</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what did they say? we're not moving this it's not <unclear>very good</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1076" who="S0421">no no they moved it and then they were like they didn't assemble it and usually they assemble it and we don't have the instructions anymore obviously</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0423">oh was it? what? they took it apart?</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0421">yeah yeah cos you have to cos it <trunc>i</trunc>it is rubbish quality but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0423">do they do that?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0421">well they took it apart and they always reassemble it cos if you move</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0423" trans="overlap">where did you buy it?</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0421">Tesco or somewhere or Argos or</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0421" trans="overlap">or something I dunno erm</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0423">and they said it's not very good quality so we're not putting it back together?</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah and they said you're probably better getting a new one</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0423">oh well your grandad could try and fix it</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0421">well yeah he was going to but I think cos mammy bought these like old wooden ones that that they she didn't have any room for so I think I might have those instead so it's like getting a new wardrobe but they're like old</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0421">cos I don't</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0423" trans="overlap">might be better <trunc>li</trunc> looking in Ikea</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0421">Ikea furniture's rubbish I've we've had stuff from Ikea before and it always fall especially wardrobes</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0423">I thought you had those big grey wardrobes they were good quite sturdy</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0421">yeah well some of them are and I think if you pay enough for them at Ikea but we've got these erm well they're not</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well there's a variety of prices for stuff there</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0421">yeah well if you get</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1098" who="S0421" trans="overlap">if you get if I'm gonna be buying the cheap ones then</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0423">there are some decent quality there though</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos my wardrobe is cheap and so is my desk and we've got rid of my desk <pause dur="short"/> cos that was always falling apart so I'm getting a new desk well it's not a new desk it's the desk that was in the computer room <pause dur="short"/> I think that might be from Ikea actually it's quite it's</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0423">yeah some of their stuff like</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0421" trans="overlap">good solid wood</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0423">some of the stuff is a bit pricier and better quality though and there's just a <trunc>ra</trunc>range of prices and quality aren't there?</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0421">yeah but if we'd been if we would have been buying something we would have looked at something cheaper but the ones we've got is they're like they're not they're not classed as antique but they're that kind of thing cos we bought they're quite old and they're like made from proper wood and everything so they should be fine</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0423">mm well I thought you were gonna get the light coloured wood for the house you know it's quite dark isn't it?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0421">yeah why were we gonna get light?</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0423">I thought she said that</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0423">I think I said to her are you gonna get wood like in the other house which is dark it's not as dark as that though</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0421">what the floorboards?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0421">yeah it is light wood it's not the pale one because</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0423">no</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0421">we don't really like that one cos it's like milky</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0421">so we got medium</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> are you having that through the house?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0421">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think we're having we might have the the lighter one downstairs cos it's cheaper <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1119" who="S0423">and where did you get that?</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0421">er B and Q I think?</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0423">oh right you should have looked in Ikea I <trunc>g</trunc> remember I got mine from there?</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0421">this was very cheap floor</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0423">was it?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0421">very cheap floor <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it was <pause dur="long"/> it was like ten pound a box or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1125" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1126" who="S0421">actually I think it was only that cheap because it was reduced so we thought we'd get the reduced one instead of the actual cheap one</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0423">ah right</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos it it came out the same price as the really cheap one</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0421">but it cos it was reduced so we thought it was probably better quality</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0423" trans="overlap">better quality</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0423">so you have you got enough to have it in your room as well?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0421">uhu</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0423">yeah it looks similar to mine in pattern it's just a bit darker yours I think mine's slightly lighter</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> see I think I have those wardrobes you've probably seen them they're like the the dark wooden ones</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0421">cos they're good quality <pause dur="short"/> probably better than the one I've got because it's like it's not even wood mine it's like mixed wood it's like wood mixed with whatever it is</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0423">you mean the Ikea one?</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0421">well I don't think it's from Ikea</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0423">I thought you meant the one that you're not keeping</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0421">yeah it's not from Ikea it's from Tesco or Argos</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh Tesco yeah they they tend to it's not necessarily wood some of these are they?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they're probably made from recycled paper and it's all</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0423">compressed and</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0421">that's it's <trunc>tha</trunc> yeah cos like my desk the drawers were always falling out and stuff erm <pause dur="short"/> so we we scrapped that and the wardrobe's made of I mean the wardrobe wasn't falling apart as such but the doors never really fit properly like <vocal desc="laugh"/> they were a bit you couldn't close them properly and stuff <pause dur="long"/> he's not got a plate a number plate that car</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> has he got one in the window? I think he has</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0423">or trade plates it should be on the outside of the car but they're like they just</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah they usually stick it on yeah</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0423">yeah I think it's I think I saw something like it</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos you can't really see it</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0423">yeah it's like a red or white colour</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like if he was doing something now and wanted his number</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you can't see it</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0423">well it's it's probably quite a it's a vehicle that's being delivered to somebody that they've bought</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0423">they call them trade plates and somebody's hired to somebody has a job just delivering cars</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0423">and they they would have these normally it is attached to the vehicle for the journey and the they they attach it's like a red and white plate</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0423">and I think you probably er apply for a licence so</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0421" trans="overlap">if it's your job to deliver cars so like would you drive there in that car and then how would you get back?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0423">I don't know what what they do to organise it or or I've never really met anyone who does it so I've er I guess they'd</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you'd think you'd have your company car and tow it wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0423">yeah they they would either use public transport or any <trunc>gar</trunc> or or you would hire a car at the other end</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0421">mm that would be a nightmare wouldn't it? you wouldn't think that would be very cheap for the company</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0423">well it all goes onto the cost of</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0423">whoever's buying the car I suppose or if if it's a big operation then you know you never know if they he then goes to whatever part of the country it's in and you go to pick up the next car to bring that back</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0423">you know you may not exactly be in the next in the same city but he's say then taking that down south then there might be a car that needs to come up north</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or south</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0423">so it might be a short journey on the train to the next car and then he brings it back home</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0423">it depends how it what <unclear/> I don't know</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0421">it's not a bad job really is it? <pause dur="long"/> quite easy</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0423">yeah I suppose you'd have to if you like driving then <pause dur="short"/> some people maybe enjoy driving jobs don't they? <pause dur="short"/> I guess the there would be you know like all jobs there are certain kind of pressures on you so again I'd say to</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0421">at a certain time</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you yeah well that needs to be there by this particular time they might have a time that it's got to be booked for cos then you've got to make it to this other place by that time and so then you might <trunc>y</trunc> get into traffic and I suppose there'll always you know there's gonna be delays sometimes when you're on the road so</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yeah you can't help it if there's loads of traffic</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0423">but well the the thing is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his job is driving so it's a</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0423">it is very very time er very much very important to kind of</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0423">keep the times right</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos er if you</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you know and he gets if you get back late to the depot they're complaining sometimes what</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0423" trans="overlap">where have you been? and you know sometimes the motorway could be shut or</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah and also if you're you can only drive for so many hours when you're driving those lorries can't you?</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0423">well yeah he's ran out of time sometimes and he's had to stay overnight somewhere</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0421">cos you have to stop you can't you just can't drive anymore</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah legally you</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0423">you'd erm it's very serious you cos if you're</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos you've got like a meter on your thing as well saying how long you've driven for haven't you?</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0423">yeah it's called a tachograph</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0423">so I think in the past it used to be you'd have to have something in your car you'd put it into a machine and it registers your time on a on a disk or something but now it's probably all digital now</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I would imagine <pause dur="short"/> and it is the driver's responsibility not to come and so if you go over the hours then you are accountable you lose your licence and have a fine and even worse <pause dur="long"/> which it it's a good thing to have because you know in the past before they had that it was drivers you know driving for far too long and they're falling asleep I mean you still get drivers falling asleep</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0423">and causing accidents and <pause dur="short"/> cos they can still I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sometimes he can work fifteen hours or something</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0423">which</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0421" trans="overlap">which is still a long time if you're like</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0423">yeah I think it's less than that for driving time but because he has to unload the vehicles</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0423">cos a lot of lorry drivers they they just sit in the</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0421">yeah they just drive</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0423" trans="overlap">lorry whiles somebody else unloads but <pause dur="short"/> the contracts his company has is that the drivers do all the unloading as well so once the vehicle's stopped it's not considering you as driving then</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0423">so even though he's still working erm it's not driving so it kind of stops the clock on his time</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well though do you think that's less for people who are carrying like hazardous liquids?</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0423">er</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0421" trans="overlap">do you think they can't drive for a long?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well probably not I mean I'd say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s is for erm <pause dur="short"/> fifteen hours sometimes he works but it it I don't think you can drive for that long</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0423">it is tighter restrictions but because he's unloading and stuff</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like that it kind of stops so I'm not quite sure what the restrictions are</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we got our washing machine and they rang us and they were like erm the delivery people were like oh yeah we're just gonna drop it wherever we wherever we park and we were like can you not bring it to the door for us at least even if you're not gonna bring it in?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0423">you're supposed to bring it in I'd insist on it</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0421">er they wouldn't bring it in they were like no we're just gonna leave it so they left it at the door</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0423">and who was that? what's that company?</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0421">it was just a it was a small er <anon type="place"/> place we bought it from</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0421">and they were like no we're just gonna drop it at the door we're not bringing it in and we're like well we want it right at the door then</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0423">I can't believe that</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0421">I know yeah</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's rubbish that I've never come across</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0421">but our washing machine's really good on the bright side</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0423">why what brand is it?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0421">AEG</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0421">yeah we got it for a good price because erm I think it's an older model</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like you know there's like <trunc>w</trunc> and we've got erm a five year guarantee on it</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0421">on all parts</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0423">that's good</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> manufacturer's warranty</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/> and was it the company you bought it off that delivered it?</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0421">yeah well I dunno their like delivery company whoever it is whoever they use</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0423">yeah cos you could complain to the company and say look whoever you're getting to deliver they just they weren't very cooperative <pause dur="short"/> I don't suppose it's gonna help you much though</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0421">no but it's alright <pause dur="long"/> yeah we were looking to get an AEG cooker as well because AEG is a good brand</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0421">but the AEG cookers are really expensive so we just</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I think all of their stuff probably is er</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah we were quite lucky with the washing machine</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0421">it was like the same price as other stuff so we got er a Hotpoint cooker</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0421">but the cooker's good as well</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0423">is it?</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0421">mm <pause dur="short"/> the person who's fitted it like the plumber</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0421">he said it was good as well</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you wouldn't wanna be getting erm he said he agreed cos we were looking at other ones we were like we didn't wanna get a Beko one and he was like yeah they're rubbish don't get one of those</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0423">yeah well</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's like he didn't</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're cheaper so they're kind of the cheaper end aren't they? so you're</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0423" trans="overlap">more you're paying the least price and they're probably not gonna last as long are they? Hotpoint's kind of they they they do it is a good brand and it's more kind of medium priced</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0423">I mean the top end <unclear/> or something but if you get the medium priced one <pause dur="long"/> you're not hungry yet are you not?</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0421">no and our washing machine we did a wash for one and a half hours and then it's got a good energy rate and it's like A plus plus</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0421">or something and we checked the electricity after we did the wash and nothing went down out of it so it mustn't have been erm</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0423">it's hardly used anything</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it's like after a kilowatt or something it like changes on the meter</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0421">and it it just it hadn't moved like it still said the same so</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0421">it's good</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I think I may have a chocolate nut and erm</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's probably melted everywhere oh right</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it's got a shell on it hasn't it?</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0421">oh right them I thought you meant the the bar</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0423">no I meant the <unclear/> you had <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1288" who="S0421">how many do you want?</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0423">well four in my hand pour more slowly otherwise they'll be all over the floor that's it</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0421">is that enough?</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0421">do you just put them all in your mouth at once?</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0423">well a couple of them</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1294" who="S0421">what does M and M stand for?</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0423">don't know <pause dur="short"/> thought you'd know that</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> munch and munch <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1297" who="S0423">could be mm and mm</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0421">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1299" who="S0423">coming into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1300" who="S0421">what's in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0423">a town called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1302" who="S0421">is that it? is there anything interesting there?</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0423">I've never been</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0421">I've heard of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1305" who="S0423">well <anon type="place"/> I think is the area where isn't it famous for potteries? is that what they call that area?</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is it?</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0423">the potteries</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0421" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0423" trans="overlap">as well <pause dur="short"/> think so <pause dur="short"/> just south of here is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1310" who="S0421">you know I've recently erm realised that there's like loads of counties in England that I didn't even know of before</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0423">like what?</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0421">I don't know but just like</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what you've not heard of?</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0423">name one</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0421">Staffordshire <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1317" who="S0423">you must have heard that before</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0421">I've heard of <anon type="place"/> but like</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's just when you kind of like realise that it's er a county</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0423">Shropshire?</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0421"><trunc>Shro</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0423">have you heard of Shropshire?</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0421">I have</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0423">Warwickshire?</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0421">yeah I have heard of the that one</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we're gonna be passing through <anon type="place"/> after that south of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> wiltshire?</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0421">yeah <trunc>th</trunc>that's a new one</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0423">yeah you've been to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1330" who="S0421">have I?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0423"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> down there at the time you know that pond with the frogs? do you remember that?</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0421">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0421" trans="overlap">how old was I?</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think we were still in <anon type="place"/> then but</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't remember ever visiting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1337" who="S0423">no?</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0421">I just know that she lives in Australia <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1339" who="S0423">you never visited her there</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0421">I know I <trunc>kn</trunc></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1342" who="S0421">I I that's kind of <trunc>li</trunc> I don't remember like moving I don't think</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0421" trans="overlap">she just kind of always I kind of</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think I kind of remember you saying though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s moving to Australia but like I've always kind of associated her with Australia and like never really here</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="long"/> we went to visit her from London with your grandad in the car</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0421">mm <pause dur="long"/> it's really annoying erm because sometimes when I've put my address in on websites like if I'm ordering something and it's like it just comes up Lancashire automatically and I'm like no <anon type="place"/> and it's like no Lancashire and I'm like no and it won't let me put in <anon type="place"/> as a county and some places</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's very</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's not many I've never really come across it</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0421" trans="overlap">have you not?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0423">I have erm</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos I've been changing my address in lots of places and it's just keeps doing it and I'm like excuse me excuse me it's not Lancashire <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1355" who="S0423">you don't think most of them brings up Yorkshire and <anon type="place"/> it used to be <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1356" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0423">but it's been a long time now so you can't blame it on it's not been updated</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0423">it's been <anon type="place"/> for a long long time <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1360" who="S0421">but I was on one website and I was looking for county and I couldn't find <anon type="place"/> and I was like okay I'm just gonna have to put in Lancashire and Lancashire wasn't there either and it it was and it did county as town <trunc>inst</trunc></u>
<u n="1361" who="S0423" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0421">yeah and I was just like I don't know what this website is doing</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0423"><unclear>it's not gonna be a very good company</unclear></u>
<u n="1364" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that website it's <pause dur="short"/> so what others have you come across?</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0421">I don't know I <trunc>ca</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1367" who="S0423">Cheshire?</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0421">no of course I know Cheshire</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0423">Yorkshire?</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0421">of course I know Yorkshire I bet there's some that you don't know</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0423">there will be yeah</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0421">yeah some really <trunc>stra</trunc> I I can't I <trunc>do</trunc> I can't think of them now but I just remember thinking is that a place? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1373" who="S0423">I can't think of any in erm there was well surely Cornwall is split into counties I can't think of any that might be in Cornwall</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0421">is is Devon a place or a <trunc>coun</trunc>?</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Devon's a county</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a county yeah</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0421">I thought it was</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0423">oh Cornwall is the county what am I on about?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1382" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh I I thought you meant is there any near <trunc>Cor</trunc> or other counties near Cornwall</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0421" trans="overlap">even</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0423">I don't know what I'm thinking</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1387" who="S0423">I was thinking all the others we've mentioned are shire</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0421">yeah yeah well because</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah we did yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we had this conversation didn't we and I was like I I thought all counties were shire but <trunc>ye</trunc> it like makes sense cos</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Devon and Cornwall</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0421" trans="overlap">most of them are</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0423">Dorset</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0421">Kent</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0423">Kent well there there is a lot of shire isn't there?</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0421">yeah a lot of them are yeah</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0423">it must have some meaning then mustn't it?</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> probably in Latin</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0421">I would like to learn Latin <pause dur="short"/> and why do people not you know? like the people who learn Latin like the scholars mainly probably why do they not speak it? like revive the dead language and speak it</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0423">well</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0421" trans="overlap">amongst yourselves <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1403" who="S0423">well that's it who would you speak it to? it would be <unclear/></u>
<u n="1404" who="S0421" trans="overlap">all your other scholar friends you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1405" who="S0423">well yeah</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0421" trans="overlap">maybe they do</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I mean well they</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0421" trans="overlap">maybe they do sit <trunc>f</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1409" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I mean well they they'd come out with phrases and whether you'd have conversations I don't know but I mean I guess do you not have to be able to speak it to practise law? I don't think you do now do you?</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but a lot of legal</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0421">yeah so like it would</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0423" trans="overlap">like legal terms</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0421">it would be like to a certain extent like spoken like when we did Dr Faustus in English literature there was parts of it in Latin</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0421">that we read out in Latin</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0421">but like some of the quotes were in Latin and I was thinking for my exam should I learn that in the Latin? or <vocal desc="laugh"/> should I <trunc>l</trunc> should I learn the English translation? cos I was thinking that examiner's probably not gonna know the Latin and they're just gonna be looking at it like</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0423">and won't won't</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0421" trans="overlap">in the end I didn't need any of the Latin quotes anyway so</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what would you have done?</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0421">well I only knew a few I would probably would have put them in Latin and just let them suffer</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0423">well yeah it like</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1425" who="S0423">that's the way it should be isn't it?</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's how it is in the book it's not necessarily a quote if it's not</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0423">taken exactly from the book is it?</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah the play</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0423">the play</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0421">so I was like well <pause dur="short"/> they can just do what they will with it</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I'm sure if they're an examiner it should be on their</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no honestly some of the</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you know the meaning of it?</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0423">well they must do surely</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0421">I don't think so some of those examiners right we got some of the the scripts back er some of the old tests and we were we were reading through what they <trunc>sai</trunc> the candidate and they got an A had written and were like they've marked that bit wrong like that that wasn't</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0421">I don't know and then our English teacher was like <pause dur="short"/> you know they just pick any old person to be examiners now anyone can be like any teacher can apply to be an examiner and they can just do it at home</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/> well you'd think that you would have to be that <unclear/> with your subject wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0421">yeah well it would be but</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0423" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0421">not <trunc>nec</trunc> they've not necessarily studied that play and if they have studied that play if they've read it and everything they <trunc>n</trunc> like there's a lot of Latin like I I only knew the Latin because I'd learnt I'd learnt you know what it meant and everything and like I don't think most people who study it unless you study it in great detail like would and I mean and like my teacher probably wouldn't have known all the Latin bits</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0421">but you'd think you'd look it up</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0421">but I think some people wouldn't bother <pause dur="short"/> they'd just be like oh okay they've quoted <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1449" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1451" who="S0423">well if your subject is to study that play then <trunc>y</trunc> how can you not know it? cos you</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you're missing parts then aren't you?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><trunc>peo</trunc>people don't people don't <pause dur="long"/> some people are like the the examiners are just doing them like while they're having their dinner like marking these papers and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> and we'd only been studying the play for like I don't know and we were already like that character that they've it it you know that that's not right or whatever</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah I thought as an examiner you you've gotta be the highest of the high really if you're marking papers</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no just any teacher</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it just it doesn't doesn't seem right does it?</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0421">you'd think it would be this like elite group who are doing them all</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0421">but it's just anyone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1461" who="S0423">well I suppose when you think how many papers they have to mark</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1464" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it would just takes for forever wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0423">yeah but even so there has to be accuracy in there</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0423">otherwise it makes a mockery of the exams <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1468" who="S0421">I thought I'd be hungry but <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0423">no I'm alright I don't think we stopped off on the way to Scotland did we? although we probably set off earlier than</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0421">yeah did we not?</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0423">today no I know we did on the way back I don't remember stopping off on the way there</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0421">yeah maybe not <pause dur="long"/> do you remember going down to Oxford and we didn't stop and we we stopped like just before we got to Oxford or something and like we could barely walk cos we'd been sat in the car for like?</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0421">I don't even know how long</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0421">cos it took us quite a while didn't it cos there was traffic it was like</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0421" trans="overlap">five hours or something</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah cos I was gonna say it's it's not that bad a drive</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no yeah there was loads of traffic</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1482" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and we were in it for like <trunc>fi</trunc>five hours or something</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or something happened didn't it yeah</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0421">yeah there was like a crash</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0423" trans="overlap">an accident or something cos you had to ring ahead didn't you?</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0423">cos I did give a bit of extra time cos I thought oh we'll arrive early and</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0423">what have you so it's just as well I did that cos of the accident</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0421">and you were like cos we were cos we were running late and you were like oh I'm gonna have to stop to go to the toilet and we got out of the car and our legs were like</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0421">and you were like hobbling along like running like ah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> did you get your tyres done?</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0423">yeah there's two new tyres on the back</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0421">oh <pause dur="short"/> and your disk fitted?</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0423">well they said it doesn't need doing cos erm the brake pads are not</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0423">it's about fifty percent so he says if you're having disks done you may as well have the pads done at the same time and they still work okay erm there's not a problem with the disk but they will need changing when when <unclear/> for the pads to be done so it's they're okay for a while <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> that was it I think yeah yeah the tyres I had on this at the back I've never changed they were on it when I originally bought it</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and they've been on it for years they were a good a good brand so the tread is isn't very worn it's still kept really good</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0423">but the side of the of the tyre because it's so old is starting to wear</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0423">er I think they were Japanese Yokohama</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0421">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0423">I think they were they're a lot dearer than the average tyre</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah the thing is Japanese cars are good and they last a long time but if you ever need a part for a <trunc>Japane</trunc> like a Japanese part they're really expensive</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well this this car Honda they have a reputation for being the most reliable</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0421">where what company's Honda?</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0423">Honda that's what they are</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0421">no but what where from?</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0423" trans="overlap">Japanese</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0421">is it? yeah</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0423">er but it has been a great car it's</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos I I did have some problems with the not many but before I got rid of it it was quite a few kind of a few times where it broke down for some reason I had loads of punctures on that as well <pause dur="short"/> erm but I used I think I used to get budget tyres and I think that's why</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0423">it's probably better to get the <unclear>brand up</unclear> or like either Yokohama on there or something the front ones I have are just a good brand before I've changed I can't remember what the front tyres were so they've always done me okay I've gone down to more the medium priced one now though so hopefully <pause dur="short"/> it it'll do a good job <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I guess it shows if you pay a bit more for something you do get better</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0423">a better life out of it well the only problem I had on this was the exhaust coming through</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but that happens when</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and that was when we were gonna go somewhere wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0423">erm</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0421"><trunc>whe</trunc></u>
<u n="1527" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think it was was it Christmas time? it</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0421">oh oh yeah maybe</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0423">well no I I went over to see you on Boxing Day or something</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and I got or the day after Boxing Day cos I got the RAC out and he checked it out and he just took</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the back of the exhaust off and he said I said oh I'm planning to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1534" who="S0421">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0423">on it we might I don't know if we went there er but I can't remember now and he said oh it'll be okay it'll just be a bit noisy</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0421">yeah maybe it was</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but I guess that's</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0421" trans="overlap">just coming to see me</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0423">just from the corrosion or whatever that's the kind of thing that will go</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah cos my my French teacher was talking to us about cars and she was like in France like cos over here there's like not many people you <trunc>kn</trunc> that'll have like an English car but in France everybody has like a French car</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0423">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but she but she said she always buys a Japanese car cos they last</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0421" trans="overlap">ages they're really good</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0423">the French as well they're not Renault they're not er <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they have one of the best reputations and they're really quite awkward cos with our patrols when they</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0423">they say some of them said to me oh never buy a Renault they're just so difficult to</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1549" who="S0423">if you need to like there was one and it had no his his lightbulb had gone</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0423">on the headlights which is a really simple thing</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0423" trans="overlap">to be able to take care of and normally anyone can do it you just you know some some of them can be a bit awkward to get into</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but he said this car I can't change the lightbulb it has to go into the</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1557" who="S0423">dealers to do it because the whole front of the bonnet the whole bonnet</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0423">has to be taken off to change it</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0423">and it has to go under the</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but yeah</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so that's ridiculous that</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but yeah my friend she just like yeah almost everyone in France will have a French car cos</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0423">well that's why it's still a successful</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0423">a profitable company cos the French you know they've been quite I suppose nationalistic and</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0423" trans="overlap">buying French whereas in this country we we don't</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0421">what are English cars? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1571" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well we used to have we we don't there are English cars still produced here but we used to have a a a a big brand you know like like Renault</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0423" trans="overlap">which was known as an the English</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is Ford English?</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0423">well the the the company Ford is American</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0423">but they have a UK Ford</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so they do design cars and build them over here</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0423">erm for the English and European market well let me just see where we're going <pause dur="long"/> and the the the the national carmaker the the the big company over here was called Rover</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or or Leyland er they they they made vans or something <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> and I don't know whether you've seen a Rover have you?</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0421">I've heard of it</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0423">yeah so they are still on the road and erm then they they they went out of business and then I think BMW bought them and</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they just decided to it just wasn't a profitable business so</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0421" trans="overlap">people buy German cars as well don't they?</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0423">yeah German cars they're a bit more</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0421">Germans have just</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the there's reliability as well</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0421" trans="overlap">generally quite good manufacturing don't they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1593" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well they they yeah for</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos AEG is German</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0423">yeah they've generally German products the manufacturing they have a great reputation yeah <pause dur="short"/> er it manufacturing in this country has really died down you know it's not</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0423" trans="overlap">at all I mean this country it was they used to call it the factory of the world cos it invented industrialisation</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and things that method of erm producing goods come from <unclear/></u>
<u n="1600" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and we used to have lots of good inventors</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0423">oh well you look at the amount of inventions</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah but now</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that are world changing has come from here</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but now it's like</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0423">it seems to be America a lot where some things come from</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0423">isn't it? like new ideas er</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0421">not so much over here</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0423">yeah well not <unclear/></u>
<u n="1610" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but like all all the old kind of inventions and things and the discoveries were like</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a lot of them were from here</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it stems from this country yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1614" who="S0421">I <trunc>n</trunc> I discovered the other day that Isaac <trunc>Newt</trunc> Isaac Newton allegedly invented the cat flap</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0423">oh right why allegedly? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1616" who="S0421">well because erm it's like obviously they don't have that much like from looking at notes and things</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0421" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0423">they always have to historians</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><trunc>his</trunc>historians think it is him some of them don't</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0421">but there's no other clear inventor so it's like pinned to him</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0421">we think it was him erm <pause dur="short"/> and apparently like <trunc>so</trunc><trunc>so</trunc>some people say that he did like cats and some people say no</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but some people say that he he's erm while he was at Cambridge University his experiments were always disturbed by his cats crying to come in</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0421" trans="overlap">erm so he put a cat flap on the door</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a bigger one for the mother cat and a smaller one for the kittens but obviously the smaller ones just went after their mother and in the big one</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0421">erm but yeah that's what he he made it for and like I I suppose like that flap kind of structure would have been like he was a physicist</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0421">so it would have kind of made sense that he would have like worked that out and everything erm but yeah yeah I was like oh that's nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0421">it's a good story good facts</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0423">maybe that's what maybe it wasn't an apple dropping on his head that he got the theory of gravity</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1639" who="S0423">could have been the flap</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0423">coming back down well why does that flap</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0421" trans="overlap">the cat flap yeah</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0423" trans="overlap">go like that? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I doubt it that's probably from <unclear/></u>
<u n="1644" who="S0421">yeah cos like some people were saying that erm <pause dur="short"/> he didn't have cats but</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0421"><trunc>ye</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0423">so it's not a definite then?</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0421">no yeah but <pause dur="short"/> that's what it's he's largely agreed to be the inventor of the cat flap</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0423">oh right I wouldn't have thought they went back so long and so far cos all I thought they were quite a modern</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0421">yeah but</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0423" trans="overlap">idea</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I mean if you imagine what that original cat flap looked like and probably like a bit of wood</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0423">well it will have been</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1655" who="S0423">carved out of wood wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but now now they're like all high tech and everything aren't they?</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0423">I wouldn't say they're high tech you mean plastic and rubber</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0421">no no they <trunc>ac</trunc> some of them are costing hundreds</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0423">why?</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and they have like microchip technology and like infrared and all sorts</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0423">do they?</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0421">like to scan your cat in</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0423">oh right is it a a proper scanning thing for it scans the iris? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1664" who="S0421">it scans the microchip inside them</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> that's taking it a bit far isn't it? it's not as though people have problems with hundreds of cats wondering in</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1667" who="S0423">through cat flaps do they? I've got another hundred cats in here today</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0421">no but <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's quite good people must buy them</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0423">well of course they do cos they can then <trunc>sa</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1671" who="S0423">we can buy a new cat flap and then you it can do this and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1672" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I've entered the competitions to win them but and if I won them like obviously it would be quite nice to have them but I wouldn't ever buy like we've just got a normal one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1673" who="S0423">yeah it's not really necessary is it?</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0423">unless you do have a cat infestation</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1677" who="S0423">and you have to stop all the the cats in the neighbourhood coming through</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> can you imagine? oh <pause dur="short"/> but yeah apparently Isaac Newton liked cats so generally that's what people think so that's nice I like to hear about cat lovers in history</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0423">do you?</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0421">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0423">the Egyptians were weren't they?</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0421">yeah there was erm an Egyptian Pharaoh who had his cat buried with him</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0421">most of them probably did mummified they mummified then didn't they?</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0423">yeah well they thought they were did they</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0423" trans="overlap">think they're sacred the cats?</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0423">or they're gods was it?</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0421">well like one of their gods was like half cat <pause dur="short"/> is that Bastet I think? <pause dur="short"/> and then they had like the Sphinx didn't they that was like half person half half lion?</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0423" trans="overlap">was that a lion?</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0421">yeah same family</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0423">well we're coming up to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1694" who="S0421">I think this is where we got stuck last time</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0423">we were just coming out of</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> last time going on the I think it was the M40 or something <pause dur="short"/> but that to <anon type="place"/> you kind of go round and to the left</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0423">er whereas <pause dur="short"/> cos we're we're not we're going er to the east of it or we're going to the west of the country so we we kind of could just go straight past <anon type="place"/> and down <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1700" who="S0421">who else? there was some writer who really liked cats as well and I was like oh that's good to know some fellow cat lovers <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember who it was</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0423">was it that one who wrote those cat books?</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0421">which ones? no it was like a classic</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what's that cat book? the American one?</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0421">American cat book? there's loads</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="1706" who="S0421" trans="overlap">of cat books in the world</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no it rhymes and everything the cat in the hat or something</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0423">what's that called?</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0421">The Cat in the Hat</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0423">is that</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0421" trans="overlap">by</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what it's called?</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0421">he's not American he's er German</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0423">oh is he?</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0421">I think well it's it's Dr Seuss</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0423">Dr Seuss yeah</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it's not Seuss it's pronounced Seuss</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but nobody pronounces it Seuss so if you say Seuss people would be like who?</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0421">so it's it's like overall pronounced Seuss</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that's how we all pronounce it</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's cos it how it looks to us isn't it but</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but he he himself said that no it's actually Seuss</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think Seuss yeah</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and is he German?</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0421">I think it sounds German I think he was German I don't think he was <trunc>Ameri</trunc></u>
<u n="1733" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well he could be a he could be American couldn't he?</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0421">oh maybe he was born</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos there's lots of</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0421" trans="overlap">there</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0423" trans="overlap">different names and just you can't assume because of his name</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0421">yeah but</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I mean I do I don't know why I thought it was American it just seems that style you know?</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0421"><trunc>may</trunc> I think he might have lived in America and then wrote them in like American English</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but I think he had German heritage</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0421">yeah I don't I don't cos he wouldn't have written them in German cos they rhyme in English or</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0423">dunno</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0421" trans="overlap">unless they've <trunc>trans</trunc> er no I don't think they're translated <pause dur="long"/> yeah but there's some stuff that I always like think like you know the Moomins?</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0421">I always I don't know why I always thought they were like a Japanese cartoon but they come from like Sweden or Norway or somewhere</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0421">they were like a a comic</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0423">yeah they didn't seem Japanese the</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0421">no don't know why I thought they were <pause dur="short"/> high quality cartoon maybe I thought it was Japanese</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1754" who="S0421">they have a Moomin land over there now</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0423">do they?</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0423">where is it Sweden?</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0421">I think it's Sweden or Norway or something <pause dur="long"/> I always get confused because there also was from one place but then I think they wrote them in another language so</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> er be interesting place to visit Scandinavia</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think it's expensive over there though</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0421">is it? <pause dur="short"/> why? the their</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't know why</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0421" trans="overlap">countryside's really nice</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0421">and they have mountains <pause dur="short"/> no they have like you know they have like nice mountains with like like lakes and like trees and things that look nice</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0423">well there's lots of countries like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1768" who="S0421">I know but I think they look especially nice in places like Norway or somewhere</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0423">are you thinking of the Fjords?</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0421">probably</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0423">I think it's Norway the Fjords isn't it?</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and they get to see the erm the Northern Lights sometimes in Norway don't they?</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0423">yeah more often than er occasionally you see them here now don't we?</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0421">yeah like they were saying that you could see them</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0423">it wasn't that long ago it was only they were saying you might see them over here but</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I couldn't see them</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0423">instead it said it was er it was a bit cloudy</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's always the cloud that gets in the way really</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0421">yeah but you there was a point where there was like erm on the internet it was saying how you could see them in most places in Europe for a while at certain times but I didn't see them <pause dur="short"/> it's quite disappointing really <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they wouldn't have been as nice as like they are if you went to see them properly it it would <trunc>j</trunc> probably just would have been like is that a bit of green in the sky?</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think it is</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0423">actually I've seen some photos of like when you were able to see them from this country and they did look good</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0421">really?</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0423">some</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0421">I saw some photos</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the top end of Lancashire</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0421">not from England</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0423">Scotland</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's spitting</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0423">looks a bit <unclear>nail</unclear> off the</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0421">what a <unclear>nail</unclear>? <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm like not from er not from this country but from other places in Europe and they did look quite good yeah</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0423">I suppose you can you can go to wherever</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0421">yeah and see them</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0423">and see them as part of a holiday couldn't you?</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0423">shall we do that next time?</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1799" who="S0423">we can go whale watching as well</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0421"><trunc>Sc</trunc>Scandinavia <vocal desc="laugh"/> you said it's expensive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1801" who="S0423">yeah we'll have to leave that till you can applaud afford to pay half of your holiday</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1803" who="S0423">I think I'll have a a I'll try a bit of a Liquorice Allsort now do you not want to try one?</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0421">I don't like</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you might like them now</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0421">I no I don't think I will</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0423" trans="overlap">when did you last taste them?</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a few years ago</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0423">there you are your taste changes as you get older</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0421">I don't think it changes that much <pause dur="short"/> if I eat one of those and I get sick</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0423">you're not going to be sick are you?</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I'm gonna blame you <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1813" who="S0423">look doesn't that look nice?</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0421">I know cos it looks like Dolly Mixtures</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0423">well smell it and see if you like the smell <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1816" who="S0421">shall I have one?</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0423">just spit it out if you don't like it <unclear/></u>
<u n="1818" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it smells like it smells a bit like Christmas cake <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1819" who="S0423">mm that is</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you like it?</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0421">no I don't like it</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought I had <unclear/></u>
<u n="1824" who="S0421">I can I'm sure I can manage to eat it <pause dur="long"/> yeah it's not kind of like the level of disgustingness where I would</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0421">throw it out it's kind of like when I have to eat Christmas cake at Christmas</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0423">don't you like it?</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0423">maybe you should try mushrooms again</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0421">I mean</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I really like mushrooms</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0421">I like mushrooms when they're thinly sliced</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0421">it's the texture of mushrooms that I don't like it's I've I</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0421">I always like the taste because I always like <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc> chicken and mushroom pasta sauce and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0421">and erm what did I have mushrooms in the other day? I don't know something but I don't like eating a whole mushroom if they're sliced or diced or something I don't mind</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0421">but if they're like in quarters or like a whole I can't eat them cos it's like oh it's all squashy and</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0421">oh they're not bad when I'm still eating the sweet bit but then once I'm left with that liquorice <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1843" who="S0423">got too much of a sweet tooth then have you?</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0421">yeah I don't like anything sour</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0423">don't you?</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0421" trans="overlap">at all <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1847" who="S0423">well I thought you liked those sour sweets</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0421">no I don't know where you get that from <pause dur="short"/> like people are like offer me like Haribo like Tangfastics and I'm like oh no thanks I don't like sour things and they're all like oh they're not even sour and I'm like yes they are I've had them before I nearly died <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1849" who="S0423">of course they're sour that's what they're promoted on isn't it?</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0421">no but most people don't think they're that sour like compared to other sweets they don't think Tangfastics are like on the lower scale for them <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I'm just like I can't eat them <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I just I don't know I don't like sour things at all nothing not lemons and like fruit is too sour I'm just like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1851" who="S0423">what about sweet and sour chicken?</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0421">that's not sour it's just sweet <pause dur="short"/> they call it sweet and sour because it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's not sweet like a dessert but it's not sour it's like sweetish savoury it should be sweet and savoury</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0423">no it's it's cos it'll have a little <trunc>bi</trunc><trunc>bi</trunc> a bite like erm there's</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0423" trans="overlap">some acidity like all foods should have</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well like oranges</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0423" trans="overlap">a balance not as sharp as that no</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0421">oranges aren't sharp oranges are sweet</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0423">well</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0423">it depends what orange</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yes sometimes I get an orange and like I'm just can't eat it but like tangerines and things then er tangerines can be sour it's hit and miss</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0423">yeah sometimes yeah</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you've got no idea</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah yeah they're horrible yeah</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you open it up and you're expecting a really nice sweet fruit and it's like oh</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0421">or like peaches and plums and things like if they're if they're sweet it's alright but er if they're not</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well they generally are they're not usually</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0421">no really?</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0423" trans="overlap">peaches and plums are generally not</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0421">we always get</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0423" trans="overlap">sour much</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0421" trans="overlap">unlucky and get the sour ones</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0423">well maybe</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's unreal</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you need to let them ripen a bit more</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0421">yeah yeah and we always <trunc>lea</trunc> I always leave the kiwis for ages now because I had a kiwi and I was just like what is this? I could barely eat it cos I'd been <trunc>ea</trunc></u>
<u n="1879" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but <trunc>ki</trunc>kiwis are not sour they're not that</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it wasn't ripe that's why</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0423">oh right well you don't want them to be too ripe cos they go to mush</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0421">yeah well do you know <trunc>li</trunc> we have these kiwis?</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well I I really like ripe fruit cos it just really brings out the flavour more</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0421">we have this kiwis at the moment cos we buy them quite often now cos I like them <pause dur="short"/> erm and I left them to ripen cos and they weren't sour but I was eating them and I didn't finish the one I was eating the other day because mammy was saying it as well cos she had one the other day and she was like inside it tastes like mediciny and I was eating it and I was like oh it does as well</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0423">what? kiwi?</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0421">yeah inside like for some reason it had like a mediciny taste</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0423">strange</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't know what it was <pause dur="short"/> cos it wasn't sour cos like</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0423">well maybe it was over ripe then</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah maybe it wasn't mushy though <pause dur="short"/> it did seem a bit too soft</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they are they're <trunc>rea</trunc> quite difficult to tell when they're just ripe</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos sometimes I have let them go too far and if you're trying to peel them and they just</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0423" trans="overlap">split open then you you you press it in your hand and it just mushes up</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0423">and then sometimes you think oh it's quite firm but not too firm</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0421">I really like mangos</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1900" who="S0421" trans="overlap">as well</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0423">I've got a nice big mango</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0421">have you?</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0421">yes because</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0423">it's for the</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0423" trans="overlap">curry though</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0421">I really oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1909" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well we probably won't <unclear/> though</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0421">I really enjoyed this mango and then grandma and grandad had never had a mango before so they got one</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0421">yeah I don't think they had and then they said it was okay and I was like yeah but was it red or was it more greeny?</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it has to be really soft</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0421">and they were like yeah it was a bit hard and I was like yeah you should have left it longer and it would have been nicer</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0423">why where did they have it?</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0421">at home we were on Skype to them ages ago</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh in Kosice?</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0423">oh right I thought you meant they couldn't get it over there</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0421">no no</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's what I <unclear/></u>
<u n="1922" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they'd just not had one</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0423">oh right no they're not nice if they're not</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0423">soft cos when they're ripe <trunc>y</trunc>you you see they're really kind of quite slimy</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0423">and juicy aren't they? but when they're not ripened they're quite hard</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and quite</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0421">Kosice</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0423" trans="overlap">there's a big difference</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0421">makes me laugh</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0423">how do you say it?</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0421">I don't know how English people are supposed to say it</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0423">how do you say it?</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0421">Kosice</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0423">oh right well that I don't think your mammy's ever said it like that to me</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0421">no <trunc>prob</trunc> she probably said it the English way I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it's it makes me laugh as well the English people saying Budapest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1939" who="S0423">well that's how the English say it Budapest</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1941" who="S0423">Budapest</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0421">Budapest</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0423">Budapest</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1945" who="S0423">well they're not Hungarians so they're not gonna say it like that</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know but it's just so funny <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I bet all people feel like that when people are saying their their country in <trunc>Eng</trunc> in English it sounds funny</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> it's funny how it's a second language to you but you're so familiar with it that you can laugh at people when you think they sound strange</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0423">when they say certain words it's I guess cos you've spoken it since you were</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0421">yeah well it's like</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you're like</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's a second</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's not like a second language is it in some ways</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well it it is a second language but it's not it's</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0423">just seems natural to you</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it's</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's it's</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like I think cos <trunc>so</trunc>some people who will who if you learn like a language to a good standard you might not consider it a second language <pause dur="short"/> you know because it's not integrated I dunno at some point you probably would but I mean I I'm not sure what</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think most people who have learnt it as a second language would where you wouldn't</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is if like in some countries they learn two or three from when they're a child</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and it just comes natural like erm er I work with people from Morocco and</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they say well they they learn they have Arabic French</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0423" trans="overlap">English and they can speak them all fluently and they do learn it from a very young</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0423" trans="overlap">age and just it's natural to them</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0421">well yeah that's kind of how I learnt erm Hungarian but I just don't use it as much and I've never been formerly taught it</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0423">well do you think you'll forget it now if you say you stop using it?</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0421">I don't I'd never forget</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0423" trans="overlap">if it's if it's too <unclear/></u>
<u n="1974" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't think I'd ever forget all of it</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but erm <pause dur="short"/> I do struggle if I've not used it in a while kind of like you know</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0423" trans="overlap">your pronunciation and so on would probably suffer wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0421">no not the pronunciation</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0421">it's the actual words</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0423">what remembering?</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so like you know in English like when you can't think of the word?</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and you're just like and obviously you know it</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because it is but you just can't think of it</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and it's like</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so it's like that</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's like that but it happens more often</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0421">erm so like</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1996" who="S0421" trans="overlap">maybe more simple words <pause dur="long"/> the pronunciation just like I don't have to ever think about the pronunciation because that's just</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0423">it comes naturally</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and like the way the words are put together</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0421">I don't need to think about that it's like the vocabulary mainly like the words that I forget</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0423">yeah so it's one of the hardest things is constructing and saying the words how it sound</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0423">I suppose if you you lost erm some of the words cos you didn't use it that's something that could probably be picked up quite quickly isn't it?</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0421">yeah like I it it gets it's gets easier to kind of put them together</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0421">and like to think of the words and things if I use it more often</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0421">but if it's been a while then I'm just like oh</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it's a shame your mammy didn't speak Slovakian to you as well</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0421">well it's hard though erm it would have been very difficult for me to learn either one of them because <pause dur="short"/> because I don't use both kind of on a daily basis between lots of people and because</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0421">I'm not using them all erm to read and write and because like all of them aren't included in my education I think both of them I wouldn't know either one to a very good standard it would have been a lot harder because mammy learnt Slovakian and Hungarian as kind of part of her daily life like she used</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0421" trans="overlap">them all the time but</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0423">well she would if she's</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0423" trans="overlap">living in Slovakia and that whole whole area</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but then but because like those two I would have had to alternate the time I used both of them to her cos it would have just been to her or to</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0421" trans="overlap">grandma and grandad and I wouldn't have been able to really</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0421">so it it only really works to learn more if you that's how your country works</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2024" who="S0421">and but although I say that I wouldn't ever forget Hungarian but mammy said that she started forgetting Slovakian cos she hardly ever uses it</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0421">and that's like</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so does she not?</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0421">her second language</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0423">yeah I guess she doesn't speak</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0423">to her parents in it so it</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0423" trans="overlap">who does she speak to? does she use it at all no?</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0421">no not really <pause dur="short"/> and she says that she's forgotten loads of words</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0421">and like my Hungarian's not it's it's like fluent but it's more conversational and I'd struggle if someone was being overly formal</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0421">or like using more complex words like I've</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it's just cos you've not heard the word before</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0423">so obviously you're not gonna know it I think</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but it would it would be like erm <pause dur="short"/> you know like when you learn new words in English?</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0421">it that's the kind of way I would have to learn them</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0421">so it wouldn't kind of be like erm learning a foreign language it would just be like learning improving my vocabulary</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0423">yeah it's like when you come across an English word that you need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="2048" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but there's more of them in Hungarian <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> and like <trunc>whe</trunc> in <trunc>ma</trunc>mammy sometimes she like says things in English that are like they they like sound funny because she's kind of like translated that directly from Hungarian into English and like you just wouldn't say it like that in English like you know certain phrases or whatever and then I do that in Hungarian as well like I say it funny</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0423">you would have thought there's not many that your mammy would say like that now and she's been so long</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0421">no no she doesn't say it often and I think like she knows that it's not right but she just kind of you know and I do that as well or like certain pronunciations that I've just learnt differently and it the pronunciation's not wrong it's just not standard so like erm like people have dialects and things</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0421">for some reason I've learnt some words with a bit of a dialect but <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2053" who="S0423">well how have you done that?</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0421">I don't</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0423" trans="overlap">if you've been speaking to <unclear/></u>
<u n="2056" who="S0421" trans="overlap">for whatever for whatever reason I've just learnt it like that and I don't know maybe it's just chance that it's part of a dialect</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0423">well your mammy said you speak quite posh Hungarian how is that?</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I no yeah I do speak like the standard Hungarian there's just a couple of words that I might not erm</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0423">yeah well you would have thought your mammy would have er er quite a strong regional accent as er from like Slovakia</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0421">no erm cos like grandma's cos like where grandad's from cos he's from a village</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0421">so they speak I sometimes struggle to understand that Hungarian because it's not like in English that it's just an accent change it's like the words change</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0421">as well so I sometimes struggled a bit with when we went to visit like his side of the family over there cos I was a bit like mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> like it's not the same words it's like they're different words erm but the Hungarian that grandma speaks and like grandad speaks that now as well <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0421">is like the standard <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but it must have different accents</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0421">they don't really</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0421" trans="overlap">not like over here</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0423">oh that's strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0421">no there's like cos like in erm Germany like northern and southern Germany have some differences in pronunciation and things I think it's a bit like that in Hungary but then when you go to like the villages it does change a bit but you're not kind of as much it's like quite standard the one I speak but but when I hear people talking and like the radio and things they sound like the way they put the words together is like better than the way I put the words together <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think I don't think I could</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what in Hungary?</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0421">yeah I couldn't put them</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0423" trans="overlap">why do you listen to Hungarian radio?</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0421">or the TV or whatever</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0421">I think they</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well of course it's not your first language is it?</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so you're not gonna be</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0421">they sound good and I'm like oh that's good and like it it sounds good and I'm like I <trunc>wi</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2083" who="S0423" trans="overlap">also people on TV they're gonna</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0421">I know but in</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0423" trans="overlap">be</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0421">in like English</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> sentences</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I I could do that like I never kind of think that about in England</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0421">I get it in books I'm like oh that's well written I like that but when I'm watching the TV or listening to the radio I never kind of think that about English because I suppose I'm quite good in English erm but in Hungarian I do find that even when like people are just speaking on TV or the radio I'm like yeah that that sounds nice</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0421">I don't speak like that</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it's good you can recognise that though</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> cos I must just speak quite informally</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0423">well of course cos that's the</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0423" trans="overlap">kind of conversation you've had isn't it?</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2099" who="S0423">it's quite warm now</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2101" who="S0423">we're not far from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2102" who="S0421">are we not?</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0423">no do you remember we went there?</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0421">yeah it was good</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
