<text id="SAZ8">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:33:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0109 S0175</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A church, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Games for a youth group night</topics>
		<activity>Games for a youth group night</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0109">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0175">
				<exactage>35</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Administration Officer</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0175">what kind of things are you doing in linguistics study?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0109">just general ELT style stuff really <pause dur="short"/> sorry I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's just a bank of building up a bank of um data that they can just use in the future</u>
<u n="3" who="S0175">so is it searching out seeing what kind of words people use? Or how they use words or?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0109">how they well yeah how how you use words or kind of grammatical constructions that actually still used rather than just taught in grammar lessons and <unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0175">okay</u>
<u n="6" who="S0109">that sort of thing</u>
<u n="7" who="S0175">mm <pause dur="short"/> like split infinitives and stuff and</u>
<u n="8" who="S0109">yep</u>
<u n="9" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Not that I understood what they are but I used to get told off by grandfather about splitting my infinitives <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0109">oh the OED allows them now so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0175">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="12" who="S0109">must be</u>
<u n="13" who="S0175">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0109">I have got more ideas than that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But not many</u>
<u n="15" who="S0175">I guess we need to think about whether we want to do it on a friend or foe <pause dur="short"/> whether we want to do it on the theme that the box picks out of more</u>
<u n="16" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> which is kind of the two choices that we face <pause dur="short"/> and so we came up with sort of choices things <pause dur="short"/> where they pick up <pause dur="short"/> which is kind of where friend or foe came cos they're ultimately the two choices</u>
<u n="18" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0175">that there are <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but when I was thinking about friend and foe as a theme and thinking of the games that go with that didn't really link very well into the box <pause dur="short"/> which isn't necessarily matter</u>
<u n="20" who="S0109">yeah that's that's a good point cos I hadn't thought about that <pause dur="short"/> I had just been thinking friend and foe help</u>
<u n="21" who="S0175">mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0109">I don't know what to do <pause dur="short"/> I find um box six a bit of a er mm I don't know how to say it <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's two ways to live</u>
<u n="23" who="S0175">go on</u>
<u n="24" who="S0109">I think it's one way to live one way to die</u>
<u n="25" who="S0175">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0109">so I don't know</u>
<u n="27" who="S0175">I guess it's two ways to live at the moment isn't it <pause dur="short"/> but then one way leads to eternal death one way leads to eternal life</u>
<u n="28" who="S0109">mhm <pause dur="short"/> how long do we actually need to leave? Cos last week's seemed to be quite a long question of the week plus</u>
<u n="29" who="S0175">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0109">talk time</u>
<u n="31" who="S0175">it was shorter than my one I think <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> My one was extra stupidly long <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0109">yeah well yours was recap <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0175">yeah that's true <pause dur="short"/> that's what I felt <pause dur="short"/> but I think if <unclear/> hadn't been there so he hadn't seen that <pause dur="short"/> um yeah <pause dur="short"/> mine was a recap <pause dur="short"/> um you should probably leave a little bit of time <pause dur="short"/> I think we will have to <trunc>k</trunc> I dunno actually whether <trunc>pa</trunc> who's doing it? Becca <pause dur="short"/> becca's doing it <pause dur="short"/> I looked it up earlier</u>
<u n="34" who="S0109">okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> it's a good idea though <pause dur="short"/> let's start off in the middle of the session <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0109">it's just then though we've got the flowers to do and the</u>
<u n="37" who="S0175">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0109">we're not actually gonna have that much time</u>
<u n="39" who="S0175">so we've got snacks <pause dur="short"/> question of the week <pause dur="short"/> and small group time <pause dur="short"/> and realistically we're gonna need at least ten minutes for question of the week <pause dur="short"/> and then fifteen minutes for small group time <pause dur="short"/> do you think? That's twenty-five minutes in total <pause dur="short"/> cos you've got to draw the box and talk about it with questions <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0109">yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0175">and then go into small groups and pray and share prayer and share</u>
<u n="42" who="S0109">and can get over the whole discussion of what colour you like first</u>
<u n="43" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's true <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I always miss that bit though because <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm producing yet another set of cards</u>
<u n="44" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0175">I should just do like come in on one Friday and just make ten more sets <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0109">um so er er oh brain <pause dur="short"/> did you say fifteen minutes?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0175">think that's too short? I think if we have more than twenty-five minutes that bit's getting quite</u>
<u n="48" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's it's too long for the</u>
<u n="49" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> for those who aren't interested in it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the boys who don't like colouring</u>
<u n="51" who="S0175">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0109">er</u>
<u n="53" who="S0175">Cos the boys were quite quick <pause dur="short"/> so ten min for question of the week <pause dur="short"/> fifteen min for prayer and share time with a game for those who finish earlier?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0109">mhm <pause dur="short"/> which will need to be quiet</u>
<u n="55" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0109">that's a challenge</u>
<u n="57" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="58" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hiya</u>
<u n="59" who="S0109">hi <pause dur="short"/> er okay</u>
<u n="60" who="S0175">it takes quite a long time to make the flowers</u>
<u n="61" who="S0109">how many are they making? Er for the morning both morning services?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0175">I assume so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how many we're making <pause dur="short"/> but it takes a long time to make the flowers <pause dur="short"/> you did it depends what they are <pause dur="short"/> did last time anyway <pause dur="short"/> took us a good half hour</u>
<u n="63" who="S0109">I think we need to end on a good game</u>
<u n="64" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0109">otherwise they'll think why did we bother</u>
<u n="66" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0175">we could have do the flowers and then do a very quick game <pause dur="short"/> cos if they came come at start a bit early</u>
<u n="68" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0175">if we don't finish praying till then but</u>
<u n="70" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0175">what we could do though is we could if we pray quite quickly and then set up the flowers <pause dur="short"/> then as soon as they start arriving they can then join us join</u>
<u n="72" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0175">in the flowers <pause dur="short"/> cos if people come at twenty past we can get them started</u>
<u n="74" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you don't have that sort of milling around time</u>
<u n="75" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0109">so in that case we don't need  we don't need  a intro game</u>
<u n="77" who="S0175">no <pause dur="short"/> we don't need an intro game <pause dur="short"/> probably need one game before snacks <pause dur="long"/> Um <pause dur="long"/> So you could do some kind of variation of Simon Says er quite quickly <pause dur="short"/> um because that's um and you could then but you make it so with forfeits or something so that it can link in with the choices thing <pause dur="short"/> so either you do what the person either you follow your leader or you rebel against the leader</u>
<u n="78" who="S0109">uh-huh</u>
<u n="79" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> and you have a choice each time <pause dur="short"/> and if you and rebel against leader's ending of the game for you</u>
<u n="80" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0175">or something <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0109">oh you mean that even if they aren't gonna get a choice whether they rebel?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0175">well they could can't they <pause dur="short"/> you can decide not to I guess you can always decide <trunc>i</trunc> how much you're concentrating <pause dur="short"/> it's  it's a bit  it's a bit weak <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos actually you tend to not  you tend to not  deliberately rebel against Simon Says</u>
<u n="84" who="S0109">I just just completely forget what I'm supposed to be doing normally</u>
<u n="85" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0109">but no I like it</u>
<u n="87" who="S0175">but that's kind of on theme</u>
<u n="88" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0175">and it's kinda short and long <pause dur="short"/> and you can make it  and you can make it  yes you can get them running around even <pause dur="short"/> you could say Simon says touch both touch all four walls <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Run around touch all four walls <pause dur="short"/> and get them running round or something <pause dur="short"/> um or it could be Simon says go and have snacks or no you know</u>
<u n="90" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0175">um</u>
<u n="92" who="S0109">Cos you you know you can  you can  make that as elaborate as or as simple as you like</u>
<u n="93" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you can get them up to do it if they wanted to or</u>
<u n="94" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> it isn't really friend or foey but it's kind of</u>
<u n="96" who="S0109">live this way or live that way</u>
<u n="97" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="98" who="S0109">only cos my <unclear/> er main idea was more on the sort of friend or foe not choices <pause dur="short"/> cos it was things like</u>
<u n="99" who="S0175">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0109">um put around the room various um I don't know like superheroes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0175">mhm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0109">or whatever and their nemeses and their sidekicks <pause dur="short"/> and you have to decide</u>
<u n="103" who="S0175"></u>
<u n="104" who="S0109">whether it's a pair or not <pause dur="short"/> and mix in some history or <unclear/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0175">but you could do that as the quiet game</u>
<u n="106" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0175">you could have pictures and facts on bits of paper and they've got to match them up <pause dur="short"/> so they have like a picture of superheroes <pause dur="short"/> there's a picture of nemesis <pause dur="short"/> a picture of sidekicks <pause dur="short"/> there's a page of sidekicks <pause dur="short"/> a page of facts or something <pause dur="short"/> don't know what the facts are anything to do with <pause dur="short"/> but anyhow</u>
<u n="108" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0175">and you can match them all up</u>
<u n="110" who="S0109">that would  that would  be nice and quiet</u>
<u n="111" who="S0175">would be nice and quiet and it'd be quite fun <pause dur="short"/> superheroes is quite fun</u>
<u n="112" who="S0109">A bit woolly</u>
<u n="113" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/> A bit woolly indeed <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0109">er</u>
<u n="115" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like that idea <pause dur="short"/> cos that can that'd be a great quiet game <pause dur="short"/> superheroes <pause dur="short"/> great <pause dur="short"/> um so when they arrive we're doing flowers <pause dur="short"/> maybe Simon Says or something <pause dur="short"/> um it might <trunc>wor</trunc> be worth having another game up our sleeves just in case</u>
<u n="116" who="S0109"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> decides to bring an army of friends <unclear/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or it it might also be well cos for some well for some years the flowers haven't taken that long because it's just been you know three things tie fine <pause dur="short"/> but last year we had take this  take this  take the do this <pause dur="short"/> put it in a cellophane <pause dur="short"/> like tie that with an elastic band <pause dur="short"/> put it in a</u>
<u n="118" who="S0109">they were nice last year</u>
<u n="119" who="S0175">cellophane thing <pause dur="short"/> then get a ribbon <pause dur="short"/> tie that <pause dur="short"/> and then use scissors to curl the ribbon <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> The number of <trunc>cu</trunc> things I cut <pause dur="short"/> I was a wreck at that bit <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um and obviously each year we're doing more and more as well</u>
<u n="120" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0175">I think we should allow half an hour <pause dur="short"/> say we start at seven twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> say seven fifty-five Simon Says <pause dur="short"/> you've got eight O five snacks haven't you <pause dur="short"/> I think it's probably fine <pause dur="short"/> we won't play Simon Says for five minutes <pause dur="short"/> we might just get another game in there <pause dur="short"/> and then eight ten question of the week <pause dur="short"/> eight twenty small groups <pause dur="short"/> er what you've got isn't it?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0109">er yeah but there's it's all movable</u>
<u n="123" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0109">I just</u>
<u n="125" who="S0175">it's just good starting off with it <pause dur="short"/> um eight it's gonna have to be they're gonna have to give twenty minutes to small group time <pause dur="short"/> there's no way we're gonna do it in fifteen minutes <pause dur="short"/> there's no point being unrealistic just er <pause dur="short"/> eight forty big game <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0109">noisy big game <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="127" who="S0175">so the other ideas I had <pause dur="short"/> er we could adapt giants wizards and dwarfs</u>
<u n="128" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0175">because that's kind of friend or foe like <pause dur="short"/> um we could do something called twin tag which is a bit like it <pause dur="short"/> or you could do a variation perhaps like stick in the mud where everyone runs round with like arm linked with somebody else at all times <pause dur="short"/> and so you physically</u>
<u n="130" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0175">I haven't worked out how exactly that would work <pause dur="short"/> but I'm sure we can work out something out</u>
<u n="132" who="S0109">I'd love to see them burrowing through people's legs</u>
<u n="133" who="S0175">together? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0175">it could be a game <trunc>c</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Or could run off backwards <unclear/> But er there's some you could probably do something like that <pause dur="short"/> um you could do um say talking about sort of <trunc>fr</trunc> foe um friend how many people can we get into an area or into a <trunc>tab</trunc> onto a table <pause dur="short"/> but not up here <pause dur="short"/> like low down <pause dur="short"/> so could we get everybody standing on a table this size? Well yes <pause dur="short"/> could we get everybody standing on the the shorter tables? Possibly not <pause dur="short"/> could we get everyone standing in a very small area of masking tape? So you can have in the</u>
<u n="136" who="S0109">getting very friendly <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0175">you can  you can  get people yeah exactly <vocal desc="laugh"/> people on their shoulders or um <pause dur="short"/> and everyone's got to have  everyone's got to have  yeah they can have just one toe in the box but they can't have the other foot on the ground <pause dur="short"/> it has to be up in the air <pause dur="short"/> so they can kinda you can kinda like lean out and or balance or something <pause dur="short"/> and you get quite a lot of people that way</u>
<u n="138" who="S0109">uh-huh</u>
<u n="139" who="S0175">all kinds of things</u>
<u n="140" who="S0109">how you seen that work? What?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0175">well no I just <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just on this website <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was looking at <pause dur="short"/> this game website <pause dur="short"/> um so we could do something like that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0175">again that's something we could do which doesn't take much prep <pause dur="short"/> um cos you can just have a couple of tables and then some masking tape on the floor <pause dur="short"/> um I <trunc>fe</trunc> if we had mm I was gonna say if we had nine square out cos if we have nine square out none of the boys will do the flowers</u>
<u n="144" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hello <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0175">hello</u>
<u n="146" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh <pause dur="short"/> you come for <unclear/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0109">very early</u>
<u n="149" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="151" who="S0175">we've come to eat the Mini Rolls and flapjacks actually</u>
<u n="152" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0109">hm</u>
<u n="154" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you don't have another key? My key's at Tesco being recut</u>
<u n="155" who="S0175">I don't have a key for that one I'm afraid</u>
<u n="156" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="157" who="S0175">sadly <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to have a key for that one</u>
<u n="158" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<u n="159" who="S0175">it would be very useful</u>
<u n="160" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I know</u>
<u n="161" who="S0175">but I don't <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">well <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> let's hope that Steve <unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0175">there's probably a key in the filing cabinet where the spare keys are kept</u>
<u n="164" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">true <pause dur="short"/> which I could just borrow couldn't I <pause dur="short"/> well done</u>
<u n="165" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="167" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">are you doing your Pathfinder planning?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> er I thought we could is this if we have more time I don't  I don't  think we'll have the time for this we could get them to design an obstacle course for one another <pause dur="short"/> and you can either be friendly or you can be foe like</u>
<u n="173" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0175">this was before I got to my choices thing <pause dur="short"/> so give them <trunc>s</trunc> like material so <trunc>ch</trunc> so I'd say obviously they've got chairs and tables and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but you know how we often make obstacle courses <pause dur="short"/> they could design one for the other team</u>
<u n="175" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">see you soon</u>
<u n="176" who="S0175">all the teams <pause dur="short"/> see you</u>
<u n="177" who="S0109">see you</u>
<u n="178" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">bye <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> memory verse game? We haven't got memory verse game yet</u>
<u n="180" who="S0109">what is our memory verse?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0175">it's um <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> three thirty-six which is I can't I haven't actually learnt it yet <pause dur="short"/> um <unclear/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0109"><vocal desc="misc"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0175">it's about something like um tut <pause dur="long"/> anybody who confesses no that's Romans Jesus is Lord is saved but anyone who does not will not  will not  have life but will have eternal separation or something <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um John three thirty-six <pause dur="short"/> can't remember exactly <pause dur="short"/> john <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> Oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> they will not see life cos God's wrath remains on them or something <unclear/> Whoever believes in the Son has eternal life but whoever rejects the Son will not see life because God's wrath remains on him <pause dur="short"/> so it's our way or God's new way are the two ways to live</u>
<u n="184" who="S0109">mhm <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> it's quite long</u>
<u n="185" who="S0175">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> They're all quite yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> though the idea I had with this to do with choices was like hangman somehow <pause dur="short"/> so they they'd do something and then they go up to a table and they say can I have the letter E and they go back somewhere else or <trunc>perha</trunc> perhaps go to a third place er where there's a leader with their with the blanks <pause dur="short"/> and they say E and then the leader's there writes down all the Es <pause dur="short"/> um and then they go back to their basic like their home base again <pause dur="short"/> and then the next person does whatever they have to do and then goes to the table and says R <pause dur="short"/> and then the then goes to the wherever the leader with their piece of paper is and says R <pause dur="short"/> but you have to do it carefully because you don't want other teams to see one another's answers <pause dur="short"/> otherwise they can just</u>
<u n="186" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0175">so they don't know which <unclear/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0109">so you could have them set up at the either side of the room <pause dur="short"/> but you'd only have be able to have about two teams</u>
<u n="189" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hadn't really thought it through completely</u>
<u n="190" who="S0109">no just thinking out now</u>
<u n="191" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="192" who="S0109">so would they huh would this have to come before</u>
<u n="193" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0109">question of the week?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> normally it does doesn't it</u>
<u n="196" who="S0109">I was just thinking if they were doing hangman <unclear/> oh no with that whole verse that's long <pause dur="short"/> no?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0175">yes but you see there's quite there's er you know it just means that actually cos you here once you have E get all the Es</u>
<u n="198" who="S0109">ah and there's a lot of Os</u>
<u n="199" who="S0175">and there's a lot of Os <pause dur="short"/> and there's a lot of I don't think I just don't think it's too bad <pause dur="short"/> it probably has most letters in it in fact</u>
<u n="200" who="S0109">uh-huh</u>
<u n="201" who="S0175">it has Js and Vs and Bs <pause dur="short"/> and like it has quite a good I haven't actually worked out what letters it has in it <pause dur="short"/> but they could even have a bible so that they can even look it up <pause dur="short"/> and then they could just go back and say what letters they want <pause dur="short"/> if they were given the numbers but not the words</u>
<u n="202" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0175">then even if they started with those <trunc>wor</trunc> those words they'd have a start <pause dur="short"/> you know the verse and chapter <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Or three dot dot three they'd say it's probably we know we ought to write out the words <pause dur="short"/> but anyhow that was a an idea I had</u>
<u n="204" who="S0109">I like it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0175">but if we're doing it before the question of the week that probably means it doesn't <unclear/> Simon Says <pause dur="short"/> which is fine cos sometimes it's <trunc>cr</trunc> it's fairly</u>
<u n="206" who="S0109">how yeah we need to make it so would they have something to do in their groups in order <trunc>befo</trunc> before they could go and say a letter</u>
<u n="207" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0109">and they in which case it would need to be quite snappy</u>
<u n="209" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="short"/> otherwise I mean everything <unclear/> they can just run and get a letter</u>
<u n="210" who="S0109">they definitely need to run</u>
<u n="211" who="S0175">they definitely need to run <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="212" who="S0109">um</u>
<u n="213" who="S0175">um so realistically how many might we have? How many teams might we need to have? Maximum four teams <pause dur="short"/> possibly three teams normally isn't it</u>
<u n="214" who="S0109">it's normally three</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="215" who="S0175">I mean you could have one lot in the créche um with the doors open but so that the words kind of <trunc>w</trunc> I can't remember where the pinboards are but anyhow somewhere in the créche <pause dur="short"/> um one lot using that blue thing um in that area there <pause dur="short"/> so the blue so they're using the side you can't see from if you're running backwards and forwards <pause dur="short"/> and one lot behind one of the <trunc>curt</trunc> or behind the curtains or behind part of the curtains <pause dur="short"/> or even against that wall there behind the curtain</u>
<u n="216" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0175">um with one curtain closed <pause dur="short"/> and then they could all run to the spot in the middle here which is quite <trunc>e</trunc> quite even for them to run to</u>
<u n="218" who="S0109">mhm <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="219" who="S0175">is that enough running?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0109">so they start from there <pause dur="short"/> and then they run out here <pause dur="short"/> and then they how how does that work in terms of or or do they start there and the boards are there and they run for the boards? Because otherwise all the boards would be here and they'll see what the teams are doing</u>
<u n="221" who="S0175">but we could introduce a bit more running by them running to get the place where you get letters from and then going back again</u>
<u n="222" who="S0109">oh</u>
<u n="223" who="S0175">is what I was thinking <pause dur="short"/> so you get to run twice</u>
<u n="224" who="S0109">uh-huh</u>
<u n="225" who="S0175">um but it's not very far for them to run but it's some distance for them to run <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how many letters there are <pause dur="short"/> and the thing is that they might come back with so I reckon <trunc>wi</trunc> the <trunc>l</trunc> leader there at the <trunc>ba</trunc> or the <trunc>le</trunc> or the leader is at the bank like and have three stations would have the <trunc>s</trunc> blank bits of paper and a pen and say when the person comes and says I want an E they just write a capital E</u>
<u n="226" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0175">just one <pause dur="short"/> and give that to them <pause dur="short"/> they run back <pause dur="short"/> give that to the leader who's in there <pause dur="short"/> and then that gets pinned up somewhere so they can all see they've <trunc>h</trunc> they've had the letter E <pause dur="short"/> and then the leader can then have a bit of time to write down all the Es <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> From their like crib sheet <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0109">uh-huh</u>
<u n="229" who="S0175">um which somehow they've got to do without the others seeing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0109">do you this is</u>
<u n="231" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0109">just to introduce a bit of choice</u>
<u n="233" who="S0175">yes</u>
<u n="234" who="S0109">could they do something where if they they can either come and ask for for a letter</u>
<u n="235" who="S0175">yes</u>
<u n="236" who="S0109">or they can ask for a riddle or a challenge or something and if they <trunc>p</trunc> get it right then they get a word?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0175">oo</u>
<u n="238" who="S0109">so the they can take the time and speed things up perhaps depending on their ability <pause dur="short"/> or answer a question <pause dur="short"/> or something <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> they still have to go back to their team presumably</u>
<u n="239" who="S0175">or if they get the question right they get two letters <pause dur="short"/> cos getting one <trunc>let</trunc> one word does help but it doesn't help you with the other cos doesn't help you with any other words does there</u>
<u n="240" who="S0109">no but they have to cotton onto that</u>
<u n="241" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0109">no <trunc>t</trunc> two letters would work <pause dur="short"/> I mean some of those are quite long words aren't they</u>
<u n="243" who="S0175">yeah <pause dur="long"/> Guess they're having to choose which letter they want</u>
<u n="244" who="S0109">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="245" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> we just don't wanna take too long <pause dur="short"/> cos we haven't got much time I don't think</u>
<u n="246" who="S0109">no and running twenty-six times back and forth is not going to take too long anyway</u>
<u n="247" who="S0175">no <pause dur="short"/> and hopefully they won't run more than that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> They might do if they keep on asking for Es all the time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay</u>
<u n="248" who="S0109">right should we <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="249" who="S0175">should we just scrap that instead of Simon Says and do Simon Says?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0109">and then memory verse</u>
<u n="251" who="S0175">okay <pause dur="short"/> then we'll snacks <pause dur="short"/> then question of the week <pause dur="short"/> then small group time <pause dur="short"/> and then we need a fun game</u>
<u n="252" who="S0109">or two fun games</u>
<u n="253" who="S0175">two fun games <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> eight forty and eight fifty</u>
<u n="254" who="S0109">we haven't played dwarfs giants thingies for a while</u>
<u n="255" who="S0175">no <pause dur="short"/> although there are three sets then and there are three ways to live</u>
<u n="256" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0109">that's true</u>
<u n="258" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I just realized that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0109">maybe we <trunc>sh</trunc> shouldn't do that</u>
<u n="260" who="S0175">I just realized that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Maybe we could just do it with two <pause dur="short"/> and either you're a friend or a foe <pause dur="short"/> either you're the same but that doesn't really work either <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0109">but</u>
<u n="262" who="S0175">maybe it's epistemologically too tight <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0109">mm <pause dur="short"/> you want to avoid stalemate one don't you <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0175">um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="265" who="S0109">hm <pause dur="long"/> What other choices games or friend or foe games are there?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="266" who="S0175">maybe we should just do giants wizards and dwarfs because it <trunc>fi</trunc> fits with like friend and foe and it's quite fun <pause dur="short"/> and if we <trunc>d</trunc> do it the last game it doesn't really matter that it doesn't really tie in with the question of the week cos it's been a long time <pause dur="short"/> I mean we've got lots of things that do tie in with the question of the week</u>
<u n="267" who="S0109">mhm <pause dur="short"/> and if it gets swished out it gets</u>
<u n="268" who="S0175">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0109">um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="270" who="S0175">and basically they're always foe unless they are the same <pause dur="short"/> is that right? In which case they're friends <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> There's always one way round where there's one beats the other <pause dur="short"/> but if they both teams come together and they're the same then they're</u>
<u n="271" who="S0109">yes</u>
<u n="272" who="S0175">is that right?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0109">yes</u>
<u n="274" who="S0175">Cos they're friends</u>
<u n="275" who="S0109">yep</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="276" who="S0175">what happens if you have three teams? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Does it work? <vocal desc="laugh"/> They could all end up chasing one another <pause dur="short"/> or they <vocal desc="laugh"/> could have two team one team chasing after two teams <pause dur="short"/> or <vocal desc="laugh"/> two teams chasing after one team <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0109"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Or just a huge group hug</u>
<u n="278" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Or a group <trunc>hu</trunc> hug <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0109">that could be qiute fun <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0175">okay</u>
<u n="281" who="S0109">it could be chaos <pause dur="short"/> it could be fun</u>
<u n="282" who="S0175">let's just think whether or not that will actually work logistically <pause dur="short"/> well I think it would be <trunc>c</trunc> complete chaos <pause dur="short"/> I quite like <unclear/> chaotic cos it's just very funny <pause dur="short"/> especially as no one understands what they have to do anyway <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> They have three teams against argh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Am I running or not? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't run <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0109">the basic principle is just run</u>
<u n="284" who="S0175">run <pause dur="short"/> no <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it depends which direction <pause dur="short"/> when both of them run off in opposite directions you're going one of these obviously not right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay <pause dur="short"/> and then we've got the eight forty game</u>
<u n="285" who="S0109">mm <pause dur="short"/> as much as I like the obstacle I think it would be too</u>
<u n="286" who="S0175">I think it'll take too long won't it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0109">long</u>
<u n="288" who="S0175">hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="289" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hiya</u>
<u n="290" who="S0175">yeah I think you're right <pause dur="short"/> I think it'll take too long <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="291" who="S0109">I am rubbish tonight</u>
<u n="292" who="S0175"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="293" who="S0109">it's not really a running around game</u>
<u n="294" who="S0175">mhm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0109">but I just wondered about something where they had um they had to basically sort themselves out into teams um by a sort of twenty questions sort of scenario where they wander round <pause dur="short"/> and they've got I don't know their their name or of who they are or their team or whatever stuck on their back <pause dur="short"/> and they have to sort themselves out and find out whether they're a friend or a foe to the people</u>
<u n="296" who="S0175">hm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0109">who they're with <pause dur="short"/> but it's more of an opener than a an eight forty game</u>
<u n="298" who="S0175">mm <pause dur="long"/> Quite like the idea though of having some kind of category then they've gotta get themselves into groups <unclear/> that somehow</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="299" who="S0109">or for the choices thing something where <trunc>th</trunc> where they mm it's a bit battleshipy sort of thing where there's a right or a wrong thing to be revealed <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="300" who="S0175">I thought about battleships cos I heard quite recently where if you go where you could have friendly fire somehow</u>
<u n="301" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0175">enemy fire and friendly fire with <vocal desc="laugh"/> mistakes and things like that <pause dur="short"/> but I couldn't work out how to do that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="303" who="S0109">or Mafia</u>
<u n="304" who="S0175">or Mafia <pause dur="short"/> yeah where you've got somebody who um yeah you don't know if they're friend or foe and you've gotta work it out</u>
<u n="305" who="S0109">oh let's play Mafia <pause dur="short"/> I like Mafia <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0175">okay <pause dur="short"/> I never really played Mafia so you can run  you can run  Mafia <pause dur="short"/> the boys love Mafia don't they <pause dur="short"/> how long does it take to play?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0109">er how long is a piece of string?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0175">Great <pause dur="short"/> perfect <pause dur="short"/> so we can judge see how they're doing whether we want to go into giants wizards and dwarfs or not</u>
<u n="309" who="S0109">mhm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0175">Cos it's a sitting down game isn't it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0109">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0175">but it's fun</u>
<u n="313" who="S0109">it'll also depend on their age <pause dur="short"/> like if we've got a particularly young group then we'll wanna cut it short <pause dur="short"/> cos they'll be a bit bored</u>
<u n="314" who="S0175">okay <pause dur="short"/> well that's fine <pause dur="short"/> and we can always <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0109"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0175">if we need to <pause dur="short"/> or Simon Says <pause dur="short"/> if we need to</u>
<u n="317" who="S0109">that's true</u>
<u n="318" who="S0175">I'll put that back up <pause dur="short"/> simon Says <pause dur="long"/> Great <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I will liaise with whoever's <trunc>l</trunc> doing flowers to work out what we need to do <pause dur="short"/> and where they're gonna be <pause dur="short"/> and all that kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> because we're gonna get some instructions <pause dur="short"/> and I'm basically free not completely free on Friday but I can be free on Friday if I need to be taught how to do something</u>
<u n="319" who="S0109">mm <pause dur="short"/> I will prepare the game for finishers early finishers</u>
<u n="320" who="S0175">excellent <pause dur="short"/> and can you run Mafia please?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0175">Cos I don't know how to do that <pause dur="short"/> um shall I think about the logistics of the hangman game?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0109">cool</u>
<u n="324" who="S0175">um <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> then it's just that's it isn't it <pause dur="short"/> giants wizards and <trunc>g</trunc> dwarfs we've just gotta decide who beats who <pause dur="short"/> um and then we'll probably want to do the opening prayers before <trunc>pla</trunc> doing I'll do the opening prayer <pause dur="short"/> are you happy to do the closing prayer?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0175">and <unclear/> I guess <pause dur="short"/> I think Scott's still gonna get snacks for us</u>
<u n="327" who="S0109">excellent</u>
<u n="328" who="S0175">Great</u>
<u n="329" who="S0109">and a final question <pause dur="short"/> would you like me to cook?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0175">oh I'd love you to cook</u>
<u n="331" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0175">I think it's meant to be my turn but I would love that <pause dur="short"/> I'm cooking for the Bickerstaffes this weekend I</u>
<u n="333" who="S0109">okay</u>
<u n="334" who="S0175">or this  or this  week even</u>
<u n="335" who="S0109">er how many people should I prepare for?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0175">mm <pause dur="short"/> if all the Pathfinder leaders are there <pause dur="short"/> I think we've got eight now <pause dur="short"/> um but I'm not sure we are all there <pause dur="short"/> um plus probably Nick and Scott <pause dur="short"/> rick has a small amount if he comes <pause dur="short"/> I'd normally cook for about ten <pause dur="short"/> in your mind cook for about ten people <pause dur="short"/> cos we can stretch it</u>
<u n="337" who="S0109">mhm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0175">and have smaller portions if need be</u>
<u n="339" who="S0109">okay <pause dur="short"/> we can always</u>
<u n="340" who="S0175">but it's like ten normal portions</u>
<u n="341" who="S0109">cook more carbs</u>
<u n="342" who="S0175">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> we can always cook more more rice</u>
<u n="343" who="S0109">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0175">is that alright?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0109">mhm <pause dur="short"/> that's perfect</u>
<u n="346" who="S0175"><unclear/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0109">I like having two weeks' notice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0175">yeah exactly you've got it means you've got a good amount of weekend to do it in</u>
<u n="349" who="S0109">well I haven't but</u>
<u n="350" who="S0175">okay <pause dur="short"/> you're away</u>
<u n="351" who="S0109">I can do it next week</u>
<u n="352" who="S0175">okay <pause dur="short"/> well at least you've got time to work out when you're gonna do it</u>
<u n="353" who="S0109">yep</u>
<u n="354" who="S0175">that's wonderful <pause dur="short"/> um yeah <pause dur="short"/> great</u>
<u n="355" who="S0109">mm <pause dur="short"/> wondering why it's on hold</u>
</body>
</text>
