<text id="SB49">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:46</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0283</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>A weekend away, décor and furniture of various houses, holiday homes</topics>
		<activity>Spouses discussing families' homes</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring,  anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T01</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0283">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Civil servant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0282">okay so what do you think of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0283">I was really impressed I thought it was going to a bit scraggedy and I didn't think that it would have the fantastic view that it's got and I thought that the erm garden and the meadow was superb I thought the way that it was <pause dur="short"/> laid out was actually really good so I thought it was a very nice house actually and very easy for a large number of people to live in</u>
<u n="3" who="S0282">and what well how did you feel about all their furnishings and everything cos I thought that everything being standardised like that I didn't know if that was a good operate or a bad operate cos it was a bit homogeneous in a way but then on the other hand it looked very clean and neat and and usable</u>
<u n="4" who="S0283">I didn't mind it being homogeneous at all I thought it's actually quite sensible to just go through the shops and buy a house <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Christmas delivered from <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> or whatever it was</u>
<u n="5" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0283">and a good <unclear/> erm no I think I don't know I think <pause dur="short"/> actually I it's it's it's sometimes a bit <pause dur="short"/> off-putting when you go to someone's or when you go to the country when when you go to a cottage and <pause dur="short"/> and you get scrag ends of furniture and scrag ends of cutlery and scrag ends of crockery and nothing fits together and it's all the seconds or all the stuff that's been thrown away so I think</u>
<u n="7" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah but that's like our house that's like our normal house that we live in now not like a holiday cottage</u>
<u n="8" who="S0283" trans="overlap">not well no</u>
<u n="9" who="S0282">goodness what our holiday cottage would be like it'd be like your granny's house</u>
<u n="10" who="S0283">well exactly</u>
<u n="11" who="S0282">a health asset</u>
<u n="12" who="S0283">I don't think my granny's house would be a health asset she</u>
<u n="13" who="S0282" trans="overlap">your mum said it was a health asset</u>
<u n="14" who="S0283" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc> my granny lived till ninety-four didn't she? so she can't</u>
<u n="15" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah but she would</u>
<u n="16" who="S0283">can't be that much of a health asset erm and my granddad lived till ninety-four as well erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>e</trunc> yeah no I know it's it's not the way that we live <pause dur="short"/> it's not the way that we live although having said that <pause dur="short"/> we do still every night eat off the <trunc>habit</trunc>habitat crockery that I bought when I first moved into my flat twenty-nine thousand years ago</u>
<u n="17" who="S0282">but and the relevance of that is what?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0283">that actually I do quite like sets of things in order imagine what you do is to go and buy different sets of crockery every week <pause dur="short"/> and and then just put them all in the cupboard and not use them</u>
<u n="19" who="S0282">no <trunc>c</trunc> that's cos <unclear/> look at so it's no that's different <trunc>i</trunc>it is a different debate but then does that do you think that means that when they come here they look at all our stuff and they go oh dude oh oh?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0283">I don't think they use that tone of voice no</u>
<u n="21" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes but we are down the opposite end of the scale we are I mean you know look this is your granny's thing and actually</u>
<u n="22" who="S0283" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="23" who="S0282">it still got your granny's lace making things inside it I'm not I'm not</u>
<u n="24" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="25" who="S0282">a funny <unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0283" trans="overlap">but the at <trunc>the</trunc> at <trunc>the</trunc> at their main home their main home is mix and match and hotchpotch that actually although <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="27" who="S0282" trans="overlap">is it?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0283">yes it is it is</u>
<u n="29" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no it's all it's all er taped sofas and and</u>
<u n="30" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no it's not</u>
<u n="31" who="S0282">and sail cloth walls and</u>
<u n="32" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no the sitting <trunc>roo</trunc> the sitting room <trunc>up</trunc></u>
<u n="33" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it is</u>
<u n="34" who="S0283">the sitting room upstairs for example's got some global IKEA bookcases and then some BILLY bookcases</u>
<u n="35" who="S0282">and a pink carpet</u>
<u n="36" who="S0283">and a pink carpet</u>
<u n="37" who="S0282">but nobody ever goes in there</u>
<u n="38" who="S0283">no well we don't even</u>
<u n="39" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and actually those chairs those two chairs are now down in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0283">I know er I think actually that the</u>
<u n="41" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh you're actually sitting in that chair</u>
<u n="42" who="S0283">yes</u>
<u n="43" who="S0282">as if nobody usually sat in that chair</u>
<u n="44" who="S0283">and she didn't say that she said oh I see you've you've managed to make use of the chair is what she said</u>
<u n="45" who="S0282">well that also suggests that it's not been made use of</u>
<u n="46" who="S0283">they <trunc>i</trunc>it suggests they had a conversation as to whether or not to take it down there and <pause dur="short"/> chose in the end to do so but I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> whether she was taken a piss out of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sitting in a chair that he hadn't sat since he brought it down or whether she was saying see? I told you that we need to take this chair down</u>
<u n="47" who="S0282">do you think it was a marital?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0283">almost certainly</u>
<u n="49" who="S0282">do you think so?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0283">not a proper one they don't I think they're quite content with each other at the moment I don't think <trunc>i</trunc>it was a sort of marital that we might have</u>
<u n="51" who="S0282">mm ah <pause dur="short"/> and it's quite</u>
<u n="52" who="S0283">why are you doing all this dirty lining washing in front of all these people?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0282">no I'm not no it's just no I'm interested in what you think and I was just saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that I wouldn't want <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't want to have a house that I left sitting there in the middle of nowhere for days and days on end and didn't go back to in case <pause dur="short"/> you know well I don't know I would I would either want to be there all the time or I would resent that I wasn't there all the time and think <pause dur="short"/> you know why</u>
<u n="54" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="55" who="S0282">why until I why am I here?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0283">but the question</u>
<u n="57" who="S0282" trans="overlap">or else I'd forget about it and I would say oh my goodness it cost me so much money and why <trunc>unti</trunc> you know I should be there because actually the heating's been on for three days but I've not been having the benefit of it</u>
<u n="58" who="S0283" trans="overlap">but I think the question is I think the question is why do you want it what do you want it for <pause dur="short"/> er because <pause dur="short"/> they might want to live in the country <pause dur="short"/> but they can't because of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> so you know until <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> leaves school <pause dur="short"/> they pretty much have to live near the school they want to be in and it's not gonna be <anon type="place"/> cos she has to grow up with friends <pause dur="short"/> so they</u>
<u n="59" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well she could have new friends</u>
<u n="60" who="S0283"><trunc>w</trunc> but I think often they probably have to be in London <pause dur="short"/> so they're then thinking okay we want somewhere that's a bolt-hole <pause dur="short"/> er and so they got that place which is actually fine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying that it was on the outside of the <pause dur="short"/> erm area they were looking at because of its distance from London we wouldn't want a place like that <trunc>w</trunc>what we have done is to move out of London <pause dur="short"/> so that we actually have that tranquillity in our daily home so we have a larger home with a larger garden with tranquillity which is absolutely fantastic that's what we want <pause dur="short"/> and then when we need to go to London we go to London <pause dur="short"/> and I go to London every day to work so I don't think the question arises <trunc>wh</trunc> and we have thought as to whether or not if we ever had any money we might <pause dur="short"/> get a country <pause dur="short"/> a a <trunc>ho</trunc> a a little cottage in the country I don't think we need to you know</u>
<u n="61" who="S0282">no but I think we also had the debate when we said well you could go somewhere different every time and actually it might be a bit constricting to have to go somewhere to the same place every time and that actually you might want to have a look at the country because and you know and go to different places like when we did all those cottages in the south-east of England that we were going to different cottages each time</u>
<u n="62" who="S0283" trans="overlap">we were</u>
<u n="63" who="S0282">and they were perhaps only ten or fifteen miles distant from each other but we saw something different and went to different places each time</u>
<u n="64" who="S0283">but then</u>
<u n="65" who="S0282">and we didn't we weren't <trunc>g</trunc> oh yes let's go back to Shrewsbury let's show those people Shrewsbury cos they haven't seen Shrewsbury yet but we'd seen Shrewsbury every weekend for the last six months cos</u>
<u n="66" who="S0283"><trunc>bu</trunc>but they have a they have a bit of what I was going to say is again as I said over the weekend actually <trunc>i</trunc>if they have taken into decision in their mid-forties to buy a place that they can go to ten times a year <pause dur="short"/> for the next forty years <pause dur="short"/> that's four hundred times <pause dur="short"/> that they're going to go there so that doesn't you know if they go there once a month</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282">is that only a pound a time then?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0283">it's a thousand pounds a time</u>
<u n="69" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's still got expensive that isn't it?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0283" trans="overlap">but it's <pause dur="short"/> yes it is <trunc>ok</trunc> but they still they still have a very <unclear/> erm if they go there <trunc>o</trunc> if they go there once a month for the next forty years <pause dur="short"/> then they can go you know once every two months to somewhere else as well</u>
<u n="71" who="S0282"><vocal desc="misc"/> well I don't think anybody goes there that often do they? and what about you know your aunt and uncle with that place in Wales where er goodness knows that must be absolutely a grim time to leave London and get to Wales on a Friday night</u>
<u n="72" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well yeah but they've done it most weekends for the last forty years</u>
<u n="73" who="S0282">really? most weekends?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0283">a lot of weekends</u>
<u n="75" who="S0282" trans="overlap">is that true?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0283"><trunc>mayb</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> at least once a month</u>
<u n="77" who="S0282">really?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0283">they go there a lot <pause dur="short"/> and now they're giving up in <trunc>the</trunc> in <trunc>the</trunc> in their eighties</u>
<u n="79" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0283">as they're older than mum he's older</u>
<u n="81" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes he is older</u>
<u n="82" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah so he's in his mid-eighties or his early eighties</u>
<u n="83" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0283">so they've been going there for forty years I I <trunc>th</trunc> you know I think it's er just it's a choice that you make <pause dur="short"/> and for the benefit of those listening on this tape we're now watching er with one eye Jamie Oliver poke a bit of rosemary through some bacon</u>
<u n="85" who="S0282">no no it's er devils on horseback</u>
<u n="86" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="87" who="S0282" trans="overlap">he's making devils on horseback erm yes okay well erm <pause dur="short"/> how old are they? yes he must be well into his if your mum is eighty</u>
<u n="88" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well she's she's not eighty she's</u>
<u n="89" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no she's not eighty yet</u>
<u n="90" who="S0283">she's seventy-eight erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0282">but he's he's a few years older than her</u>
<u n="92" who="S0283" trans="overlap">I mean yeah she's seventy-eight <pause dur="short"/> and he's a couple of years older than her so he's about eighty</u>
<u n="93" who="S0282">oh is that? oh hang on a second that party when was that last party? was that his eightieth? his eightieth and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s thirtieth fortieth</u>
<u n="94" who="S0283">fiftieth</u>
<u n="95" who="S0282">fiftieth</u>
<u n="96" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0282">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah well I don't know</u>
<u n="98" who="S0283" trans="overlap">that was last year</u>
<u n="99" who="S0282">I mean er would you go to oh er I can't I can't imagine I would I think I would just end up feeling</u>
<u n="100" who="S0283">well from <anon type="place"/> that was a bit of a pain in the backside</u>
<u n="101" who="S0282">well at least they were on the west hand side of London</u>
<u n="102" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you know it's not the they haven't they're not starting out from <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="104" who="S0283">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but erm er I think I would end up I would end up feeling that it was a chore I think</u>
<u n="106" who="S0283">I would go</u>
<u n="107" who="S0282" trans="overlap">to have to go there on a Friday</u>
<u n="108" who="S0283">I would go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I mean to sort of</u>
<u n="110" who="S0283">from here but I wouldn't go to <anon type="place"/> from where they live</u>
<u n="111" who="S0282">no but even here I mean and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was just talking a while ago about when they had to go down and see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents in erm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0283" trans="overlap">mm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0282"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0283">no <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> and how grim it was on the M3</u>
<u n="116" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0282">on a <pause dur="short"/> friday <pause dur="short"/> and how er and how the only way they could do it was to go home have their dinner <pause dur="short"/> and then set off at eight o'clock or nine o'clock at night and that was the only way to get through there with a clear run because at any other time that you might choose any time over the weekend</u>
<u n="118" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0282">you just got stuck in a traffic jam on that on the A303 or whatever it is</u>
<u n="120" who="S0283">well as I say if he was driving from here and he didn't have to get out of London <pause dur="short"/> that's one thing but the thought of going to the M3 <pause dur="short"/> every Friday is just a pain in the back side</u>
<u n="121" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0283">and then having to get past <anon type="place"/> every Friday is a pain in the back side</u>
<u n="123" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0283">but then <pause dur="long"/> I think two hours <pause dur="short"/> is broadly <trunc>accep</trunc> well it took two hours to get to the cottage</u>
<u n="125" who="S0282">mm no no</u>
<u n="126" who="S0283" trans="overlap">more than two hours more <trunc>th</trunc> er but you would want to do it for a long weekend and not for three not for two days</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282">well just you know the way we've <trunc>d</trunc> honestly you've hardly got time to turn round haven't you? I mean and look at them we've left them next day and they've got how many they've got six duvets to wash and God knows what you know so actually how can you <trunc>e</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> you know it's this lovely idea that you have people for the weekend but the dishwasher went I don't know how many times you got all that washing</u>
<u n="128" who="S0283" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="129" who="S0282">on the Friday night and you got the cleaning</u>
<u n="130" who="S0283" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="131" who="S0282">ah did you hear what erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s place? <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc> erm their bed their bed had no bed <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> slept by other people their bed was absolutely filthy and she said when you went to get after the shower you put you looked down and put to put your foot on the bathmat and the bathmat was absolutely filthy and they didn't know and everything in the in the house was utterly filthy <pause dur="short"/> so you know other people who'd been invited for the weekend had slept in that bed and they hadn't cleaned they hadn't changed the beds</u>
<u n="132" who="S0283">my parents would</u>
<u n="133" who="S0282" trans="overlap">she said <trunc>th</trunc> and she said they were really <trunc>di</trunc> really disgusted</u>
<u n="134" who="S0283">well I hope the people who've been there before were <unclear>cautious</unclear></u>
<u n="135" who="S0282">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0283">what are we testing this for? is this for idiom is this for what?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0282">I've got to send it to them in order to</u>
<u n="138" who="S0283">but what are they testing for?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0282">for audibility <trunc>usea</trunc>useablity</u>
<u n="140" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no no what what what do they want to pick up? the use of idiom or use of language linguistics or what?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0282">erm <pause dur="short"/> that is comparative <pause dur="short"/> well the reason I'm doing the test this test</u>
<u n="142" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no I know I know I know I know</u>
<u n="143" who="S0282" trans="overlap">alright it's okay fine the reason they're doing this is because they're comparing the past recordings of people <trunc>p</trunc> speaking in the past</u>
<u n="144" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0282" trans="overlap">they specifically want people who're indigenous English speakers English is their first language and they were brought up in this country</u>
<u n="146" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0282">because it is about the use of English language <pause dur="short"/> some of them <unclear/> was they're particularly interested in young people and teenagers and how they spoke so next <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="148" who="S0283" trans="overlap">it's gonna be reem innit?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0282">yeah <trunc>w</trunc> so I suppose it's probably then about <trunc>langua</trunc> <trunc>u</trunc>use of language use of idioms use of of of of erm <pause dur="short"/> their slang</u>
<u n="150" who="S0283" trans="overlap">jargon slang</u>
<u n="151" who="S0282" trans="overlap">slang etcetera etcetera and also I suppose probably also it'll be census construction and</u>
<u n="152" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0282">and vocabulary and stuff like that so I I would imagine it's gonna be about vocabulary as well you know how big people's vocabulary is and how erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> is or</u>
<u n="154" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0282">how wide ranging <trunc>th</trunc>the number of words that people use in general conversation etcetera</u>
<u n="156" who="S0283">interesting well that's an interesting study</u>
<u n="157" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0283" trans="overlap">we've done twelve minutes now which is probably enough for them to test <pause dur="short"/> the audibility isn't although actually I'm not making a huge impact on the old erm oscillator thing so I hope I'm loud enough</u>
<u n="159" who="S0282">well I don't know I have to listen back to it and see what happens</u>
<u n="160" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>wh</trunc>where do you think the microphone is</u>
<u n="161" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I did it I had it in the car I was doing recording in the car and I was doing directions so I had it on my lap in the car and I thought it was gonna be like in the old days when you did tapes</u>
<u n="162" who="S0283">well what's what's happening now? no it's <trunc>h</trunc> it's barely hearing me at all</u>
<u n="163" who="S0282">well <trunc>i</trunc> I well it might be no good I just have to</u>
<u n="164" who="S0283" trans="overlap">where's the microphone?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0282">I don't know where the microphone is</u>
<u n="166" who="S0283">well shall we stop it and listen to ourselves and see what's happening?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0282">ah I suppose we could do couldn't we? okay next</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
