<text id="SB9K">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:24:28</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0192 S0198</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In mine and ANON's flat, Sussex</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>University, linguistics, timetabling, tuition fees, research, lecturers, language classes, food, cooking, vegetarianism, animal treatment, food preparation, studying, dinner, supermarkets, languages, lunch, food combinations, South Korea, men and women in South Korea, festivals, China, travel, computer games for sale, family, back gardens, flats.</topics>
		<activity>A morning post-study</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0198">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Gillingham, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Easten</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>27</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0192">what did you get sorted today then?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0198">I started to build a I've separated my seminars next week into three separate documents and I'm just pasting over the quotes that I think might be useful for that particular day</u>
<u n="3" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0198">some of them might not be relevant but I feel like at some point they'll be general discussion points</u>
<u n="5" who="S0192" trans="overlap">might be able to</u>
<u n="6" who="S0198">that I can sort of bring up at any time</u>
<u n="7" who="S0192">might be able to bring it up</u>
<u n="8" who="S0198">erm just starting to do that really organising my quotes I've read through a few things quite a lot of information we've studied so far isn't there?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0198">we've studied quite a bit</u>
<u n="11" who="S0192">definitely</u>
<u n="12" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0192">erm well we've been doing it for a few months now <vocal desc="laugh"/> haven't we?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0198">but then I've got I mean the second language acquisition and research I've got quite a lot of specific things that I have to prepare before Wednesday lots to do first it's all about introduction and defining language and then complete this questionnaire and also he's attached this to it which is something completely different I guess these are quotes to go along with what we're doing here what is language? how do we use it? and things like that but</u>
<u n="15" who="S0192">mm yeah all I've done so far is sorted everything out done my library referencing and printed the things off I need I still need to erm do the things that they've set me to do</u>
<u n="16" who="S0198">yeah yeah that's what I <unclear/> do</u>
<u n="17" who="S0192">and do the readings that they've set me to do</u>
<u n="18" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and just I haven't even finished organising those ideas yet I mean I've still gotta do I mean we've got today and tomorrow and also <unclear>look</unclear> we've got Monday and Tuesday and <trunc>Wed</trunc> you know it's not</u>
<u n="19" who="S0192">no yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0198">and what <trunc>conc</trunc> slightly concerned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is <unclear>they're</unclear> gonna start uploading <vocal desc="cough"/> er <trunc>pr</trunc> er specifics for language variation until the day before or something cos he hasn't done anything for preparation for that week <unclear/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0192">no I emailed the language description analysis lady cos although she's given me a load of pre-readings she hasn't actually set us anything to do</u>
<u n="22" who="S0198">no no</u>
<u n="23" who="S0192">whereas pidgins and creoles and syntactic theory have both set me</u>
<u n="24" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0198">don't really know whether to email him or whether that was kinda hassling him because</u>
<u n="27" who="S0192">it might be hassling him a little bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0198">he did say yesterday he is uploading bits by bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0192">I mean you're all in the same boat</u>
<u n="30" who="S0198">yes exactly</u>
<u n="31" who="S0192">so if he hasn't uploaded it for you he hasn't uploaded it for anyone so</u>
<u n="32" who="S0198">and I'm sure like with the general general erm general reading I've done it's erm even if he hasn't set anything as long as I go in there with a collection of quotes about <unclear>and</unclear> just copying over summarising what the basically the opening sentences they include in introductions to socio-linguistic books just have a bunch of them on there about language variation and what essentially it is</u>
<u n="33" who="S0192">I mean</u>
<u n="34" who="S0198">so as long as I can participate in that respect of it <unclear>I don't know what more</unclear></u>
<u n="35" who="S0192">he seemed pretty chilled to me</u>
<u n="36" who="S0198">it's called an introduction anyway the first seminar so yeah he does seem pretty chill I wonder what they're gonna do about <pause dur="short"/> the erm the clash that I have on my timetable</u>
<u n="37" who="S0192">yeah I mean if they're expecting us</u>
<u n="38" who="S0198" trans="overlap">cos in my head I had three to six again</u>
<u n="39" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if these things are mandatory I bet you'll get away with it I bet you won't have to do it <unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I it's it's possible they might tell me that I can I just do the first two hours and I always lose the third hour or they might say we give this slot one to three but we don't actually they don't actually go on for three hours</u>
<u n="41" who="S0192">what do you mean if it's two hours?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0198">well that I do one to <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="43" who="S0192">one to three is only two hours</u>
<u n="44" who="S0198">oh then I do the first hour then</u>
<u n="45" who="S0192">yeah so you just come in and do an hour <unclear>before the next class</unclear></u>
<u n="46" who="S0198">oh yeah sorry erm one to three is only two hours</u>
<u n="47" who="S0192"><unclear>that is a bit naff</unclear></u>
<u n="48" who="S0198">they didn't yeah they obviously hadn't thought that through or if we're lucky they'll look at the timetable for whatever reason it can be done earlier that day</u>
<u n="49" who="S0192">that would be nice</u>
<u n="50" who="S0198">but that would depend on</u>
<u n="51" who="S0192">chances are they'll move your thing later</u>
<u n="52" who="S0198">er what? my language <trunc>s</trunc>?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0192">second language acquisition</u>
<u n="54" who="S0198">yeah I mean I suppose they can do can't they?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0198">but just for me? that seems a bit mm harsh think about</u>
<u n="57" who="S0192">it's not just for you it's for everyone oh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0198">no it's not cos er most of the people</u>
<u n="59" who="S0192">you're right unless they're required to go to these as well</u>
<u n="60" who="S0198">but most people <unclear>will</unclear> unless they're required to do something similar which they might be er might do</u>
<u n="61" who="S0192">they might be mightn't they? cos it's just general language and linguistics erm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0198">ah I was quite looking forward to finishing at five that day but</u>
<u n="63" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well my</u>
<u n="64" who="S0198">six seems so late</u>
<u n="65" who="S0192">my timetable's mental <unclear>like</unclear></u>
<u n="66" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0192">I feel like I've got quite a lot to do</u>
<u n="68" who="S0198">with these added sessions</u>
<u n="69" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I've got four <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="70" who="S0198">every other week it's like you know that's like another module and you</u>
<u n="71" who="S0192">well basically I'm in uni four days a week and out of those four days two of them I'm in uni well one I'm in uni for eleven till six another one I'm in uni from nine till three</u>
<u n="72" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0192">that's quite long days</u>
<u n="74" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0192">and I've got two full long days like that you haven't got shit that even compares to that</u>
<u n="76" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="77" who="S0192">it's rubbish I'm not actually best pleased about that</u>
<u n="78" who="S0198">but you can use that time in between to just study at uni</u>
<u n="79" who="S0192">but it's a lot more work that means I have to have the books that I need for class plus the books that I need to study with plus I need to bring my laptop on top of my food I don't see how I'm going to be able to carry all of this</u>
<u n="80" who="S0198">well just take your laptop <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0192">when you actually think about these things practically it's not actually that easy</u>
<u n="82" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well I'm sure I know I understand that but er it's not easy but you're you're very organised you're very able I think that you can maximise this time quite successfully</u>
<u n="83" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I know it's just extra stress that I don't really need</u>
<u n="84" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="85" who="S0192">I'm not</u>
<u n="86" who="S0198">you'd prefer to come home obviously</u>
<u n="87" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't study do you want a cigarette by the way? I've rolled one</u>
<u n="88" who="S0198">yeah okay I'll have a little of that one</u>
<u n="89" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0198">even if you just study the lesson that you er</u>
<u n="91" who="S0192">I mean I've gotta deal with it haven't I? I haven't got any choice</u>
<u n="92" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the lecture that you had that morning <unclear/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0192">I know I know</u>
<u n="94" who="S0198">do the lecture and then do the seminar work that's set for the following class or whatever <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0192">I may have to</u>
<u n="96" who="S0198">do the seminar and just focus on one thing during that time</u>
<u n="97" who="S0192" trans="overlap">depends if she's put it up though isn't it? because erm on Wednesday I've just finished a pidgins and creoles seminar</u>
<u n="98" who="S0198">you'll have oh okay yeah yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0192">so she may not've yet uploaded next week's lecture and <trunc>semin</trunc>seminar</u>
<u n="100" who="S0198" trans="overlap">lectures <unclear/> whatever <vocal desc="yawn"/> but I'm sure you'll have work to do</u>
<u n="101" who="S0192">and I don't have access to a printer or anything and like</u>
<u n="102" who="S0198"><unclear>I mean</unclear> you can print at uni <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0192"><unclear>but that's and</unclear> then have to put money on that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0198">mm I think if you just go to the library find yourself a little corner it's just</u>
<u n="105" who="S0192">I'm gonna have to</u>
<u n="106" who="S0198">just focus on one thing that day</u>
<u n="107" who="S0192">I'm gonna have to take in my laptop and but it's just seems like a lot to carry and then I have to prepare I have to make sure I've got food ready and <unclear>like</unclear> all that kinda it's just a lot more work for me</u>
<u n="108" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I mean yeah you do have to take food in those days don't you?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0192">yeah it's just a lot more work for me <pause dur="short"/> that's all but it can't really be avoided can it?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0192">it just means that next semester I may very well just do the core modules</u>
<u n="112" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0192">depending on how I find this it's a shame cos I'd like to do phrenology and I'd like to do quite like to do world Englishes as well <unclear>but</unclear> erm depends how well I cope with this semester</u>
<u n="114" who="S0198" trans="overlap">cos world Englishes is just fifteen</u>
<u n="115" who="S0192">yeah I don't really understand</u>
<u n="116" who="S0198">it's a post-grad but it's fifteen</u>
<u n="117" who="S0192">yeah so they don't offer it to undergraduates I guess</u>
<u n="118" who="S0198">yeah okay</u>
<u n="119" who="S0192">but it's still a lesser weight</u>
<u n="120" who="S0198">I wonder why? it must build on <unclear>some of the theory that they have in</unclear> <unclear/> I don't know why they won't <unclear/> offer it to an undergrad</u>
<u n="121" who="S0192">research in language and use erm I don't really understand how it works it's fifteen credits the same as pidgins and creoles yeah?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0192">except in pidgins and creoles they do two hours a week</u>
<u n="124" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0192">and syntactic theory in research in language and use we do one and a half research in language and use is just two papers and the other ones I've got presentations and four papers</u>
<u n="126" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="127" who="S0192">they don't seem weighted correctly you can't really call them both fifteen credits <unclear/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0198">I guess the er yeah <unclear>no they're not</unclear> I guess the research in language and use is just er the <trunc>cr</trunc> you know they put the minimum amount of credit they can to it or something <unclear>and that's</unclear></u>
<u n="129" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did say that it <trunc>w</trunc> took more organisation to do the</u>
<u n="130" who="S0198">yeah yeah she did yeah she didn't sound like yeah it was an easier option at all so just gotta see how it goes I suppose <unclear>it's</unclear> just stay organised stay on top of it hopefully as you said after we've met everyone yesterday you know people are gonna need guidance through this sort of thing aren't they? I guess that's what these Wednesday things are about I dunno</u>
<u n="131" who="S0192">I don't know what that's about really why <trunc>w</trunc> I didn't fully understand it we just listen to their</u>
<u n="132" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0192">hear about their research? <unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0198">I guess it's it's the they're <trunc>s</trunc> trying to give us ideas during that time</u>
<u n="135" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0198">dissertation ideas and how you go about doing it I suppose so that we <unclear/> something</u>
<u n="137" who="S0192">I was only in uni nine hours a week undergrad er <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="138" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="139" who="S0192">twelve hours a week now</u>
<u n="140" who="S0198">I know I actually thought there would be less contact time erm than there is going to be certainly <unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0192">ah it is a masters isn't it?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0198">guess you're paying for it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0192">yeah you are</u>
<u n="146" who="S0198">get as much out of it as possible</u>
<u n="147" who="S0192">it's certainly not cheap is it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="149" who="S0192">six thousand pounds</u>
<u n="150" who="S0198">could be more <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said his cost seven</u>
<u n="151" who="S0192">oh did it?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0198">and I don't think he did I'm pretty sure he's at <anon type="place"/> and not <anon type="place"/> I'm not positive</u>
<u n="153" who="S0192">I mean certain masters cost different amounts <unclear/> <unclear>you do</unclear></u>
<u n="154" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah maybe because he does lab stuff and things like that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0198"><unclear>you know</unclear> yeah I know science masters I <trunc>w</trunc> I don't know how much did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> say how much his cost <unclear>there</unclear>?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0192">eight yeah I think or nine or something</u>
<u n="158" who="S0198">eight or nine at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0192">I mean all the ones at the <trunc>t</trunc>top ten unis cost <unclear>like</unclear> eight or nine <unclear>pretty much</unclear></u>
<u n="160" who="S0198" trans="overlap">are gonna be charging like eight or nine I can sort of appreciate <trunc>s</trunc> you know I mean the cost is ridiculous regardless but I can sort of understand it slightly more for things that do require lab work and stuff but linguistics? I mean I guess if you're willing to cover costs of fieldwork but erm masters like <anon type="place"/> putting it up to eight thousand</u>
<u n="161" who="S0192">I think they did that because they knew they were jumping up the league tables</u>
<u n="162" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0192">this year</u>
<u n="164" who="S0198">I mean it is a bloody good place can <trunc>y</trunc> ah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0192">they've gone up quite a bit</u>
<u n="166" who="S0198">I feel like people speak better at <anon type="place"/> could you imagine going somewhere <unclear>like</unclear> really high up? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0192"><unclear>well yeah</unclear> I think <anon type="place"/> is probably high enough for us</u>
<u n="168" who="S0198">it's probably a good choice for our niche</u>
<u n="169" who="S0192">you could try and go to an even better uni for your PhD</u>
<u n="170" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0192">because you're not really doing that much contact <unclear>hours</unclear> and by that point you've got a erm I mean effectively you could go from a top seventy uni to a top thirty top twenty uni depending on where you left it</u>
<u n="172" who="S0198">how do you <unclear>fall</unclear> into doing your PhD <unclear>straight from</unclear> your masters?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0192" trans="overlap">to a top ten well you effectively just carry on your research I reckon</u>
<u n="174" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0192">if you've got a good idea for your masters</u>
<u n="176" who="S0198" trans="overlap">start in our field</u>
<u n="177" who="S0192">quite often people turn their masters into PhDs</u>
<u n="178" who="S0198" trans="overlap">turn into PhDs continue that</u>
<u n="179" who="S0192">yeah effectively</u>
<u n="180" who="S0198">I did wonder at undergrad if I could turn my if you were allowed to turn your dissertation into a masters but I had a <trunc>f</trunc> your masters dissertation but no I don't think you can</u>
<u n="181" who="S0192"><unclear>really</unclear>?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0198">cos you've already got half the word count or all of the word count depending on</u>
<u n="183" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0198">the size of your dissertation</u>
<u n="185" who="S0192">it doesn't make any sense does it? and you you've er your dissertation's gonna have to be based on what you're taught you know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0198">I've got a feeling that in history I thought that the dissertations were ten twenty thousand a masters not ten not fifteen or ten</u>
<u n="187" who="S0192">erm they may well be</u>
<u n="188" who="S0198">they may be weighted to such a point that you are just because it's history you're</u>
<u n="189" who="S0192">because you're not doing field research</u>
<u n="190" who="S0198">you're <trunc>doi</trunc> yeah I mean you're doing what what else are they gonna be setting you throughout that masters other than to er <trunc>t</trunc>to? <unclear/> to prove</u>
<u n="191" who="S0192" trans="overlap">write a big piece of work</u>
<u n="192" who="S0198">that you can yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0198">whereas in linguistics you're <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean the TEFL one is fifteen thousand</u>
<u n="196" who="S0198">yeah it is</u>
<u n="197" who="S0192">the ELT one is longer but I guess their field research is lower I mean they might not even have to do field research</u>
<u n="198" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I don't know it depends on er</u>
<u n="199" who="S0192">they er they might just be writing a long-assed paper on second language acquisition <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear>well</unclear> they might have to do <vocal desc="yawn"/> <unclear>a like</unclear> case study</u>
<u n="201" who="S0192">but it's harder for them</u>
<u n="202" who="S0198"><unclear>she</unclear> did say in erm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0192">because they have to observe classes if they're doing it just based on TEFL</u>
<u n="204" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah but he did say in that opening thing that they have students there to be observed like</u>
<u n="205" who="S0192">yep</u>
<u n="206" who="S0198">you they have a language department that you can use</u>
<u n="207" who="S0192">yep but how much is each person gonna be observing? I don't reckon they probably have to do more than like five observation hours or something like that</u>
<u n="208" who="S0198"><unclear/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0192">do you know what I mean? and then it's all set up for them they just go and sit in a class and it's all ready to go and then just observe it whereas we have to come up with an idea which can be a complete scope of absolutely anything they're not gonna be out there doing research on the public about dialects and stuff in ELT</u>
<u n="210" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0192">it's got nothing to do with teaching English</u>
<u n="212" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah no</unclear></u>
<u n="213" who="S0192">erm so therefore their their process of research is already set up yes they probably have to decide what they're observing in the class but the class is already there so they don't actually have to set it up so I reckon our research proposal what we actually research is harder</u>
<u n="214" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0192">what we have to come up with</u>
<u n="216" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0192">and therefore we write less words</u>
<u n="218" who="S0198">I'm er concerned as well I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> slightly touched on it yesterday I'm sure he did about erm I don't know if it's when we were just talking to him but that you I feel like with language variation the big project that's due in after Christmas you choose what it is that you're you're researching you choose an area cos I said I said</u>
<u n="219" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah he said something about</u>
<u n="220" who="S0198">language variation has got a huge scope and er blah blah blah and he said well that's why we cover these different points so that you can find the area that you wanna research</u>
<u n="221" who="S0192">yeah do you have to do some kind of project <unclear>or something</unclear>?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0198">yeah well there's a five thousand word essay and</u>
<u n="223" who="S0192">what's that on?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0198">and the er there there's only two assignments in language variation a literary <trunc>r</trunc> literary literature review and er the essay so I assume you choose something do a literature <vocal desc="laugh"/> review and then produce the essay for it so basically it's a mini dissertation</u>
<u n="225" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0198">so in total <trunc>th</trunc>that's like</u>
<u n="227" who="S0192" trans="overlap">nice though cos you'll be nice and prepared for dissertations won't you?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0198">well in the <trunc>f</trunc> yeah I suppose by that point I've would've practised but</u>
<u n="229" who="S0192" trans="overlap">this is why for me</u>
<u n="230" who="S0198">I'd imagine it's in a different area</u>
<u n="231" who="S0192">I'd quite like to do first language acquisition but now I think about it more for the chances of what I'm gonna be doing a dissertation on first language acquisition isn't actually that useful</u>
<u n="232" who="S0198">that useful</u>
<u n="233" who="S0192">erm whereas discourse analysis is</u>
<u n="234" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0192">world Englishes is</u>
<u n="236" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0192">if I want to do er especially if I wanna focus on anything to do with our recordings</u>
<u n="238" who="S0198" trans="overlap">how many can we choose? so we've got fifteen is it the same amount? oh no dissertations how much is that? thirty?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0192">erm thirty</u>
<u n="240" who="S0198">oh does that come in the summer term <unclear>though</unclear>?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0198">so it doesn't count towards our spring term credits</u>
<u n="243" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="244" who="S0198">so we still need seventy-five</u>
<u n="245" who="S0192">yeah well in the spring term we still do another core module</u>
<u n="246" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0192">which is like the one that we're doing now research in language and use</u>
<u n="248" who="S0198"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0192">but erm where is it?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0198">probably <unclear/> in here somewhere</u>
<u n="251" who="S0192">oh you have a <trunc>ho</trunc> oh no it was hole-punched</u>
<u n="252" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0192">let's have a look</u>
<u n="254" who="S0198">so world Englishes is just fifteen credits so <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0192">yeah so</u>
<u n="256" who="S0198">so you could yeah <unclear><trunc>b</trunc> like</unclear> balance it out with something here</u>
<u n="257" who="S0192" trans="overlap">with another one of this I'd be</u>
<u n="258" who="S0198">like semantics or phrenology perhaps would you do that?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0192">erm I'd probably go for phrenology rather than semantics</u>
<u n="260" who="S0198" trans="overlap">to complement <trunc>s</trunc> yeah to complement cos then you'd have the you would've covered the syntax</u>
<u n="261" who="S0192">if yeah if I could do <trunc>phrenolo</trunc> yeah I mean I've got the core I'd like to be kind of what she is a little bit</u>
<u n="262" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0192"><unclear/> like I speak grammar</u>
<u n="264" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="265" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0198">I see yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0192">well</u>
<u n="268" who="S0198">see I think I'm <trunc>prob</trunc> I'm probably more</u>
<u n="269" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> know quite a bit about grammar</u>
<u n="270" who="S0198">like perhaps <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0192">history psychology based</u>
<u n="272" who="S0198">depends he seems more like he <trunc>c</trunc> he could've you know could've just done a degree in history</u>
<u n="273" who="S0192">I mean it's a field that you can do that in</u>
<u n="274" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0192">so it's alright but</u>
<u n="276" who="S0198">which is why I don't know whether er</u>
<u n="277" who="S0192">first language acquisition interests me I find it quite fascinating what children do and how they learn languages and that may go very well with your second language acquisition</u>
<u n="278" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0192"><unclear/> discourse and communication analysis I'm a little bit concerned she's nice but</u>
<u n="280" who="S0198">she won't take any shit I don't think</u>
<u n="281" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I reckon she's yeah I reckon she's she's very strict</u>
<u n="282" who="S0198">and I think she'll be quite direct with you</u>
<u n="283" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0198">that's the thing I got about er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> also he er I'm pretty sure he he'll just he won't he he won't like faff about</u>
<u n="285" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="286" who="S0198">he'll directly ask you just out of hand</u>
<u n="287" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but he might yeah I mean he might have well if they do run like <trunc>s</trunc> er <anon type="place"/> certificates</u>
<u n="288" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0192">and they know about CELTAs and DELTAs they've probably got more of that methodology with their</u>
<u n="290" who="S0198">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0192">their way of teaching</u>
<u n="292" who="S0198">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0192">whereas <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just <trunc>f</trunc> hasn't really taught so he's just gonna be like</u>
<u n="294" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0198">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="297" who="S0192">so it's not a bad thing they might actually be better teachers for it but</u>
<u n="298" who="S0198">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="299" who="S0192">erm it will probably be harder but discourse and communication analysis if that is actually about you know like things that you've recorded and then analysing it that's gonna be <unclear>bloody</unclear> useful</u>
<u n="300" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it would be pretty useful</u>
<u n="301" who="S0192">and would go well with phrenology and probably world Englishes so at the minute I'm leaning on that</u>
<u n="302" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0192">but then that means I have to do four modules again which means I've come out and done quite a few modules if I come out with the degree that I've done</u>
<u n="304" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah well unless I <unclear>don't <trunc>th</trunc></unclear> unless we unless you just choose those two core modules then that's just er a lot of people are gonna be in that position I think</u>
<u n="305" who="S0192">mm but I mean some I mean er <trunc>s</trunc> by the sounds of things people were just choosing the the main modules weren't they?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0192">I mean what did she say she was doing? I mean if she was doing forensic <trunc>s</trunc> linguistics and the discourse <unclear/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was doing these two was she?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0192">so she's doing four</u>
<u n="310" who="S0198">yeah she is she's <unclear/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0192">so it must be fairly common but I mean if I do another four I'll've come out with eight modules that's quite a few</u>
<u n="312" who="S0198"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <unclear/> I don't know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing</u>
<u n="313" who="S0192" trans="overlap">plus the MA dissertation is another thirty well they run pidgins and creoles again</u>
<u n="314" who="S0198">yeah they do</u>
<u n="315" who="S0192">I mean you could do quite well in that if I've already fucking done it</u>
<u n="316" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like you could do really well in it how would they argue that we've plagiarised or not? you were here while I studied it and therefore learnt about it yourself and now you've taken a course in it I mean there's nothing wrong with if you already know Spanish you can take a certificate in Spanish that gives you a qualification in Spanish</u>
<u n="318" who="S0198">no yeah that's true</u>
<u n="319" who="S0192">so if you already know pidgins and creoles you can take a qualification in it</u>
<u n="320" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but I <trunc>ha</trunc> I don't know <trunc>pidg</trunc> I haven't actually been</u>
<u n="321" who="S0192">no but by the end of this semester</u>
<u n="322" who="S0198">studying with you</u>
<u n="323" who="S0192">I will be telling you about it</u>
<u n="324" who="S0198">yeah you could certainly <unclear/> help explain things for me</u>
<u n="325" who="S0192">so I mean you could do pidgins and creoles and come out they might be like oh cheeky but</u>
<u n="326" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0192">but you could come out with quite a good grade <unclear/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0198">I think it depends how language variation goes for me and second language acquisition depends on what I'll choose next semester</u>
<u n="329" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0198">I don't when I'll we have to make these decisions if for example <trunc>lang</trunc>language variation's particularly successful then I might choose language <unclear>and gender</unclear> even though it never initially appealed to me I can it might be something <unclear/> semantics perhaps</u>
<u n="331" who="S0192">mm so what do we have to do? research proposal?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I wouldn't mind semantics discourse <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="333" who="S0192">semantics was quite tricky I think they said</u>
<u n="334" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0192">and it's very perceptive</u>
<u n="336" who="S0198">yeah well that's why <unclear>I yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="337" who="S0192">research proposal this module will provide specific guidance for your dissertation to help you in the choice of a research topic type of research project and appropriate methodology will work in conjunction with the presentations given by the English language and linguistics staff during the year</u>
<u n="338" who="S0198">yeah that's exactly it yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0192">ah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0192">it will also be so this has got some direct link into those things <unclear/> <unclear>enrolled</unclear></u>
<u n="342" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and will work in conjunction</u>
<u n="343" who="S0192"><unclear>oh</unclear> we've got those the whole year then pretty much</u>
<u n="344" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0192">it's just part of the course <unclear>man</unclear> they work you</u>
<u n="346" who="S0198">and then the language class on top of that I have</u>
<u n="347" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> you do</u>
<u n="348" who="S0198">we're gonna be busy <unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0192">yeah basically we just have to just do this all the time</u>
<u n="350" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0192">I mean <vocal desc="sigh"/> friends have to understand that</u>
<u n="352" who="S0198">yeah <unclear>I know well</unclear> hopefully</u>
<u n="353" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if can your your friends can like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> imagine doing all that work she did for her MA in one year?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0192">like and we still have to have a job and see people and go shopping and clean and all the normal stuff</u>
<u n="356" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0192">that everybody has to do that stuff takes up time</u>
<u n="358" who="S0198"><vocal desc="yawn"/> takes up a lot of time</u>
<u n="359" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does that one or at least she did</u>
<u n="360" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0192">is this up to date now? has it got?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0198">no it hasn't got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in it</u>
<u n="363" who="S0192">hasn't got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in it at all</u>
<u n="364" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0192">yeah it has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0198">no but it hasn't in the explanation parts</u>
<u n="367" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0198">I don't think</u>
<u n="369" who="S0192">ah they just copied and pasted those</u>
<u n="370" who="S0198">oh no they might be alright but there's an introduction from each of the lecturers and he's not there</u>
<u n="371" who="S0192">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just does this oh no he does world Englishes as well</u>
<u n="372" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0192">interesting</u>
<u n="374" who="S0198">if you read his little blurb about him his that's his area</u>
<u n="375" who="S0192">does he seem friendly though? <unclear/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0198">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0198">I don't know who</u>
<u n="381" who="S0192">what a great job they have <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>look</unclear></u>
<u n="382" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0192">I can't wait until we can teach modules and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know you focus on something she's like right I do the syntactics and pidgins and creole modules that's all she does on here <unclear>and</unclear> she must do some other undergraduate modules</u>
<u n="384" who="S0198">yeah yeah they do</u>
<u n="385" who="S0192">but you just teach modules</u>
<u n="386" who="S0198" trans="overlap">she does <trunc>Eng</trunc> she does</u>
<u n="387" who="S0192">and you make a module handbook</u>
<u n="388" who="S0198">English language</u>
<u n="389" who="S0192">I'm I like to be organised this kind of thing would be perfect if I could lay out at the beginning and go right student</u>
<u n="390" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0192">there's your module handbook</u>
<u n="392" who="S0198">this is what we're doing this year</u>
<u n="393" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I've already planned it <trunc>l</trunc> check on Study Direct because every week I'm gonna upload the next week's <unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear>and this is</unclear></u>
<u n="395" who="S0192">cos that's basically what I was doing with my blog like if I could've given them instructions every week and set them homework</u>
<u n="396" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0192">like if they had to do that I'd just upload it to that blog that I was doing</u>
<u n="398" who="S0198">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and then <unclear>they would have</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0198">no I mean it's like if you're organised and you know what you're doing then their job shouldn't actually be too bad</u>
<u n="401" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0198">because they <trunc>h</trunc> I mean maybe all the undergraduates are a bit of a pain in the arse <vocal desc="laugh"/> actually</u>
<u n="403" who="S0192">mm they might be</u>
<u n="404" who="S0198">but masters you're just you're you're very much responsible for even undergrad <unclear>they leave</unclear> you you're responsible to go and actually do the work if you don't do it you fail so</u>
<u n="405" who="S0192">mm it's definitely gonna be strange being with a bunch of undergraduates by the sounds of things unless one of these other people that we haven't met yet have chosen it or I guess somebody on a part time module has done it?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0192">I could be the only masters student in there</u>
<u n="408" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0192">which might be a bit strange <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0198">mm yeah I wonder I bet some you'll have some part timers in there or something although they are running pidgins and creoles twice so that might have something to do with <unclear>that too do you know what I mean</unclear>?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0192">yeah I didn't know they were running it twice yeah we've got the final cut now haven't we? this is it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0198">it's begun</u>
<u n="413" who="S0192">we could've <trunc>s</trunc>should've emailed this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear>I guess they were gonna show it to us</unclear> so forensic linguistics is twice and pidgins and creoles is twice</u>
<u n="414" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I wonder if she's replied about <unclear/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0192">she might not've done I'm glad they were on phrenology though</u>
<u n="416" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does that I'd be tempted by that who's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? there are two <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>s</u>
<u n="418" who="S0198">the other one is the</u>
<u n="419" who="S0192">what does she do?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0198">semantics one</u>
<u n="421" who="S0192">is that all she does?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0198">and no she</u>
<u n="423" who="S0192">oh no she does first language acquisition interesting <pause dur="short"/> fair if you could teach any of these modules which would you go for?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0198">mm don't know not till I start doing them I suppose</u>
<u n="425" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear>no</unclear> we don't know do we? bloody hell so much to do</u>
<u n="426" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0192">we have to effectively just start and <unclear>they'll stop</unclear></u>
<u n="428" who="S0198">erm what are we having?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0192">takes time just printing it all and getting to <unclear/> and</u>
<u n="430" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear>getting organised and er</unclear></u>
<u n="431" who="S0192">doing all this kind of shit</u>
<u n="432" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah exactly going to and from uni is time consuming in itself</u>
<u n="433" who="S0192"><unclear>I know</unclear> I think we just need to stop watching stuff in the evening at least until we're confident that we're on top of things <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0198">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0192">erm I don't know get less sleep or something seven hours is a bit much isn't it? I'm sure we can live off six</u>
<u n="436" who="S0198">yeah I thought that</u>
<u n="437" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0198"><unclear>I was thinking of</unclear> that lying in bed I was thinking this is this is valuable time right here not falling asleep just yet</u>
<u n="439" who="S0192">can certainly wake up early I'm in at nine but I mean if we wake up at seven that still doesn't give me that long</u>
<u n="440" who="S0198"><unclear>yeah but the thing</unclear> you have to leave at like eight to go and get the train don't you?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0192">yeah I do yeah so that only just just gives me enough time</u>
<u n="442" who="S0198" trans="overlap">or quarter to eight</u>
<u n="443" who="S0192">oh man it sucks I basically have to get home and just crack on like immediately</u>
<u n="444" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0192">be so much nicer if I just woke up and could get on with stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0198">there's days that I <trunc>s</trunc> wake up at seven <unclear>though and I'm</unclear> obviously gonna study <unclear/> admittedly I'm at home but I do I will be waking up at seven and I'll be in a classroom until eight PM</u>
<u n="447" who="S0192">yeah and me</u>
<u n="448" who="S0198">so I'll spend the entire day studying or learning or something with no chance to like</u>
<u n="449" who="S0192">and then what? <unclear>if</unclear> you're gonna come home and eat and then study again?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I'll just get more and more tired and then study <unclear/> days I think <unclear/> Tuesdays are gonna be <unclear>quite</unclear> quite tiring</u>
<u n="451" who="S0192">is Tuesday the one with your language?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0198">language class <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0192">I mean it's a job isn't it? effectively</u>
<u n="454" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0192">we're doing a job overall it says</u>
<u n="456" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0192">you're meant to spend about forty hours on it <unclear>is that</unclear> is that it? that doesn't sound right</u>
<u n="458" who="S0198">it is why once you've</u>
<u n="459" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it doesn't add up quite</u>
<u n="460" who="S0198">once you've been working full time for a few years or whatever studying seems easier</u>
<u n="461" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0198">than when you did it before because you do you like have</u>
<u n="463" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear>there's there's</unclear> a hell of a lot to study though</u>
<u n="464" who="S0198">you just apply er approach it as though it's an eight hour working day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0192">when you actually think about the whole thing</u>
<u n="466" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> massive breaks in between it yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0192">and you're like we've got all this work to just to do the first semester</u>
<u n="468" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="469" who="S0192"><unclear>then er</unclear> we have to do a whole another semester</u>
<u n="470" who="S0198">the amount of work I feel like I've done just to prepare myself for week one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and then a dissertation I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> it seems ridiculous</u>
<u n="472" who="S0198">I know still gotta just keep that ball rolling for every week</u>
<u n="473" who="S0192">for a year basically</u>
<u n="474" who="S0198">well yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0192">are you ready to work for a year?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0192">see how we go</u>
<u n="478" who="S0198">iron in here <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0192">what on earth are we eating? <unclear/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0198">we have eggs</u>
<u n="481" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="482" who="S0198">we can have egg a little bit of baguette still</u>
<u n="483" who="S0192">we never re-potted these things</u>
<u n="484" who="S0198">erm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0192">oh that came back to life a little bit</u>
<u n="486" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0192">maybe give it a bit more water hang on let me just give this a drink <unclear/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0198">mm how many eggs are there?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0192">you have to give this erm lemon grass a drink <unclear><trunc>ever</trunc>every few er days</unclear></u>
<u n="490" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they <trunc>c</trunc> people were</u>
<u n="491" who="S0192">careful making noise around there it's a little bit close isn't it?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0198">oh four eggs</u>
<u n="493" who="S0192">we have four eggs</u>
<u n="494" who="S0198">it's a fine line isn't it?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0192">it's really hard to</u>
<u n="496" who="S0198">I do have respect for people though that have just out of a moral obligation will not eat meat because of the way we treat animals</u>
<u n="497" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0198">I think that's good but it's very hard to come across someone that's so passionate like so <unclear>kinda</unclear> disciplined that they don't eat eggs or</u>
<u n="499" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0198">cheese or drink milk or like</u>
<u n="501" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0198">basically vegan I think</u>
<u n="503" who="S0192">which still</u>
<u n="504" who="S0198">true vegans are very difficult to come across <unclear/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0192">imprisons the animal or erm lactates it puts it in the <unclear>pen instead of free</unclear></u>
<u n="506" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah and even like free range eggs</u>
<u n="507" who="S0192">oh free <trunc>ra</trunc> mm well</u>
<u n="508" who="S0198">I mean er well what do you think the criteria of free range really is in the legal world?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0192">no no</u>
<u n="510" who="S0198">cos I bet it's not quite as free as you think it is</u>
<u n="511" who="S0192">no all it is is just the chicken's got a bit of space to move around in</u>
<u n="512" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they're <trunc>probabl</trunc> they're not battery farmed where they're stacked up on top of each other</u>
<u n="513" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0198">but I don't suppose they're running around in the fields either they might be in an enclosed pen</u>
<u n="515" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no well they'll have a bit of space but</u>
<u n="516" who="S0198">but</u>
<u n="517" who="S0192">they'll be able to stand up and move around but they're still being <unclear/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0198">yeah but to what extent they can still shuffle around</u>
<u n="519" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0198">erm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0192">right</u>
<u n="522" who="S0198">but I do respect people that do try and try and to not eat meat cos I think it's bad <unclear>how</unclear> we treat animals <pause dur="short"/> what about to eat?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0192">I don't know</u>
<u n="524" who="S0198">er</u>
<u n="525" who="S0192">I don't know what there is we've got eggs</u>
<u n="526" who="S0198">we've got four eggs</u>
<u n="527" who="S0192">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0198">we have a load of broccoli</u>
<u n="529" who="S0192">got wraps <unclear/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0198">we have wraps and some veg</u>
<u n="531" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we have tomatoes</u>
<u n="532" who="S0198">oh you were thinking scrambled egg veg wrap? cheese?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0192">maybe <vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't really like broccoli in that</u>
<u n="534" who="S0198" trans="overlap">or <unclear/> although that <unclear>meat's</unclear> not good</u>
<u n="535" who="S0192">I know that you just like to chuck any vegetable with anything at any point but</u>
<u n="536" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I know I know I know it's just cos we have the broccoli</u>
<u n="537" who="S0192">I like broccoli obviously</u>
<u n="538" who="S0198">what are we gonna do with them?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0192">but I just don't think it goes very well in a wrap</u>
<u n="540" who="S0198" trans="overlap">erm we can just</u>
<u n="541" who="S0192">I'd make it more carroty oniony erm do we have any other veg? <unclear/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0198">are four eggs enough to scramble?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0192">yeah there's pepper</u>
<u n="544" who="S0198">do you need milk to scramble? cos that's not I'm not sure that's good milk</u>
<u n="545" who="S0192">oh has it gone off?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0198">when I put it in my tea yesterday it curdled and that's usually a sign that it's going bad</u>
<u n="547" who="S0192">bloody hell how long have we had it for? it's full</u>
<u n="548" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="549" who="S0192">never buy one of that size</u>
<u n="550" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh no yeah it's definitely gone er I bought it for before we like for when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that came but it never got used</u>
<u n="551" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0198">I think I was intending to make smoothies or something I dunno it's bad milk</u>
<u n="553" who="S0192"><vocal desc="yawn"/> right yeah don't do that so</u>
<u n="554" who="S0198">can you scramble eggs without milk?</u>
<event desc="sound of banging"/>
<u n="555" who="S0192">oh god does this thing stop it from leaking? surely you should actually put it that way?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0198" trans="overlap">just put it there</u>
<u n="557" who="S0192">surely?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0198"><unclear/> no no no <unclear/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0192">well what do you mean no no no? why no no no no?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0192">what's wrong with it? but if you put it this way it doesn't really stand does it? <unclear/> falls over</u>
<u n="562" who="S0198">well put it down here now it's gone <pause dur="short"/> alright?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0192">alright erm we've got carrots haven't we?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0198">we've got pepper</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">carrot pepper onion</u>
<u n="566" who="S0198">onion</u>
<u n="567" who="S0192">oh this pepper's gone bad</u>
<u n="568" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0192">oh bugger you see stuff goes off quickly here definitely</u>
<u n="570" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0192">but I can cut around it <unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0198">it's cos we bought them like that when did we? oh actually <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0192">wasn't that long ago at all it was just when we last went shopping</u>
<u n="574" who="S0198">ah that's true</u>
<u n="575" who="S0192">I mean it's long enough for it to go mouldy I guess <unclear/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I think that was on Monday though we went shopping</u>
<u n="577" who="S0192">we'll just cut that off we've got half a <unclear>pepper</unclear></u>
<u n="578" who="S0198">we've got a load of carrots and onion</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">that half's fine this half's <unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0198">yeah there's potato</u>
<u n="581" who="S0192">there is potato it gets a bit hectic when we have potato there</u>
<u n="582" who="S0198">yeah it takes a while to do as well</u>
<u n="583" who="S0192">mm not very good with potato</u>
<u n="584" who="S0198">onion</u>
<u n="585" who="S0192">surely this bit of pepper's alright isn't it?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0198">yeah tomato we have so</u>
<u n="587" who="S0192">I just think I mean tomato's a veg just carrots this bit of pepper onions</u>
<u n="588" who="S0198">garlic</u>
<u n="589" who="S0192">garlic tomato</u>
<u n="590" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0192">no ginger</u>
<u n="592" who="S0198">alright no ginger</u>
<u n="593" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ginger doesn't go in it you've got the wrong flavours going in have you washed your hands?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0198">mm not recently</u>
<u n="595" who="S0192">give them a wash <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> and what? we're having it in a wrap?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0198">I guess so done it before <unclear/> alright</u>
<u n="597" who="S0192">spinach has finished hasn't it?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0198">yeah used that up with er dinner yesterday I believe</u>
<u n="599" who="S0192">cool <unclear>we've</unclear> gotta go shopping what is it we were cooking again? do you remember?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0198">on that second language acquisitions in my first lesson we were discussing what is language <unclear/> and he's included a couple of <trunc>quo</trunc>quotes one of them's the classic one about armies and borders</u>
<u n="601" who="S0192">oh is it?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0192">it is a bit of a classic <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0198">yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>some things that</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> what did what did I say just before that? <unclear/> what are we doing again? yeah what are we buying? what food? <unclear/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0198">well</u>
<u n="607" who="S0192">we've got beef haven't we? we have beef</u>
<u n="608" who="S0198">we have beef and that does <unclear>something like</unclear></u>
<u n="609" who="S0192">that needs to be thawed</u>
<u n="610" who="S0198">oh for tomorrow?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0198">yeah well that's alright <unclear/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0198">it's not today is it?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0192">and we need to soak chickpeas</u>
<u n="616" who="S0198">erm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0192">don't we?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0192">we've got lentils</u>
<u n="620" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0192">erm we could make a lentil curry at some point</u>
<u n="622" who="S0198">we er next week we have Sunday Monday Tuesday and then we just need something for a Wednesday Thursday dinner because Friday you're not here and I'll sort myself out</u>
<u n="623" who="S0192">yeah so we just need two dinners but we've also got lunches</u>
<u n="624" who="S0198">yes yeah yeah yeah we have er so obviously vegetables</u>
<u n="625" who="S0192">hummus</u>
<u n="626" who="S0198">er hummus</u>
<u n="627" who="S0192">that's not gonna last all week though</u>
<u n="628" who="S0198">erm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0192">but then I'm not I don't really need it for Thursdays</u>
<u n="630" who="S0198">yeah Thursdays we're home</u>
<u n="631" who="S0192"><unclear/> it's quite convenient actually although I'm busy I'm busy at the beginning of the week because we can prepare on Sunday</u>
<u n="632" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0192">for erm</u>
<u n="634" who="S0198">so Monday Tuesday Wednesday</u>
<u n="635" who="S0192">that's when I need to take lunches in</u>
<u n="636" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0192">Monday I have to take a lunch Tuesday I don't I come no I come home at lunch so I'm gonna be pretty hungry I'm gonna need something because I don't finish till midday</u>
<u n="638" who="S0198" trans="overlap">so <unclear/> it'd be good for something to be prepared</u>
<u n="639" who="S0192">so yeah basically Monday Tuesday Wednesday I've gotta take in lunch</u>
<u n="640" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="641" who="S0192"><unclear>which is a</unclear> bit crappy so I need a proper system going on here for have we got the correct Tupperware necessary to be able to take some hummus in er maybe a boiled egg some cheese some cut up veg?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I mean we have got a couple of containers <unclear/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0192">that's the kind of stuff I'm gonna need</u>
<u n="644" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0192">you don't like <unclear/> do you?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0198">nah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0192">just do one we don't wanna make this too big if it's going in a wrap</u>
<u n="648" who="S0198">yeah er yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0192">does that sound alright?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0198"><unclear>I'll just</unclear></u>
<u n="651" who="S0192">do we do we have the Tupperware <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0198">we've got some Tupperware I think there's enough for you to take stuff in mm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0192">gonna have to take in <unclear>one of</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0198">yeah I think so <unclear/> I suppose</u>
<u n="655" who="S0192">what about if you wanna take stuff in?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0198">the problem becomes when we're already using it to store stuff in the fridge cos some of that Tupperware I need to just throw out</u>
<u n="657" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but we can't</u>
<u n="658" who="S0198">cos not everything's got a lid like that's a good size for things but if we're already using it</u>
<u n="659" who="S0192">I need quite small little convenient ones something I can like you know</u>
<u n="660" who="S0198">we might need to grab <unclear/> <unclear>more</unclear></u>
<u n="661" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that just a bit just a little bit of veg like that</u>
<u n="662" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah the lid doesn't fit on that</u>
<u n="663" who="S0192"><unclear>maybe</unclear> another one that is kinda like</u>
<u n="664" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0192">where can we buy Tupperware?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0198">er</u>
<u n="667" who="S0192">I need batteries as well for this recording thing do we need to write this stuff down?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0198">oh what? like er double A battery?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0192">double A batteries yeah where has the notebook gone honey?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0198">I don't know? is it on the <trunc>sh</trunc> is it on the bookshelf in the library?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0192">erm no I don't see it</u>
<u n="672" who="S0198">down there by my behind you</u>
<u n="673" who="S0192"><unclear>is it behind</unclear> <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0198">look at me <unclear/> my folder</u>
<u n="675" who="S0192">erm so what was it? some batteries <pause dur="short"/> batteries and what?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0198">Tupperware?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0192">Tupperware</u>
<u n="678" who="S0198">not a lot just enough basically for you</u>
<u n="679" who="S0192">yeah basically just a mini set for me</u>
<u n="680" who="S0198" trans="overlap">just a couple of containers</u>
<u n="681" who="S0192">erm is there anything else <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0198" trans="overlap">so that can probably</u>
<u n="683" who="S0192">before Monday</u>
<u n="684" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="685" who="S0192">nothing you can think of?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0198">that can probably be be bought we're <trunc>g</trunc> obviously we're going to Aldi so</u>
<u n="687" who="S0192">is there a Poundland near there?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0198">there is a Poundland</u>
<u n="689" who="S0192">do they do Tupperware?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0198">yeah I think so if you're just getting a couple of little ones it shouldn't be <unclear>too</unclear></u>
<u n="691" who="S0192">there was also that other shop near there wasn't there? do you remember? that weird little hardware store that you went into</u>
<u n="692" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0192">they do like batteries and</u>
<u n="694" who="S0198">oh yeah that's yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="695" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they probably do Tupperware <unclear/> no <unclear/> <unclear>it's not really</unclear></u>
<u n="696" who="S0198">we'll go there first before Aldi cos it's small anyway</u>
<u n="697" who="S0192">it's on the way</u>
<u n="698" who="S0198">and then er</u>
<u n="699" who="S0192">but yeah we need more batteries for the recording equipment <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta hear back from them I had to send them my details I'm gonna have to send the invoice off in the next few days I would think cos I go to my parents at the weekend I can't be doing it then</u>
<u n="700" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="701" who="S0192">oh I nearly cut myself</u>
<u n="702" who="S0198">how many hours have we got so far? <unclear/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we're gonna finish this month with about twenty-five</u>
<u n="704" who="S0198"><unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="705" who="S0192">I think it's like four hundred and fifty pounds or something so we made the four hundred pounds that we needed to make</u>
<u n="706" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0192">but no more</u>
<u n="708" who="S0198"><unclear/> so hopefully we can both go home and get well no you'll be going home I won't be you'll get a few hours with your maybe with your family?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0192">that's the plan</u>
<u n="710" who="S0198"><unclear>and then</unclear> hopefully I'll get a few hours with friends</u>
<u n="711" who="S0192">yeah hopefully you can get a good few hours</u>
<u n="712" who="S0198">and then hopefully when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or whatever comes <unclear>over</unclear> in October</u>
<u n="713" who="S0192">yeah I don't know if we're still gonna make our target er I mean we might do</u>
<u n="714" who="S0198">you could get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0192">we might do <unclear/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0198">and although we haven't got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for the entire evening she could come up quite early in the day and have lunch and everything here</u>
<u n="717" who="S0192">yeah do you think she would?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0198"><unclear>if we</unclear> invited them in for lunch or dinner <unclear/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0192">if I cooked again</u>
<u n="720" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0192">yeah I mean I could do that</u>
<u n="722" who="S0198">garlic <unclear/></u>
<u n="723" who="S0192">yeah er yeah that sounds like a good idea doesn't it? and then we can record them while we're doing it they were pretty good before</u>
<u n="724" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't amazing</u>
<u n="726" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0192">if he spoke a bit more at certain points then <unclear/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0198">yeah he <unclear>er</unclear> could've done</u>
<u n="729" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was a good talker</u>
<u n="730" who="S0198">yeah I mean he's used to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> talking</u>
<u n="731" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0198">mm how many carrots? just one?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0192">it's alright I can do the carrot</u>
<u n="735" who="S0198">are you sure you don't want me to peel it?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0192">that's no I mean if you're happy to do it I'll start cooking</u>
<u n="737" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0192">erm yes you need to peel it</u>
<u n="739" who="S0198"><unclear/> do you want me to peel it?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="741" who="S0198">like</u>
<u n="742" who="S0192">yes peeling it would be great I can chop it if you want? chuck it here</u>
<u n="743" who="S0198">anything else you would wanna take for lunch other than veg hummus egg?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0192">erm I dunno what do you think? piece of fruit or something?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="746" who="S0192">I don't really need anything more than that <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="747" who="S0198"><unclear>maybe</unclear> an apple or something</u>
<u n="748" who="S0192">oh apples would be nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0198"><unclear/> good <unclear/> carry it in your bag with all your books</u>
<u n="750" who="S0192">do I write apples on the list? or just we just remember <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0198"><unclear/> remember <unclear/> fruit <unclear/> erm how do you want this cut? do you wanna <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0192">I'll just do it yeah is this knife clean? have you been using it for something?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0198" trans="overlap">what about? oh yeah I used it <unclear/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0192">cool</u>
<u n="755" who="S0198">what about er Thursday Wednesday Thursday <trunc>lun</trunc> er dinner?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0192">oh what we?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I thought seeing as we're having mince now maybe chicken but cos we're having ragot  on Monday Tuesday and Wednesday aren't we? er Monday Tuesday</u>
<u n="758" who="S0192">yeah we need more celery I think</u>
<u n="759" who="S0198">so</u>
<u n="760" who="S0192">let's not forget that <unclear>again</unclear></u>
<u n="761" who="S0198"><unclear/> just a few <unclear/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0192">erm okay we just cooked chicken <unclear>didn't we</unclear>?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0198">yeah but then we were gonna do beef <unclear/></u>
<u n="764" who="S0192">so either lamb or chicken I guess</u>
<u n="765" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0192">is it just? do you just put mince together? if it's minced then <unclear/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I do put it a little bit together but I just put lamb or beef together <unclear/></u>
<u n="768" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but I I could do like a I could do a lamb keema</u>
<u n="769" who="S0198">mm that would be nice yeah have we had a keema since we've been here?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0192">no we haven't oh keema in a wrap might be nice</u>
<u n="771" who="S0198"><unclear>yeah</unclear> let's have a keema <unclear/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I feel like if you made a nice solid keema wrap even if you could find the biggest wrap you could</u>
<u n="773" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="774" who="S0192">and then chilled it that'd be tasty to take for lunch</u>
<u n="775" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0192">and just take it already made cos it's just like it goes quite dry so it shouldn't get too saucy if you cook it down properly</u>
<u n="777" who="S0198">well if we make one on Wednesday and could save a little bit you could take it for your lunch Friday</u>
<u n="778" who="S0192">erm probably not</u>
<u n="779" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="780" who="S0192">I've got a bit of a hectic day on Friday bit worried that I'm going to my family at the weekend when I need to be studying <unclear/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0198">studying yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0192">but then <unclear/> I guess I can study on the train can I? I mean I can at least read a book</u>
<u n="783" who="S0198">yeah will you be taking your? do you know how you're getting from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> yet?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0192"><unclear>yeah</unclear> I think my dad's picking me up</u>
<u n="785" who="S0198">oh he is? what time do you get into <anon type="place"/> that evening?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0192">erm I'm not certain</u>
<u n="787" who="S0198">oh he finishes early that day that's the problem</u>
<u n="788" who="S0192">I'm only being picked up at yeah that's the problem I'm only being picked up at four thirty</u>
<u n="789" who="S0198">okay</u>
<u n="790" who="S0192">erm so I'll probably be in <anon type="place"/> by about five I'm meant to be taking him out for a meal as well <unclear>remember</unclear></u>
<u n="791" who="S0198">yeah I know</u>
<u n="792" who="S0192">and obviously I've paid for my train back <unclear/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0198">oh that's good</u>
<u n="794" who="S0192"><unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="795" who="S0198">helpful</u>
<u n="796" who="S0192">very bit worried that we're gonna overspend quite a bit if we're both</u>
<u n="797" who="S0198">oh are we having curry wraps for dinner?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0192">I guess so yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0192">ah there we go we don't have any meat that can go in this do we really? <unclear/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0198">mm no</u>
<u n="802" who="S0192">erm yeah so I don't know oh it's going in my eyes</u>
<u n="803" who="S0198">probably a good idea to always keep a pack of sausages in the freezer or something that we can use for <unclear>if you</unclear> want a bit more for lunch one day or something</u>
<u n="804" who="S0192">or grab something erm <trunc>s</trunc> I mean I would agree but sausages? is that the best <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0198">yeah I dunno sausages</u>
<u n="806" who="S0192">they're not the most versatile be better to just have a bit of pork again</u>
<u n="807" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0192">just a pack of pork</u>
<u n="809" who="S0198">yeah have we seen any pork?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0192">I think they have them there's also turkey mince</u>
<u n="811" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="813" who="S0198">that might be a bit <unclear>really nice</unclear></u>
<u n="814" who="S0192">turkey mince is quite common in England my mum uses it quite a lot</u>
<u n="815" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0192">that they need whisking into a thing</u>
<u n="817" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I guess it's for people that don't eat erm red meat</u>
<u n="818" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0198">or er dark meat <unclear/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0192">put a bit of salt and pepper in it a bit of paprika</u>
<u n="821" who="S0198">mm have we had any salt? we're gonna buy salt</u>
<u n="822" who="S0192">no we don't need salt</u>
<u n="823" who="S0198"><unclear/> salt are we?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0192">yeah maybe write that on the list yeah?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0198">mm I've got egg on my hands let me <unclear/></u>
<u n="826" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0198">put it on the list salt</u>
<u n="828" who="S0192">oh apples</u>
<u n="829" who="S0198">apples</u>
<u n="830" who="S0192"><trunc>j</trunc>just thinking of what we don't normally get what else did we say we don't normally get? we wanted some turkey mince didn't we?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0198">maybe yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0198">have you seen it at Aldi?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0192">well yeah I think so <unclear/> how many wraps are you having?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0198">I dunno there's four left</u>
<u n="836" who="S0192">after this?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0198">no there's just four left there's only eight in these packets aren't there?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0192">I suppose we don't have to have the curry with wraps tonight could have it with rice or something</u>
<u n="839" who="S0198">yeah so do you wanna cuppa? erm</u>
<u n="840" who="S0192">is there anything else? I mean we've got loads of potato</u>
<u n="841" who="S0198">oh we could have it with wedges or something</u>
<u n="842" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah we could make some wedges that might be quite tasty mightn't it?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0198">oh this is</u>
<u n="844" who="S0192">there's not a lot in there though</u>
<u n="845" who="S0198">oh those damn damn onions</u>
<u n="846" who="S0192">what have you just done?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0198">no this is fine</u>
<u n="848" who="S0192">you put way too much</u>
<u n="849" who="S0198">no <unclear>it's</unclear></u>
<u n="850" who="S0192">I've already just put a load in here honey</u>
<u n="851" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh have you?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0192">why did?</u>
<u n="853" who="S0198">you said salt and pepper <unclear/> about the eggs</u>
<u n="854" who="S0192">no yeah I put it in why did you do that? we're not making a fried rice</u>
<u n="855" who="S0198">that's fine it'll be alright</u>
<u n="856" who="S0192">it's very very peppery that's I mean that was a lot that you put in regardless of what I put in</u>
<u n="857" who="S0198">it's because I was turning and it wasn't come out coming out</u>
<u n="858" who="S0192">I know I just you shouldn't've started whisking it I could've got some out</u>
<u n="859" who="S0198">it'll be fine <unclear>won't even taste it</unclear></u>
<u n="860" who="S0192">I'm sure it'll be very very peppery</u>
<u n="861" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I'm not afraid of a bit of pepper</u>
<u n="862" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well it's not <unclear>shut up</unclear> <unclear/> where is the <trunc>pep</trunc> the paprika? I can't even find it</u>
<u n="863" who="S0198"><unclear>it's there er</unclear></u>
<u n="864" who="S0192">it's not there though is it? I've looked <unclear>in there</unclear></u>
<u n="865" who="S0198"><unclear>no it's</unclear> <unclear/> <unclear>there then is it</unclear>? <unclear/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0192">can't see it <unclear>can we</unclear> use chilli?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="868" who="S0192">could use that</u>
<u n="869" who="S0198"><unclear>there</unclear></u>
<u n="870" who="S0192">it was facing the other way</u>
<u n="871" who="S0198">are you cooking these wraps as well? or are you just having a wrap?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0192">I was gonna cook it <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>will that do</unclear>?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear/> <unclear>too much washing up here</unclear></u>
<u n="874" who="S0192">grab us that little bit of butter <pause dur="short"/> fry those eggs</u>
<u n="875" who="S0198">oh yeah you <unclear/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="long"/> think it'll be alright is that the butter?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0198">yep it is</u>
<u n="878" who="S0192">wow I'm getting really hungry now</u>
<u n="879" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="880" who="S0192">do you want it in wraps? <unclear/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0192">with a bit of <unclear>cheese it</unclear></u>
<u n="883" who="S0198"><unclear>cheese it</unclear></u>
<u n="884" who="S0192"><unclear>cheese it</unclear></u>
<u n="885" who="S0198">just worried is it too saucy? <unclear/> if it leaks out just have it on the plate</u>
<u n="886" who="S0192">I'll try and cook it down</u>
<u n="887" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0192"><unclear/> and erm once I add the eggs to it they soak up a bit of the sauce as well</u>
<u n="889" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0192">not a lot but a bit enough is this water fresh? is this what I poured a minute ago? <unclear/></u>
<u n="891" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh yeah it must be</u>
<u n="892" who="S0192">are you sure?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I just drank some <unclear/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0192">why is there always a piece of wrap missing?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> because I can't help it</u>
<u n="896" who="S0192">you really can't that's so it's a very strange thing you take such a small bit it's not even worth it</u>
<u n="897" who="S0198">mm I know well a big bit would hinder the</u>
<u n="898" who="S0192"><unclear/> <unclear>thinking though</unclear> it's just a strange thing that you do</u>
<u n="899" who="S0198"><unclear/> can I pinch some of that?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0192">course you can <unclear/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0198">it looks like a fairly nice day again</u>
<u n="902" who="S0192">it's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0198">had that one night of rain since we've been here <unclear/></u>
<u n="904" who="S0192">I don't say I want rain but the nice weather just makes you wanna go out</u>
<u n="905" who="S0198">yeah I know</u>
<u n="906" who="S0192"><unclear>which is difficult</unclear></u>
<u n="907" who="S0198">the cold stormy stuff <unclear/> cup of tea</u>
<u n="908" who="S0192">I mean winter is coming</u>
<u n="909" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="910" who="S0192">you can't deny that be nice if they had a nice</u>
<u n="911" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's not gonna stay warm is it?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0192">be nice if they had a nice clear winter I reckon it's gonna be really foggy at points</u>
<u n="913" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="914" who="S0192">saw the fog the other day <unclear>when we couldn't like</unclear> see past the train station</u>
<u n="915" who="S0198" trans="overlap">seemed really dark and not be able to see across the campus</u>
<u n="916" who="S0192">I mean you say the weather's nice but I was at home for a week and a half and it was pretty gloomy <unclear/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>no</unclear> that's I said like since we moved into the flat it's been <unclear>much</unclear> nicer</u>
<u n="918" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="920" who="S0192">I mean we've still had a few gloomy days but there's definitely been definitely been <unclear>sunny days</unclear> without a doubt</u>
<u n="921" who="S0198">sunnier than expected</u>
<u n="922" who="S0192">yeah what the fuck happened there?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0192">I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0198">something explode?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="927" who="S0198">this isn't</u>
<u n="928" who="S0192">saucepan expanded or something</u>
<u n="929" who="S0198"><unclear/> this one?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0192"><unclear/> spoon need some cheese grated on that as well we're gonna have to buy some more cheese I take it?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0198">yeah get some in for the week</u>
<u n="932" who="S0192">it's reasonably priced</u>
<u n="933" who="S0198">need to kind of get er</u>
<u n="934" who="S0192">I'm so glad there's a shop like Aldi around</u>
<u n="935" who="S0198">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> we can survive at Aldi might not be the best stuff</u>
<u n="936" who="S0192">I mean it's coming from the EU right? everything's from the EU</u>
<u n="937" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear>er dunno I think a lot of stuff's from England don't know</unclear></u>
<u n="938" who="S0192">I mean they do you can't just lie about that so if it's from England there's a standard</u>
<u n="939" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0192">it's just a cheaper shop because people cannot afford any more to shop at Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="941" who="S0198" trans="overlap">Sainsbury's all the time yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0192">and places like that there are people that just can't afford and therefore it can't work you have to have some cheaper shops</u>
<u n="943" who="S0198">cheaper shops yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0192">cos the British public are not paid enough there are still plenty of people that go to Tesco's and plenty of people who go to Sainsbury's and all these places</u>
<u n="945" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0192">some people just have to</u>
<u n="947" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="948" who="S0192">so they've filled a niche I think it was over all the prices went up didn't it? and I guess people are just like crap and then these companies came in <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="949" who="S0198"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0192">it's good that they are you know</u>
<u n="951" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0192">compared to Korea it's definitely cheaper</u>
<u n="953" who="S0198">yeah it is <unclear/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0192">it seems pretty stable as well you can get a big yellow melon for seventy P</u>
<u n="955" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah I'm not expecting anything to I mean some might go up by a few pence from inflation or something but I'm not expecting the price of actually any produce to really change <unclear/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0192">no it shouldn't <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="957" who="S0198">think that they just have <unclear>that</unclear> set price <unclear/></u>
<u n="958" who="S0192">well we get a good amount of the week's shopping for twenty-five quid</u>
<u n="959" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="960" who="S0192">probably do have to go shopping twice a week though</u>
<u n="961" who="S0198">yeah but that's for er storage reasons I suppose</u>
<u n="962" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="963" who="S0198">it's not like people buy like freezer <trunc>loa</trunc> freezer load of <trunc>pro</trunc>produce or meat or <unclear>anything</unclear></u>
<u n="964" who="S0192">no really can't</u>
<u n="965" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="966" who="S0192">which is a bit annoying</u>
<u n="967" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="968" who="S0192">so we're gonna keep on with the three meals thing? I thought we weren't gonna do that</u>
<u n="969" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean</u>
<u n="970" who="S0192">kinda have to it just makes sense <unclear>cos we're</unclear> just too busy</u>
<u n="971" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it makes it helps out during the week especially seeing as there might be time like on a Tuesday I'm not gonna eat dinner with you <unclear/></u>
<u n="972" who="S0192">no you can't can you?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="974" who="S0192">so I've gotta eat dinner on my own</u>
<u n="975" who="S0198">and</u>
<u n="976" who="S0192">what are you doing for food in the interim? what time will you be back that day?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0198">don't know I haven't checked the time of the trains coming back <unclear/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what time does it finish?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0198">eight o'clock</u>
<u n="980" who="S0192">eight o'clock?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0198">yeah it finishes at eight</u>
<u n="982" who="S0192">so you do three till eight?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0192">on a Tuesday</u>
<u n="985" who="S0198">it's a long time to be in a classroom</u>
<u n="986" who="S0192">yeah it is quite a while I mean thankfully you're doing like beginners French</u>
<u n="987" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="988" who="S0192">that's gotta be about as easy as it gets really</u>
<u n="989" who="S0198">and I suppose whatever happens happens I mean I'm not expecting it to be too <unclear/></u>
<u n="990" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean I think it's good I think it maybe looks a bit bad that you're doing beginners French but I think it looks good that you were doing it so you could travel <unclear/></u>
<u n="991" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0192">there's a genuine purpose to it</u>
<u n="993" who="S0198">yeah rather than just</u>
<u n="994" who="S0192">and you've travelled quite a bit</u>
<u n="995" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>exactly</unclear> rather than dunno I feel like it looks better if you try and go for something a bit unusual or whatever</u>
<u n="996" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0198">but I don't actually but then the motivation for me learning it is purely that motivation rather than the one to that I actually need it</u>
<u n="998" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="999" who="S0198">if I'm gonna do a language lesson in twenty weeks it would be nice for it to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1000" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0192">I'll probably catch up with you in about a month of Rosetta Stone or whatever</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> cheers</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what? well er just saying cos I don't think you'll have much time to study outside of the class and how much can you really learn in a class? I can sit down and grab a couple of those books and like just write it out and I'm pretty sure that I reckon I could learn quite a bit of French if I had the time in about six months I reckon I could be basically conversational like Spanish in er six months</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0198" trans="overlap">if you had six months</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0192">I had</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0192">like we had in Korea where I could study for a few hours a day</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0198">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0192">like two or three hours a day on French or something</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0198">I mean they've done studies to prove that <unclear/> second language acquisition is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1012" who="S0192">you didn't even put this on you said you put it on</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0192">what are you doing? <unclear/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0198">you can erm</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0192">this isn't ready now this is ready that's not ready</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0198">oh well I'll just have mine as it is</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0192">what? great so cos you couldn't be bothered to turn it on</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0198">look I thought you were turning it on darling <unclear/></u>
<u n="1020" who="S0192">what? you said I'm turning it on and I said what? already? or something and then</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1022" who="S0192"><unclear/> yeah but you <trunc>s</trunc> you still turned it on</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0198">we'll check it later shall we? see who says what I did turn on anyway I turned it on at the mains</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0192">but you didn't actually turn it <unclear/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0198">I didn't start heating it up yet</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0192">which you and you haven't done the cheese what have you done?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0198">I've been cleaning we were making space</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I asked you to do the cheese <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you not remember?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0198">I got the oh yeah yeah I heard that I was gonna do it when it was nearer the time it's just grating some cheese</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0192" trans="overlap">like now now we're ready <unclear/></u>
<u n="1031" who="S0198">oh well you can</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0192">this isn't ready so we're waiting on this</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0198">well why don't you you grate it onto it there immediately do you have to pre-grate it then? okay fine</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0192">so it'll melt oh for <trunc>fuck</trunc></u>
<u n="1035" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0192">I don't like having this that's happened to me every single time throwing it out the window</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0192">it bothers the crap out of me it has no purpose</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I like it it does it <unclear/> <unclear>them</unclear></u>
<u n="1040" who="S0192">what for what purpose?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0198">and then you can keep it in the fridge</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0192">you never need to</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0198">throwing things out the window for one it's not our garden</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do you want any more?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0198">what?</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0192">do you want any more?</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1048" who="S0192">do you want cheese? sorry</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0198">that's that's <trunc>en</trunc> that's enough just make it a bit of a <unclear/> at some point</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0192">I'm meant to have two wraps here where's my other plate? <pause dur="short"/> or are you just doing them one at a time?</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0198">yeah I guess <unclear/> the other one in the curry</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0192">shall we just eat this one first?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0192">that's dry enough isn't it?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0198">yeah it looks good doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0192">thing is that squeezes the erm</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0198">juice out of the tomato some more</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it squeezes the juice out anyway so it's not too much of a problem thing is this thing's not hot enough so can't actually do it</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0192">cos you didn't do your duties your duties</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0198">I mean it'll just cook it slower will it?</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0192">what will?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0198">or will it not sear it in the way you want to?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0198">George Foreman</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0192">yeah it will just cook it slower I guess</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0198">tea's <unclear/> hasn't it?</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0192">it's getting warm but er you might find it heats up quicker though if it's got two metal bits together than if it's got <unclear/></u>
<u n="1073" who="S0198" trans="overlap">something in between it</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0192">something in between it</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0192">but erm anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="1077" who="S0198">there's logic to that</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0192">there's logic to everything I say</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0192">I'm a logical person how much do you think goes in here? like two scoops?</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/> <unclear>that's good</unclear></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0192">alright <pause dur="short"/> just hope that isn't too much this thing stays hot it looks a bit like too much to me <unclear>er what is</unclear> that? that is absolutely gross</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0198">yeah what is it?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0192">I've no idea but that is some terrible cleaning</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean how did it even get there? what is it?</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0192">I'm about to wrap my wrap after I've touched</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1088" who="S0192">what is it? poo?</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0198">it must be a bit of old food or something that's got squashed somehow</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1091" who="S0198">very recently looks like chocolate but</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0192">chocolate? it didn't feel like chocolate</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what does that bit <unclear/>? don't know</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0192">no if only this was <trunc>eg</trunc> er chicken and not egg <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>there I've taken</unclear> to folding it right over <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh what? that's the first time that's ever happened to me</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0192">that's game over isn't it?</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0198">where's my one?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0192">I can't do it no I'm gonna have your one</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0198">why? I'll just eat this as it is it doesn't bother me</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you just I'll just eat this as it is you only get one</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0198">oh do I?</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0192">why? did you get two? if you have two then yeah</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0192">like that</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0198">mine was a bit smaller <unclear/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0192">I didn't get any cheese in it though there's like loads of cheese in that</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0198">well why don't we both just have?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1109" who="S0198">well why don't I have these two? and you can toast both of yours oh no cos then you've still not got the cheese</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0192">well I mean I can add more cheese to mine but do you not want yours toasted <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0198">yeah no I'll toast this one that I've just made</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0198">or that can go on when yours goes on and then I'll just eat this one</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0192">no put this on now I've got I've got two to go on I'll have to do mine at the same time really put it in the middle they cook quicker oh I'm disappointed can I have another plate? <unclear>and</unclear> your plate</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1115" who="S0198">do you mind if I just wait to cool down <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0192">yeah do you want me to bring that one through? I'm just eating this one <unclear/></u>
<u n="1117" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0192">I think the George Foreman is hotting up now</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1120" who="S0192">maybe I put too much cheese in</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1122" who="S0192">there was a bit of <trunc>chee</trunc></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0198"><unclear>hopefully</unclear> this one <unclear/></u>
<u n="1124" who="S0192">I feel like there was a bit too much in it</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0198">yeah put a little less in and have some on the side maybe</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0192"><unclear>yeah</unclear> that's what I'm gonna try to do</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0198">this one I think my one was smaller than this one</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0192">I think I was paying too much attention to showing you how to roll it and not paying enough attention to actually rolling it</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0198">what? is that all leftover?</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0192">yeah we're gonna have it on the plate aren't we?</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0198"><unclear/> really get the spatula out come on here give</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1133" who="S0198">yes erm</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0192"><unclear/> where's your spatula?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0198">where is the spatula?</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0192">I dunno it's your</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0198"><unclear/> this one by accident</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0192"><unclear>kind of don't come</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1139" who="S0198">no oh did a you right in front of me</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0192">right in front of you was it? need to get this one on</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0198"><unclear>the panini basically we</unclear></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1143" who="S0198">are we watching anything? or just eating it?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0192">wasn't planning on it no</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0192">cos we're erm still talking <unclear/></u>
<u n="1147" who="S0198">still gotta get time to rock on as well haven't <unclear>they</unclear></u>
<u n="1148" who="S0192">we're still talking aren't we?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0198">yeah alright then I'll set up a chair or two as a table</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0192">sounds nice</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0198">sun is shining and the weather is sweet</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0192">yeah the sun is nice <shift new="singing"/> sun is shining the weather is sweet <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1153" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that your best Rasta Rasta voice?</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0192">no it's</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0198">best best Bob?</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0192">all I've gotta do is just actually just do a creole voice</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>now you know how to do it though</unclear></u>
<u n="1158" who="S0192">I'm practising my creole Jamaican creole</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0198">going to a</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1161" who="S0198">going to a job interview</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0198">that's what you can that's your skill</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0192">well I can talk in Jamaican creole</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1166" who="S0192">kinda pointless so do you want any on the side? er where's your thing?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0198">dunno probably got enough there but yeah I mean is it worth saving that for anything?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0192">for what?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/> put it on there</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0192">I mean can you eat it cold? what's it like cold?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0198">just cold egg and stuff I suppose</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0192">be a bit strange wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0192">is that enough food?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0198"><unclear>plenty</unclear> time for you run this crowd</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0192">yeah so <unclear/> is just a TMA marker</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0192">I think it's got some substroke influence on the Niger-Congo languages <unclear/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0198">so what does that mark? <unclear>to</unclear></u>
<u n="1180" who="S0192">past tense or modality</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0198">oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0192">aspect progressive erm perfective</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0198">so does it only change according to what it's like <unclear>inflecting</unclear> so to speak rather than what's what's actually being said? it doesn't get so if it's past it'll be like <unclear/> for example regardless who's saying it or?</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0192">no that yeah they have a different marker for past a different marker for perfective and a different marker for something else</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0198">okay yeah</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0192">but it doesn't have any meaning</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0198">no yeah</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0192"><unclear/> terrible</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0198">oh this cheese you wanna scrape up that cheese</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0192">yeah I know I need the spatula</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0198">yeah it's right next to it</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0192">I definitely wanna scrape up that cheese I'm a bit disappointed all come out</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0192">a whole horrible mess that one needs a little bit more I think</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0198"><unclear/> that cheese scrape it off later</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0192">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1197" who="S0198">yeah you don't wanna scrape the George Foreman on er the metal</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0192">I'm not gonna scrape the George Foreman</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0198"><unclear/> cheese <unclear/> fine</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0192">use the bread itself</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0198">mm mop it up</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0198">does this need turning off? or have you already turned it off?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0192">I've already turned it off I believe</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0198">ah <unclear/> something</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0192">give it a wipe not sure on the stuff external to the wrap</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> if it's necessary whatever it'll get eaten it's in its purest form I suppose</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear>tastes any good</unclear></u>
<u n="1209" who="S0198">no it tastes good</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0192">does it?</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0198">I like it tomato egg look at that chunk of tomato mm tomato</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0192">I think it tastes too peppery <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1213" who="S0198">I don't think so do you actually?</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0192">no mm that bit was a bit like a pizza</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0198">yeah with the tomato and the cheese</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0192"><unclear/> like tomato and cheese</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0198">don't get egg on pizza usually though do you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1220" who="S0192">no bit of a strange pizza but it's funny that we've allocated certain things to certain things</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0198">certain things yeah</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and then you go to Korea and you're like no</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0198">don't put sugar on my garlic bread</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0198">but there's a good although things like if someone had put something else on your garlic bread like cheese you'd be like oh that's you know that's good</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0198">it just depends what they put together or what is put together</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0192">I mean do you think strawberry yoghurt cornflakes and lettuce is a good mix?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0198">not really no</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1231" who="S0198">I think it was a bit odd</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0192">very strange</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0198">I'm not sure why</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1235" who="S0198">why that how that came about to be honest</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear>only very</unclear> strange people would do that but it's not that strange there's nothing strange about it</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0192">anything can go with anything</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0192">and it's purely perception</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0198">what you think is good or not good</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0192">from years and years and years of not putting yoghurt with lettuce</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0198">I mean yoghurt on salad isn't so strange it's the flavoured crappy strawberry yoghurt on salad with cornflakes</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0192" trans="overlap">with cornflakes <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was laughable when you first saw that in Korea it was just like what?</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0198">what is this? those times at school where you think you got your bloody fruit like they just get it backwards the fruit'd end up in mayonnaise and the</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0198">salad would end up in some really strong fruit thing mm</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0192">very strange it's kind of a strange concept that we contributed to another society for four years</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0192">when erm was a part of that society</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0198">made friends with people of the society</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0198"><vocal desc="cough"/> hung out with</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0192">our families must think it's a bit odd <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1255" who="S0198">yeah where do you call home?</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0192">do they really have any concept of what life's been like for us?</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0192">I know they hear it from us but</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0198">it's hard to</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0192">I mean <trunc>m</trunc>my mum and your mum get really nervous and struggle when they go for a job interview or something</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0192">can you imagine them being that first day of our first school in Korea being put up on a podium and <trunc>c</trunc> er can you imagine them doing this <unclear>shit</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0198">not particularly</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0192">even finding how to get to the schools navigating the buses or the roads</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0198">how did you find out how to get to <anon type="place"/>? did someone tell you?</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0192">yeah I think I was told to catch the bus</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0198"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0192">other people got driven</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0198">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> used to get picked up every day</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0198">went to her classes of six or seven children and then got driven home</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0192">it's cos she's a girl</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0198">what? that she got picked up?</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0192">I reckon</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0198">I think the teacher was just passing through anyway</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0198">but maybe because she was a new girl to the country</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah but I reckon teachers passed through me</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0198">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0192">I'm pretty sure to a certain degree girls had preferential treatment I think it was a little bit easier being a girl not really worried about rape out there or anything apart from other Westerners</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0198">some people'd disagree</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0192">you don't get treated worse cos you're a girl</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0198" trans="overlap">people like people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> definitely seems to have some bad treatment for being female</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0192"><unclear>oh well</unclear> she's living in a big city now I mean I don't know Korea's changing as well <anon type="place"/>'s changing every few years</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0192">there's a lot more port workers there now</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0192">I imagine things are getting less so but like I don't know I just think you're more trustworthy as a female teacher erm and when I first went into the elementary school they told me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like you can't touch the children and like they'd've never said that to a girl</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0192">to have a principal be like yeah basically we don't like foreigners to my face I don't think they'd say that to a girl and that kind of stuff <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got away with you know what she did just cos she cried guy would've never got away with that</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0192">we had to we had to do volleyball and stuff like that we had to girls can <trunc>p</trunc> you know should but can get out of it <unclear/></u>
<u n="1293" who="S0198"><unclear/> just as much as guys can volleyball's just I don't wanna er I think that just depends on the person</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0192">yeah but when you play volleyball there's no expectation you just have to stand there</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0198">I mean</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0192">as long as you're there contributing with us they're like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> spiker they get you right up there</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0192">they make you play for the teams they do all this kinda stuff you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0198">yeah they do if the girl's good at it I'm sure</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0192">and you probably didn't even have to do the female stuff so basically we had to do the male stuff but did you have to lay out the food or do anything like that?</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0198">yeah I always did that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0192">mm?</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0198">always helped clean up</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0192">but did you have to?</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0198" trans="overlap">otherwise I'd just be stood there doing nothing I dunno I felt like I should</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0192">mm I mean it's different in the teachers' office but like when you came to the after thingy after volleyball thing</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0192">were you setting up the food then?</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0198">yeah often I'd help yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0198">and go and bring the tables in and</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0192">that's one thing do you not agree with me? it's a little bit easier for a girl</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0198">I think it depends on I think other things</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0192">erm in the rural public school</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0198">I think the other I think there are other things that can make it harder to be a girl</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0192">I was talking about rural public school I mean I agree maybe it's harder for you to take control of your class</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0198">I think it depends I think it depends a lot on the schools and your co-teachers how that can be affected as well</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0192">as a guy I did have a certain amount of power over my female co-teachers</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0192">I think automatically</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0192">even though I was foreign didn't quite work but I am the type of person to push it a little bit to test it <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0198">mm <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1326" who="S0192">that's probably why I discovered it</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0198">see if it does work</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0192">I mean there's a weird dynamic though cos quite a few of the co-teachers are female and immediately a youngish female teacher doesn't really wanna be seen hanging around with a male foreigner too much</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0198">no yeah</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0192">cos rumours will start spreading er they don't want that kind of stuff so I had to the point where co-teachers aren't even talking to me coming to me <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0192">tell me something then walk off</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0198"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1334" who="S0192">I'm pretty sure some of it was partly because I was a guy and I was young and they all thought I was handsome <pause dur="short"/> some girls couldn't even talk they'd just giggle I'm talking about grown women</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1336" who="S0192">the <unclear>library er owner</unclear> or whatever</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0192">were you made to stand up on the podium and give a speech? cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0198">I had to stand up</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0192">but you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> weren't</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0198">I had to stand up and be introduced on the podium at sports day I don't remember talking</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0192">no we both had to give a speech to all the parents and the children and the teachers</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0198">again that can be school specific</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0192">can be but there were four of us two it happened to guys</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0198" trans="overlap">my school had a talk scholar as did as did er</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0198">as did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0198"><unclear/> talk scholars</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it was only mine that didn't they basically made me do the work of the talk scholar didn't they?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0198">oh yeah in the afternoon classes</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0192">yeah bastards</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>although</unclear> I got paid more for it and if I had if I'd've rolled over I wouldn't've done if I'm not the type of person I am</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0198">yeah <unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="1358" who="S0192">I wouldn't've got paid for that</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0192"><unclear>they never would've done it</unclear></u>
<u n="1361" who="S0198">some people do though they're crazy <pause dur="short"/> it's really shitty that very few national holidays are actually real national holidays and <unclear/> can make you go in</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1363" who="S0198"><vocal desc="cough"/> like really Chuseok being up in the air maybe maybe not that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0192">you can't really call it a national holiday can you? if it's er</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0198">I mean if Chuseok's up for grabs then any of them are right?</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0192">yeah oh it's Chuseok yeah definitely I mean that's</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0198">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got it off in the end but</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0192">there must be some people that don't</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0198">yeah <unclear>they wouldn't've said that</unclear></u>
<u n="1370" who="S0192">that's their Thanksgiving that's their bloody Christmas</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0198">who's sending their children to school then too? give them a break</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0192">mm do you want another cigarette?</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0198">yeah go on then <unclear/> have you got water?</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0192">yeah I've got a little bit here if you want there's enough for you</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0198">I still have to shower and</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0192">yeah I mean we've gotta shower go out and shop and then we need to come back and just crack on cos I mean what's the time already?</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0198">at least tomorrow <unclear>we do is just get it on and then</unclear></u>
<u n="1378" who="S0192">yeah takes a little while to set up but we'll get it on in the morning</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0198">I think by the end of today</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0192">do we have enough pasta? what did we have?</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0198">yeah we've got a whole pack of pasta <unclear>but again we</unclear></u>
<u n="1382" who="S0192">do we have any spaghetti though?</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0198">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0192">do we not wanna shut the door?</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0198">oh no we had a little bit <trunc>s</trunc> of spaghetti but not enough to count for a meal I don't think but we might have a bit of leftover pasta the two might do cover three dinners I'll check</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0192">we could buy some spaghetti though</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0198">yeah I don't suppose it's very expensive er <unclear/></u>
<u n="1388" who="S0192">maybe add that to the list</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0198">today I just wanna by the end of today I'm gonna <unclear/> <unclear>I don't suppose</unclear> although I don't know there's a lot of SNA work I've gotta do now</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0198">but erm by the end of today I wanna be prepared for week one and then tomorrow it's just studying again as usual</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0192">I don't know if I can really prepare for <trunc>w</trunc> I mean of course I can prepare for week one I can do the readings that they've set and stuff</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0192">but erm she's given me an assignment I've got stuff to do for the seminar <unclear>and like</unclear></u>
<u n="1395" who="S0198">yeah so</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0192">pidgins and creoles seminar is separate I have my lecture on Monday and my seminar on Wednesday</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh I see <trunc>sh</trunc> you're waiting you're wondering if you should wait until the lectures yeah</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so I kind of feel like I should do the lecture before I do the seminar</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0198">that's true</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0192">so I can do the reading but it means that between <trunc>M</trunc>Monday and Tuesday I'm really busy like Tuesday afternoon <unclear>I come</unclear> I'm I'm off so I'm gonna I've set myself actual slots and I er I've given myself lots of free study slots</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0192">but I've given myself five hours of each subject the er for like two hours or three hours is like the day before or like around it do you know what I mean? maybe not quite the day before I've got like one that's kind of far away and then one that's close</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0192">so I can definitely make sure I'm prepared <unclear>that</unclear> I can get on with it like</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh right yeah give yourself like a yeah</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0192">my study slot before the particular class <unclear>just</unclear></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0198">class yeah</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0192">which means it has to be some days before I've taped it to my desk as well</u>
<u n="1409" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1410" who="S0192">Korean style</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0192">they always had a piece of glass didn't they?</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0192">well I didn't think it was a terrible idea but it's a big piece of glass now</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0192">I think it would be better to just have some tape like some kind of I suppose it's still just as much it's just plastic <unclear/></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0198">little pinboard or something <unclear/></u>
<u n="1418" who="S0192">yeah that's true if you have the erm the pods</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the sun's got lower I think</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0198">do you remember the sun ever bothering my eyes when I sat here?</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0192">probably is getting a bit lower maybe it's a bit earlier in the day</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0192">I mean the arc lowers doesn't it? it goes like that whereas in er on the equator it basically just goes <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1425" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0192"><anon type="place"/> stays here</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1428" who="S0192">for hours between there and there for like six hours or something eight hours and then in the last three hours like two to three hours it comes all the way down it sets it's quite the sunset's quite impressive out there as well cos they're quick <unclear/></u>
<u n="1429" who="S0198">yeah you really see the sun go down</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0192">yeah the sun is setting</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0198">I know it's really like it's hitting the ocean</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0192">and then all that wind comes if you're anywhere on the coast</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0192">with a clear day watching the sunset</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear>man</unclear> that wind in the</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0192">it's like the sun is squashing</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0198">where were we in China?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0192">the wind into the sea</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0198">and the wind would whip up</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0192">oh god yeah that was windy place in general it's cos the only time we've ever been to China was winter</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0198">what was that called that place?</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0192">it's pretty cool we did two winter trips to China</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0198" trans="overlap">Pingyao</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0192">ah Pingyao wasn't really windy was it?</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0198">no what was I thinking of?</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0192">Pingyao was really smoggy it didn't have a lot of wind or anything</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah where am I thinking? it was the second time <unclear/></u>
<u n="1448" who="S0192">Pingyao everyone was burning <trunc>c</trunc>charcoal bricks weren't they? <unclear/></u>
<u n="1449" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0192">erm the second trip?</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0192">when we went to Yunnan</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0192">we went to Dali</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0198">oh Dali it was Dali</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0192">Dali had those mountains</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0198">it was Dali that got windy wasn't it? in the town market area</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0192">we did a couple of slightly hairy treks</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0192">there like up in the ice up on those mountains got a bit hairy and also on the erm Tiger Leaping Gorge when we went a bit wrong</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0192">that got pretty pretty hairy</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0192">as well that was er</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0198">we were like no let's go back</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah can't be this way</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0198">this whole</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0192">I had a really good time both times in China</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0198">yeah same they were both really good trips</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0192">I think we chose good spots I'd like to er if I were to live in China I'd like to kind of select a uni that is I'd like to see the pay go up though</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0198">in a place that you'd wanna live <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah is that what you were gonna say?</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0192">yeah somewhere I'd wanna live</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0192">like could you live in Harbin all year round?</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0198">no I dunno</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0192">it's a long old winter and</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0198">it wasn't a particularly pleasant town I didn't think it was fine it had a high street and that I suppose it wasn't that bad actually</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0192">yeah I mean down by the ice and stuff it was quite nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="1479" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it just seemed treacherous trying to walk around on the ice <unclear/></u>
<u n="1480" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but er the problem is that it's like scorching hot for half the year well not for half the year for like three months or something it got hot pretty quick there didn't it? I remember looking and it was still cold in Korea but it was like</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0198">yeah yeah it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="1482" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear><trunc>ho</trunc>hotter there</unclear></u>
<u n="1483" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0192">it was a bit strange erm</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1486" who="S0192">I don't think I could live there all year round it was good to go for a month <unclear/></u>
<u n="1487" who="S0198">I wonder what it'd be like when that river's flowing? be weird seeing it gradually freeze</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0192">mm freeze solid as well</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0192"><unclear>yeah</unclear> I dunno where I'd live I think where erm what's her face is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s probably quite a good spot</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0198">yeah she's down in</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0192">she's <trunc>pr</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc> I mean you're not</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0198"><unclear>she</unclear></u>
<u n="1494" who="S0192">I don't know if it's a great spot actually she's probably if she doesn't leave that island too much it's probably an alright place to live it's the most tropical part of China it kind of looks a bit like Vietnam and like places erm so if she just stays there but all she's got really near to her are massive cities she's got Zhangjiang where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> were she's got Guangzhou she's got Hong Kong Macau they're all pretty close but that's kinda it</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0192">it's like another twelve to eighteen-hour bus journey up to like erm I can't remember the name of that state now it's got Dalian in it and like you know those like limestone cast <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> went there that's not too far from them but she's another few hours from the coast I think China's humungous</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0192">constantly having to do twelve-hour trains and not really covering very much at all</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0198">that's humungous</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0192">it's pretty good though the train that we took from erm</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0198">that squirrel's always there</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0192">where was it from? <trunc>Qingda</trunc>Qingdao to Qufu</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0192">that was got up to like three hundred and something kilometres an hour</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0198">that was quite that was that nice train wasn't it? that was just a day train</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that was a proper nice bullet train it wasn't that expensive was it? it was like twenty quid or something</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0198">was that like five hours or something?</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0192">took us quite far yeah</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0198">it wasn't a sleeper was it?</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0192">erm and then we took a train from Beijing to <trunc>Har</trunc>Harbin what happened there? wasn't there like a problem? there were like no tickets how did we get a ticket? there were no sleeper tickets</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0198">there were no sleeper tickets</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0192">even that far in advance</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0198">did we get one in the end though? what happened?</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do you remember? we booked it ten days in advance and there were no sleeper tickets</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0198">so did we go by day?</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0192">yeah we had to go by day and we got on a fast train again it was a pretty nice train again</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0192">we went by day we arrived at night though it was already dark do you remember? and we were like <trunc>un</trunc> in that underground car park ready to take a taxi it was like really quite cold <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0198" trans="overlap">did we still have even though it wasn't <trunc>sch</trunc> even though the time wasn't scheduled for a sleeper did we still get a sleeper bed though? or were we in seats?</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0192">no I think we were in seats I remember seeing you could see erm you know like the other train that had a dial that told you the speed?</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0192">this one had a dial that told you the temperature</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0192">do you remember? cos we were like looking at the temperature and seeing it getting colder and colder as we were like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1525" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm and then we got out cos it was night time that was the coldest night wasn't it? when it got down to minus</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it was about minus twenty when we arrived I thought erm</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0198">yeah I thought it got lower than that</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0192" trans="overlap">was it? no I think the next night was the coldest night or something and then it warmed up for a few days I think it got down to like minus twenty-seven or something I think was like the coldest we got to but it was actually on a <trunc>m</trunc> bit of a mild patch for a couple of nights</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0198">that was a tiny little room we had there as well so</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0192">yeah frozen solid everything was frozen solid</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh yeah the windows outside</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0192">what a cool place you actually live in the ice like proper</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0198">you couldn't leave your shit on the windowsill cos it would freeze</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no cos it'd freeze yeah the windowsill inside your room but the rooms were all hot</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0198">yeah they did heat them</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0192">we weren't cold</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0198">we were never cold</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0192">no inside</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0198">the only time is maybe <vocal desc="cough"/> <trunc>sh</trunc> the problem was er if the showers were hot they had a tendency to be boiling do you remember?</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0192" trans="overlap">how much does it cost to? yeah</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0198">and I got that weird skin shit going on on my legs</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0198">all those like dried winter rashes or something</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0192">the cold'd screw your skin up</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0198">it was hardy on our skin</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0192">how much did it cost them to heat that place?</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0192">it's minus thirty</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0192">pounding against the wall like trying to cool down the place and they managed to keep it like toasty inside</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0198">yeah it's kind of amazing actually I mean surely that stuff does break and people just die or something it's not like you're in Canada <unclear/></u>
<u n="1552" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1553" who="S0198">in Toronto dealing with the temperatures</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0192">yeah definitely not you're in northern China you're about as close as you can get to Russia and Mongolia in in China really without being in the without being in Outer Mongolia I'm glad I finally understand the difference between Inner Mongolia and Outer Mongolia</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0198">Outer Mongolia mm</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0192">Inner Mongolia is simply Mongolia</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0192">Outer Mongolia is well used to be Mongolia but China took it</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>expansion of erm China into Mongolia</unclear> erm shame that just like China just took to that and</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0192">it's pretty crap isn't it? I mean <vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah because they didn't want to be</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0192">is the problem</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0198">it wasn't a choice was it?</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0198">and they were an established</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0192">yeah one of the oldest civilisations on the planet</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0192">I mean we met the Dalai Lama</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0192">how amazing is that? didn't shake his hand or anything but we had a teaching from him</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0192">we were only</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> for the tea and biscuits <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1574" who="S0192">it was probably only like ten people</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0198" trans="overlap">weird little shitty radios they make you buy for no reason</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0192">how <trunc>th</trunc> how many people away do you think he was? like ten people?</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0198">yeah he wasn't very far away we were round the side <unclear/></u>
<u n="1578" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I'd say he was about like ten people I think</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0192">maybe like ten rows maybe fifteen at the most</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0198">no I wouldn't even say it was <unclear>ah no</unclear> cos people er</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we had a very clear view of him</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0198">cos when people started praying there there was quite a bit of room for them to</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0198">to squat and bend down so he <trunc>c</trunc> ah see what that squirrel just properly yanked something out of the tree then</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0192">yeah erm</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0198">it's a proper resident that one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1588" who="S0192">we had to get a special ID card didn't we? to go and see the Dalai Lama</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0198">still have it</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0192">yeah I think I still have mine</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0198" trans="overlap">in my bits and bobs somewhere</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0192">I've got all those notes and coins</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0198">yeah I've got I've got a thing under the bed of just er shite like at one point I was still collecting bloody stubs and stuff <unclear>and I</unclear> stopped doing that it got silly</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0192">I think before we move out of here another task that we have is to like sell and to get rid of stuff</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0192">I'm gonna try and sell my CDs after things calm down like in January</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0198">mm my parents <unclear>replied about that Ebay</unclear> <unclear/> message</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0192">Ebay? what? those things your dad <trunc>s</trunc> was selling?</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0192">fair <pause dur="short"/> what was he selling again? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0198">er some like vintage Nintendo game things they're called Nintendo watches I don't know if you've ever seen one they're like little rectangle things that fold out and then</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0192">wear it as a watch</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0198">no no no it's a <trunc>com</trunc> it's a little handheld it's er kind of like a Game Boy but like a Nintendo a different version they're like <trunc>s</trunc> there was like a Donkey Kong one and like different packaging and stuff they must've had a brief blip in the nineties or something because I never</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0192" trans="overlap">how did your dad get hold of them?</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0198">I think he gets them from he's <unclear>probably</unclear> found them at boot fairs he's had them for like</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0192">just cheap</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0198">he's had them for a few years he just hasn't he's just been waiting until I've been home to sell them as though it's gonna bring me like <vocal desc="laugh"/> hundreds of pounds when it's really just gonna be like two hundred quid</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0192">mm that's not too bad</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0198">but I feel bad cos I know they don't have much money and I know my dad keeps spending shit on me and I just feel like he should take at least half of it</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is your mum bothered about it?</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0198">no my mum doesn't care she doesn't worry too much</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0192">I mean our parents haven't spent much on us in the last ten years really</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0198">no <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1614" who="S0192">so I guess if we're home now they might wanna treat us <unclear/></u>
<u n="1615" who="S0198">be really good just for someone just to win a large amount of money</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0192">they probably want to treat you because they want to make you want to come home</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0198"><unclear/> ah can't think about leaving yet</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0192">cos they wanna show you how easy it is to be at home and how your family can help you out and all that kinda stuff I reckon there's an insidious plan afoot</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1621" who="S0198"><unclear>I dunno</unclear></u>
<u n="1622" who="S0192"><unclear>hello do I wink or something</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1624" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">shall I winkle it out with my winkle</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0192">pickers</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1628" who="S0198">winklepickers er that actor's really random</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0198">he's a really like good person did you notice though when he the episode where they get married</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1632" who="S0198">the episode he marries Sophie his parents are kind of in the background but you never see them or meet them</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0198">they're never he never interacts even though he has mentioned his other I thought that was weird that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1635" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0198">they obviously hadn't</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0192">hadn't used those characters yet</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0198">hadn't didn't know how to work them into the plot</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they probably didn't need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1640" who="S0198">whereas having an episode just about them visiting</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0192">for Christmas</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0198">gives them a good breadth of character development</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0192"><unclear/> definitely it's a real Jezing <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> better go and answer that I wouldn't wanna Jez it</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0192">or do a Mark all in my pants <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1646" who="S0198">they are funny parents</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0192">Mark in my pants yeah</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0198">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah poor Jeremy</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> poor Mark poor both of them</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0198">no Mark is er as er Dobby said you're a total dick</u>
<u n="1651" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1652" who="S0192">yeah yeah he kind of is do you think Jez isn't then?</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0198">well no I mean they're both dicks aren't they? in their own ways but er not in a <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're too funny to for it to matter</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0192">Jez is</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0198"><unclear>it's</unclear> I think it's quite realistic in some ways</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0192">yeah I mean to a certain degree people are pretty crazy</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0192">life is a bit of a Peep Show</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0198">and life is a bit er just shit</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0192"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1661" who="S0198">sometimes <unclear>a lot of people are</unclear></u>
<u n="1662" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean obviously it's exaggerated</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0198">yeah and also er it's also they also <unclear>highlight in thinking er</unclear> that it is sort of self-inflicted to an extent</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0198"><unclear>it's</unclear> because of er who they are and</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0198">the decisions that they make that things happen to them</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0198">just need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1670" who="S0192">can't help themselves <unclear>though cos it's just</unclear></u>
<u n="1671" who="S0198">definitely have the thoughts</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0192" trans="overlap">kind of has a more nature than nurture aspect to it they are who they are and they can't really change</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0198">I wonder what the last season'll be like</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0192">yeah I don't know hope it's funny</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0192">I'm sure it will be all the other seasons before have been pretty damn funny</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0198">the last one well the baby'll be quite big</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0192">perhaps</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0198">oh another squirrel's coming down to <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="1680" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear>I dunno</unclear></u>
<u n="1681" who="S0198">come check out what's going on with his mates</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0192">ah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1683" who="S0198">er are there <trunc>li</trunc> are there like just a chain of trees that</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1685" who="S0198"><unclear>all</unclear> go round this area? do they all live <unclear>on</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0192">oh you said a chain of trees what go around this area</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0198">oh did I?</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0198">that's interesting</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0192">which or that</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0192">yeah I presume so he's right coming down what's his little mate gonna do?</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0198">I dunno share are they friends?</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0192">I don't know</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0198">he's gonna pop up the other side I mean I dunno I swear that fencing down there is getting worse</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0192">hopefully they'll have a fight yeah maybe do you reckon they're gonna fight?</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0198">yeah where is he? the other one</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0192">he knows he's there I think</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0198"><vocal desc="cough"/> is that why he's moving away with the food?</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0192">yeah perhaps it's nice to have squirrels just well it's not our garden is it? we don't actually have a garden but</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0198">no but it is a bit of wilderness none the less</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0198">and the squirrel definitely helps with the vibe</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0198">actually having a creature out there every day</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0192">and pretty much everyone's seen it it's come over haven't they?</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and the fact that there's fruit trees and the fact that nobody uses their garden otherwise we'd if <trunc>s</trunc> if if somebody if they just used their garden a lot then we'd constantly be staring at each other</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we'd feel more conscious yeah</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0198">we'd probably have we'd probably end up talking</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0192">that garden's a mess this one could get used</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0198">I keep forgetting</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but if they're not using it <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="1713" who="S0198">that that garden next door</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0192">is part of our house</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0198">is part of our house <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1717" who="S0198">you realise that I keep forgetting cos whenever we talk about them and the fact no whenever I come in I always talk about the fact that we don't know who lives downstairs clearly they er that couple lives there and that guy lives there <unclear/></u>
<u n="1718" who="S0192">surely <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are gonna see this as proper terraced housing</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0198">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0192">this is how we do it</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0192">like you've got</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0198">you get your little rectangle bit at the back</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1725" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1726" who="S0192">that we don't have access to</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0192">there's like them them them them</u>
<u n="1729" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">them</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0192">them so how many neighbours do we actually have?</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0198" trans="overlap">someone's like when they realise they could turn these houses into little flats</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0198"><trunc>s</trunc>someone started laughing</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0192">and fairly nice little flats</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0192">yeah and then they've just done the whole thing <unclear>and they just went</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1738" who="S0198" trans="overlap">as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said hers was a purpose built block of flats in <anon type="place"/> and I <trunc>th</trunc> quite liked it I thought it was quite nice like it was a proper flat like it you know it was fairly new and everything but erm she did say it was quite a bit smaller than this</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0198">and I think it was</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0192">we have</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1743" who="S0192">six neighbours</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0192">six different households that are attached to us</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0192">that's insane</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like one two</u>
<u n="1750" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">three</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0192">four five six</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0198">mm with numerous couples or whatever in these</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0192">now that is terraced housing cos normally in a proper terraced house if you own the house</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0192">like a small little house like my mum had or something</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you'd only have two people</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0192">then it's just your next door neighbours on either side</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0192">that's just two</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0198">we've got them above and below</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0192">I don't think you can get any more than this there is no way of having more neighbours</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0192">unless your building is some really long shape that connects with a bunch of other buildings</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no this is the only way it's like being in er flats I suppose you've got them either side of you but not what's nice about this this flat is that we get the front and the back of the building</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0198">I think there are some flats that we looked at before that have come up where you just get one side of it</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0198">they split they split it differently</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0192">definitely I agree</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0198">so it's nice that we go</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0192">across the whole building</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0198">so you've got a front and a back</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0198"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1775" who="S0192">I think this was a good find I really don't think we could've found much better than this</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0192">with what we were trying to do okay we need to shower and get ready</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0198">yeah we do</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0198">shall we do that now?</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0192">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
