<text id="SBA6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:19:36</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0509 S0510</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON &amp; ANON's home, Hastings</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cooking, Food, local events, Theatre and Cinema, Doctor Who</topics>
		<activity>Mother and Daughter discussing food and TV</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0509">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hastings</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0510">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Receptionist</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0510">mm yeah that that rice was very tasty I know I know you found that a little bit hot didn't you?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah really hot</u>
<u n="3" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was trying to figure out why it was so hot I know that she did when she made it she obviously did use chilli but I mean not excessively but I think</u>
<u n="4" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0510">what gave it that particular heat was the mustard seeds that she used in it</u>
<u n="6" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="7" who="S0510">erm cos I noticed there was a lot of mustard seeds in there</u>
<u n="8" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0510">so I think it was probably a combination but the lemon for me just perfectly balanced balanced it out</u>
<u n="10" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no it doesn't take anything away it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0510">really?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0509">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0510">no she was erm she was telling me that she'd been cooking rice on Saturday because in southern India where she's from she's from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="15" who="S0510" trans="overlap">erm oh no hold on hold on no she's not from <anon type="place"/> I lied she's from <anon type="place"/> erm but still south</u>
<u n="16" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="17" who="S0510">erm during monseen <trunc>mo</trunc> <vocal desc="misc"/> monseen <trunc>so</trunc> monseen susan</u>
<u n="18" who="S0509" trans="overlap">monsson</u>
<u n="19" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0510">erm monsoon season</u>
<u n="21" who="S0509" trans="overlap">season</u>
<u n="22" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">have you seen the monseen?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0510" trans="overlap">monseen?</u>
<u n="24" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0510">yeah erm they tend not to eat meat and they eat a lot of vegetarian food</u>
<u n="26" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="27" who="S0510">and this is in part because of their the drastic changes in temperature the heat and the rain</u>
<u n="28" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0510">erm <trunc>the</trunc> partly I think it's to do with the fact that erm with all those rains often come sort of waterborne diseases like cholera and things like that</u>
<u n="30" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0510">and so they're more traditionally they've been more reticent to eat meat during that period because of the amount of you know?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0510">disease and that that could be transmitted but also because obviously the cow and all the rest of it are sacred you know? to Hindus</u>
<u n="34" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0510">erm particularly as well erm during this month their sort of monsoony month er it's a sin actually to to kill a erm an animal</u>
<u n="36" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh for what?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0510">that is because it's often their breeding season as well so</u>
<u n="38" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0510">to kill one that is either you know? erm with well I don't know with eggs or or you know?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0510">sort of</u>
<u n="42" who="S0509">with young</u>
<u n="43" who="S0510">with <trunc>yo</trunc> well pregnant</u>
<u n="44" who="S0509">pregnant yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or whatever yeah erm so there's lots of things that tie into it but mainly religiously also in the ayurvedic erm ayurvedic medicine which is sort of you know? traditional Indian medicine</u>
<u n="46" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="47" who="S0510">erm apparently during monsoon season you know? with those fluctuations in temperature and everything your immunity is supposed to be erm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="49" who="S0510">lower so er they they just <trunc>encour</trunc> you know? they encourage them to eat lots of vegetarian food or non-meat food basically</u>
<u n="50" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0510">so she was cooking up a storm on Saturday erm doing lots of different rices and I don't know if you noticed with that rice I'm going to have to ask her where she got it from and I have a feeling she probably ships it over from India</u>
<u n="52" who="S0509">really?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0510">because it's so much</u>
<u n="54" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0510">it's such a longer grain it's more like a basmati rice</u>
<u n="56" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0510">it's a much longer grain erm I mean she obviously cooks it to perfection she's a very good good cook erm <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I wouldn't mind trying to get hold of some of that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I mean it's possible there's an Asian or you know? erm like Indian rather food shop that</u>
<u n="60" who="S0509">that will sell it</u>
<u n="61" who="S0510">that will sell it but I'd imagine it's it is</u>
<u n="62" who="S0509">specialist</u>
<u n="63" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0509">yeah I can't get those Icelandic biscuits anywhere they're really <unclear/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0509">I know</u>
<u n="67" who="S0510">they are like erm Rich Tea on steroids those Icelandic biscuits aren't they?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0509">yeah a bit</u>
<u n="69" who="S0510">do you not? do you not see the parallels with Rich Tea?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah but they're really <unclear/> the erm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0510">that's true</u>
<u n="72" who="S0509">the Icelandic ones</u>
<u n="73" who="S0510">aha yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0509">yeah it's really nice</u>
<u n="75" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm I like it <unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I know I mean they are such they're like tablets aren't they?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0510">they're such big</u>
<u n="80" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they're like you know like they have sea biscuits? that like seamen would take</u>
<u n="81" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0509">they're like those</u>
<u n="83" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah or those ration biscuits you know? <unclear/> for when those mountaineers go up</u>
<u n="84" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="85" who="S0510">you know?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0509">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0509">except they actually taste of something which I think the other ones don't</u>
<u n="91" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0509">I think they're kind of like sustenance only</u>
<u n="93" who="S0510">mm yeah no enjoyment factor <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="95" who="S0510">or no flavour</u>
<u n="96" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="97" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0510">ah so how much did it cost to ship a packet of those Icelandic <vocal desc="laugh"/> biscuits?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0509" trans="overlap">like fifteen quid just for the shipping</u>
<u n="101" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh my goodness and the biscuits themselves were?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0509">like three quid</u>
<u n="103" who="S0510"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I was like oh great I can buy some oh no I can't</u>
<u n="105" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0509">that would just be ridiculous I might as well fly over there</u>
<u n="107" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0509">and like stock up</u>
<u n="109" who="S0510">actually yeah you might be able to you know? make yourself a profit selling them on the open market</u>
<u n="110" who="S0509">yeah oh my god</u>
<u n="111" who="S0510" trans="overlap">could go <trunc>ov</trunc> you know? fund your fund your flight and</u>
<u n="112" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0510">trip to Iceland by</u>
<u n="114" who="S0509">yeah get like one of those cheap flights on like an off day</u>
<u n="115" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and like just hop over there fill up a suitcase with</u>
<u n="117" who="S0510" trans="overlap">find a shop</u>
<u n="118" who="S0509">fill like you don't even need to take any insurance cos you can just go there and come back on the same day</u>
<u n="119" who="S0510" trans="overlap">exactly same day yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0509">just fill up a suitcase with as many of the biscuits as you can</u>
<u n="121" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0509">and then bring them back</u>
<u n="123" who="S0510"><vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0509">it's like probably there's nobody ever here who actually knows what they are</u>
<u n="125" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> call for them yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0509">or would pay like three quid for them</u>
<u n="127" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0509">which is unfortunate</u>
<u n="129" who="S0510">ah maybe you could get a little you know? market market stallholders mind you that's a long old</u>
<u n="130" who="S0509" trans="overlap">maybe I can</u>
<u n="131" who="S0510">sort of trail then isn't it? of kind of pushing it to lots of individual retailers and</u>
<u n="132" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I was talking to erm this guy on Sunday when I was at work who does the seafood and wine festival</u>
<u n="133" who="S0510">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and he was talking about how it's like literally a thousand quid for a pitch</u>
<u n="135" who="S0510">I wondered how much it was cos there was a lot of talk in the social media</u>
<u n="136" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0510">this year about the <trunc>exor</trunc> exorbitant prices but didn't say what the price was</u>
<u n="138" who="S0509">cos he was one of the guys who started it this guy he does ciders</u>
<u n="139" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="140" who="S0509">and he was in <anon type="place"/> yeah he was I was <trunc>say</trunc> oh did you go to see food and wine the other week</u>
<u n="141" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and he was like oh yeah I was selling cider and he's been doing it from the beginning</u>
<u n="143" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="144" who="S0509">erm and yeah it's just not good</u>
<u n="145" who="S0510">so how much did it start out at? did he say?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0509">well I don't think it started out as much at all I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> I don't know</u>
<u n="147" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0509">I don't know if it was anything but</u>
<u n="149" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0509">but it's just become more and more expensive and like more</u>
<u n="151" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0509">like he was saying er less local and more like the big restaurants like <anon type="place"/> and that</u>
<u n="153" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah aha</u>
<u n="154" who="S0509">are doing it which is kind of defeating the point you know?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah cos it's <trunc>al</trunc> although <anon type="place"/> are local but yeah all the smaller local eateries and</u>
<u n="156" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0510">producers and everything just can't afford those kind of</u>
<u n="158" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah no</u>
<u n="159" who="S0510">a thousand pound a day was it?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0509">I think for the whole for the whole weekend including</u>
<u n="161" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or for the two days <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0509">but still</u>
<u n="163" who="S0510">but you've still got to make a lot to cover that sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0510">and then you've got all the staff that you're paying or you know?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0510">er okay if you're doing it as a one man band <trunc>fa</trunc> fair enough</u>
<u n="168" who="S0509" trans="overlap">fair enough</u>
<u n="169" who="S0510">but really you need more than that to</u>
<u n="170" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah cos he was he was saying as well how it you know? he'd been doing it before and then it on the first time he ever tried to do it it was like raining but then it got more popular and he was</u>
<u n="171" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0509">there were like two of them running this stall and one of them got food poisoning and was just like lying down</u>
<u n="173" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0509">so he was running this stall single-handedly when it became really popular</u>
<u n="175" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah ah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0509">you know? and er yeah crazy time</u>
<u n="177" who="S0510">that's not a very good erm advert for their stall though if it mind you it wasn't food it was alcohol but</u>
<u n="178" who="S0509">yeah and he even got yeah no it was yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it was unrelated food poisoning</u>
<u n="180" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0509">yeah should've mentioned that by now</u>
<u n="182" who="S0510">mm <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0510">ah that's a real shame isn't it?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0510">and and also <vocal desc="cough"/> I know everybody I'm generalising now cos I just said everybody</u>
<u n="187" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0510">that's not true but erm a lot of people erm <pause dur="short"/> don't like the fact that these sort of festivals you know? that start off local and</u>
<u n="189" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0510">kind of <unclear/> or</u>
<u n="191" who="S0509" trans="overlap">become <unclear/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0510">yeah and and then you know? they become out of well just out of reach of the the local</u>
<u n="193" who="S0509">community</u>
<u n="194" who="S0510">community that they're they're servicing or you know? producers and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="195" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah cos that's what he that's <unclear/> it used to be producers and now it's it's not</u>
<u n="196" who="S0510" trans="overlap">aha yeah and and that's what it was supposed to be about showcasing just what amazing</u>
<u n="197" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0510">you know? local food and wine you can get</u>
<u n="199" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0510">but yeah when it becomes as big as that then sadly what tends to happen is that the smaller man gets cut out really</u>
<u n="201" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and that's who it's sort of all about in the first place</u>
<u n="203" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0510">such a shame</u>
<u n="205" who="S0509">it is indeed yeah well cos I was saying as well it's the first year we haven't been</u>
<u n="206" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0509">so it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0509">it's just <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0510">yeah it didn't look that inviting to be honest I think I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no it just looked crammed and like</u>
<u n="212" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0509">we were only going to go in and buy food</u>
<u n="214" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0509">and I <trunc>co</trunc> there are other places that I can buy food and I can buy food from most of these places without paying to go in there</u>
<u n="216" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0509">yeah I know it's only a nominal sum but even then</u>
<u n="218" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just the it's the fact that you are</u>
<u n="219" who="S0509" trans="overlap">if they they do have music going on though to be fair I suppose</u>
<u n="220" who="S0510">I didn't hear any of it</u>
<u n="221" who="S0509">oh well they had that tent though didn't they? so there should have been</u>
<u n="222" who="S0510">did they have that beachside? because like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0510">oh they did in the end oh</u>
<u n="225" who="S0509">well it looked that's what it looked like to me anyway</u>
<u n="226" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right mm I know when they were doing or supposed to be doing the beach festival erm part of the problem with that other than the lack of funding initially</u>
<u n="227" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0510">was that there was work being done on the RNLI building</u>
<u n="229" who="S0509" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0510">so they couldn't have that spot</u>
<u n="231" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0510">erm but you know the bigger thing was they were more likely to get funding putting it where they put it in the end</u>
<u n="233" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="234" who="S0510">erm the council supported it more</u>
<u n="235" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0510">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> I hope to go back though</u>
<u n="237" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0510" trans="overlap">just to check it out and see what it's like</u>
<u n="239" who="S0509">yeah well we were busy this year really <unclear/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0510" trans="overlap">we were</u>
<u n="241" who="S0509">was that when auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was down?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0510">yes it was and of course she's not a seafood girl really</u>
<u n="243" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="244" who="S0510">so</u>
<u n="245" who="S0509"><unclear/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah it wasn't really somewhere she was wanting to go and then I was going to go the following weekend and then our plans went awry</u>
<u n="247" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0510">with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0509">have you spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> recently?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0510">I have yeah erm well not spoken to her but in contact with her yeah <unclear/> yeah er she's definitely up for Hamlet</u>
<u n="253" who="S0509">oh yeah I was forgetting about that when is that?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah she's</u>
<u n="255" who="S0509">is that the fifteenth or something?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0510" trans="overlap">it's the fifteenth of October she's really excited about it by all accounts</u>
<u n="257" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear>me too</unclear></u>
<u n="258" who="S0510">erm yeah and auntie ah did I tell you auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said don't worry about getting the money back to me you keep the money and go see Hamlet</u>
<u n="259" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah go and see yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0510">or you know?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0509">go yeah go see something else</u>
<u n="262" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but I would like to see Hamlet</u>
<u n="263" who="S0509">yeah?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0510">yeah I would as I'm missing out on Benedict and and sorry <unclear/> I would like to see Macbeth</u>
<u n="265" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0510">did I? I said Hamlet again didn't I?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah you did</u>
<u n="268" who="S0510">oh dear</u>
<u n="269" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0510">that food clearly didn't help</u>
<u n="271" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0510">I obviously need a knock on the head erm yeah I'd love to see the Macbeth film do you know what the running time is on it but they had the premiere yesterday</u>
<u n="273" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh did they?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0509">wait it's erm BFI film festival soon as well isn't there?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is it?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0509">yeah yeah yeah I think</u>
<u n="278" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="279" who="S0509">like <trunc>nex</trunc> yeah next month in October</u>
<u n="280" who="S0510">oh right so</u>
<u n="281" who="S0509">so it won't be part of that but I just remembered that that's something that's happening</u>
<u n="282" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0509">er what was I going to say? <pause dur="short"/> something relatively interesting</u>
<u n="284" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0509">that's now escaped me</u>
<u n="286" who="S0510">to do with Hamlet? or?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0509">oh Arthur Darvill you know Arthur Darvill who played Rory?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh he was in Doctor Who yeah oh yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0509">he I've discovered that he he can sing and it's it's <trunc>qui</trunc></u>
<u n="290" who="S0510" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0509">yeah he's in like a Broadway thing but it's it's erm it's quite funny cos they had him on radio one this was a while ago now but I found the video of it er stumbled across it erm and he does this parody to erm Let It Go from Frozen</u>
<u n="292" who="S0510">oh yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0509">and the last line is my agent is contactable every day and it's just this hilarious parody of him going on about like how he's not in Doctor Who any more and he's a he's a proper actor</u>
<u n="294" who="S0510" trans="overlap">actor <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0509">like leave me alone I don't I'm not in it any more</u>
<u n="296" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0509"><unclear/> I'll have to play it he gets really into it as well</u>
<u n="298" who="S0510">wow well he's done well then to get on Broadway after that cos I I mean outside of Doctor Who I wasn't aware of him</u>
<u n="299" who="S0509">no I think he was more theatre though you see</u>
<u n="300" who="S0510">oh he was right mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah cos that yeah I'm sure he'd worked with Matt Smith in theatre before</u>
<u n="302" who="S0510">mm oh yeah I'm forgetting Matt Smith <unclear/> theatre boy</u>
<u n="303" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they all have theatre careers to start with does erm Amy what was her name?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0510">Amy</u>
<u n="305" who="S0509" trans="overlap">Karen Gillan</u>
<u n="306" who="S0510">Karen Gillan that's right mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0509">I don't know I don't know what she did</u>
<u n="308" who="S0510">she's done okay for herself though</u>
<u n="309" who="S0509">yeah <unclear/> this thing was going round on Twitter the other day I probably <trunc>fe</trunc> found the Arthur Darvill thing</u>
<u n="310" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="311" who="S0509">erm fifteen second Shakespeare lyrics and it's all these people that like celebrities doing erm <pause dur="short"/> shakespeare lyrics er Shakespeare style lyrics</u>
<u n="312" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm wow</u>
<u n="313" who="S0509">and they're like saying lyrics from songs but in this like really overdramatic way</u>
<u n="314" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0509">and it was really funny</u>
<u n="316" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0509">have you seen it?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0510">no I haven't you'll have to show me</u>
<u n="319" who="S0509">I will</u>
<u n="320" who="S0510">so it kind of gives the lyrics a whole different erm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0509">twist</u>
<u n="322" who="S0510">twist yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0510">sounds good</u>
<u n="325" who="S0509" trans="overlap">it's very good</u>
<u n="326" who="S0510">mm I must say I was quite impressed with the new Doctor Who</u>
<u n="327" who="S0509">yeah?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0510">yeah erm I was finding myself being drawn into it you know the other morning when you had it on?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0510">whereas <trunc>w</trunc>with Matt Smith by that last series I was just like oh this is just ridiculous</u>
<u n="331" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh yeah by the last series <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0509">it's still the same writer though that's the thing</u>
<u n="334" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is it really?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0509">oh yeah Stephen Moffat although the episode might have been written by somebody else</u>
<u n="336" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0509">but he's still the guy in charge but he writes Sherlock as well</u>
<u n="338" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0509">and</u>
<u n="340" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0509">Sherlock's brilliant but he just gets a bit</u>
<u n="342" who="S0510" trans="overlap">now I know but I seem to remember with the Matt Smith Doctor Who those really bad ones they tended to be the bad ones were Stephen Moffat written</u>
<u n="343" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and yet like you say he kind of writes Sherlock and that's brilliant</u>
<u n="345" who="S0509">and he's a he's a when he was doing Doctor Who as like he would be a guest writer sort of thing</u>
<u n="346" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0509">he was really good you know?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0509">he did the first weeping angels episode he came up with the weeping angels</u>
<u n="350" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh god yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0509">he did brilliant episodes</u>
<u n="352" who="S0510">mm mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0509">but then it just kind of a little bit ah when he was actually part of it</u>
<u n="354" who="S0510">yeah I got a bit bored with it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0509">yeah well so did I and I was really sad</u>
<u n="356" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0509">yeah and then you know Matt Smith left and that was it</u>
<u n="358" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0509">for me but I'm I'm I'm willing to give it another go especially since Clara's leaving</u>
<u n="360" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0509">everyone who who I know who likes Doctor Who hates Clara</u>
<u n="362" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0509">it's quite funny</u>
<u n="364" who="S0510">it's just that you think she is sort of like a know it all character</u>
<u n="365" who="S0509">I don't know yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or is it cos of that that relationship with the doctor seems a bit too cosy too soon</u>
<u n="367" who="S0509">yeah there's just something about her</u>
<u n="368" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0509">bit <pause dur="short"/> unenjoyable</u>
<u n="370" who="S0510">mm <pause dur="short"/> what's that? I've forgotten the actors name now that</u>
<u n="371" who="S0509">oh god erm I do know it oh my god</u>
<u n="372" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> think of it Peter no erm <unclear/> Peter</u>
<u n="373" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0510">Capaldi</u>
<u n="375" who="S0509">oh you were on about him?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0510" trans="overlap">Capaldi yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0509">oh yeah I thought you were talking about the woman who plays Clara</u>
<u n="378" who="S0510">oh no</u>
<u n="379" who="S0509">Jenna Coleman that's her name</u>
<u n="380" who="S0510">oh yeah yeah alright</u>
<u n="381" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0510">no he plays it very well</u>
<u n="383" who="S0509">yeah?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0510">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm that episode on Saturday it was we should have known really it was such a good twist</u>
<u n="385" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0510" trans="overlap">but of course he knew what Davros or whatever his name is Davros sounds like a it's like a kebab shop owner or something but</u>
<u n="387" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0510">he was like the head of the Daleks</u>
<u n="389" who="S0509">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0510" trans="overlap">erm yeah we should have known that he <unclear/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but then he sent his will to the Mistress I did I thought she was funny I like her</u>
<u n="392" who="S0510">Missy oh she was brilliant</u>
<u n="393" who="S0509">well it's the master but in a different incarnation</u>
<u n="394" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="395" who="S0509">did you not realise?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0510">I didn't no cos obviously I wasn't in from the beginning of that one</u>
<u n="397" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="398" who="S0510">you see</u>
<u n="399" who="S0509">yeah but she was in last series as well</u>
<u n="400" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no I don't remember her in last series</u>
<u n="401" who="S0509">she was in the last episode</u>
<u n="402" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="403" who="S0509">which is one of the few that I watched</u>
<u n="404" who="S0510">right mm hm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0509">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="406" who="S0510">cor those berry <trunc>bi</trunc>biscuits are nice</u>
<u n="407" who="S0509">are they?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0510" trans="overlap">have you had any?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="410" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0509"><unclear/> can I have a bite?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0510">yeah well have one</u>
<u n="413" who="S0509">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0509"><unclear/> I'll just do those apples now</u>
<u n="416" who="S0510">so the apples are going in are they? so <unclear/> really old recipe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0509" trans="overlap">now I think I've got I think I've got too many I'm not going to lie I don't think it's going to fill this tin</u>
<u n="418" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0509">I I I <unclear/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they obviously had bigger Granny Smith's then sorry smaller Granny Smith's in <unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0509" trans="overlap">erm probably like a bigger tin they probably had like a massive tin which</u>
<u n="422" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh you know what you could do it in darling?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0509">what?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0510">in in the ceramic casserole dish</u>
<u n="425" who="S0509">well it's too late now I've lined it and things and I don't want to really want to re-roll and I'll probably use that to do erm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah ah shame</u>
<u n="427" who="S0509">thingamajiggy</u>
<u n="428" who="S0510">well you're getting as bad as me now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0509">you know you know</u>
<u n="430" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> whatsit</u>
<u n="431" who="S0509">erm apple crumble</u>
<u n="432" who="S0510">oh you're doing a crumble as well oh</u>
<u n="433" who="S0509">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0510" trans="overlap">or you could use a spare you use the spare for the crumble is it?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0509">oh I could do yeah that's a good idea</u>
<u n="436" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0509">yeah that'll work woohoo</u>
<u n="438" who="S0510">mm hm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0509">there's this mixture that goes onto these apples that's literally butter and sugar</u>
<u n="440" who="S0510">wow</u>
<u n="441" who="S0509">and I may have tasted some</u>
<u n="442" who="S0510">you may have?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0510">just some? or a lot?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0509">no just like a little a little bit of the thing</u>
<u n="446" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0509">but it was really nice and I was like this this is what would kill me</u>
<u n="448" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="449" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0509">is is this enough? is this too many? let's scoop some out onto the thing</u>
<u n="451" who="S0510">mm are you not going to erm par bake it first?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0509">it didn't say to on the recipe</u>
<u n="453" who="S0510">oh you don't want a soggy bottom dear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0509">good job I'm not a professional baker</u>
<u n="455" who="S0510">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0509"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0510">whose recipe did you use?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0509"><trunc>Al</trunc>Allrecipes online website you know?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah was it the BBC one?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0509">no it's a different one</u>
<u n="461" who="S0510" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="462" who="S0509">but like they rate it and it's quite like a popular site so you get lots of ratings and reviews</u>
<u n="463" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="464" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and it's had like five stars</u>
<u n="465" who="S0510">oh great yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0509">hopefully it'll be good</u>
<u n="467" who="S0510">mm so can we look forward to a a portion tonight then?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0509">I hope so</u>
<u n="469" who="S0510">now I need to go out and get some milk don't I?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0510">shall I get something else to go to go with it like some cream or something?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh yeah you could do yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
