<text id="SBDD">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:09</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Knitting, celebrities, the Olympics, art, Easter</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking while making tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">oh what's that your uh</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">this is a <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">is that the one that you just started or?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">it's another chicken</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115">that one of your  one of your  collection of chickens?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">what I think I might do is like at work um thought I might like give them to some people with a little <trunc>Ea</trunc> with a little Cadbury's Crème Egg in as like a Easter present</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">well that is quite a good idea uh well creative anyway</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">yeah well like</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">just like as as a present so</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">well just cos like why not</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">uh and then afterwards you might be able to use it as a as an egg warmer</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037" trans="overlap">egg warmer <pause dur="short"/> yeah of course</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">I'm sure people would like them</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115">what does an egg warmer? Like when do you when would you use that?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">like when you've made a boiled egg in between eating the boiled egg and dish putting it on the plate like</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">that's when I suppose <pause dur="short"/> I dunno it's a bit stupid isn't it really?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115">what? The idea of having a a coat for an egg or the idea of making a little chick and giving it to people with uh with a Crème Egg inside it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think  I think  you know the answer to that and I think you know that the answer's both of those</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115">well it's the unstoppable force of creativity</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037">well I can't just help I can't help myself can I?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115">no uh it seems that you you um you know you you have to make chickens um yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well not just chickens <pause dur="short"/> the planters are coming along and my other unspecified unmentionable uh knitting antics <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">guerrilla knitting</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> that's uh <trunc>y</trunc> you've certainly improved a lot I think since</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">well just got my</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">you pretty much started from from nothing didn't you about a a year or so ago?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037">yeah I mean I've knitted before then but only like <trunc>scar</trunc> like square things you know <pause dur="short"/> and only really like just knits and purls I didn't know how to like increase and decrease and didn't know how to crochet which I can do now although very tentatively</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115">what's increase and decrease what's that?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">like so you know if you were knitting a jumper or something? You might wanna make it narrower towards the top or <pause dur="short"/> you know sleeves you make them smaller um at the bottom</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's the sort of width yeah <pause dur="short"/> um thickness isn't it?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's like adding more stitches <pause dur="short"/> adding more stitches so that you so you know if you  if you if you  decreasing it goes like towards the triangle shape and opposite a thing</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> also like different different type of stitches in different places and stuff?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">yeah I mean I've just done more experimenting I think <pause dur="short"/> um still sort of a beginner really <pause dur="short"/> well you know semi beginner</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right well <pause dur="short"/> I reckon you've uh you've graduated from like the first year</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">of um of uh knitting</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">you should see some of me nana's knitting then you'll know how much of a beginner I am like</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">what kinda stuff does she do then?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">well some of them are baby things like <pause dur="short"/> she knits on very small needles so it's very intricate and takes a lot of time</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115">oh I see</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">it's probably why old old ladies can't bloody see a bat cos they've spent hours like poring <trunc>o</trunc></u>
<u n="45" who="S0115" trans="overlap">can't see a they can't see a bat</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">can't see can't even see a bat</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they <vocal desc="laugh"/> they've spent ages like poring over knitting patterns so <pause dur="short"/> anyway so she knits  she knits  in very small like very small needles and she knits with very fine wool and she knits very fancy patterns with like you know loops and holes with like frilly bits and twiddly bits and stuff</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Very good <pause dur="short"/> loops holes frilly twiddly bits <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">exactly</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">what and they're also diddly</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">twiddly and diddly bits yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah well yeah I would have to see some of it to um to judge that</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037" trans="overlap">apparently she's made a lot for</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">the the new yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037" trans="overlap">baby <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> so</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so what are we what we watching after uh after this then?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">I wondered about maybe watching that Silent Witness thing <pause dur="short"/> but have a look and see</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it was uh <pause dur="short"/> why? Oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> of course uh</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">dominion of Death or whatever it was</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">yeah yeah and uh actually yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">I can make a little <trunc>ho</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I think slowly but surely unless I find another hobby I'll just like coat the house knit like <trunc>kn</trunc> knit warmers for like everything like chair warmer <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> warmer</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115" trans="overlap">D'you <pause dur="short"/> knit the whole house <pause dur="short"/> with uh <pause dur="short"/> so there's no way back from this uh from this knitting <pause dur="short"/> this is a cul de sac <pause dur="short"/> it's a dead end of uh knitting</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'll just knit you a whole like um like a jump like a jump suit in maybe in that colour what d'you think? Or maybe those two together?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037">I could knit you a stripy jump suit</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">maybe <pause dur="short"/> could take up engineering and make like a</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037">it's more expensive though knitting's quite cheap <pause dur="short"/> like that was one fifty</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I suppose you you need the parts and you know if you wanted to like build something out of uh <pause dur="short"/> well you know like uh woodwork or whatever</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">yeah I mean I think</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">try to like sculpt something like</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">well I was thinking like I've been keeping me eyes peeled for a um a palette you know like I was saying</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115"><trunc>Y</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">Cos I wanted to build one of those palette gardens</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">uh oh right yeah of course yeah remember you saying yeah yeah you said uh you rest it on the wall and then yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">you sort of cover the the back and the sides</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and then <pause dur="short"/> and then you um yeah so you then you fill it with plants <pause dur="short"/> so it's like a movable garden so like one day you can have it here one day you can have it here <pause dur="short"/> but essentially it's <trunc>vir</trunc> it's vertical so like for people like us who've got no real back yard space</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">then it's useful</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> henson's sacked</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">I know he chucked ice <pause dur="short"/> he got pissed on a plane and chucked ice cubes at someone</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">which one was he?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">Gavin Henson? He's a Welsh rugby player he used to go out with Charlotte Church <pause dur="short"/> I mean Charlotte Church not Tcharlotte Church</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh no the Wales team but the that's the uh world championship team isn't it?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">he hasn't been playing in the <trunc>Wale</trunc> in the Wales national team recently</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">oh why was he not really in it and</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037">he was in it um a while ago but</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">not not in the Five Nations then?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">he wasn't in the Six Nations no</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">sorry the Six Nations</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">wasn't good enough</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">he's obviously a talented rugby player and it's unfortunate that well I've missed it</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">that was a statement that they've issued <pause dur="short"/> about like I think they've gone round asking uh Welsh people whether they you know think he deserves to be</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's just a bit of an idiot like <pause dur="short"/> cos he's been on</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">well he got drunk which is what rugby players are supposed to do</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was in the morning though <pause dur="short"/> he was obviously like still drunk</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115" trans="overlap">on a plane in the morning?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">it was a plane from Glasgow</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">to?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">Cardiff</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">still drinking in the morning he throws ice cubes</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">at a passenger or something</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">and then he got <pause dur="short"/> you know they were angry at him <pause dur="short"/> he got banned from flying with that airline uh for six months and he's he got sacked from his thing</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh there he is on Strictly Come Dancing</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115">twenty ten</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037">he's been on another thing like something about bachelor like</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there he is with Charlotte Church</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">something about a bachelor like um where girls were like winning the chance to like go on a date with him or something rubbish</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">and he's a bit weird</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">yeah maybe a bit  a bit  like yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">I think he's a bit mad yeah <pause dur="short"/> well anway</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that why Charlotte Church was going out with him then?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> they've got two babies I think or two or three babies</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">still going out with him?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> she divorced him</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">or at least she <pause dur="short"/> they're not together any more</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">I didn't know they had loads of babies <pause dur="short"/> I didn't even notice that <pause dur="short"/> when did she get all those babies?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I don't follow her that closely</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">no well probably for the best</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">so yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">that's just a silly sketch</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">so um</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> yes so uh it doesn't seem there isn't any sport on uh today</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's not there was <trunc>l</trunc> so much on for a while wasn't there like every single night?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">yeah there was loads of football wasn't there?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">but I think it's because like we've been watching like um cups and stuff so it's getting towards the end so there's only like a few matches left</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115" trans="overlap">competitions really yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah actually it is coming towards the end of the  end of the  uh season isn't it?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037" trans="overlap">season yeah <pause dur="short"/> may isn't it? Something <pause dur="short"/> I don't exactly know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">uh yeah sort of yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then um</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">so yeah I mean</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> uh the</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">so that's there's less <trunc>ma</trunc> less and less matches aren't there? Obviously <pause dur="short"/> obviously</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">I think it's isn't Middlesbrough and Birmingham sort of going for uh and some others going for promotion meanwhile uh</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">well I think</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">meanwhile em Wolves are looking like they're definitely uh definitely down</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aww <pause dur="short"/> poor old Wolves <pause dur="short"/> I feel sorry for them</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">they are poor</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">they shouldn't have sacked Mick McCarthy though you know that's not gonna do them any favours is it?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh is it it's the <trunc>Scous</trunc> it's it's their owners man the Scouse mafia</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">they're talking about</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">about Andy Warhol um things there</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037" trans="overlap">on the yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">some of those <pause dur="short"/> some sort of <pause dur="short"/> dunno how he makes those um</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">pop art?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">yeah that those things</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">they're screen printed I think</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">so it's a photo that's been printed on</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I think</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">it's it's just it just looks like a black and white photo of um Marilyn Monroe and he's he's simply coloured in sort of on top of it</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah screen screen printing you can do it I did it at college and you can do it where you um have <trunc>s</trunc> like shapes cut out for example <pause dur="short"/> so you make like a template and you basically like sweep the the <trunc>da</trunc> the colour through different parts of it so you might put black on that bit and orange on that bit and</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">so what's the colour made out of?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">it's like a ink</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">so you have like a  like a  template</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115">not uh like a not a coloured um sheet of paper?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">well you could do <pause dur="short"/> I mean you can do all different ways I mean <pause dur="short"/> he's not that good is he really?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115">that's an older older one is it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">I dunno</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115"><unclear/> uh <pause dur="short"/> no I think looking at those Andy Warhol um Madonna ones I think that's it's it seems to be quite unspectacular in mm technique</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I suppose it was pretty different at the time though I mean though like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> the techniques seem to be quite quite basic</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">uh then there was also um what else did he do he sort of did like Campbell's Campbell's soup didn't he?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> pop art yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">that wasn't uh <pause dur="short"/> why's it called pop art actually?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> popular yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115" trans="overlap">easy to do</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">like throwaway I suppose like</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">and uh yeah that doesn't sound very <trunc>complem</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">very what?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">complementary you know it doesn't sound</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037" trans="overlap">does it not? Don't know you'll have to</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it sounds like a <trunc>dis</trunc> yeah like a disposable</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know that much about art I mean <pause dur="short"/> despite my uh</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115" trans="overlap">disposable like like a tin of  like a tin of  soup <pause dur="short"/> eh?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">I said I don't know that much about art</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you have you your qualifications um in</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Despite my qualifications <pause dur="short"/> you'll just tease me about that forever won't you?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well that's no you've <trunc>g</trunc> you've got some really interesting <pause dur="short"/> no I wasn't even teasing I mean you you've got some really interesting um A levels you know like you've got uh</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037" trans="overlap">interesting? You <trunc>don</trunc> shouldn't do A levels because</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">really unusual <trunc>co</trunc> you know combination</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">yeah that's not <trunc>alwa</trunc> that's not the best plan I wouldn't recommend it</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">you know cos you had uh</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">some niche career's advice</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <trunc>En</trunc> English <pause dur="short"/> um biology <pause dur="short"/> uh art</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">and um um maths and like physics so that was like well <trunc>s</trunc> bout as well spread out a collection as you can get</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I obviously wasn't very decisive as an eighteen year-old <trunc>s</trunc> sixteen year-old</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">so <pause dur="short"/> it is ones to do but it's</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm that was a mistake as well <pause dur="short"/> pointless <pause dur="short"/> should've just done three <pause dur="short"/> and absolutely like blasted them <pause dur="short"/> but never mind</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and therefore</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">never mind <pause dur="short"/> can't <pause dur="short"/> I don't regret it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but uh <pause dur="short"/> no I mean like that's silly <pause dur="short"/> no I was  I was  saying that that they were a good  a good  uh good selection</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">yeah for someone else to do not to do yourself <pause dur="short"/> you just laugh at somebody who'd just done that</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">if you have those qualifications then like you said you the thing that you'd be perfect for would be like an optical uh engineer or something an optical uh like a fence maker or something</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> optician <pause dur="short"/> yeah fence maker</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">uh was that what the the what they you you could've been a fence maker?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">na that was at <pause dur="short"/> I mean did you ever do that at school like one of those I can't remember what it was called <pause dur="short"/> you had to answer like loads of questions</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">uh oh <trunc>y</trunc> um surveys</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it had a funny name?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">no I um <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that I <trunc>d</trunc> mine would just be</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you had to answer loads like hundreds of questions about yourself</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they would just be insulting like</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">and then at the end it was like Your career should be dee duh duh duh duh dee dee <pause dur="short"/> and then mine was like picture framer <pause dur="short"/> and like fence erector so that was a bit of a letdown</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">yeah that was probably still in its  in its  like beta stage that was where it was</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037" trans="overlap">on balance <pause dur="short"/> yeah well <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I should write back to them and be like <pause dur="short"/> Dear and then whatever the company name <vocal desc="laugh"/> I spent my life trying to be a fence erector only to find actually I was more suited to something else <pause dur="short"/> Never mind</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh Fantastic Job Solutions <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you had to have detailed psychometric tests</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">I've left that a bit baggy haven't I?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">can't guess <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to go to Scotland some time actually looking at that map over there <pause dur="short"/> oh this is the snow isn't it? That's it's minus two up in uh Scotland <pause dur="short"/> um but here it's five</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but look it's sweeping down</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">um yeah it's that northeasterly northeasterly chill coming down there</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037" trans="overlap">look <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's not too far <pause dur="short"/> it's only it's Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> look that's tomorrow four PM that's coming home from work time</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">that's the rain sort of</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">that's not gonna be nice</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">it's gonna get uh <pause dur="short"/> actually it's gonna be a little bit warmer but uh foggy</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">look <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> two degrees</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">so quite but</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">people are in their bloomin bikini on the beach</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115"><trunc>Middles</trunc> Middlesbrough are sort of six <pause dur="short"/> and still still reasonably warm though um tomorrow afternoon like if you look at the map and we're like eleven degrees down the bottom</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but that's <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it was twenty odd the other day</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">and a chilly three for uh Scotland <pause dur="short"/> north Scotland</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">ah that's not gonna be very nice at the bank holiday weekend</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">yeah looks like uh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">that's rubbish</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">could be Easter uh Easter's cancelled or something <pause dur="short"/> easter indoors</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">that's no good is it?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">what did we do last Easter?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">can't even remember</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">perhaps not as much as we</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">probably ate loadsa eggs and just carried on probably</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't think we did  we did  as much as maybe we shoulda done</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> but it would've been when was it like the middle of April or something uh end of March</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">maybe we just like <pause dur="short"/> what is it oh it's there's a guy on a cross</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">is it Jesus?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">ah it's look who it is it's Von Trier <pause dur="short"/> excellent ah I'll definitely watch that</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's uh it's a special crucifixion episode of uh <pause dur="short"/> I can imagine what he's gonna do he's gonna take his body <pause dur="short"/> it's not Lars Von Trier his name's uh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah what's he called?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">Von Trier is is the controversial film director from Denmark</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh what's he called <pause dur="short"/> willem? No <pause dur="short"/> van <pause dur="short"/> van <pause dur="short"/> he's got a Von or a Van <pause dur="short"/> hasn't he?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">has he?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's oh no that's ah it'll come to us in the middle of the night or something</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh why uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's not uh Kurt Huygens is it?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">na</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">Van Hagens</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">Gunther Von Hagens</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">ah right yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037">well remembered</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">I dunno where that came from like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">depths of um</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">uh he he's gonna get all these dead pickled bodies like out that he's got which he pickles in in the special way his special technique that he pickles them using um</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> crucify one <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> plasticin plastidation plastinatiousing</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">plasticination or something</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">I wouldn't have remembered that word actually but</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037"><trunc>Plas</trunc> something about plasticine anyway <pause dur="short"/> goodness I'm terrible</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and um he's gonna get his bodies and he's only gonna go and stick them up on you know take all the skin off and everything and stick them up on a load of crosses so we can all see how unpleasant crucifixion actually is</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ugh <pause dur="short"/> no but actually I did <trunc>on</trunc> I saw one once that he did in conjunction with like an actual doctor so it wasn't just his like grizzly you know behaviour <pause dur="short"/> he did it with like an actual</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah no no no the I never objected to to any of it really I mean <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was great science and uh</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115">Great great <trunc>entreprene</trunc> or whatever <pause dur="short"/> uh opportunism or whatever the word is um <pause dur="short"/> he's creatively coming up with a way to make money make himself famous <pause dur="short"/> show some science <pause dur="short"/> be educating</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't find it that disgusting what he does <pause dur="short"/> it's just like the human body isn't it like you say</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I don't mind it at all</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037">it's just like what it really looks like underneath <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sh</trunc> while it is a little bit weird I suppose it's just real</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> uh yeah no I think it's <trunc>f</trunc> it's <trunc>f</trunc> it's great and obviously the people have signed up to it <pause dur="short"/> um we saw another one where it was a guy who uh yeah he like had himself mummified didn't he? That was uh</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115">like interesting thing to do but um <pause dur="short"/> yeah so he put so he's he's gonna sort of take people and like perhaps hang them on crosses and like so you can see how crucifixion works from the inside perhaps is it <pause dur="short"/> it's like he's uh <pause dur="short"/> is that  is that  what you think he'd do or or am I just way off the <trunc>m</trunc> off the mark there?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> he's probably gonna do something horrible isn't he? Is he gonna look at like the forces on</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">yeah that's what I was thinking he's just gonna like</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">like whether it was possible and</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">possible? Oh you mean how if he was really? Yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I <trunc>r</trunc> I saw a thing that said that <trunc>i</trunc> they wouldn't have put the holes through your hands cos it just rips out rips through your hands</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah cos uh it rips through yeah <pause dur="short"/> well like someone told me that um</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037">but they would put it through your wrists and through your ankle bones</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115" trans="overlap">through the in the wrist yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah a lot of these old techniques you can't tell if it was like the um you know uh the uh people who writers exaggerating at the time</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">so</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">but definitely in the book he shows him his hands doesn't he the stigmata? In the book <pause dur="short"/> the book being the Bible <vocal desc="laugh"/> Whoops</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean but then in in the book the the Bible this that's the problem is that  is that  they're they they're not that reliable <pause dur="short"/> um like the Bible might say or some pictures might say</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">that it went um</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037" trans="overlap">wonder what Damian Hurst's gallery things are</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">or when <trunc>f</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">that's in a grizzly vein as well</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">well Ramsey's Kitchen Nightmares Embarrassing Bodies or Damian Hurst?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">yeah Damian Hurst's on now <pause dur="short"/> with his uh sheep and all</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">another one of these uh these modern artist types that uh may be a tad on the overrated side <pause dur="short"/> controversial statement</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> sorry I was just counting stitches</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115" trans="overlap">modern art <pause dur="short"/> load of rubbish <pause dur="short"/> discuss</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">hey look it's Noel Fielding <pause dur="short"/> he looks almost like a girl <pause dur="short"/> I do like him like</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115" trans="overlap">think he he is half girl</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm sure he wouldn't be offended by that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and one quarter woman and the final quarter is um</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">spaceman?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> bit weird</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">he's a very effeminate guy he's it's uh</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">ah that's a good</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">ah this is For The Love Of God the crystal skull thing and there was a lotta <pause dur="short"/> or was it a diamond skull <pause dur="short"/> and um that's diamonte <pause dur="short"/> it's his uh it's a shark <pause dur="short"/> I think I saw one of them in Berlin think it was his uh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh did you?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">uh I saw  I saw  I think maybe more than one of his in Berlin <pause dur="short"/> I saw his sheep I think</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">in in in Berlin uh</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">he must have so much money</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">A lot of time</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">maybe we should watch this <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd be quite interested</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">okay <pause dur="short"/> is it not on um conflicting with something we were gonna watch like?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">well it's nine o'clock I mean that thing's probably on <pause dur="short"/> silent Witness</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">silent Witness</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">if you'd rather watch that <pause dur="short"/> but we'd have to do that now</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">shall I turn it off?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115" trans="overlap">stop yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">press</u>
</body>
</text>
