<text id="SBEV">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:51:20</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-07</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0336 S0363</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Friends, boyfriends, cars, holidays, work</topics>
		<activity>Catching up with Rach</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, requesting, inviting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0336">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wegberg</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0363">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Peterborough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bourne</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Events Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0363">hey</u>
<u n="2" who="S0336">hello</u>
<u n="3" who="S0363">thought you'd be in the new ride</u>
<u n="4" who="S0336">yeah I know like a few people have said like <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh I should have brought my car we've got erm like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bought a bike last week <pause dur="short"/> mm last weekend or the weekend before which we're not going to be able to get in my car so I kind of thought it made sense to bring this one <unclear/> disappointed</u>
<u n="5" who="S0363">what you can't get the bike in it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0336">into my car</u>
<u n="7" who="S0363">oh I see</u>
<u n="8" who="S0336">it's erm <pause dur="short"/> it's only a three door so</u>
<u n="9" who="S0363"><unclear/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0336">do you want to turn it up? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0363">oh damn it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0336">been a long time since I've driven this car as well it's really and it feels like a lot heavier than mine it's really funny</u>
<u n="13" who="S0363">I got some driving gloves for Christmas they're so handy aren't they?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0336" trans="overlap">they're really good yeah <pause dur="short"/> I managed to get these from ASOS they had like extra small as well which is even better</u>
<u n="15" who="S0363" whoConfidence="low">bloody <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh deary me <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0363">always forgetting that er landing light there's a barman going anywhere nothing happens you think oh turn it off then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0336">oh no <pause dur="short"/> where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this morning?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0363">er he was in Manchester last night</u>
<u n="19" who="S0336">uhu</u>
<u n="20" who="S0363">he's driving back at the moment <unclear>so he said</unclear> no I'm not gonna be here</u>
<u n="21" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0336"><unclear/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0363">yeah go might go <pause dur="short"/> if we get er enough to time go see some mattresses <unclear/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0336">oh very exciting</u>
<u n="25" who="S0363">oh yeah so exciting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0336">I I love a good mattress test me</u>
<u n="27" who="S0363">you can get lying get lying down on it don't you?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0363">good</u>
<u n="30" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh the first time we went we went to like <anon type="place"/> in town and we went like on our way back from like having coffee with some of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friends and like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was with us and he was like watching us try out all these mattresses like this is really awkward</u>
<u n="31" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0336">I was like well you didn't have to come <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0336">I'm sure you'll find something <pause dur="short"/> we were like pleasantly surprised cos the mattress we picked out originally in <anon type="place"/> was like six hundred pounds and we were just being like ridiculously like kind of</u>
<u n="35" who="S0363">you want to get what you wanted though</u>
<u n="36" who="S0336">yeah we're like</u>
<u n="37" who="S0363" trans="overlap">but yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0336">we really wanted something comfy we managed to settle on something that was like not as good but still pretty good for like a third of the price of <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="39" who="S0363">well that's what I've said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said don't <pause dur="short"/> cos I I'd sleep anywhere so it's more him than me</u>
<u n="40" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0363">and erm I said don't hold back on price cos I'm like</u>
<u n="42" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0363">I said cos you're the one who's funny about sleep</u>
<u n="44" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0363">like super funny about it so I can't <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that's how it ended up with us as well cos like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is very much like once he's sleep he's asleep but I like fidget so much so I had to get one for <unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0363">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0336">oh the joys of adulthood</u>
<u n="49" who="S0363">I know</u>
<u n="50" who="S0336">when you're worrying about mattresses</u>
<u n="51" who="S0363">oh funny</u>
<u n="52" who="S0336">any work we're cooking tonight</u>
<u n="53" who="S0363">we <unclear/> got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister <unclear/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I hate the word fiancée boyfriend coming over <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0336" trans="overlap">fiancée fiancée</u>
<u n="55" who="S0363">coming over for dinner I haven't seen him in a while</u>
<u n="56" who="S0336"><unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0363">er well I think erm <pause dur="short"/> you know have you been watching that shop for less</u>
<u n="58" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="59" who="S0363">recently? <pause dur="short"/> erm I've watched two now it's where they basically go and do an intervention with a family</u>
<u n="60" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="61" who="S0363">who are like shopping ridiculously</u>
<u n="62" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0363">and they've all got certain problems and erm basically firstly this this family they they their biggest problem's where they don't look what's in their erm kitchen before they go</u>
<u n="64" who="S0336">I hate that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0363">and don't write a list and don't plan meals erm <pause dur="short"/> so they're always just <unclear/> basically a hoarder of food</u>
<u n="66" who="S0336" trans="overlap">just got too much food <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0363">so they're buying way too much food and the husband he buy he likes to just try things new</u>
<u n="68" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0363">so he's always just picking he doesn't really know what they are he picks up like jars of stuff</u>
<u n="70" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0363">and said oh we'll try that some time so their biggest thing is they had to plan their meals and then obviously only buy the stuff that you need for those meals</u>
<u n="72" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0363">and then they have a day off for whatever the husband's name was for him to do whatever he likes <unclear/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0363">so he can still go <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> anyway er this last week's one their biggest one was <unclear/> family er were buying brands</u>
<u n="76" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="77" who="S0363">basically just buying brands cos they think it's better</u>
<u n="78" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0363">erm and the wife she's got four kids so she's <pause dur="short"/> buys things <unclear/> she says she not the biggest cooker</u>
<u n="80" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0363">and she and even that she'll buy <unclear/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="83" who="S0363">and stuff like that</u>
<u n="84" who="S0336">yeah cos she can't be bothered to cook <unclear/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0336">right okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0363">things like that <pause dur="short"/> they were extortionate whatever their their shopping was</u>
<u n="88" who="S0336">really?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0363">like <pause dur="short"/> well close to four hundred quid a week they would spend</u>
<u n="90" who="S0336">it's <unclear>daftness</unclear></u>
<u n="91" who="S0363">it turned out be like something like eight grand a year six grand a year</u>
<u n="92" who="S0336">on food oh my god</u>
<u n="93" who="S0363">on food <pause dur="short"/> so their thing was obviously erm <pause dur="short"/> first of all <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> shop around don't just go cos it's a brand</u>
<u n="94" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0363"><unclear/> so cos what they do they then go in and they they change your kitchen over and they take everything out of packaging they did it with the first one</u>
<u n="96" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0363">they take everything out of packaging and just label it like tea</u>
<u n="98" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0363">or coffee and it's so funny some people when they haven't even changed their brand they're like this isn't the same this has definitely devalued stuff <pause dur="short"/> erm it's like</u>
<u n="100" who="S0336" trans="overlap"><unclear/> cos they they were expecting it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0363">yeah for instance one thing they this couple the other night like marinated chicken</u>
<u n="102" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0363">from Marks and Spencer</u>
<u n="104" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="105" who="S0363">and <unclear/> but they hadn't changed it at all and they were like this just looks awful and then she was like I can't even eat my chicken cos I know it's value value brand and that chicken just tastes awful dry and disgusting I I can't eat it</u>
<u n="106" who="S0336">that's hilarious</u>
<u n="107" who="S0363">and they were like it's the same <pause dur="short"/> she was like no <pause dur="short"/> so it's that was weird but also they were talking about convenience and being in jars and stuff I now and I was thinking about you cos you've obviously you've been having to make everything from scratch as well <unclear>recently</unclear></u>
<u n="108" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0363">but I've all the time don't buy bolognese sauce any more or lasagne sauce I make that from scratch</u>
<u n="110" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0363">but I was like how the fuck do you make a curry sauce from scratch? not that I would <unclear/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0336">yeah a little bit it's it's like tinned tinned tomatoes and coconut milk essentially</u>
<u n="113" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0336">erm obviously it's got loads of other spices but that's like the bulk of it</u>
<u n="115" who="S0363"><unclear/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's like <trunc>t</trunc>two tins for a pound it's really cheap to make it from scratch <pause dur="short"/> but it's just an effort</u>
<u n="117" who="S0363">yeah <unclear/> and then obviously one of the things they made her do was erm they didn't give her <trunc>car</trunc>carrot batons they gave her carrots</u>
<u n="118" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0363">just she was like and then she was <unclear/> they taste so much better than carrot batons was like yeah because carrot batons have been peeled and been washed and they just soak up all the water all they are is water based soon as you open that bag they dry up</u>
<u n="120" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0363">so <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> she said you should see when she's cutting these carrots she's like oh so much effort <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0336">oh my god</u>
<u n="123" who="S0363">I was laughing <pause dur="short"/> so much anyway they made this main attention to get this make this meal it was quite quick erm and it tastes good and it was all prepared yourself</u>
<u n="124" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0363">out of nothing and they made that it's just like chopped roasted vegetables like courgettes</u>
<u n="126" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0363"><unclear/> and there was little tomatoes and bits like that then you shove your chicken on top and then you drizzle it in oil and</u>
<u n="128" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0363">and shit and spices whatever you want with that and then I don't know what you put it with yet</u>
<u n="130" who="S0336">well it sounds nice</u>
<u n="131" who="S0363">probably new potatoes or something</u>
<u n="132" who="S0336">sounds good <pause dur="short"/> we're meant to be <unclear/> erm <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and my mum tonight</u>
<u n="133" who="S0363">oh yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0336">and I kind of like sprung it on mum I was just like oh and we've not got plans for Saturday shall we just invite our parents round? cos apparently since we've moved in we've never cooked for his parents which I think is quite bad</u>
<u n="135" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0336">it's been like six months erm <pause dur="short"/> and like mum bless her doesn't often go out on Saturdays so I was like oh might as well and then last night I was like have you had any inspiration about what to cook? and he was like no you organised this you sort the dinner</u>
<u n="137" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0336">I'm like okay oh</u>
<u n="139" who="S0363">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't I haven't thought about it at all <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I was going to go this afternoon after I went round Tesco and try to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0363" trans="overlap">well if you wanna go to Tesco on the way back with me I need to pick up my stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0336">I haven't got a clue and the like opinions that <unclear/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have got into such a habit of like cooking the same kind of meals cos we've really got really like kind of like comfortable with them</u>
<u n="143" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0336" trans="overlap">and I don't really wanna do that and I don't wanna like I don't wanna pick something that's gonna take me ages either</u>
<u n="145" who="S0363">no yeah that's good</u>
<u n="146" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0363">I text your mum yesterday</u>
<u n="148" who="S0336">did you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0363">last night <pause dur="short"/> I was like <pause dur="short"/> I text her really bad <unclear/> really grumpy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0336">I'm sure she appreciated that</u>
<u n="151" who="S0363">what did she say? I was like <unclear/> I knew she'd be watching it <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I text her going that's a win to England like <unclear/> hopefully watching the game <unclear/> and hope you're well she said yes I've seen you throughout until the last ten days well should have won that good to watch I said I'll give you the first half but I'm afraid I'm afraid you've won no points in the second half</u>
<u n="152" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0363">I think I've lost my voice from screaming so much <unclear/> she's like harsh my boys took some knocks for this <pause dur="short"/> I had <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> that's cute</u>
<u n="154" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she loves it <pause dur="short"/> I bet she had like a whole host of those as well like going like ha ha</u>
<u n="155" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0363">yeah probably <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I did think that after ours that I'm going to support Wales now</u>
<u n="158" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0336">I do I do I do enjoy the six nations we were actually out last night my dad <pause dur="short"/> dad's going to Saudi on Monday</u>
<u n="160" who="S0363" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0336">I don't know if I told you?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0363">you did say ages ago about it but I don't think it would come round so quick</u>
<u n="163" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah so he's off on Monday for three months so <trunc>w</trunc> he called us and he said what do you want to do for dinner? so we went to the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> which was really nice but obviously the rugby was still kinda on but it was like round the corner from where we were so we couldn't see him <pause dur="short"/> so I didn't actually watch it last night though</u>
<u n="164" who="S0363">it was a good game</u>
<u n="165" who="S0336">I do enjoy it <pause dur="short"/> it's a hard game cos like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s definitely not a rugby person so like</u>
<u n="166" who="S0363" trans="overlap">well he's not sport at all is he?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="168" who="S0363">so maybe tennis but that's about it</u>
<u n="169" who="S0336" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah I can't really see him having it on <pause dur="short"/> although he might get into it like he's also like fairly easy in that respect <vocal desc="laugh"/> like it might take a little bit of convincing but once it's on he gets really into it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0363" trans="overlap">I mean I don't I don't watch sport like <unclear/> really I think I'm just a like what's the word? <pause dur="long"/> national sport</u>
<u n="171" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0363">like just really <unclear/> watching</u>
<u n="173" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0363">watching</u>
<u n="175" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0363">cricket</u>
<u n="177" who="S0336">it's a lot easier when you've got somebody to like get behind</u>
<u n="178" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0336">I can't I don't I don't understand like <trunc>foot</trunc> like football supporters who like just watch like any football game</u>
<u n="180" who="S0363">they like don't like support either convenience</u>
<u n="181" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0363">they're like well we really want to see where they come in the cup it's like how on earth do you keep track of that? I'm like what fucking cup are they playing now?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's so <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="184" who="S0363" trans="overlap">is it a league game? or is it?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0336">and it's so unnecessary as well because if you watch something like Match of the Day you kind of get a round up anyway so why do you have to watch like <pause dur="short"/> all of the games?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0363" trans="overlap">it's more fun to watch that</u>
<u n="187" who="S0336">weird weird</u>
<u n="188" who="S0363"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> then I say that and then it's on and then I get into and I'm like I'm like telling they're stupid idiots <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> look at them fannying about outside the goal and I'm like oh obviously it just irritates me</u>
<u n="189" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0363">irritate winds me up <pause dur="short"/> thing is as soon as I pick a side that I want to win cos I don't support anybody <pause dur="short"/> they're the ones that are fucking losing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> always tends to be the way <pause dur="short"/> so excited about your holiday?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0363">yeah I've really not been thinking it it's crazy</u>
<u n="193" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0363">not thinking about and I just thought today oh god we're going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0336">that's very exciting</u>
<u n="196" who="S0363"><unclear/> two weeks today</u>
<u n="197" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0363">have you decided what day you're doing your <pause dur="short"/> or are you going to?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0336" trans="overlap">no I haven't really I haven't really planned anything I was actually going to speak to you about it because I didn't know whether you fancied doing like a joint something at some point like <pause dur="short"/> joint meal or a joint <pause dur="short"/> something <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know</u>
<u n="200" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0336">I'm not doing anything on my actual birthday erm <pause dur="short"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are gonna go away on the Friday night <pause dur="short"/> erm I think we're just gonna head out towards <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> then</u>
<u n="202" who="S0363">find somewhere</u>
<u n="203" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah and then go go for some nice walks in the Peaks yeah on Saturday</u>
<u n="204" who="S0363">that sounds really nice</u>
<u n="205" who="S0336">erm so I'll be out Friday and Saturday anyway <pause dur="short"/> I don't really fancy trying to like rush something together on the Sunday just for the sake of doing something so I'm not really that fussed like I probably should be I'm just not like</u>
<u n="206" who="S0363">I know I'm the same though</u>
<u n="207" who="S0336">I just don't really care it's another birthday I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been asking what what I'm doing I'm like I don't know like I don't care <vocal desc="laugh"/> which doesn't really help I'm like don't set aside any time because you know I feel bad <vocal desc="laugh"/> I feel bad if we don't do anything <pause dur="short"/> cos I think it's like it's obviously like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday is the same weekend so it's like if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing something you do it don't worry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> how is erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is she good?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0336">yeah she's alright</u>
<u n="210" who="S0363">she settled down south?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0336">yeah kind of like I haven't really seen her in ages to be honest <pause dur="short"/> erm I haven't seen her since New Year I don't think she's had like a few busy weeks and paths haven't crossed etcetera erm <pause dur="short"/> I think she's doing okay like she's not like she's not really that comfortable in <anon type="place"/> so she tends to come home every weekend or like <pause dur="short"/> or she's been up to see her friend in <anon type="place"/> and stuff like that so I don't think she's settled settled it's a weird one</u>
<u n="212" who="S0363">it's more of a she's just there for work</u>
<u n="213" who="S0336">yeah she's literally there just for just for the job and I think <pause dur="short"/> I think it's hard cos she enjoys it but</u>
<u n="214" who="S0363">the social side does grind on you a little bit doesn't it?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah it's just and like she's already admitting that she's not going to be able to do it long term and then I'm kind of thinking like <pause dur="short"/> how long are you planning to stay there like? you know what what benefit is it to you really? but <pause dur="short"/> it's her decision at the end of the day like</u>
<u n="216" who="S0363">her and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="217" who="S0336">yeah I mean I think they had they had <pause dur="short"/> they had a tricky time of it after New Year I think because they've been together a while now they've been together since sort of like May time and like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just like you know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like he's just so chilled about everything <pause dur="short"/> but like to a fault like he just didn't seem to care about anything and like you can tell he liked her but like he just wasn't like going out of his way to do anything like <pause dur="short"/> and like you know</u>
<u n="218" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> be spontaneous or</u>
<u n="219" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah well the thing is he actually just didn't wanna make plans he'd be like oh we'll probably do something at the weekend but then like wouldn't wouldn't actually like commit to doing stuff and she's like how on earth am I like meant to plan my life bearing in mind I like I live miles away like and we need to have plans like otherwise we're not gonna see each other I'm not gonna just hang around and hope that on a Saturday afternoon he rings me and says like are you free? do you want to do something?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0363">that sounds more like dating</u>
<u n="221" who="S0336">I know it's weird</u>
<u n="222" who="S0363">ringing on a Saturday afternoon you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0336" trans="overlap">and like like <pause dur="short"/> I mean she's not the first person to tell me and I don't not not one to judge but before Christmas she did tell me like they've not used the L word yet</u>
<u n="224" who="S0363">mm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0336">and I thought right well everybody comes to that of their own kind of pace but like guys have been seeing each other like eight months now like <pause dur="short"/> that's quite a long time <pause dur="short"/> she's like well I think we're there but I just don't think either of us wants to say it I'm like</u>
<u n="226" who="S0363">well sometimes <unclear/> might be just my judgement but if if she does love him</u>
<u n="227" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0363">why worry about saying first?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0336">exactly <pause dur="short"/> I said it first and I don't</u>
<u n="230" who="S0363" trans="overlap">I said it first <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't hold it in any longer <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I don't really care <pause dur="short"/> I know like that's the thing though as soon as you feel it it is really weird it feels like it's ready to burst out</u>
<u n="232" who="S0363"><unclear/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0363">if you definitely loved that person <pause dur="short"/> and still they haven't said anything and you're still holding back though that won't</u>
<u n="235" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0363">I think that would really grind on you</u>
<u n="237" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it's weird and I think she's worried about pushing him away like because this is his first proper relationship so I think he's</u>
<u n="238" who="S0363" trans="overlap">and he's very blasé about it</u>
<u n="239" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah I think he's finding the whole situation really intense it's really weird like I had quite an in-depth conversation with her about it at one point in that like it kind of seems like for ages he was holding onto the idea that like he didn't want to meet someone now like <pause dur="short"/> he</u>
<u n="240" who="S0363" trans="overlap">has a set plan in his head</u>
<u n="241" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah he had a <trunc>hea</trunc> he had plan in his head you know he wanted to move to Cambridge he wanted to he wants to do his own thing and you can see that in him like you can see him very much likes doing his own thing he's really independent erm so I don't he was ready to meet a girl who was then gonna like dictate that or like have an opinion on like you know what he's doing and so for ages I think he was holding onto this idea that like he wanted to be independent he wanted to be single he wanted to be this he wanted to be that but actually like you can't choose when you meet someone like</u>
<u n="242" who="S0363">no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0336">like <pause dur="short"/> if if somebody said to me a few years ago oh by the time you're twenty-five like you'll be in a really serious relationship you would of bought a house you'll be talking about kids you'll be talking about marriage and it won't and it won't scare the shit out of you I'd be like fuck off</u>
<u n="244" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0336">like I had no plans to be in that position by the time I was twenty-five like</u>
<u n="246" who="S0363" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="247" who="S0336">twenty-eight approaching thirty maybe but like not twenty-five</u>
<u n="248" who="S0363" trans="overlap">maybe <pause dur="short"/> cos everyone has a little bit of a plan in their head don't they?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0336">exactly like but the thing is when you meet when you meet someone that you're willing to make those plans with</u>
<u n="250" who="S0363" trans="overlap">things change</u>
<u n="251" who="S0336">yeah things change so I think they're actually all the better for it it all come came to a bit of a head when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like look <pause dur="short"/> I really like you but I'm not gonna just kind of <pause dur="short"/> deal with all of this and do as you please like you have to make more of an effort you know you have to kind of prove to me that you want this because at the moment it seems that you can take it or leave it which isn't very nice</u>
<u n="252" who="S0363">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0336">erm <pause dur="short"/> and apparently they both had a bit of a cry and <pause dur="short"/> apparently like it was on a Sunday so she went home then and then on a Monday night straight after work he was calling her sort of saying like I'm sorry I've been stupid <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="254" who="S0363">I mean that would be the best opportunity</u>
<u n="255" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I think they're better for it now but I think he's also one of reasons I haven't seen her in ages cos I think I think she's still kind of like <pause dur="short"/> she's a bit like me in as much like she's got a lazy boyfriend so that she ends up running round doing everything and that's what it was with me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at the start like I felt like I was making all the plans and I was making all of the effort <pause dur="short"/> erm and it sounds like she's still doing the same so she's still running round like she's driving to <anon type="place"/> in the week and <pause dur="short"/> she's the one that's kind of</u>
<u n="256" who="S0363">they're the same group aren't they? I mean they're useless at making plans <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I they haven't spent time together <pause dur="short"/> that they've planned <pause dur="short"/> in a year and a half the only time they see each other is when me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have made plans and they've tagged along I'm not joking <pause dur="short"/> it's been really bad they're so they're just shit at keeping in touch erm <pause dur="short"/> that's like semi amusing but it's just like stupid <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0363">could have <unclear/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0336">mm I don't I've I've only ever been once I don't know the way</u>
<u n="260" who="S0363">oh <pause dur="short"/> I'll take you back</u>
<u n="261" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0363">what a douchebag he should of let you go</u>
<u n="263" who="S0336"><trunc>s</trunc>sit there</u>
<u n="264" who="S0363">I know it's a roundabout but seriously</u>
<u n="265" who="S0336">I know</u>
<event desc="sound of car"/> <pause dur="long"/>
<u n="266" who="S0336">yeah everybody's good <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seems <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seems good although I'm dying for him to meet someone because he just I think he's ready for it like he obviously enjoyed being single for ages and I think he's just really ready to have have somebody in his life now but he erm he went to he went to Canada recently for ten days</u>
<u n="267" who="S0363">yeah was he with a girl?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0336">yeah it's all very strange so like obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to the Philippines</u>
<u n="269" who="S0363" trans="overlap">Philippines I thought it was with her?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0336">yeah so he met a couple of girls out there <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> apparently they were all very into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> which was all quite cute and he had a bit of a weird romance while he was out there with erm a girl that he'd actually met before cos she'd come to <pause dur="short"/> she'd come to the UK for one reason or another</u>
<u n="271" who="S0363">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0336">erm so they'd met before and they'd kind of hit it off so they started kind of like <pause dur="short"/> oh it's sounds crude but they were basically just sleeping together</u>
<u n="273" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0336">so she'd come to his hotel room and at the weekend they'd kind of like sleep together and just hang out and whatever and then erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said she started to develop feelings so he had he had to end things cos that was the gentlemanly thing to do erm but what we didn't know was there was this other girl that he happened to have met out there who he's kind of been like Facebook chatting to like</u>
<u n="275" who="S0363">so having a bit more of an intimate relationship <unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah like he said like he said the <trunc>composi</trunc> like they always have plenty to talk about on Facebook they talk like every couple of days and stuff which is quite nice and then she invited him over to Canada which is where she actually lives erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> being <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and kind of embracing life cos he tends to do that he's like oh yeah cool I'll come to Canada erm so he booked some flights out there they weren't too expensive and then she planned basically his whole trip like she booked him booked him skiing she booked him like on all these coach tours and all this kind of stuff so he turned up and like I think it was fairly like what did he say? open-minded about the prospect of romance but was also quite aware that you know</u>
<u n="277" who="S0363">she lives in Canada</u>
<u n="278" who="S0336">yeah and she he wasn't really sure what to expect erm <pause dur="short"/> so he said he arrived and he was like really open-minded about it all but in a few days he'd kind of already realised that they actually didn't have a lot in common he said it was really weird to say that they've been talking for like months on Facebook or whatever as soon as she as soon as he met her in person he found it really really hard to talk to her so like</u>
<u n="279" who="S0363">god you two are like kind of similar aren't you really? you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah oh I mean yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0363" trans="overlap">quite picky <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0336">me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like it's I think that's well we're both sarcastic knobheads</u>
<u n="283" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0336">erm but yeah so he sort of thought like oh god like even things like you know he's asking her what her hobbies were and stuff like that she just didn't have any and it's just like what do you talk about with someone if they don't have like</u>
<u n="285" who="S0363">I'd be like <unclear/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0336" trans="overlap">hobbies or interests or whatever? and I was like I don't know erm <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> he still slept with her because he's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0363">and he was there</u>
<u n="288" who="S0336">and he was there and he was in Canada and embracing it and all this kind of shit but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was all very weird he said and then like <pause dur="short"/> she's a bit older she's like twenty-eight or something and she just wouldn't let him pay for anything so like and she'd booked him on all these tours and stuff and she wouldn't let him pay her back</u>
<u n="289" who="S0363">try and be a bit like a toy boy</u>
<u n="290" who="S0336">yeah so he basically got kept it was really weird he said he had a great time and obviously he got to see some cool things but he said it was weird <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always comes back with these stories he went to like I think he went to no maybe Berlin actually he went <pause dur="short"/> went somewhere with some friends some uni friends maybe and erm he came back saying that he'd like basically met this girl on the street <vocal desc="laugh"/> and ended up bringing her back to their like kind of hotel room suite whatever <pause dur="short"/> and ended up having sex with her in the bathroom and I was just like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like <pause dur="short"/> why? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and like he even like regaled the fact that like they were to get to it as he as he phrases it and erm they realised they didn't have a condom so they actually then went out back into town <pause dur="short"/> on the hunt for a condom</u>
<u n="291" who="S0363">well at least he was smart</u>
<u n="292" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0363">that way</u>
<u n="294" who="S0336">it's a bit of a mood killer that though isn't it?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0363">little bit</u>
<u n="296" who="S0336">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah he always has stories it's quite funny <pause dur="short"/> he's on Tinder now as well which is hilarious</u>
<u n="297" who="S0363">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> met a guy on Tinder and she's still dating him</u>
<u n="298" who="S0336">oh right my cousin is dating a guy off <trunc>Ti</trunc>Tinder and my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is in a relationship with a guy she met on Tinder like <pause dur="short"/> it happens</u>
<u n="299" who="S0363">well I get it though a little bit more because <pause dur="short"/> well not get it that sounds wrong but <pause dur="short"/> for instance well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's <trunc>inv</trunc> she she obviously didn't know anyone from her primary school or anyone from uni there</u>
<u n="300" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0363">so it works quite well but also it's giving you the chance to bump into that person locally without <pause dur="short"/> needing fate to help you <pause dur="short"/> I suppose</u>
<u n="302" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is nice in as much as like even though that it's bad that it's like done <unclear/> it's like</u>
<u n="303" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0336">sometimes it takes away the like cos you know like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have got themselves into situations where they're talking to someone online they don't really fancy them but they're really nice or whatever and then they go on a date and they're like I didn't really fancy them <pause dur="short"/> and it's like well that's just a whole waste of your time at least if like initially you know like yes I fancy you</u>
<u n="305" who="S0363" trans="overlap">and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0336"><unclear/> it's a step in the right direction then isn't it? cos if you get on then you know they already like like the look of you</u>
<u n="307" who="S0363">yes yes yes yes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0336">apart from there's obviously people on Tinder that just go yes</u>
<u n="309" who="S0363">yes yes yes yes yes <pause dur="short"/> erm but also like I what I don't like is the fact that well it's it's because it's convenience again</u>
<u n="310" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0363">don't have a inner world where you have to go to dance <pause dur="short"/> you don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0336" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="313" who="S0363"><unclear/> those <unclear/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0336">and like we live in a world where like a lot of guys do just go out to pull <pause dur="short"/> and it's really hard to decipher between those and the people that are actually looking for a girlfriend or something a bit more serious</u>
<u n="315" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or once <unclear/> you know where they do pull</u>
<u n="316" who="S0336">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0363">might be something else</u>
<u n="318" who="S0336">easy world but I'm sure he'll meet someone but he's just like he's at a he's at a really weird point in his life where I don't think he really knows like what he wants so he doesn't know if he wants to stay in <anon type="place"/> and like all this kind of stuff</u>
<u n="319" who="S0363">he seems like he's living on the edge on the start of an adventure like trying to do all these different things</u>
<u n="320" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice to see actually cos for ages <pause dur="short"/> he was just like properly squirrelling money away like <pause dur="short"/> cos he pays a little bit of rent at home but not a lot and he doesn't have a lot of outgoings so he was saving like five hundred pound a month just like literally squirrelling it away <trunc>bef</trunc> like before he knew it he had like fifteen grand and he was like oh I've got a deposit for a house blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and I was like that's great but like <pause dur="short"/> are you sure that's what you want? <pause dur="short"/> and like since going to Manila I think he's just realised that that's not what he wants like</u>
<u n="321" who="S0363">he hasn't spent all of it?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="323" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0336">but he goes</u>
<u n="325" who="S0363" trans="overlap">he spent five of it</u>
<u n="326" who="S0336">yeah he basically did turn round he bought himself a new car and he's been going on all these holidays and he wants to travel and he wants to do things so <pause dur="short"/> I can't really blame him like <pause dur="short"/> it's what it's what being young's for isn't it really? yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen the girls in ages</u>
<u n="327" who="S0363">no no</u>
<u n="328" who="S0336">been texting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a bit because obviously she's been moving so I've been like trying to track her down so I'm hopefully seeing her next week but I think she's just had I think it's been really stressful cos I know like when I'm when I what I kind of like caught up with her before Christmas she had so much stuff planned <trunc>f</trunc> in January with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was costing her a small fortune and it was so she knew she wasn't going to have any money <pause dur="short"/> and then she had all the stress of like looking <pause dur="short"/> looking for well <unclear/> looking at houses and stuff and they're talking about putting <pause dur="short"/> like reservations on plots and all this kind of stuff and then <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> she just was really stressed last time I spoke to her she just said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s an idiot with money as well which you kind of see like</u>
<u n="329" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0336">he doesn't I don't think he pays rent to live at home <pause dur="short"/> so he's just got used to kind of like</u>
<u n="331" who="S0363">having loads of disposable cash</u>
<u n="332" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah and just doing whatever he wants</u>
<u n="333" who="S0363" trans="overlap">what does he do <pause dur="short"/> again?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0336">he works at erm Travelex something</u>
<u n="335" who="S0363">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0336">so he won't be on huge money anyway but <pause dur="short"/> I think she was just getting a bit annoyed cos she was very much like paying for everything like</u>
<u n="337" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0336">and and when they're talking about like saving for a house and all this kind of stuff like she's already basically admitted she knows that she's the one that'll have to pay the deposit <pause dur="short"/> and she's just getting a bit annoyed that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s still going out and doing whatever he wants and not really acknowledging that</u>
<u n="339" who="S0363"><unclear>and but</unclear> do they definitely want to do it then? or</u>
<u n="340" who="S0336">I think so all it's all a bit it's a bit strange anyway <pause dur="short"/> like sometimes when you hear them talking like they like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came round to have a look at the house at one point <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and we were chatting about stuff and he was asking like what came with the house and all this kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> and like they couldn't even agree like really stupid like obviously our dining room is technically in our living room so it's carpeted</u>
<u n="341" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0336">and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like I really like this you know I think I think carpets are like underrated like they're just so much warmer like it's nice to have carpet like underfoot and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like no way you're having a carpet anywhere in our house like <pause dur="short"/> like maybe upstairs but nowhere downstairs is going to be carpeted because you just can't be trusted and I was just like <pause dur="short"/> wow oh this bodes well when you can't even agree on this</u>
<u n="343" who="S0363">mm <pause dur="short"/> true</u>
<u n="344" who="S0336"><vocal desc="cough"/> and then thinking about it and thinking well no like to be fair like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s houses never been carpeted downstairs like she's always she's always gone for like a hard floor</u>
<u n="345" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0336">because she knows like she knows she likes hosting and all that kind of stuff and carpets are just dangerous erm <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking of like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house like is a brand new house that she's got the whole of the downstairs like vinyled like or <pause dur="short"/> carpeted but it's funny that they couldn't even agree on that I thought this bodes well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0363">strange</u>
<u n="348" who="S0336">anything new with you or not really?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0363">no</u>
<u n="350" who="S0336">same old</u>
<u n="351" who="S0363">oh mum did I tell you mum and dad have booked a family holiday?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="353" who="S0363">yeah mum and dad have cos they turn sixty this year they wanted to do a big family holiday with everyone you know grandad <pause dur="short"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the kids <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <pause dur="short"/> probably her guy if</u>
<u n="354" who="S0336">there's a new guy on the scene?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0363" trans="overlap">there is a new guy I'll tell you about this in a minute</u>
<u n="356" who="S0336" trans="overlap">oh exciting</u>
<u n="357" who="S0363">and then me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and grandad have booked a house in Wales and it looks amazing</u>
<u n="358" who="S0336" trans="overlap">oh that's cute</u>
<u n="359" who="S0363">so erm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0336" trans="overlap">south of Wales or?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0363" trans="overlap">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> yeah south of Wales in the edge</u>
<u n="362" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0363">right on the tip</u>
<u n="364" who="S0336">interesting near the Mumbles?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0363">I have no idea</u>
<u n="366" who="S0336"><unclear/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and it's amazing the house looks gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> its got like erm games room <unclear/> in it and stuff</u>
<u n="368" who="S0336" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0363">so <unclear/> bar we're going there in July cos obviously we got to wait for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to go onto school holidays</u>
<u n="370" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0363">and erm so it's for their sixtieth but also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> turns thirty a few days before we go as well</u>
<u n="372" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's exciting <pause dur="short"/> oh that's really cute</u>
<u n="373" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah really nice we're doing that <pause dur="short"/> erm and what's really nice is mum and dad were there <unclear/> gran was <unclear/> she said look all just you have to take it in turns to make a meal for everyone in the evening so</u>
<u n="374" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0363">let's splash out so that's what we're doing <pause dur="short"/> so we'll get back Monday night or something</u>
<u n="376" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0363">have to make dinner for everyone <unclear/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0336">will it get competitive? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's what I said I want to go first</u>
<u n="380" who="S0336">yeah set the bar</u>
<u n="381" who="S0363">set the bar high <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so that that will be really that's really exciting <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> cos I was really panicked cos I told you before I was panicking about all these holidays we've got to take</u>
<u n="382" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0363">but they've done it and it's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0336"><unclear/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0363">I think it's fine but I've still got a few days left so</u>
<u n="386" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0363">I've got take for a hen do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I'm really like I'm really irritated by that thread but I feel rude if I leave <pause dur="short"/> but it's really annoying <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0363">I know I saw the one that erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> put up the other day and I was like oh that's going to irritate</u>
<u n="390" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0363">I just could feel it</u>
<u n="392" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0363">like I could I could sense that they won't put it and they just put a it's happened to me</u>
<u n="394" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0363">I was like they don't wanna do that or</u>
<u n="396" who="S0336" trans="overlap">well I think it's also the case of like they they</u>
<u n="397" who="S0363" trans="overlap">planning on top of their plans</u>
<u n="398" who="S0336">yeah and they've made the mistake of sort of saying oh there's not much to do around the area <pause dur="short"/> so people are kind of going like oh what about this? what about that? but what they should of done is kind of just held off</u>
<u n="399" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0336">there's no need to put that really like cos I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="401" who="S0363" trans="overlap">oh don't be polite just by saying if you've got any options it would be great and then not accepting it</u>
<u n="402" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly like what they should of said I mean <pause dur="short"/> with a hen party as well I don't think people need to know miles in advance like you could of organised a load of stuff and then on the day been like if you wanna do this like a group of us are gonna go off and do this if you don't then you could do this or like <pause dur="short"/> if if they wanted to take control they should've taken control <pause dur="short"/> but I I kind of think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s idea's kind of cute but</u>
<u n="403" who="S0363" trans="overlap">I like it</u>
<u n="404" who="S0336">I think it's quite I don't know how she's going to</u>
<u n="405" who="S0363" trans="overlap">do it</u>
<u n="406" who="S0336">organise it no</u>
<u n="407" who="S0363">that's difficult <unclear/> cos the treasure the actual you've got to get out there <pause dur="short"/> and do it</u>
<u n="408" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah and like with clues and stuff how are you going to be able to organise clues until you've seen the area like it's just a bit I mean I <pause dur="short"/> and also it doesn't sound like much of a group activity it sounds like the kind of thing like you'd say to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like oh you're going on a treasure hunt <pause dur="short"/> it just sounds a bit boring <pause dur="short"/> like she's going on a treasure hunt and she gets a prize but like what are the rest of us going to stand and watch like?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0363">yeah I hope we all get to go</u>
<u n="410" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="long"/> but we'll see <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they'll have plenty to say about it all <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0363" trans="overlap">just happy to get there when <unclear/> and just <unclear>try</unclear> a nice house for a few days</u>
<u n="412" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> have if so you've got three holidays this year</u>
<u n="413" who="S0363">I know it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="414" who="S0336">that's so indulgent <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0363">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's not my fault my sister takes a frigging week for her wedding <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0336">I know christ <pause dur="short"/> it will be good you'll have a really good time though <pause dur="short"/> so much to look forward to as well this week this year will just fly by</u>
<u n="417" who="S0363">I couldn't believe the other day I was like I knew we were into February but I was like oh my god it's already the fifth of February I mean where did this week go? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and Feb's always such a short month anyway so it just doesn't hang around very long</u>
<u n="419" who="S0363">no <pause dur="short"/> it's crazy I was just like <pause dur="short"/> I thought it must be like the first or second the fifth February? and I looked at the date and I was like for god's sake</u>
<u n="420" who="S0336">I don't know where we're going <unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0363">oh no you keep going</u>
<u n="422" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="423" who="S0363">you turn off at D</u>
<u n="424" who="S0336">at D <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="425" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0336">it's it's been ages since I've been over it's so bad <pause dur="short"/> I've just got so used to <unclear/> to see me like it's like so</u>
<u n="427" who="S0363" trans="overlap">why did you flash him?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0336">I was trying to <unclear>look for these</unclear></u>
<u n="429" who="S0363">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0336">it's not my car I don't know where everything is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0363">erm <pause dur="short"/> I've been doing this route like this is the way I'd go if I was going to Coventry so</u>
<u n="432" who="S0336">oh okay</u>
<u n="433" who="S0363">like I've been up here a few times this week <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah like is they I mean they come to <anon type="place"/> a lot so I've seen them you know if they've been to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or they've been to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've like tagged along and stuff so I <trunc>s</trunc> I feel like I've seen them loads in the last year but I definitely haven't been out to see them which is bad <pause dur="short"/> it just does seem like a mile away</u>
<u n="435" who="S0363">it is a mile away really</u>
<u n="436" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can see why they've done it like <pause dur="short"/> it must be nice for them to be closer to work and stuff</u>
<u n="437" who="S0363">yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I still find that <pause dur="short"/> I'm the one that to text them if I need to do something</u>
<u n="438" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0363">which surprises me cos <pause dur="short"/> I think they <unclear/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0336">yeah like I don't know I don't know when when they do stuff with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't know who it is that gets in touch to be fair but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether they like they're so removed out here that they almost think like</u>
<u n="441" who="S0363">no one <unclear>thinks of them</unclear></u>
<u n="442" who="S0336">no <pause dur="short"/> and it's hard as well because like <pause dur="short"/> they're not the kind of people to host stuff like if I wanted to see you I'd probably say oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come round for dinner</u>
<u n="443" who="S0363">yes</u>
<u n="444" who="S0336">and like but they're not those people are they? they'd be like oh guys shall we go <unclear>out</unclear> for dinner?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0336">I don't know why they don't like cooking I think they could be good at it</u>
<u n="447" who="S0363">I don't I think they <unclear/> they wouldn't have anywhere to host it</u>
<u n="448" who="S0336"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but like you just make do don't you?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0363">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0336">yeah so tell me about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s new boy</u>
<u n="451" who="S0363">oh yeah so erm his name is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's thirty-seven</u>
<u n="452" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="453" who="S0363">and he has two kids</u>
<u n="454" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="455" who="S0363">but not married <pause dur="short"/> never married the lady</u>
<u n="456" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="457" who="S0363">they just separated</u>
<u n="458" who="S0336">yeah?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0363">last year they've been separated now <pause dur="short"/> for over a year I think</u>
<u n="460" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="461" who="S0363">and erm <pause dur="short"/> she really really likes him and she she never said it about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0363">yeah she really really likes him <pause dur="short"/> and then I was like she said cos I was talking to her the other day about the holiday and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> she said about oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll probably come <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if he'll come for the whole week if he'll come up</u>
<u n="464" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0363">he said that sounds really cool <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> I was like how's things going? she was like really good now like he's erm <pause dur="short"/> he's got a new little apartment which sounds nice she's spent time there and she's got stuff there</u>
<u n="466" who="S0336">ah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0363">and I said oh she said I think I need to introduce him a bit earlier this time she says we're not technically official but we basically are</u>
<u n="468" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0363">I said oh bring cos dad wants to a <pause dur="short"/> meal well dad doesn't <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> which really surprised me has all but wants to organise a big meal for dad's sixtieth</u>
<u n="470" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0363">like Sunday the twenty-eighth or something like that <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> he wants us all to come and I said <unclear/> why don't you bring him to that? she's like yeah I think I might do do you think it will be a bit full on? I said whatever you do it's always gonna be full on</u>
<u n="472" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="474" who="S0336">I think it's almost better to introduce somebody in an <trunc>eve</trunc> like on an occasion like that because they don't get bombarded by like one person like you know if you literally just</u>
<u n="475" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="476" who="S0336">if she just brought him home it would be very personal like meeting</u>
<u n="477" who="S0363">parent</u>
<u n="478" who="S0336" trans="overlap">her parents and stuff whereas like when you when there's a massive group of you like that like you just have little conversations with people <pause dur="short"/> and even though there's a lot of people to take in like it's not serious you don't</u>
<u n="479" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0336">people aren't like oh so you know tell me your life story like over dinner <pause dur="short"/> that's exciting</u>
<u n="481" who="S0363">yes and he looks really nice</u>
<u n="482" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0363">I've seen a picture of him <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> you know <unclear/> it's this turning on the right <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0336">I I don't think I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I I don't think I'd be put off by somebody having kids</u>
<u n="485" who="S0363">and I know I not any more I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I think it's changed hasn't it?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0363">I think what I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was because he was thirty-seven <pause dur="short"/> erm and she said oh he he said he'd still be open to getting married cos he never married before obviously</u>
<u n="488" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0363">all I said the only thing I would be conscious of was that would he have more kids? cos like you'd want to have kids</u>
<u n="490" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0363">but obviously it's not something you want to do as an opening line</u>
<u n="492" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="493" who="S0363">but then you don't wanna get too far down the line and be like <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0336">I'm sure that's you'd like to think that's something he would pick up on though</u>
<u n="495" who="S0363">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="496" who="S0336">even if you've got kids if you're if you're with a younger person you have to anticipate that they might want kids themselves</u>
<u n="497" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she was like joking about cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> jokes about obviously about nearly being thirty</u>
<u n="498" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0363">she's a year away from it I suppose and erm blah blah blah that she wouldn't be single forever and whatever and she's like oh no I might just <pause dur="short"/> suddenly I just have two kids <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you never know how life turns out do you? <pause dur="short"/> has she met the kids?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0363" trans="overlap">you don't <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> which I think is good</u>
<u n="502" who="S0336">I think that's good as well <pause dur="short"/> sounds like he's doing things properly</u>
<u n="503" who="S0363">yeah I think he's quite smart</u>
<u n="504" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0363">both boys</u>
<u n="506" who="S0336" trans="overlap">that was my that was my biggest like begrudge of like people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she got involved with people that had kids was just that like she became such an integral part of that kid's life</u>
<u n="507" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0336">that the breakup wasn't just breaking up with the dad it was breaking up with the kid as well which is just horrible</u>
<u n="509" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> which is what I'm trying to explain to you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who came around the other day whose got</u>
<u n="510" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0363">girlfriend troubles <unclear/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0336">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0363">she's got a kid I was like she is probably keeping you at arm's length because when you were there nearly all the time <pause dur="short"/> it was her son asking where you were and asking where you'd been and when you were coming round</u>
<u n="514" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0363">you know you've already started and she probably keeps her life with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0336">so what was the drama? like <unclear/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0363" trans="overlap">I think that he she just needed her space</u>
<u n="518" who="S0336" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="519" who="S0363">and she wanted to spend some more just one on one time with her son when she had the chance to rather than having him there as well</u>
<u n="520" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0363">cos I can I can totally get that</u>
<u n="522" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0363">but I said to just you know give her that time and like when it gets to ridiculous amounts of months or whatever</u>
<u n="524" who="S0336" trans="overlap">that way?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0363">yes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> god I haven't been this way <unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0363">and then at the bottom of here you turn right erm <pause dur="short"/> I said the <pause dur="short"/> the only thing I said is don't worry about it for a while and if it gets like ridiculously long be a bit like <unclear/> really serious it's better <unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0363">but you don't want to push that thing you don't rush that thing <pause dur="short"/> like just focus on you and her for a while</u>
<u n="530" who="S0336" trans="overlap">he needs he needs he needs to be a hundred percent sure that he's committed to that as well</u>
<u n="531" who="S0363">oh he is</u>
<u n="532" who="S0336">he is?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0363">he totally is</u>
<u n="534" who="S0336">good <pause dur="short"/> that's quite sweet</u>
<u n="535" who="S0363" trans="overlap">he is oh god so much he like takes him swimming on his own he's like totally into it <pause dur="short"/> he like wears his heart on his sleeve this guy bless him <pause dur="short"/> like he wants to always give so much that he can</u>
<u n="536" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0363">the night before erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> after Christmas he got her a four hundred pound watch plus some other bits or whatever <pause dur="short"/> he was like what do you think <unclear/> so what you think that's a decent present for like Valentine's Day? I was like a card</u>
<u n="538" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0363">and he was like oh no he's like no seriously I was like don't worry I was like what have you done? he goes oh well I've booked for her to go to a spa for two people I was like <pause dur="short"/> well that's really really nice I mean I wouldn't say no to it but</u>
<u n="540" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0336">yeah I'd be lucky to get a fucking card</u>
<u n="542" who="S0363">said I I know standard I'll get I'll get some probably flowers <unclear/> I suppose a card and he's sending her flowers to his her work on Friday on the Friday the thirteenth I was like he was like <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0336"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0363"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> full on <unclear/> you know <unclear/> out there he he'd give everything</u>
<u n="545" who="S0336">yeah bless him</u>
<u n="546" who="S0363">I think he's moving tomorrow and everything <pause dur="short"/> he's that kind of person bless him</u>
<u n="547" who="S0336" trans="overlap">she's obviously just like you said being careful</u>
<u n="548" who="S0363">she's being careful <pause dur="short"/> she went to my school</u>
<u n="549" who="S0336">really?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0363">because I remember my first day at <anon type="place"/> and he was like like she knows you I was like what?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0336" trans="overlap">what's her name?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0363">erm she's two years older than <unclear>me</unclear> her name is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0336">no I don't know her</u>
<u n="554" who="S0363" trans="overlap">I kind of recognised her <unclear/> I was like I don't know who <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is then I facebooked her <unclear/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0363">and erm <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really have any mutual friends with her apart from <pause dur="short"/> thing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="557" who="S0336" trans="overlap">oh right that's weird</u>
<u n="558" who="S0363">but he was obviously in her year</u>
<u n="559" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0363">and then obviously looked at other people she was friends with there was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not that I ever spoke to him I know he went to my school <unclear/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0363">and then <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but not as many people as you think <pause dur="short"/> no not <unclear/> I I <unclear/> what we knew from that year</u>
<u n="563" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0363">or whatever <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> so yeah she <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0336">these road are mental</u>
<u n="566" who="S0363">but I think there is an easier way but they take this is the most <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> easier way <pause dur="short"/> this is a dangerous road</u>
<u n="567" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0363"><unclear/> these corners quite fast</u>
<u n="569" who="S0336">turns <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0363"><unclear/> it's okay</u>
<u n="571" who="S0336">oh so there's some drama there</u>
<u n="572" who="S0363">I think it's alright now I think he thought that she'd like try and end it cos he was like oh she was like we're very two different people</u>
<u n="573" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0363">come on cos she keeps herself to herself and he's like <unclear>hand for my</unclear> heart <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0363">I said don't take it as a erm erm bad thing I think you know you've just got to see where you are he thought it was like ending he thought it was over</u>
<u n="577" who="S0336">oh ah ah <pause dur="long"/> yeah like you I suppose like your extended group of friends now</u>
<u n="578" who="S0363" trans="overlap">turning right here</u>
<u n="579" who="S0336">is like they're older I suppose like I was just thinking like <pause dur="short"/> oh I just hope <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets a girlfriend like none of this like actual drama</u>
<u n="580" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0336">you've got you've got kids and</u>
<u n="582" who="S0363">got kids living next door to us soon</u>
<u n="583" who="S0336">really? <pause dur="short"/> what's the latest with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or whatever? is is engagement on the cards?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0363">who knows? I think I think he'd be mad to not to propose to her this year <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> we got quite drunk we went to this like poker night a few weeks ago like a work do thing</u>
<u n="585" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0363">and er <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got really really drunk she was in the car like we were in the taxi back she's like why won't you just marry me? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I'm like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are like absolutely wetting ourselves laughing but I can see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in front <unclear>thinking</unclear> fucking shut up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="587" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0363">but I think if he's gonna do it I think he cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think he'd want to do it with friends around him</u>
<u n="589" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0363">I'd be I wouldn't be surprised if he proposed when we went skiing</u>
<u n="591" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="592" who="S0363">now I've told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so many times I've like you need to stop</u>
<u n="593" who="S0336" trans="overlap">asking yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0363">asking him talking about it like I find it hilarious</u>
<u n="595" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0363">but if you stop it like it's gonna be more of like a surprise like you don't wanna be feel like you've forced it</u>
<u n="597" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0363" trans="overlap">as such</u>
<u n="599" who="S0336">and also like <vocal desc="cough"/> sounds really stupid but like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always jokes like whenever I complain about him not buying me flowers he says that he sets the counter so like <pause dur="short"/> if I've asked if I've moaned about him not buying me flowers like it would be shit if he went out and bought them the next week so</u>
<u n="600" who="S0363">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0336">you know it resets the counter well every every time she brings up him in <pause dur="short"/> asking her to marry him</u>
<u n="602" who="S0363" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0336">it resets the counter she's like fucking herself over <pause dur="short"/> she needs to she needs to not tell her tell her she needs to not reset the counter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0363">I will I'll say that to her <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>s</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> done you know always puts it in there he's now <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> get the ring out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0363">I was like you shouldn't bring that up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0336">hope he does otherwise that's gonna be so awkward isn't it?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0363">well she's given him like basically she's she turns thirty-three this year I think <pause dur="short"/> and I think she said she's gonna give him till thirty-four <pause dur="short"/> so obviously but he knows as soon as they get married</u>
<u n="609" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it's here isn't it right?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0363">yeah <pause dur="short"/> soon as they get married she'll want to start trying for a baby</u>
<u n="611" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0363">and I think that's why he's trying to hold off so much not so much to marry her</u>
<u n="613" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0363">on one he knows that you know once he says will you marry? you know planning will go into full mode everything will be focused on that</u>
<u n="615" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0363">and then <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> and the next thing will be as soon as they are married I think you know she'll she'll want to have kids</u>
<u n="617" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0363">down this one</u>
<u n="619" who="S0336">this one?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0363">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0363" trans="overlap">I usually just park like parallel behind it</u>
<u n="623" who="S0336">okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh <unclear/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0363">oh the radio's coming on <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's like what's that noise?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0336" trans="overlap"><trunc>cha</trunc>chatting away <pause dur="short"/> well I'm sorry it took us a lot longer</u>
<u n="626" who="S0363">no don't worry</u>
<u n="627" who="S0336">I should of I should of like googled where it was I completely forgotten <pause dur="short"/> haven't I? oh thanks</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
