<text id="SBFR">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:17:14</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-09</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0255 S0256</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Meeting friends, food, dentist, ice skating (hobbies), Facebook, school uniform – ties, words/language.</topics>
		<activity>Family catch up</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0255">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Boston, Lincs</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Boston/London/Peterborough</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>account manager - sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0256">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Grantham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Civil servant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0255">so I went and met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for lunch today cos it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday tomorrow and then I found out when I was there it was actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday on Sunday</u>
<u n="2" who="S0256">oh right</u>
<u n="3" who="S0255">so that which I didn't know but so I was they're giving <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all these presents and saying oh happy birthday happy birthday</u>
<u n="4" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0255">and going I hadn't got anything for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0256" trans="overlap">a little bit awkward</u>
<u n="7" who="S0255">yeah but oh no but she was laughing saying don't you dare don't worry</u>
<u n="8" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0255">don't get anything and I was yeah yeah there so she'll obviously get something next week when she's not expecting it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0255">but so we went to Clarks erm which is in the <anon type="place"/> Theatre and it's in underneath you know as you walk in?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah the one that is free for <unclear/> or whatever it was?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0255">is that what it was?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0256">I think so</u>
<u n="15" who="S0255">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="16" who="S0256">I think it was that for a little while I <trunc>d</trunc> and then it was something else I think but think it's changes all the time I think it changed about three times when I was there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0255">yeah well no we we went well I went in there and there was a wood bar across the door and it was only a few minutes to twelve so I started thinking I've got the wrong time they're on day or I knew I'd got the right day so I went back outside to wait for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm but by the time she came we went in it was fine it was open</u>
<u n="18" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0255" trans="overlap">but we sat outside there er it was absolutely beautiful looking over the river</u>
<u n="20" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0255">and there were swans on the river and there was actually a barge parked up next to the you know the the <anon type="place"/> barge?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0255">there's actually a <trunc>b</trunc> a barge and people were coming off it just</u>
<u n="24" who="S0256">yeah there were there was sometimes when we used to be there there was one there I think it used to be a regular one there that's</u>
<u n="25" who="S0255">maybe it does holiday things or day trips or something</u>
<u n="26" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah maybe something don't know</u>
<u n="27" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0256" trans="overlap">not sure</u>
<u n="29" who="S0255">but so so we <trunc>ha</trunc> erm had had a really nice lunch we decided to have a glass of Prosecco because it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday</u>
<u n="30" who="S0256" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0255">nearly and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday nearly</u>
<u n="32" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0255">with a large glass of water because obviously they were going back to work</u>
<u n="34" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0255">we were both er we're all driving <pause dur="short"/> erm yes that it so it was really nice</u>
<u n="36" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0255">really nice</u>
<u n="38" who="S0256">yeah no I didn't get didn't go outside much today I went out erm for a wander on my lunch and obviously then <pause dur="short"/> when I walked back to my car because I wasn't feeling great so I just couldn't tell if I was warm or not so I kept my hoodie on</u>
<u n="39" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0256">so I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I must have looked a bit strange walking round in in a big hoodie and everyone's walking around in like T-shirts <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos I just couldn't <trunc>ev</trunc> I well I didn't warm up quick enough and I was like I'm fine I'm just going to stay snuggled up in my hoodie</u>
<u n="41" who="S0255">so what was it was it a lesson this morning?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0256">erm no that was just because I was just feeling rough with my tooth</u>
<u n="43" who="S0255">oh right oh <trunc>ri</trunc> sorry I thought you went to the ice rink</u>
<u n="44" who="S0256">no no no outside at work</u>
<u n="45" who="S0255">oh right okay</u>
<u n="46" who="S0256" trans="overlap">on my lunch break <pause dur="short"/> so I didn't didn't spend much time outside cos I just wanted to get there and get back really <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0255">mm just as well our <unclear>advice</unclear> was cancelled then for tonight</u>
<u n="48" who="S0256">yeah I wouldn't have been able to do it anyway because erm on the dos and don'ts it says that you're not allowed to do any strenuous activity anyway so I think they'd class <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0255">ice skating <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0256">yeah I think that would count as strenuous activity and exercise</u>
<u n="51" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0256">so no I'm gonna go tomorrow night cos it'll be on then so</u>
<u n="53" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0256">I'll do it then</u>
<u n="55" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0255">and it's cos Rainbows hasn't started yet has it?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0256">no it's Wednesday tomorrow anyway</u>
<u n="59" who="S0255">oh yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0255" trans="overlap">today's Tuesday</u>
<u n="62" who="S0256">yeah so no erm it'll be good I cos I I've got a lesson tomorrow morning <pause dur="short"/> and then I'll have <unclear>advice</unclear> in the evening but I'm gonna <pause dur="short"/> go straight from work <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna try and build a bit of time back up from today</u>
<u n="63" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0256">so</u>
<u n="65" who="S0255">so will you be alright tomorrow? is will that be a long a <trunc>l</trunc> enough time in the morning?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0256">yeah yeah yeah he says like on the day</u>
<u n="67" who="S0255">oh that's alright then</u>
<u n="68" who="S0256">in fact</u>
<u n="69" who="S0255">well I think that was that was really good though <trunc>g</trunc> ringing and going and getting him to check it</u>
<u n="70" who="S0256" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0255">your tooth</u>
<u n="72" who="S0256">yeah I'm glad I did because it's a lot better now <pause dur="short"/> but I know it must have been bad for me to say yeah I'm gonna go and get it checked I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's it's good <pause dur="short"/> I'm happy it's out now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0255">so do you feel less wise now you have less wisdom teeth?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0256">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> one tooth's fine</u>
<u n="75" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0256">I always say a secret genius in the making so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0255">you <trunc>s</trunc> you say you say what?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0256">I say <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm a secret genius</u>
<u n="79" who="S0255">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0256">erm no it's good though it still feels weird</u>
<u n="81" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0256">cos <unclear>so</unclear> so having a tooth there now that it's it's strange that it's gone but</u>
<u n="83" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0256">I'm glad it is it's so much more comfortable I can actually feel I've come back to me</u>
<u n="85" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0256">that's nice</u>
<u n="87" who="S0255">so tell me what you do with the skating now</u>
<u n="88" who="S0256">erm well we've got the we'll be starting work on the Christmas so er show soon cos it's we normally know by October what we're doing and so we should know if they're talking about like Cinderella or Mary Poppins or Jungle Book or something like that but</u>
<u n="89" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0256">erm hopefully this year if it's a show it'll probably just be our lot so then we might get to do a bit more as well <pause dur="short"/> so that'll be nice erm just practising for my test at the minute though I'm waiting for my test date it shouldn't be long <unclear/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0255" trans="overlap">how how long roughly?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0256">I wouldn't say it would be that long like I think we'll know the date soon and then it just depends on when there's enough people to put in for a test cos they won't bring a <trunc>ju</trunc> a judge in if it's only like one or two people wanting to test they want to have like a full morning's worth of testing before they'll bring a judge</u>
<u n="93" who="S0255" trans="overlap">so they have to wait until they've got</u>
<u n="94" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0255" trans="overlap">enough people <pause dur="short"/> were there lots of people last time?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0256">there was a fair few yeah erm lots of people do a number of different tests so people do like their elements and their freestyle and their field moves on the same day <pause dur="short"/> so then it erm <pause dur="short"/> it just ends up being that the there's not necessarily that many people but there's enough people to do a number of different tests otherwise it's a waste of a judge's time to come in and a waste of the money</u>
<u n="97" who="S0255" trans="overlap">so what's are they in a particular order that <trunc>y</trunc> you have to do one lot then another then another or is it just you'll do</u>
<u n="98" who="S0256" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0255" trans="overlap">different levels in each type?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0256">yeah you have different levels in each type so like it goes up to ten and then you have it in freestyle <pause dur="short"/> er so like the that's like your programme and you have elements which is like your jump spins things like that erm and then you have field moves which is showing off like the skills and the basics of skating to show that you can do footwork and things and then you've also of course you've got dance and they all go up to ten so I've got my field moves level one I've passed and my free level one I've passed and I'm working on my field moves level two my free level two and I'm working on my elements level one and two so that I can put in for them</u>
<u n="101" who="S0255" trans="overlap">so when?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0256" trans="overlap">once I've done level one</u>
<u n="103" who="S0255">when you do the test thing then can when they come to test you could you be doing two or three different things is that what you normally do?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah you well you can either do it depends really what you've got ready for testing er my level twos aren't quite ready for testing yet so I'm not putting them in but I could very easily do level one and two in in in elements while I'm doing my level two and three and my level two in field moves but they're</u>
<u n="105" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0256">not quite polished enough yet that we're ready to put them in they're nearly there with some of them but there's just bits where they're not quite ready like my my sit spin isn't quite low enough</u>
<u n="107" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0256">so then it's not ready to be tested</u>
<u n="109" who="S0255">oh that's alright</u>
<u n="110" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0255">so like what was the last show that you did with the ice skating? I'm trying to remember</u>
<u n="112" who="S0256">that was the gala</u>
<u n="113" who="S0255">oh that's right yeah so that was all just loads of different bits</u>
<u n="114" who="S0256">yeah it it was rubbish really and I'm glad that we're not doing that this year we're doing an actual show this year</u>
<u n="115" who="S0255">I think the last show was that the like The Lion King?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0256">The Lion King yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0255">that was really good</u>
<u n="118" who="S0256">or the er African Adventure as it was formerly known <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0256">yeah no it I think the problem was because we did a gala the the other groups like the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> joined it because they could just put stuff in that they were putting in the <anon type="place"/> gala</u>
<u n="121" who="S0255">yeah so they it isn't really</u>
<u n="122" who="S0256" trans="overlap">so they weren't great so there was more people that and more coaches involved so it meant that there wasn't it wasn't the same as when it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>  and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like <trunc>ru</trunc>running it it's not quite the same it as as that but this year if there's a show</u>
<u n="123" who="S0255" trans="overlap">then you'll get the continuity and they'd know how to bring the best out in everybody rather than</u>
<u n="124" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="125" who="S0255">lots of people having an input</u>
<u n="126" who="S0256" trans="overlap">and it's controlled</u>
<u n="127" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0256" trans="overlap">like last year with our group the we ended up being given cast offs from <trunc>ano</trunc>another group</u>
<u n="129" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0256">that were a lot lower level than us and we had to like dumb the whole routine down for them which meant that those of us that were higher levels weren't getting to do anything or show off anything and it also meant we didn't have enough time</u>
<u n="131" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0256">to do what the coaches wanted to do but if it's a if it's a show like with here <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> won't because they've got the <anon type="place"/> gala that they do every year so if that's on they won't do the show</u>
<u n="133" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0256">because they <trunc>do</trunc> it's too much of a commitment with just starting</u>
<u n="135" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0256">it just means it'll be the <anon type="place"/> Skate Academy lot so like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s lot that'll do it and and it'll be a lot more availability and we'll have to do more</u>
<u n="137" who="S0255">well that's good because like even if you're in a group and a lot of the stuff you're having to do isn't at that high standard you should be able to hopefully do two or three or little bits yourself</u>
<u n="138" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0255">to go off and actually do a little bit more</u>
<u n="140" who="S0256" trans="overlap">well some of the people that were in the groups like the top two circles</u>
<u n="141" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0256">are at the same level as me which is fine</u>
<u n="143" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0256">and have a good work <trunc>eth</trunc>ethic as well because it's the problem is you get the ones that just muck around and don't wanna do it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0256">you get the ones where they're learning the basic the most basic of moves that we've all been doing for years</u>
<u n="147" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0256" trans="overlap">and then it's they don't know how to do it and you that's when you can see there's gonna be a problem because you can't put anything too complicated in</u>
<u n="149" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0256">because they won't do it won't be able to do it and then those of us that are that are at the top of our group because we're sort of the in-between ones we're not quite we're almost at the level of the lower lot in the higher group but they're pushing to keep up with the top group whereas if you do a show the ones that <trunc>wer</trunc>were at the top of the top group</u>
<u n="151" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0256" trans="overlap">will be the main characters</u>
<u n="153" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0256">with some of the ones lower down being some of the main characters</u>
<u n="155" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0256">you'll then have the ones that almost at our level being at our sort of level and we could all be in a group together</u>
<u n="157" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0256">because they're closer to our level some of them are are trying doubles and just about landing axels but they're actually more comfortable doing the lower down jumps so then</u>
<u n="159" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0256">we'll all be around the same sort of level and a lot of people have said well not a lot but some people have said they're not doing it this year any more they're not sure if they're going to do it they might help out instead</u>
<u n="161" who="S0255">cos that's one good thing with you you can actually have the flexible time at work this year can't you?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah yeah at least I have</u>
<u n="163" who="S0255" trans="overlap">whereas before you'd really struggled didn't</u>
<u n="164" who="S0256" trans="overlap">and I've got the October half term off</u>
<u n="165" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0256" trans="overlap">which was a very</u>
<u n="167" who="S0255">er</u>
<u n="168" who="S0256">clever plot of mine because usually we have extra rehearsals in in October half term</u>
<u n="169" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0256" trans="overlap">and I can never make any of them</u>
<u n="171" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="172" who="S0256">but it was free there was like one space across the week left and I was like I'm having that thank you very much</u>
<u n="173" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0256">so I've got that off so then even if we're not doing anything I can still go in and skate or do other things but if we have</u>
<u n="175" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0256">got it planned work that we'll be doing which we usually do</u>
<u n="177" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0256">I'll be able to commit to more rehearsals</u>
<u n="179" who="S0255">so what date's that roughly?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0256">er it's the week after my birthday</u>
<u n="181" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="182" who="S0256">so like the twenty-fifth of something I think it is something like that twenty-fifth twenty-sixth cos my birthday's on the Wednesday which I've got off and then it's <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it'll be about the twenty-sixth I think or twenty-seventh it's the end of October</u>
<u n="183" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0256" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="185" who="S0255">that picture of dad is that the one where you went to stay near <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0255">erm tell and it was when you went up the stairs did what was it you had to duck?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0256">oh yeah er for</u>
<u n="189" who="S0255" trans="overlap">just made me think</u>
<u n="190" who="S0256" trans="overlap">cos it was like a converted barn or something so like those are the <trunc>ba</trunc> like beams going across the top of the stairs so as you if you like if you were staying in a bedroom that was upstairs it looked like something out of like an old story book</u>
<u n="191" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0256">you had to duck under this beam to actually <vocal desc="laugh"/> like get get to the bedrooms the problem is you'll probably forget about that in the the morning and trip over and fall flying down the stairs so</u>
<u n="193" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0256">I thought it was safer to stay in the little room <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0255">yeah oh I know mum was saying all about it saying about all the things that were there from was it the old erm when it was a stables?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0256">yeah that's it a stables it wasn't a barn it was a stables yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0256" trans="overlap">my room was just big enough to swing a cat in but</u>
<u n="199" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0256">it was it was fine apart from the</u>
<u n="201" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><trunc>wi</trunc>without a beam <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0256">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> exactly but the problem was cos it was erm right down on the ground floor and because there was fields nearby</u>
<u n="203" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0256">there was a mass of spiders so I was on spider patrol cos nana doesn't likes spiders does she'so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was</u>
<u n="205" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="206" who="S0256" trans="overlap">on spider patrol</u>
<u n="207" who="S0255">it was funny one of my friends put on Facebook something about erm saw the biggest spider ever it was so big it actually stopped and waved at me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah that's what this one was like that I found</u>
<u n="209" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0256" trans="overlap">there are some big spiders I don't know what it is there seem to be lots recently haven't there?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no it's this time of year <trunc>wi</trunc> it's when they</u>
<u n="212" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0255">erm the the harvest they they cut all the the weed</u>
<u n="214" who="S0256" trans="overlap">it's probably because</u>
<u n="215" who="S0255">and the the spiders all come out</u>
<u n="216" who="S0256" trans="overlap">there hasn't been Facebook has there? and people have got more so that when they're posting on Facebook</u>
<u n="217" who="S0255" trans="overlap">people are putting pictures of <trunc>sp</trunc></u>
<u n="218" who="S0256" trans="overlap">they post the silliest things</u>
<u n="219" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0256">whereas you think a couple of years ago you probably wouldn't have had that your Facebook was just about what are you doing you know keeping in touch with and now it's just post a picture of a spider <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0255">exactly yeah that's what makes me laugh on Facebook when people that or about the tenth person that puts it's snowing it's snowing it's snowing and somebody puts yeah I could look out the window <vocal desc="laugh"/> and see it's snowing</u>
<u n="222" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0255">but thanks for telling me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah but then but then you you go on Facebook and you see it's snowing and if you were told you <trunc>th</trunc> is it? and then go <unclear/> oh it is</u>
<u n="225" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0256">like you <trunc>ha</trunc> like you have to verify what they're saying like I don't trust that you're saying it's snowing</u>
<u n="227" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0256">I've got to go and just check the facts</u>
<u n="229" who="S0255" trans="overlap">and then people click like</u>
<u n="230" who="S0256">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0255">that you like that they've said it's snowing</u>
<u n="232" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0255">is that the fact you like it's snowing or you fact you like that they said it's snowing?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0256" trans="overlap">or is it just because they're your friend and you think mm they've not got enough likes?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0255" trans="overlap">you just yeah you just</u>
<u n="236" who="S0256" trans="overlap">at this stage and like everything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0255">oh</u>
<u n="240" who="S0256">yeah it is funny some of the things people put put on there</u>
<u n="241" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0256">it's er it makes me laugh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0255">at the minute everyone's putting on all the pictures of the kids starting first day at school the first day of</u>
<u n="244" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I got a little bit fed up of that I think well I don't mind like the first day of primary school</u>
<u n="245" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0256" trans="overlap">and I don't mind the first day of big school but I don't want to know that your child's starting year five you showed me</u>
<u n="247" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah six</u>
<u n="248" who="S0256" trans="overlap">when they were starting year one</u>
<u n="249" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah seven yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I don't yeah like great they're starting big school brilliant they're starting primary school oh they are cute you know but then after that it's like <pause dur="short"/> no I don't need to know</u>
<u n="251" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0256">I'm not bothered by your child at that much now like</u>
<u n="253" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0256">you know show me the odd picture but that's fine but</u>
<u n="255" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0256">my my feed was just full of first day back to school pictures</u>
<u n="257" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0256">for like two or three days</u>
<u n="259" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I I I saw quite a lot of those</u>
<u n="262" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0255">as well <vocal desc="yawn"/> but then I mean we've still got the picture of you and the picture of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> both starting secondary school</u>
<u n="264" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0255" trans="overlap">the the photo yeah of your first</u>
<u n="266" who="S0256" trans="overlap">well your</u>
<u n="267" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well I mean I've got pictures that I took in the garden of both of you each time</u>
<u n="268" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I remember those</u>
<u n="269" who="S0255">I've got pictures of you both on your first first day at school</u>
<u n="270" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0255">and then erm er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got the the the official <trunc>pi</trunc>pictures from the first year at at</u>
<u n="272" who="S0256" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0255">er at secondary</u>
<u n="274" who="S0256">oh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0255">she's got those</u>
<u n="276" who="S0256">I know</u>
<u n="277" who="S0255">and she says she likes that cos that's how she remembers you when you were both little</u>
<u n="278" who="S0256">yeah I don't</u>
<u n="279" who="S0255" trans="overlap">before you grew up</u>
<u n="280" who="S0256" trans="overlap">look anything like that now though</u>
<u n="281" who="S0255">no you don't actually it's it's funny looking back at some of the old pictures</u>
<u n="282" who="S0256" trans="overlap">and I was all like oh hello I'm all done up ready for school</u>
<u n="283" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that was it it was good though cos the school made you have pride in your appearance and we insisted that you still kept that and did that as well</u>
<u n="284" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0255">so</u>
<u n="286" who="S0256">it slipped after the first few years though</u>
<u n="287" who="S0255">but that's fair enough that's exploring the boundaries</u>
<u n="288" who="S0256" trans="overlap">the shirt comes out and you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0256">tie comes down a little bit</u>
<u n="291" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah I remember when I was at school with our tie it was the fashion everyone used to have it in a really really big knot</u>
<u n="292" who="S0256">yes</u>
<u n="293" who="S0255" trans="overlap">with just this tiny little bit poking out</u>
<u n="294" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0255">and then we decided we changed it and we used to just do the back of the tie like a mod a really thin tie</u>
<u n="296" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0255">you had the back of the tie</u>
<u n="298" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0255" trans="overlap">going right down like that</u>
<u n="300" who="S0256">yeah no we had the really big knot and the er and the little bit of tie but I I couldn't be bothered with that <pause dur="short"/> I didn't do it like really long but</u>
<u n="301" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I used to have it like loose but no I wasn't</u>
<u n="303" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0256">wasn't part of the crowd <vocal desc="laugh"/> that did the like real big knots or anything so I didn't bother</u>
<u n="305" who="S0255">yeah it's funny</u>
<u n="306" who="S0256" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0255">it makes you think like so who does the fashion and who decides or whether</u>
<u n="308" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0255">one cool person does it or person who thinks they're cool?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0256" trans="overlap">we used to just <unclear/> each other's ties so there's no point</u>
<u n="311" who="S0255" trans="overlap">what's that mean?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0256">where you get hold the tie and then pull it down really hard and it like <trunc>tight</trunc> tightens the knot really bad like bad so then they can't undo it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0255">you're such a cruel child</u>
<u n="314" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I didn't do it no other people used to do it</u>
<u n="315" who="S0255" trans="overlap">you just said we just used to</u>
<u n="316" who="S0256" trans="overlap">like my friend's group used to do it and then I was the one that got very good at undoing the knots so everyone used to come to me and go</u>
<u n="317" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0256">cos I was good at undoing knots</u>
<u n="319" who="S0255" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="320" who="S0256">so they used to come to me</u>
<u n="321" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0256">and say can you undo this? and I'd go stand still</u>
<u n="323" who="S0255">I was always really good at undoing knots if you got like</u>
<u n="324" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0255">a string ball of string really bundled up</u>
<u n="326" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0255">I'd be the one I'd sit there and I'd have the patience I would just sit and keep working it and moving it</u>
<u n="328" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah or necklaces that's the <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0256" trans="overlap">where if the necklace is where you have to like wiggle it really carefully</u>
<u n="331" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0256">and then get it out so that it doesn't break</u>
<u n="333" who="S0255" trans="overlap">it's a real sense of satisfaction</u>
<u n="334" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0255" trans="overlap">it's working it out and just <trunc>dr</trunc> gradually working each bit and doing it</u>
<u n="336" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0255">and</u>
<u n="338" who="S0256">I like that so yeah I was a <unclear>pinger</unclear> undoer <vocal desc="misc"/> I don't think that's a word I think I've just made up a word</u>
<u n="339" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0256">oh I I made up a <trunc>wor</trunc> I can't remember what it was I made up a word the other day and I can't remember what it was but it and it it was such a silly thing I ended up combining two words just randomly made up a word and went it wasn't what I was aiming for but I don't remember what it was though</u>
<u n="341" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0256">but it was <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was just really weird and I was like okay</u>
<u n="343" who="S0255">language is fascinating though</u>
<u n="344" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I think you should be able to make up words or</u>
<u n="346" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0255">or you know put words together and express how you're feeling</u>
<u n="348" who="S0256">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah although the mind's boggling right now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0256">I can't remember what it was like it's gonna bug me</u>
<u n="351" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0256">but I I don't even remember I think it was something like I was saying I'm great and something else or whatever you know when you do you <trunc>jus</trunc> just mush the two together and it ends up being some sort of</u>
<u n="353" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0256" trans="overlap">that was it I said jarble it was meant to be jargon and garble I was like</u>
<u n="355" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0256">I'm garbling or it's jargon and I went</u>
<u n="357" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah I'm jarbling</u>
<u n="358" who="S0256" trans="overlap">oh what it is I'm jargle it's or it's jargle and I went that's not a word <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0255">no it should be though</u>
<u n="360" who="S0256">jargle I think so yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0255" trans="overlap">it should be it's a good word</u>
<u n="362" who="S0256">it's yeah when you're talking jargon but you're garbling it jargon jarble sounds like a gerbil though</u>
<u n="363" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0255">this is getting silly</u>
<u n="366" who="S0256">I don't know <unclear/> fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0255">oh</u>
<u n="368" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well I think that's forty-eight so that must be ten minutes we</u>
<u n="370" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I hope they're going to get that at the end again we</u>
<u n="371" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> so thank you</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
