<text id="SBG4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:05:37</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-06-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0415 S0417</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home Cork</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>History, Gerentology, geriatrics, anti ageing, telomeres, energy resources, comets, global warming, Vikings, life expectancy, pyramids, tectonics, immortality, travelling, risk, holidays, kayaking, arranging weekend away, delayed speech, icons, autism</topics>
		<activity>Discussion with ANON about history, ageing, gerontology and more.</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0415">
				<exactage>46</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig></lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cork, Ireland</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>46 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>r_ireland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>r_ireland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>r_ireland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>IT manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2>Irish</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0417">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>not currently working, caring for toddler</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>some French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0417">yeah so he got the <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>det</trunc> distinction</u>
<u n="2" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear/> history thing but it was oh what was it called? conflict in the modern age or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0417">oh right</u>
<u n="4" who="S0415">all about warfare and the wars Cold Wars and that kind of craic</u>
<u n="5" who="S0417">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0415">my god I'm only slurping tea now <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0417">long as you don't shupple shuffle <unclear/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0415" trans="overlap">how do you get these books off the shelf on purpose?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0417">yeah cos you're quite you're just going to get if you forget about <unclear/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0415">it's insane</u>
<u n="11" who="S0417">well I was going to talk a bit about <unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0415" trans="overlap">oh what are you going to talk about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? tell me what you're going to talk about</u>
<u n="13" who="S0417">be careful of be careful of that</u>
<u n="14" who="S0415" trans="overlap">unseating the recording device</u>
<u n="15" who="S0417">yeah not knocking it all the time and flapping pages too much <pause dur="short"/> erm anti-ageing do you know much about it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0415">like erm gerontology? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0417">erm I didn't know that's what it was called</u>
<u n="18" who="S0415">yes you did you're the one that told me oh no he didn't sorry isn't geriatrics like? isn't geriatrics treating illnesses relating to oldies eh old oldies old age?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0415">oldies but isn't gerontology preventing old age?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0417">you've got something on your leg <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0415">is it still there?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0417">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I would have thought gerontology is the study of geriatrics</u>
<u n="24" who="S0415">no</u>
<u n="25" who="S0417">illnesses</u>
<u n="26" who="S0415">sorry what did I say? <trunc>geriatr</trunc> yeah geriatrics is what did I say it was?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0417" trans="overlap">for old people geriatrics are old people</u>
<u n="28" who="S0415">yeah but geriatrics is the study of or is treating illnesses related to old age  gerontology is the prevention of things that come out of old age</u>
<u n="29" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0415">so it's like stopping your age</u>
<u n="31" who="S0417">oh I <trunc>did</trunc> I didn't know that</u>
<u n="32" who="S0415">least that's what your that bearded men <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says on the TED talk</u>
<u n="33" who="S0417">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah there seem to be a sort of a few different ways people are trying to <trunc>s</trunc> I don't know cos they cos you go on about <unclear>telomeres</unclear></u>
<u n="34" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear/> about what?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0417"><unclear>telomeres</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear>telomeres</unclear> at the end of erm erm telling me well people that have longer <unclear>telomeres</unclear> generally tend to think not they age slower but it's kind of like I've heard one person</u>
<u n="37" who="S0417" trans="overlap">you you know you don't have to do all the talking? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0415" trans="overlap">I don't have to do all the talking</u>
<u n="39" who="S0417">soon as <unclear/> oh god it would be really hard and you're like <vocal desc="laugh"/> soon as I try and say something</u>
<u n="40" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> why are you complaining? why are you complaining? you wanted me to talk I'm talking</u>
<u n="41" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0415" trans="overlap">like <unclear/> or I'll be run out of things and you'll have to take over</u>
<u n="43" who="S0417">this is my topic though</u>
<u n="44" who="S0415">but one thing it says like <unclear>telomeres</unclear> like <unclear/>analogies like one of those little things at the end of your shoelaces that stop them <unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0415">so instead of application like eventually you're <unclear/> isn't a lot of ageing to do with imperfect copies of your cells being made?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear/> so like <unclear>telomeres</unclear> kind of prevent that so long as they are better <unclear/> look younger and all that</u>
<u n="49" who="S0417">well eventually they run out as well don't they?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0415" trans="overlap">that's just one thing <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0417">don't know how how long that's going to be</u>
<u n="52" who="S0415" trans="overlap">over to you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0417">yeah but he was going on about that but it seems that even if we do that I think naturally only puts in like five to ten years even if we erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0415">it helps it's not</u>
<u n="55" who="S0417">I thought it was more than that actually yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0415"><trunc>w</trunc> but that guy called out seven major things we'd have to do <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0417"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0415">but as well</u>
<u n="59" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0415">his whole theory was that it would be kind of edited didn't say that right but it's like so as long as you get on like first day they add five years then ten years and then they'd keep enhancing those techniques till eventually they'd be adding on hundreds of years and it's like</u>
<u n="61" who="S0417">I suppose what you'd hope you'd hope though it's that the thing that got added on to your life like for example telling you you might then die of something unrelated to telomeres so you want whatever therapy</u>
<u n="62" who="S0415" trans="overlap">but you can always get run over by a bus <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0417">yeah I know do you think though? cos I was trying to imagine this is something I was also trying to do imagine a world where you could live for two hundred years and what? cos I think if you could live for two hundred years people would value life more but maybe I'm wrong</u>
<u n="64" who="S0415">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0417" trans="overlap">and we would be more safety-conscious with more care about people</u>
<u n="66" who="S0415">well in some ways safety conscious is surely is like I mean even if you went up to a hundred now if you wanted to live to a hundred then I'm going to die at twenty so</u>
<u n="67" who="S0417">well I I really when I went to <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0415" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0417">one of the things that struck me it just felt like life was cheap life was cheaper people expected to die earlier so people were taking risks that were quite shocking sometimes you know? it's just</u>
<u n="70" who="S0415" trans="overlap">oh I see what you mean kind of I'll be dead soon so what does it matter?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0417">well I suppose they weren't thinking like that I suppose most people just wanted to survive and live as long as they like but <unclear/> there seemed to be a kind of</u>
<u n="72" who="S0415">well if you want to to coin a phrase literary predictive</u>
<u n="73" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0415">literary predictive kind of model like in science fiction <unclear>can go a couple of ways</unclear> but that's there are major recurring themes in science fiction and it's often proven to be very predictive when it comes to the ways societies evolve and and it drives things in science that but like a lot of them there's a couple of things like where first of all you've got to move from like a scarcity model to a post-scarcity model like at the moment everyone's fighting over resources and things because resources are kind of getting scarce you need to get to a stage where you've got basically abundant cheap energy cos once you've abundant cheap energy then you can grow loads like then you start moving out of a scarcity model into a post-scarcity model where everyone's attitude begins to change because the same dynamics aren't at play in the sense obviously people are still human there are still the same kind of human characteristics but in terms of geopolitically like</u>
<u n="75" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0415">if you didn't if everybody could have as much food and energy as they want as much stuff as they had well then you wouldn't have to fight over those things</u>
<u n="77" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0415">and then you could like you know? devote your time to more purer pursuits and but that's <trunc>ki</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you know? <vocal desc="misc"/> but yeah I've always wanted since I was very very young I wanted to live forever and people people would go why do you want to live forever? that's just nuts I was surprised cos I thought everyone wanted to live forever but it's like nearly hardly anyone I talked to goes no like sorry hardly everyone <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc> nearly everyone I talked to goes no I've never come across somebody who's yeah I want to live forever too</u>
<u n="79" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0415">so I'm kind of going what the fuck alright for me it's just like it's like when you read about history and you read about all the amazing things that have happened over the last ten thousand years I mean can you imagine being a spectator at all of that?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0415">and like and then if you look at what's going to happen in the next ten thousand years and what you might see and experience</u>
<u n="83" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0415">on the other side if you're the only one who's living forever then everyone around you is dying or passing away and there's a lot of that's why kind of you need a that's why it becomes very difficult unless you have a everyone else living for a long time but then in another science fiction you've got or if you live so much people get bored and they just kind of want to go out they kind of <pause dur="short"/> they go into virtual worlds and hibernation or whatever wake me in ten thousand or wake me in a hundred wake me in five thousand years and if it gets exciting kind of</u>
<u n="85" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0415">but I think it would be amazing brilliant <pause dur="short"/> just think who the hell wouldn't want to live forever? you're just nuts if you don't want to live forever</u>
<u n="87" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0415">maybe not forever forever but at least an awful long time</u>
<u n="89" who="S0417">yeah <pause dur="long"/> well I suppose if these technologies were around to let other people live longer than at first they wouldn't be available to everyone would they? suppose depending who makes them</u>
<u n="90" who="S0415" trans="overlap">no there'd probably be eh kind of for the rich would be living forever but when you think of it like well what's the statistics about? <pause dur="short"/> like whatever you know? something like this is not exactly the one percent of the world own ninety-nine percent of the wealth kind of thing</u>
<u n="91" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0415">the world is already pretty fucked up like that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0417">so you know some people think that telomere is might be the key to ageing in cancer? <unclear/> erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0415">in what way?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0417">stops the process by which cells <trunc>es</trunc> so especially cancer cells lengthen their telomeres erm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0415"><trunc>w</trunc>what do you mean by? shortening them and making them go away is it? cancer</u>
<u n="97" who="S0417">cancer cells <trunc>w</trunc>when they replicate very prolifically erm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah and then if <pause dur="short"/> yep so if their if their so if their their ability to hold on to their telomeres is disruptive to the cancer cells then you can only ever grow so long so they just won't be able to grow it and like they grow at real really fast rates</u>
<u n="98" who="S0415" trans="overlap">isn't that dangerous cos you could accidentally do it to the rest of the <pause dur="short"/> the erm the cells in your body? <pause dur="short"/> there's something in this diagram here that I remember reading before oh yeah apparently in a thousand years from now most words currently spoken will be extinct</u>
<u n="99" who="S0417">most words?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0415">yeah due to the rapid evolution of language no single present day word will have survived a thousand years' time</u>
<u n="101" who="S0417">but we're speaking words that have been used two thousand years ago</u>
<u n="102" who="S0415" trans="overlap">no we're not they're all different slightly if you look at look into like Google and say define word like frippery there was frepe and all French that turned into frippery and then fripper they're constantly evolving and changing a lot of them are have origins of old words but <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0417">mm so they might be they might be able to understand it or would we be able to understand it? but it just would be</u>
<u n="104" who="S0415" trans="overlap">don't know did you ever watch that movie Cloud Atlas?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0415">do you know they all speak in a funny kind of?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0417" trans="overlap">that was quite isn't that by that fella? he lives here</u>
<u n="108" who="S0415">I don't know but do you know?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0417">I reckon he's tach he's tax dodging</u>
<u n="110" who="S0415">what?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0417">why would he go to live in?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0415">why would he live in the wonderful country you're currently living in is it?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0415">with with the people who are from that country that you're now just suddenly trashing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0417">well I</u>
<u n="116" who="S0415">smart move there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0417">yeah but why would he move here?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0415">why would who move here?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the fella <unclear/> whatever his name is</u>
<u n="120" who="S0415">what? many people really like this country it can be a bit boring but it's just for <trunc>s</trunc> like celebrities love this country cos lots of houses like Sarah Jessica Parker has a house up in <anon type="place"/> and nobody bothers her</u>
<u n="121" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0415">herself and Matthew whatever his name is <unclear/> they just come over and people go how's it going? and that's it like you know?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0415">don't tell but that's an unusual example but there are loads of celebrities who've put houses like tucked away in <anon type="place"/> and west of Ireland and and that stuff but <pause dur="short"/> like the tax exemption thing too now but that's only up to forty grand or something a year per person no?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0417">is it?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0415">remember we looked that up I was looking for artist exemption for my amazing tax avoidance scheme</u>
<u n="127" who="S0417">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh maybe you looked it up then</u>
<u n="128" who="S0415">but</u>
<u n="129" who="S0417">where we were both going to be painters</u>
<u n="130" who="S0415">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0417">still good</u>
<u n="132" who="S0415">it's yeah it's amazingly incredible erm legal</u>
<u n="133" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0415">spin</u>
<u n="135" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><trunc>exem</trunc> with horse horses and writing <unclear/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0415" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0417">no I'm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0415" trans="overlap">it's it's work well it's it's any kind of work like it can be sculpture oh <trunc>ho</trunc></u>
<u n="139" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><trunc>hors</trunc> be horses it's racing <unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0415">I know but that's that's <trunc>ridic</trunc> you see Charlie Haughey made the entire <unclear/> industry tax-free they didn't even have to submit a tax return stating what they were earning right?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0417">really?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0415">so it was like just minting it right and but now now it's still that way but I think they actually have to submit tax returns but it's still fucking ridiculous one section of the thing getting off <trunc>s</trunc> of the population getting off tax-free</u>
<u n="143" who="S0417">so what else did they say in like a thousand years? is that to show us in the future?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0415">ah this is a timeline of our future ah <pause dur="long"/> erm in two thousand years Greenland ice melted ice sheet completely melted with extreme global warming causing it to <unclear/> sea levels six metres high now</u>
<u n="145" who="S0417">so will it mean <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0415" trans="overlap">you know that comet Hale-Bopp that was around in nineteen ninety-seven?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0415">that's not coming back for another two thousand years</u>
<u n="149" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0415">two thousand three hundred so if you missed that tough</u>
<u n="151" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0415">like <pause dur="long"/> mm says here in a thousand years from now twenty-nine percent of twentieth century carbon dioxide will still be there thirty percent</u>
<u n="153" who="S0417">oh right</u>
<u n="154" who="S0415">here's one that's <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> in ten thousand years' time the earth's axis will have reversed summer and <trunc>wint</trunc>winter months reversed northern hemisphere suffers more extreme weather due to high percentage of <unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0417">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0415">eighteen thousand eight hundred and sixty years from now the lunar Islamic calendar and the solar Gregorian calendar will share the same year <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>taking their time</unclear> eighteen thousand years</u>
<u n="157" who="S0417">I wonder what it would be like actually <pause dur="short"/> do you think any of our <unclear/> will actually remember us? or even bother to find out about us?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0415">yeah because we can put all videos on YouTube which are going to be archived and catalogued forever more</u>
<u n="159" who="S0417">but do you think they'd bother? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0415">not every single one of them but I think it will become more culturally interesting to there'll be video archives of all your ancestors and families going back that's why in some ways social media is very important in a sense if you want to preserve something for your <trunc>des</trunc>descendants</u>
<u n="161" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah but the only video the only video of me is one doing the Irish games over the hurdling and falling on my face</u>
<u n="162" who="S0415" trans="overlap">well that doesn't even have a name on it so they won't know but my point is that's why in some ways it's a really good thing and not a narcissistic thing to put stuff up on social media of yourself and your family especially video cos imagine if you're ten thousand years from now or even a hundred years from now or two hundred years from now and you're looking back and go oh my god that's my great great great great great great look at her there talking and like I mean imagine if you could do that for people who are five hundred years ago now like be going wow that's amazing look what they're wearing</u>
<u n="163" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0415">like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0417">but I suppose it wouldn't be amazing to them cos they'd be used to it used to being able to see it as for us it would be amazing</u>
<u n="166" who="S0415">no the concept wouldn't be amazing but I still think actually seeing for the first time cos you're not gonna wake up and be a baby and then see all your ancestors going back like a thousand years in one day or anything</u>
<u n="167" who="S0417">mm mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0417"><unclear/> be weird to sort of see like you could probably see your great great great great great great great what if you looked exactly like one of them?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0415">mm?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0417">though you'd have a <trunc>l</trunc> you'd have a lot to choose from though that thing going back in family trees <unclear/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yeah you would</u>
<u n="173" who="S0417">if you go through your direct line <unclear/> even</u>
<u n="174" who="S0415">just be exciting</u>
<u n="175" who="S0417">mm <pause dur="long"/> at least they'll be reducing road accidents</u>
<u n="176" who="S0415">mm half a million years' time they'll <unclear/> into these reactors to show <unclear/> five hundred thousand years <pause dur="short"/> woah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0415">takes a million years for glass to decompose</u>
<u n="179" who="S0417">really?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0415">I suppose it's photodegradable is it? is glass photodegradable? or is that plastic? probably glass as well sorry it would have finally dissolved</u>
<u n="181" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh dissolved <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos it will just get into fine pieces dust glass dust</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="182" who="S0415">I don't know how true this is but it says in five million years' time the Y chromosome will have weakened to the point of crumbling making men impossible don't know what the hell that is but</u>
<u n="183" who="S0417">five million years?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0415">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't really have to worry about it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's basically just because it's it was a kind of anomaly in the first place isn't it?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0415">mm?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0417">the Y chromosome</u>
<u n="188" who="S0415">is it?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0417">yeah it was supposed to be X X and then something happened like an anomaly and that's what made men women were here first <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0415">in fifteen million years the Mediterranean will have vanished</u>
<u n="191" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> something mm?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0415">in fifteen million years the Mediterranean will have vanished Africa will collide with Eurasia</u>
<u n="193" who="S0417">it's still quite a long time for it to collide</u>
<u n="194" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0417">but then won't the water have risen anyway though? so <unclear/> much bigger maybe Italy will disappear</u>
<u n="196" who="S0415">don't know</u>
<u n="197" who="S0417"><unclear/> global warming</u>
<u n="198" who="S0415">say what?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0417">did you know?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0415">no I didn't</u>
<u n="201" who="S0417" trans="overlap">did you know about telomeres?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0415">maybe I did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0417">but erm do you think they just get shorter through age?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0415">I thought it was <vocal desc="misc"/> <trunc>d</trunc><trunc>d</trunc> sorry is this a like a question? or a quiz?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah it's a question not a quiz <unclear/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0415" trans="overlap">do they not get shorter the more times you replicate it?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0417">yeah but erm people seem to be born with different</u>
<u n="208" who="S0415">lengths</u>
<u n="209" who="S0417">lengths</u>
<u n="210" who="S0415">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0417">erm I think newborns have eight thousand base pairs and about three thousand base pairs in adults</u>
<u n="212" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0417">and only fifteen hundred in elderly people</u>
<u n="214" who="S0415">right</u>
<u n="215" who="S0417">but erm this person erm I think she was erm criticised for it she <trunc>j</trunc> I think she won a <unclear/> no <unclear/> quite a lot of awards for her work scientific work but she she looked into how stress affects telomere</u>
<u n="216" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0417">and erm she looked at chronically ill children erm and their <trunc>mo</trunc> their mothers mothers who have chronically ill children</u>
<u n="218" who="S0415">yeah?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0417">compared to the mothers who didn't erm and the more stressed they were there was more people who had chronically ill children erm and erm their telomeres became shorter lifetime than you would have expected</u>
<u n="220" who="S0415" trans="overlap">god it's just so</u>
<u n="221" who="S0417">so and then it said that and they said when I I don't know quite how long it took or how bad it <unclear/> the worst stressed it was an extra decade on their life off their life</u>
<u n="222" who="S0415">god</u>
<u n="223" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0415">so if you're stressing me I should just say get out of my face?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0417">yeah I was thinking the other way round actually</u>
<u n="226" who="S0415" trans="overlap">or I'll die the <trunc>o</trunc> the other way round? <unclear/> well vice versa it's supposed to be</u>
<u n="227" who="S0417">mm <unclear/> mm god</u>
<u n="228" who="S0415">actually <pause dur="short"/> you know erm here? so like this is going to be hard to describe <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0417">what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0415">it's too much like kind of data and information</u>
<u n="231" who="S0417">what was that thing about living longer though? that looked interesting</u>
<u n="232" who="S0415"><unclear/> things that affect living longer life quitting smoking and things like that</u>
<u n="233" who="S0417">mm <pause dur="long"/> god <unclear/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0415" trans="overlap">oh my god these are like common <trunc>mis</trunc> common misconceptions</u>
<u n="235" who="S0417">oh okay</u>
<u n="236" who="S0415">did you see what I did there?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0417">went in to <trunc>diff</trunc></u>
<u n="238" who="S0415" trans="overlap">no miss conceptions</u>
<u n="239" who="S0417">is that supposed to be funny?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0415">I don't know I thought it was funny anyway it's Vikings' horned helmets Vikings' horned helmets never actually existed created by a costume designer in the nineteenth century in the Wagner opera</u>
<u n="241" who="S0417" trans="overlap">you go ahead you go ahead and laugh</u>
<u n="242" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0417">it's funny cos</u>
<u n="244" who="S0415">completely made up</u>
<u n="245" who="S0417">did they erm did they have Viking helmets in Viking years?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0415">nope</u>
<u n="247" who="S0417">was it trying to be authentic do you think? apart from all the naked naked amazing people</u>
<u n="248" who="S0415" trans="overlap">I would imagine it is I would imagine it is trying to be authentic as any show would try what do you mean naked people? <unclear/> authentic</u>
<u n="249" who="S0417">naked lady just taking a very hot bath</u>
<u n="250" who="S0415">taking what?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> in the sea last time</u>
<u n="252" who="S0415">sea that was a symbolic thing where she was</u>
<u n="253" who="S0417">yeah right</u>
<u n="254" who="S0415">wait a minute</u>
<u n="255" who="S0417">I didn't think didn't think <unclear/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0415" trans="overlap">it was the philosophy that's that's <unclear/> my point in terms of the story she participated <unclear/> slave so it was a symbolic thing where she went into the lake a slave and came out a free woman and changed her clothes</u>
<u n="257" who="S0417">yeah that's what <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0415" trans="overlap">the fact that she was you know? bitchingly hot and sexy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0417" trans="overlap">amazing good body yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0415">just completely incidental to be honest</u>
<u n="261" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0415"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0417"><unclear/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0415">oh medieval chastity belts were not anti-adultery devices</u>
<u n="265" who="S0417">they weren't what?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0415">the <trunc>m</trunc><trunc>m</trunc>medieval chastity belts they weren't preventing adultery they were actually invented by <trunc>br</trunc>British people to prevent kind of what do they call it? dangerous masturbation</u>
<u n="267" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0415">there you go</u>
<u n="269" who="S0417">bit weird really <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0415"><vocal desc="misc"/> do you know sharks get skin cancer?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0417">sharks?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0415">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0417">no</u>
<u n="274" who="S0415">they do</u>
<u n="275" who="S0417">like so much that they die I mean bad skin cancer</u>
<u n="276" who="S0415" trans="overlap">they get <pause dur="short"/> does this mean that sharks don't get cancer? they do particularly skin cancer</u>
<u n="277" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0415"><vocal desc="misc"/> so yeah <unclear/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you know if you listen to this back you'd be talking a like about <unclear/> analysing or if they were analysing male to female kind of <vocal desc="laugh"/> you'd be totally dominant the whole time for like ninety percent talk</u>
<u n="280" who="S0415">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0417" trans="overlap">and when and when I when I talk they're usually probably it's that wouldn't guide the conversation sometimes and not even being responded to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0415">yeah what's that?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0417">very funny</u>
<u n="284" who="S0415">what are you saying?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0417">not really very funny at all</u>
<u n="286" who="S0415"><unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it changes depending on where I sit</u>
<u n="288" who="S0415">yeah it's it's kind of like</u>
<u n="289" who="S0417" trans="overlap">is it the <trunc>l</trunc> is it the left ear this time</u>
<u n="290" who="S0415">it's it's kind of what is it?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0417">it's usually the right ear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0415">so hang on I'll coin it well it's psycho selective aural disruption</u>
<u n="293" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0415">peace out</u>
<u n="295" who="S0417">so you could say it in poncy ways is it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0415">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0417">incredible what do you think the life expectancy was like I don't know erm in classical Greece?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0415">in classical Greece for who? <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0417" trans="overlap">erm for everybody</u>
<u n="300" who="S0415">er am I going to be shocked? or kind of is it? or could it be something I expect?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0417">just have a guess</u>
<u n="302" who="S0415">forty-eight</u>
<u n="303" who="S0417">twenty-eight</u>
<u n="304" who="S0415">fuck</u>
<u n="305" who="S0417">see the trouble is this almost all of these take into account infant mortality</u>
<u n="306" who="S0415">oh I see so there was tonnes of <trunc>infa</trunc></u>
<u n="307" who="S0417" trans="overlap">it skewers loads</u>
<u n="308" who="S0415">so basically if there's a high a very high mortality a skewing of the figures</u>
<u n="309" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0415">but so then like the average people the average age of people who didn't die before five say is probably like fifty</u>
<u n="311" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0415">or sixty or something?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0417">yeah should be like after the first like couple of years <unclear/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0415">I see</u>
<u n="315" who="S0417">mm god I didn't realise like the Palaeolithic times are saying thirty-three but that at age fifteen life expectancy was an additional thirty-nine so it's like fifty-five</u>
<u n="316" who="S0415">I see</u>
<u n="317" who="S0417">I would have thought some Palaeolithic people live longer I can't quite get my head around them being jumped up that much</u>
<u n="318" who="S0415">what? really? what about better medicine? nutrition? shelter? less wars? less</u>
<u n="319" who="S0417">yeah but I would have thought some Palaeolithic people might have good shelter and enough to eat</u>
<u n="320" who="S0415">that's why it's inept it's not it's not a</u>
<u n="321" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm I see <pause dur="short"/> well they say for example they say they looked at English aristocracy <unclear/> for example back in medieval Britain the life expectancy then? guess what</u>
<u n="322" who="S0415">for the aristocracy?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0417">no for general and then for the aristocracy</u>
<u n="324" who="S0415">including mortality rate <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0417">erm at birth yes it would</u>
<u n="326" who="S0415">forty-two</u>
<u n="327" who="S0417">thirty</u>
<u n="328" who="S0415">fuck</u>
<u n="329" who="S0417">that's that's really low for medieval times isn't it?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0415">yeah but it's still probably yeah <unclear/> infant mortality</u>
<u n="331" who="S0417">but if you if you were like if you'd survived till age twenty and you were a member of the aristocracy and you were a man</u>
<u n="332" who="S0415">mm and you were a man?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0417">yeah you could expect</u>
<u n="334" who="S0415" trans="overlap">cos basically having children kills you</u>
<u n="335" who="S0417">I don't know I suppose the figures they got would have been but erm er yeah maybe as well erm from twelve hundred to thirteen hundred just sixty-four years</u>
<u n="336" who="S0415"><unclear>I see</unclear></u>
<u n="337" who="S0417">and thirteen hundred to fourteen hundred forty-five cos the bubonic plague</u>
<u n="338" who="S0415">I see</u>
<u n="339" who="S0417">and then from then time on like around seventy so for ages blokes have been living till seventy if you're you know? <unclear/> but we've added on quite a lot of extra <unclear/> but you would have thought the aristocracy could have had loads even more than us maybe it's medical care that they really lacked</u>
<u n="340" who="S0415"><trunc>d</trunc> <vocal desc="misc"/> in the present?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0417">I mean they had loads of food and servants and warmer houses and things didn't they? but maybe they just didn't have good medical care</u>
<u n="342" who="S0415">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0417">I wonder what it was? what it was then? and what's the? where do you live longest? which country do you reckon in the world?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0415">Japan</u>
<u n="345" who="S0417">yeah and which?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0415">nailed it</u>
<u n="347" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like loads of countries <unclear/> in Africa it's at forty-five fifty thirty-five whatever I forget it's pretty low</u>
<u n="348" who="S0415">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0417">I suppose it takes into account infant mortality <pause dur="short"/> the Lancet says that Japanese life expectancy is due to</u>
<u n="350" who="S0415" trans="overlap">the what? The Lancet?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0417">The Lancet</u>
<u n="352" who="S0415">as opposed to The Lancet</u>
<u n="353" who="S0417">I was saying I was <trunc>ac</trunc></u>
<u n="354" who="S0415" trans="overlap">you're in Ireland you don't have to be posh like</u>
<u n="355" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I I was actually making a joke</u>
<u n="356" who="S0415">oh I see I see that was lost to me <unclear/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yes erm Japanese life expectancy due to</u>
<u n="358" who="S0415">fish</u>
<u n="359" who="S0417">diet and public health and</u>
<u n="360" who="S0415">taking care of the elderly</u>
<u n="361" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><trunc>e</trunc> equal opportunities</u>
<u n="362" who="S0415">in Japan?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0415">they treat women like shit traditionally in Japan in workplaces and things allegedly</u>
<u n="365" who="S0417">do they?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0415">yeah apparently</u>
<u n="367" who="S0417">oh well The Lancet says equal opportunities <unclear/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0415">but it's their diet <trunc>d</trunc> <trunc>l</trunc> really lacks red meat in a big way</u>
<u n="369" who="S0417">had loads of fish and that kind of thing</u>
<u n="370" who="S0415">god look at all the sugars sucrose lactose fructose glucose</u>
<u n="371" who="S0417">you know the oldest confirmed reported age of a human being?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0415">a hundred and twenty-one</u>
<u n="373" who="S0417">very close a hundred and twenty-two</u>
<u n="374" who="S0415">ah god imagine like if I was on some quiz</u>
<u n="375" who="S0417" trans="overlap">that's very close</u>
<u n="376" who="S0415">like for a million euros</u>
<u n="377" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0415">and I was ah be like that was of some woman was she French?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0417">yeah I think so Jeanne Calment</u>
<u n="380" who="S0415">Calment the rubbish in my head</u>
<u n="381" who="S0417">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0415">do you know this thing about diuretics? apparently the diuretic effect of caffeine is offset by the amount of water in the caffeinated drink</u>
<u n="383" who="S0417" trans="overlap">what? no erm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0415">sorry I didn't mean to</u>
<u n="385" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0415">yeah it doesn't say in the Bible that Satan rules hell <pause dur="short"/> stunned silence</u>
<u n="387" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I suppose if he was a fallen angel did he set up hell? or did he just go there? I can't remember</u>
<u n="388" who="S0415">but I don't know enough about the Bible but I do believe</u>
<u n="389" who="S0417">you're a Catholic</u>
<u n="390" who="S0415">I do believe that</u>
<u n="391" who="S0417">so am I</u>
<u n="392" who="S0415">yeah so</u>
<u n="393" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0415">withdraw that accusation cos it has no relevance but I do believe that</u>
<u n="395" who="S0417" trans="overlap">you went to church more than me</u>
<u n="396" who="S0415">are the seraphim angels?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0417">but he was an angel wasn't he Satan?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0415">no seraphim S E R A P H I M the seraphim</u>
<u n="399" who="S0417">mm I've no idea</u>
<u n="400" who="S0415" trans="overlap">they're maybe they're all angels but I just thought the fallen angels were the <trunc>on</trunc> basically <trunc>li</trunc> who live in hell <unclear/> continues didn't they rise up against god?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah well at least if eh the the angels fell down went to hell or formed it</u>
<u n="402" who="S0415" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0417">I don't know but I suppose it's probably always been there or is it not? was it the Garden of Eden? but then Adam and Eve just I don't <trunc>re</trunc> I'm confused now cos Adam and Eve</u>
<u n="404" who="S0415">angels are not human</u>
<u n="405" who="S0417">I know but Adam and Eve there was was a bit like they were saying that everything was lovely and abundant until Eve ate the apple that's when all the rot started</u>
<u n="406" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> but what's that got to do with Satan and the seraphim and all that?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0417">yeah I was I was wondering what it has to do with that cos it's like a thing over hell</u>
<u n="408" who="S0415" trans="overlap">oh I see I think it could be something the seraphim well you know? maybe seraphim were fallen <trunc>a</trunc> maybe they're not the demons they're what were they not fallen angels who wanted to save humanity against god's wishes or something?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0415">or when they were cast out down to walk the Earth forever I could be mixing up a whole load of crap probably in fairness</u>
<u n="411" who="S0417">do you know who John Sperling is?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0415">John who?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0417">John Sperling</u>
<u n="414" who="S0415">how do you <trunc>s</trunc>? how do you spell it?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0417" trans="overlap">or was <unclear/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0415">as in <trunc>Sper</trunc>ling</u>
<u n="417" who="S0417">S P E R L I N G</u>
<u n="418" who="S0415" trans="overlap">Sperling?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0417">Sperling</u>
<u n="420" who="S0415">John Sperling give me a hint</u>
<u n="421" who="S0417">he had loads of money</u>
<u n="422" who="S0415">he had loads of money?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0417">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0415">that's a that was that wasn't a hint that was terrible</u>
<u n="425" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0415">but eh</u>
<u n="427" who="S0417">he's a businessman a businessman</u>
<u n="428" who="S0415">did he do something? <unclear/> life or something?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0417">erm he founded a like a <trunc>u</trunc>University of Phoenix</u>
<u n="430" who="S0415">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0417" trans="overlap">and which is now part of an Apollo Group <pause dur="short"/> and made loads of money anyway he was quite eccentric <pause dur="short"/> erm and erm he was but he was born really poor in Missouri from a poor sharecropper family his mother was like a fundamentalist Christian and his dad worked on the railway he spent years</u>
<u n="432" who="S0415">to get away from the mother</u>
<u n="433" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he had this mad life where he spent years as a sailor and he wandered around as a hippie in the nineteen fifties</u>
<u n="434" who="S0415">uhu</u>
<u n="435" who="S0417">erm and then he got a degree and Masters that kind of thing <unclear/> PhD in Cambridge <unclear>down there</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> erm oh in history there you go so your fella might be</u>
<u n="436" who="S0415">sorry what?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0417"><trunc>h</trunc>his his erm PhD was actually on English history eighteenth century history</u>
<u n="438" who="S0415">how long would it take one person to make the Great Pyramids?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0417" trans="overlap">that's funny <pause dur="short"/> one person?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0417">thousand years</u>
<u n="442" who="S0415">four million <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0417">oh my god</u>
<u n="444" who="S0415">apparently</u>
<u n="445" who="S0417" trans="overlap">they had they had loads of slaves didn't they?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0415">obviously they have like you know a very <unclear/> you'd have to question the veracity of that figure</u>
<u n="447" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah but anyway this bloke he put loads of money into erm immortality cos he believed he wanted to be immortal as well like you</u>
<u n="448" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0417">but unfortunately he died erm I bet he's I bet he's got to get his brain his head frozen</u>
<u n="450" who="S0415">see yeah er well <pause dur="short"/> I still believe maybe some kind of amber resonance put the whole lot in there see if you freeze things you get this crystallisation process in the in in the kind of liquids of things and the thread to cell membranes</u>
<u n="451" who="S0417">oh <unclear/> science fiction</u>
<u n="452" who="S0415" trans="overlap">so like then you'd nanites as well to replair repair all that shit as well as defrosting and things but</u>
<u n="453" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0415">that's why I'm more going maybe for just some kind of quick <unclear/> do you know? what's the thing they do in food where flash freeze but you can't have freezing just saying</u>
<u n="455" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0415">just has to be kind of hermetic is that a thing? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0417">he spent twenty million dollars trying to clone a dog called Missy</u>
<u n="458" who="S0415">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0417">seven years</u>
<u n="460" who="S0415">and what was the point of that?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0417">god the project was called Missy Missy <unclear/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0415">erm okay but what was he trying to do? what was in it for him?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0417">I don't know because maybe it was his dog anyway was supposed to put a loads of money to immortality research that kind of thing but then he died and he didn't</u>
<u n="464" who="S0415">percentage of the world's oceans that have been explored? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0417">two percent</u>
<u n="466" who="S0415">no but in the right kind of vibe</u>
<u n="467" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they're huge aren't they? <unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0415" trans="overlap">five percent</u>
<u n="469" who="S0417">in the middle of the oceans they are just so deep and every big mountain range is <unclear/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0415">er yes</u>
<u n="471" who="S0417"><unclear/> the plates moving apart and all the bubbling volcanic activity has made a huge amount of <unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0415" trans="overlap">basically all continents are surely just big mountains popping out of the water <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0417">yeah but in between them you know? like in like in the middle of the African America</u>
<u n="474" who="S0415">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0417">they're moving apart all the time <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0415">oh right</u>
<u n="477" who="S0417">does it matter? <pause dur="short"/> so where do? where do you want to go for a one night's break with me?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0415">one night?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0417">could be two could be really really <unclear>distant</unclear></u>
<u n="480" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> play my cards right erm I don't know</u>
<u n="481" who="S0417">you don't like going away at all do you?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0415">it's not that I don't like going away it's just I'm the worst person in the world in that sense like left to my own devices I'd quite happily go on holidays and just kind of work on projects and things that I like</u>
<u n="483" who="S0417" trans="overlap">you're autistic</u>
<u n="484" who="S0415">cos the</u>
<u n="485" who="S0417" trans="overlap">do you have holidays in your head?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0415">no no just not see I don't subscribe to this it's not the actually going to exotic places can be very interesting and kind of erm what other words with inish inish enjoyable but like I think I don't subscribe to this sole view that like people are obsessed okay <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> went on holidays oh we have we have to go away we have to go somewhere and look it so there's a guy at work now he's gone on holidays with two young children only one and three for two weeks down in <anon type="place"/> okay that's fine you know? it's but like it'll be hard work and it would be very but for me like this <trunc>th</trunc>there's more to <trunc>goi</trunc> to going on <trunc>hol</trunc> taking holidays or vacation should be about more to do with doing things that you like to do that you <trunc>co</trunc> you don't get time to do when you work and not necessarily just travelling to somewhere different cos it should be about enjoying the time that you have to do the things that you like not this kind of mad arms race we must go somewhere let's go oh I haven't been there yet <unclear/> like you know? no no</u>
<u n="487" who="S0417" trans="overlap">if you if you weren't working would you be interested in going to other places just anyway?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0415">if I was independently wealthy and kind of had all the time in the world then yeah I'd spend a portion of that time going to other places because they could be very interesting but as well I'm also</u>
<u n="489" who="S0417" trans="overlap">say if you retired would you? would you go away every now and again?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0415" trans="overlap">lots it would depend how much money I had <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0415">but but as well like I think some people are a bit mad I mean like mad too like in the sense that we talked about risk earlier on like</u>
<u n="493" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0415" trans="overlap">a lot of parts of the world are extremely dangerous to be honest like you know?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0415">most parts it's like you know? the fact that</u>
<u n="497" who="S0417">but you usually love taking risks</u>
<u n="498" who="S0415" trans="overlap">the fact that the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0417">you <trunc>dri</trunc> you drive fast</u>
<u n="500" who="S0415">I don't drive fast <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're you're the worst you're just you're scared getting into a car you're you can be a judge of someone driving fast or not when like you know? you're terrified of being in a car <unclear/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I know but you generally like taking risks <unclear/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0415">I wouldn't agree with it but like I when I'm driving I don't take risks</u>
<u n="503" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0415">when I'm on that motorway there I would go a hundred and twenty kilometres an hour which is the speed limit and not feel that that's fast cos all the other traffic is going and it's kind of built for that kind of thing but like there are drivers drivers take risks or do crazy things like they try to overtake</u>
<u n="505" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0415">in crazy situations</u>
<u n="507" who="S0417">no I know you don't I know you don't</u>
<u n="508" who="S0415" trans="overlap">I'll never do anything like that like I want to live in that sense like but but anyway</u>
<u n="509" who="S0417" trans="overlap">but you you take the mick out of me sometimes for not taking risks so</u>
<u n="510" who="S0415">ah yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you you have to wait for a green man to cross the road and that's kind of <unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0417" trans="overlap">what's the what's the problem with waiting for the green man?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0415" trans="overlap">because cos <unclear/> no but but our our our like</u>
<u n="513" who="S0417" trans="overlap">but we pay but we pay for this safe system</u>
<u n="514" who="S0415">coming back to your to your to your to your erstwhile imminent friend doctor <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or whatever his name is</u>
<u n="515" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I <trunc>d</trunc> I do <unclear/> cross the road without a green man</u>
<u n="516" who="S0415">like</u>
<u n="517" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0415">that's what I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> close enough</u>
<u n="519" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="misc"/> yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0415">like if he was measuring it in morts I'm sure he'd be going actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know what? crossing the road without the light being green is like you know? little or no extra risk</u>
<u n="521" who="S0417" trans="overlap">actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says he doesn't erm yeah he doesn't take huge amounts of car journeys cos car journeys are up there</u>
<u n="522" who="S0415">we're talking about crossing the road <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0417" trans="overlap">with the risks I'm not that bad crossing the road I manage to cross roads that I <unclear/> there is no roads I don't manage to cross</u>
<u n="524" who="S0415" trans="overlap">I just think like I just think like as an average barometer of whether someone is risky or not you're the wrong judge I think because you tend to be very risk-averse</u>
<u n="525" who="S0417">mm okay I don't but but yeah no I was just <trunc>as</trunc> anyway back to the</u>
<u n="526" who="S0415">back to the holidays</u>
<u n="527" who="S0417">yeah before you started beating me with the risk risk <unclear/> whatever it is</u>
<u n="528" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I think you <trunc>s</trunc> I think you'll find you started it by accusing me of being a very risky driver <vocal desc="laugh"/> to which I took great umbrage to</u>
<u n="529" who="S0417">no I don't say you're a very risky driver but you do</u>
<u n="530" who="S0415">drive fast</u>
<u n="531" who="S0417">you do drive fast you</u>
<u n="532" who="S0415" trans="overlap">on a motorway</u>
<u n="533" who="S0417">you you like being a a well like in the trampoline you're you you do you're you like jumping high</u>
<u n="534" who="S0415">yeah yeah yeah okay but</u>
<u n="535" who="S0417">you like running fast</u>
<u n="536" who="S0415" trans="overlap">but I think you're <trunc>confu</trunc> like I would never in the trampoline consider doing a flip or anything like that</u>
<u n="537" who="S0417">yeah I know no I know that</u>
<u n="538" who="S0415" trans="overlap">like <unclear/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0417">I'm not I'm not actually being very critical</u>
<u n="540" who="S0415" trans="overlap">I know but but I think that there's a nuance to it in the sense no I know you're not being critical</u>
<u n="541" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0415">but there's a nuance that okay I just use the trampoline for bouncing in a very straightforward way I've tried to bounce as high as I want but I don't use it for doing flips or anything ridiculous like like</u>
<u n="543" who="S0417" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="544" who="S0415">I think ah I I'll do things within the confines of the regulations of <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="545" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0415">like you know I like going on roller coasters</u>
<u n="547" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0415" trans="overlap">there's a sense that because usually they're very well <trunc>ma</trunc></u>
<u n="549" who="S0417" trans="overlap">usually <vocal desc="laugh"/> apart from <vocal desc="laugh"/> yesterday</u>
<u n="550" who="S0415" trans="overlap">but eh but that's one of the few accidents you've ever heard of like</u>
<u n="551" who="S0417">I know</u>
<u n="552" who="S0415">give me like they usually the big ones usually very good safety regimes very well designed</u>
<u n="553" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah I would have thought Alton Towers is probably better than the piers</u>
<u n="554" who="S0415">and I still can't figure out how fecking you can have a crash on a roller coaster when there's only one set of cars going at a time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0417">well see maybe they were like they released a second set say by accident</u>
<u n="556" who="S0415">yeah but then <unclear/> safety features built in that kind of</u>
<u n="557" who="S0417" trans="overlap">at the wrong time</u>
<u n="558" who="S0415">within proximity things and all kinds of stuff</u>
<u n="559" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0415">that's why <unclear/> but anyway back to the holiday thing you see I I'm like at odds with the vast majority of people</u>
<u n="561" who="S0417" trans="overlap">but you're</u>
<u n="562" who="S0415">where they like for me for me a holiday in inverted quotes right or is like</u>
<u n="563" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0415">time off to do whatever the fuck I like <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's a holiday right? now I think it possibly in the strictest sense of the word a vacation or something like <trunc>the</trunc> that's another word did mean actually travelling</u>
<u n="565" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0415">or some <unclear/> but that's different the like I don't if holidays means actually the the original word but like so it's <trunc>l</trunc> I like</u>
<u n="567" who="S0417">but we get like a night or two with me</u>
<u n="568" who="S0415">but that's different that's not <trunc>nec</trunc> that's the but that's taking time apart</u>
<u n="569" who="S0417" trans="overlap">and that's there that's apart from our <trunc>holi</trunc> our other holiday</u>
<u n="570" who="S0415">that's taking time out for ourselves that's not saying that's kind of different in a way to a holiday in my mind like you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0415">like in <trunc>ire</trunc> no can be there can be both my point is like they're not necessarily erm have to be</u>
<u n="573" who="S0417" trans="overlap">you're not going to be miserable are you? you will enjoy it you will enjoy it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0415">erm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0417">oh</u>
<u n="576" who="S0415">do I generally tend to be miserable if we're away?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0417">sometimes you can <trunc>s</trunc>sometimes you can be</u>
<u n="578" who="S0415" trans="overlap">careful now careful <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> less than enthusiastic</u>
<u n="579" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="S0415"><vocal desc="laugh"/> see I think that reflects as well though I mean you're an you've kind of always been an avid explorer and traveller like and you really really enjoy it I'm probably I could probably <vocal desc="misc"/> look I love history and things like that and I <unclear/> but I could probably take it or leave it it's no reflection on you it's more a reflection on</u>
<u n="581" who="S0417">yeah but even if we're say doing things like eating lunch that kind of thing isn't it just nice doing that with me anyway wherever we are?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0415"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>do</trunc><trunc>do</trunc>do you remember that Dara O Briain thing? where he'd go <vocal desc="laugh"/> no actually that was more <unclear/> I'm more it's a trap like eh obviously it's going anywhere with you is a splendid what's the word? eh</u>
<u n="583" who="S0417">opportunity just to</u>
<u n="584" who="S0415" trans="overlap">not opportunity splendid <pause dur="long"/> kind of <pause dur="short"/> splendid</u>
<u n="585" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you can't even think of the word</u>
<u n="586" who="S0415" trans="overlap">no there's a particular kind of <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> it's just a splendid thing in itself</u>
<u n="587" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0417">you know?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0415">it's kind of erm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0417">there is one <trunc>pla</trunc> you could I was <unclear/> there was some places you could go where you say you can do kayaking as well that kind of thing</u>
<u n="591" who="S0415">eh see this is what I'm saying about you you're very conscientious about what other people want to do</u>
<u n="592" who="S0415">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0417">like</u>
<u n="594" who="S0415">of course cos I want you to enjoy yourself too</u>
<u n="595" who="S0415">yeah but but you see <unclear/> strange kind of like like no no and <trunc>tha</trunc> and that's actually sweet like there's nothing wrong with that but I mean it's</u>
<u n="596" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0415">kind of eh <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> it's in some ways it's <trunc>k</trunc> like no I wouldn't normally worry about that kind of thing if I want to go kayaking then it's up to me to go kayaking in my own time when I want and it shouldn't be down to you to fucking wrap it into your holidays just cos like just cos I'm too lazy to get off my own ass and do it like</u>
<u n="598" who="S0417">it's more like I know you're not always the easiest to kind of feel like you've been <unclear/> if I know that you're doing one thing that you'll like it kind of makes me feel better it does actually help me <pause dur="short"/> as long as you go go along with it feeling alright about it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0415">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> see I don't really <pause dur="short"/> I just think people overthink all these things <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0417">but I know that before say if I've gone away then erm I found it a bit of a burden in the end knowing that there's not a lot of things we're doing that you really like</u>
<u n="601" who="S0415" trans="overlap">so you've gone away or we've gone away</u>
<u n="602" who="S0417">we've gone away together and then in the end I quite liked being able to do one or two things that I know you like cos it actually just makes me feel a bit better</u>
<u n="603" who="S0415">mm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0417">otherwise I feel overburdened so you could just do it for me</u>
<u n="605" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0415">so</u>
<u n="607" who="S0417">to just help me enjoy myself</u>
<u n="608" who="S0415" trans="overlap">like hang on so to make you not feel guilty you do things that I enjoy but I can just do them to make you happy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0415">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/> doesn't isn't it essentially contradictory?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0417">it's just</u>
<u n="612" who="S0415" trans="overlap">I want you to enjoy yourself but I want you to do it to keep me happy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0417">yeah because you <unclear/> no no I don't use it <unclear/> and then I just and then I do end up feeling overburdened and then it does take out my enjoyment if it puts in a kind of clearer way</u>
<u n="614" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>th</trunc> maybe this is the core of my point about things and it's not necessarily a very thought-out point or something that I will go to war to defend right? but <trunc>thi</trunc>this blending of different objectives which again isn't necessarily a bad thing right but like it's kind of like okay take the holiday and spending time together and doing activities like yeah it's amazing if you can blend all those three things together but like sometimes need it for yourself no not for yourself like like I think sometimes people put themselves under too much pressure to try and get them all together <trunc>ra</trunc>rather than kind of go allocating different times to those different kind of activities it's like oh my god</u>
<u n="615" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0415">it's like now when people get married no we have to have the best wedding ever we got to have this we got to have that we got to do this funky crazy dance that everyone thinks is cool</u>
<u n="617" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0415">like you know? rather than just now I'm not saying that can't be amazing and brilliant at a wedding</u>
<u n="619" who="S0417">yeah no I know what you mean</u>
<u n="620" who="S0415">but like I suppose my key point</u>
<u n="621" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> your key point you're so funny sometimes</u>
<u n="622" who="S0415"><vocal desc="laugh"/> my key point really is that I think people are very different to each other often I don't mean the couples necessarily I just mean in general and sometimes it can be easier to just <pause dur="short"/> understand and work with the differences rather than trying to make them rather than trying to get rid of the differences <unclear/> trying to say</u>
<u n="623" who="S0417">I suppose it depends on it like so if you were never going to go away together then I don't just end up going away with other people all the time and in the end it would just actually it would kind of cause problems so I think there are some things that would</u>
<u n="624" who="S0415">cos you'd be off shagging around the world is it?</u>
<u n="625" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0415">okay but let me rephrase that so okay but what if we? okay but okay but here's my point but and again I'm not actually trite about you saying that I'm more going</u>
<u n="628" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0415">if we never went away travelling together and you always had to do it yourself and we never had time where we went off and just had some nice time with each other</u>
<u n="630" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0415">like what I'm trying to say really is that if you had plenty of time where we went off and did something nice with each other but we didn't travel together possibly that and I don't mean you I'm just this is just an example</u>
<u n="632" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0415">possibly then that would be fine but it's where you've got the absence of both where it becomes problematic</u>
<u n="634" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0415">does that make sense?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0417">oh yeah I mean <unclear/> I don't think</u>
<u n="637" who="S0415" trans="overlap">whereas obviously if you can do them all together that's even better still but</u>
<u n="638" who="S0417">yeah I mean I suppose if we were one of the couples right which a lot of people are where they they they feel like they have to do everything together and they don't do anything apart then probably wouldn't be here now would we? because there's plenty of things that we we do independently you know? we're relatively kind of independent like that probably <trunc>un</trunc> more unusually than most cubbies are couples aren't actually as as independent so</u>
<u n="639" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> so what you're saying is basically we're just a bad fit for each other</u>
<u n="640" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0415">that's the nub of your point then is it?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0417">erm well we could <trunc>d</trunc> go down that road if you really want to <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh you're flapping pages loads</u>
<u n="643" who="S0415">apparently the average global life expectancy in nineteen hundred was thirty-one and in two thousand and eleven it's seventy that's shockingly alarmingly progressive</u>
<u n="644" who="S0417">yeah that <unclear>must be</unclear></u>
<u n="645" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear/> was basically slowly ran then it's kind of if it's that kind of curve that would tie into the whole extending life and gerontology thing this is how I bring this conversation from where it started all the way back</u>
<u n="646" who="S0417" trans="overlap">no <trunc>beca</trunc> no because <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah but you'd already be like fifty-five or something to seventy-five really</u>
<u n="647" who="S0415" trans="overlap">but my point is the curve is accelerating</u>
<u n="648" who="S0417">erm yeah but not as much as you'd think because the infant <trunc>morta</trunc>mortality is <trunc>a</trunc> lots of babies were stillborn</u>
<u n="649" who="S0415" trans="overlap">oh you're saying that's skewing the figures?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0415">saying now we've got a very low infant mortality but yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0417">I mean women were having like eight children and expecting you know a couple of those to die in their early years which is kind of</u>
<u n="653" who="S0415">so we're actually not living longer it's just that</u>
<u n="654" who="S0417">we are living longer</u>
<u n="655" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yeah we are living <trunc>l</trunc> but to the extent that the figures say it's more that more <trunc>ba</trunc> all the babies are surviving</u>
<u n="656" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0415">that's what the <trunc>commu</trunc> <unclear/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I mean it's amazing <unclear/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0415" trans="overlap">I let you win that point <unclear/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but it's amazing isn't it? I mean like erm babies born a few months earlier are even surviving now but the sort of the</u>
<u n="661" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0417">they're increasing the infant sort of expectation of survival as babies expectation of <trunc>survi</trunc> that <trunc>mu</trunc> that's like that's probably gone off the curve isn't it? so accelerated a lot <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0415">god <pause dur="short"/> four and a half million years ago the Earth's temperature exceeded the melting point of iron which is why all the iron <unclear/> turned into liquid flowed to the centre of the planet heated into <unclear/> lighter elements such as <unclear/> and then formed a sort of mantle crust <unclear/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0417">I know it's a very hot volatile place isn't it now? I think we should get erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> assessed</u>
<u n="665" who="S0415">assessed?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0417">yeah not as in kind of <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know? hello and who are you? and</u>
<u n="667" who="S0415">assessed for what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0417">I don't know</u>
<u n="669" who="S0415" trans="overlap">assessed under what criteria?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I suppose there's a few things we could either I've risen away like if if there was endless money and loads of time we'd be hearing his speech and erm like his little autistic tendencies but they're all</u>
<u n="671" who="S0415" trans="overlap"><unclear/> cut to the chase and have you researched this? and do you know what the options are already? cos usually you have and you do</u>
<u n="672" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0417">yeah I have some it's just I mean</u>
<u n="674" who="S0415">okay and if you were to</u>
<u n="675" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I don't really know which one</u>
<u n="676" who="S0415">okay but probably you've probably narrowed it down to three into parts and fucking ridiculous research behind it so of those three how much would they roughly cost and where would they be?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0417">erm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0415">cos I know you know I just know you know</u>
<u n="679" who="S0417">you you know that <anon type="place"/> that you used for last time how much they cos I looked at them and they didn't seem to have that whole</u>
<u n="680" who="S0415" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0417"><unclear/> well they had some lists of tests they didn't actually have a speech kind of testers place maybe assessments so I don't know how much it will be</u>
<u n="682" who="S0415" trans="overlap">sure it's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to work as an OT she used to work down in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0415">she she said to me one day they were better like she was better but then she would <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0417">what? the ones in <anon type="place"/> are better <unclear/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yeah but I I don't know anything about it</u>
<u n="687" who="S0417" trans="overlap">are they? is there one in the city as well?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0415">is there?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0417">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> they do a erm like a autism test for two hundred and fifty euros but it's just it's not really erm it's just a</u>
<u n="690" who="S0415">do you get a cert saying autistic not autistic <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0417">no I know you don't you</u>
<u n="692" who="S0415" trans="overlap">or do you slot it on a spectrum?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0417">it's more of a kid of a erm <pause dur="short"/> a parameter I don't know</u>
<u n="694" who="S0415">but is there like?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0417" trans="overlap">it's not a diagnostic test <pause dur="short"/> see I don't know about his hearing but there could be something in his hearing I mean I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't really think there's huge problems with him really</u>
<u n="696" who="S0415" trans="overlap">no but he needs to talk within the next months in a big way or then we'll kind of be worried</u>
<u n="697" who="S0417">I just think this <trunc>may</trunc> I think he will I think his speech is delayed and well I don't know whether</u>
<u n="698" who="S0415">you should try that you were looking for icons The Noun Project dot com</u>
<u n="699" who="S0417">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh I actually did find loads of icons free on the web but</u>
<u n="700" who="S0415"><unclear/> but anyway</u>
<u n="701" who="S0417">well I do know I mean I suppose there's two things of thought we could just wait and in in all I think I think if we waited and did nothing I think he'd be kind of alright but then if there's a possibility he's got something mild then we might be able to help him a bit more I don't know</u>
<u n="702" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0417">cos it's only it's so hard so hard to say isn't it?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0415" trans="overlap">sorry how much did she say? did she say how much it cost?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0417">it's two hundred and fifty euros for the <unclear/> test</u>
<u n="706" who="S0415">you don't get a free kind of consultation where you're in for ten minutes cos they think</u>
<u n="707" who="S0417">yeah I see yeah yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0415">do you usually get referred?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0417">and see if I went to the doctor again I think it would be too I don't know if</u>
<u n="710" who="S0415">the doctor's clueless <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0417">the doctors and you know those nurses or whatever they completely they haven't even got back to me to do his two years' assessment even though I've asked twice</u>
<u n="712" who="S0415">mm mm</u>
<u n="713" who="S0417">and and they were I don't really have loads of faith in but I mean that's another</u>
<u n="714" who="S0415">that's another hour's conversation <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0417" trans="overlap">that's another yeah that's <unclear/> another avenue you could go down say look I think his speech is delayed blah blah blah and they might refer us to somebody and then like erm</u>
<u n="716" who="S0415">but yeah there's a there there's a downside there's worrying <unclear/> referred us to three more things that cost us a fortune that really I don't know it'd have to be balanced</u>
<u n="717" who="S0417">mm yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0415">probably can't hurt to have a conversation with with a <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0417">well</u>
<u n="720" who="S0415">I mean I'd quite happily ring them and have a conversation with them <unclear/> on the phone</u>
<u n="721" who="S0417">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think to be assisted in any of those that would still cost money but yeah yeah yeah maybe you should do that</u>
<u n="722" who="S0415">no just they might go well you know what? bring him in for ten minutes and we'll tell you whether we've had any whether we think he should have an assessment you know? they might just say something like that</u>
<u n="723" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0415">you know what I mean like? it's very hard <trunc>li</trunc>like cos I presume people are generally referred to them</u>
<u n="725" who="S0417">I suppose so but even then they probably need to be a team of <trunc>pe</trunc> I mean yeah maybe you're right but they probably need to be a team of people to be able to think anyway</u>
<u n="726" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yeah but they have the different people in there and things like <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0417">mm <pause dur="short"/> I suppose what we probably need probably isn't there but yeah maybe that's a good first call if you just call them</u>
<u n="728" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yeah but at least they could go yeah we've seen loads of kids we're not worried about him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0417">well I'd I imagine last few wouldn't be that worried about him but part well I suppose part of me is thinking a little bit if it was a question of money and we just missed you know? we missed a</u>
<u n="730" who="S0415" trans="overlap">you're thinking you're thinking of early intervention</u>
<u n="731" who="S0417">yeah or maybe</u>
<u n="732" who="S0415">the importance of</u>
<u n="733" who="S0417">yeah <unclear/> couple of years off school and erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="734" who="S0415">yeah but like if we tried it like I definitely think like spending two hundred quid now to get is better than spending having to spend more or do a lot more or do a lot more work</u>
<u n="735" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0415">when there's more damage done</u>
<u n="737" who="S0417">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0415" trans="overlap">once like this what I think you know none of us are seriously worried</u>
<u n="739" who="S0417">but <unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0415" trans="overlap">he's special but special in a sense that like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="741" who="S0417" trans="overlap">no I'm not really worried</u>
<u n="742" who="S0415">but like</u>
<u n="743" who="S0417">and the amount of like like even in the past week he seems to be getting things like no and look he knows what look <trunc>me</trunc> he knows what a lot of things mean so erm</u>
<u n="744" who="S0415">and as well like he's interacting like in the last month or six weeks with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> every night like in the playpen</u>
<u n="745" who="S0417">yeah he bonds really well only with a few of us but he's not I can't imagine not being <unclear/> I mean somebody who's severely autistic for example would be like <trunc>n</trunc>not wanting to have people anywhere near them and having eye contact and not</u>
<u n="746" who="S0415" trans="overlap">yeah he's very cuddly and</u>
<u n="747" who="S0417">yeah and so I don't think he's severe in <trunc>an</trunc> or somebody who's severely deaf would have would not be yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0415" trans="overlap">like he's funny and humorous</u>
<u n="749" who="S0417">not be able to say something if somebody with severe speech thinks whatever one of those he's not</u>
<u n="750" who="S0415">but he can say every word under the sun</u>
<u n="751" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0415">he just doesn't couldn't be arsed</u>
<u n="753" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah but I I suppose part of me cos I was wondering whether sometimes I think with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> maybe I should have gotten him assessed earlier maybe maybe it was nothing too but I think sometimes I struggled on where somebody you need a bit more with than other people and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a bit like that but in different ways like the things that he he's doesn't quite get that other kids can get I mean I think they're both really enjoyable</u>
<u n="754" who="S0415" trans="overlap">and this obsession with screaming when people are talking</u>
<u n="755" who="S0417">yeah he's really sensitive to sound and erm have to do quite a lot of things again and again with him like the alphabet again and again and again <unclear/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0415">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah but you know? he's quite he's <trunc>extr</trunc> he's extreme that way but erm I think he's breaking out of it now but hopefully erm but he likes ordering things but yeah I'm not really worried about him just just maybe it's better to give him give him a kind of head start I don't know I mean there there's this this group that I've erm I've found which is is a little bit of a mad American group full of mums whose kids seem to be like learning PhD PhDs</u>
<u n="758" who="S0415" trans="overlap">Hyper Legacy dot com</u>
<u n="759" who="S0417">yeah Hyper Legacy and they're all full of kids who can read early but they're all all obsessed or interested in numbers and letters early but have speech delay so they're they're like just like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0415">do they all speak eventually?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0417">yeah see a lot of them were saying you know? they were diagnosed autistic and they were erm and then it just all those autistic <trunc>ten</trunc>tendencies just kind of disappeared after like the age of seven</u>
<u n="762" who="S0415">I think dissipated is a nice word</u>
<u n="763" who="S0417">dissipated yeah and there's some people who seem to have kids who are autistic and it there's no there's not really so much out there he can tell a lot between them mm</u>
<u n="764" who="S0415">so</u>
<u n="765" who="S0417">and there's some kids who just seem to be like that but they didn't have speech delay they were just normal and they just weren't very bright <unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="766" who="S0415">indeed</u>
<u n="767" who="S0417"><vocal desc="sigh"/> ah ah we did well</u>
<u n="768" who="S0415"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0417">erm but anyway so is that? erm so a lot of them are sort of fighting for it to be a distinct erm <unclear/> that I mean I don't really understand how like <unclear/> just need to be <unclear/> kid really early and they'll be <unclear/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0415">yeah</u>
<u n="771" who="S0417">but he seems like he was he's had quite a lot of difficulty either that or she was <unclear/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0415">mm</u>
<u n="773" who="S0417">really going overboard with how much time she spent with him <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0415">oh my god it's five to ten</u>
<u n="775" who="S0417">oh well <pause dur="short"/> so anyway</u>
<u n="776" who="S0415">so <pause dur="short"/> so matter of fact job done</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
