<text id="SBVQ">
<header>
		<rec_length>2:05:09</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0049</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Business, marketing, beauty products, buying and selling on the internet, family, holiday plans, dimensions and measurements</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking mainly about the development of a small business called Honest Skincare.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements, buying/selling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0049">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>27 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Small business owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Where was I? Huh</u>
<u n="2" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> so he's just invested in somebody?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so he's just invested in this guy who makes those magnetic boards for dyslexic students</u>
<u n="4" who="S0049">how long <trunc>w</trunc> how long ago was that?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">quite recent <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> noisy aeroplane <pause dur="short"/> um tut and so you know I imagine that he's got stockpiles of cash that he's willing to invest in people <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about your candles and the wax and the organic</u>
<u n="6" who="S0049">ah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">you can put it on your skin afterwards and</u>
<u n="8" who="S0049">and <trunc>d</trunc> what did she say?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">and I told her what else did I say? Oh I told her about the exfoliator that you can um</u>
<u n="10" who="S0049">dry it off</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">yeah that <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="12" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">yeah that's oil-based not well gel-based not shower cream-based <pause dur="short"/> and she sounded really oo that's what a novel product</u>
<u n="14" who="S0049">oh did she?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">and I explained all about your skin problems and that being you know the one of the impetuses behind</u>
<u n="16" who="S0049">oh</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">you setting up your business <pause dur="short"/> and yeah so she said give him a call or send him a text message to see if at least you know you can get er <trunc>mee</trunc> meet up <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="18" who="S0049">that'd be great</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">if</u>
<u n="20" who="S0049">where do they live?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">they live in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0049">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> so close</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">not far from me <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> and so I don't know he I know he's quite busy <pause dur="short"/> but maybe one of the days when you haven't got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">we could go round together and</u>
<u n="28" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> that'd be great hon <pause dur="short"/> cos I've um today I've <trunc>st</trunc> I've just sent off to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0049">all the labels <pause dur="short"/> she sent sent me them all through so she sent all the labels but there were loads of um tut changes <pause dur="short"/> for instance there was she'd put and signs instead of the cross signs and things like that <pause dur="short"/> and um oh well I'll show you <pause dur="short"/> so I've just sent those <pause dur="short"/> and then I've just e-mailed somebody about a stamp <pause dur="short"/> because I don't know the best way to do it <pause dur="short"/> because Honest logo it's got Honest <pause dur="short"/> then the facial range has got the brown line <pause dur="short"/> the body's got the green line <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>f</trunc> body's um <trunc>f</trunc> tut candles have got the orange line <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> but I don't want to buy three separate stamps with three different colours <pause dur="short"/> cos it's gonna cost a fortune</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0049">so I've just e-mailed this stamp company to say could I have a stamp pad with three lines in and then just honest logo on its own <pause dur="short"/> because obviously I can't sell a candle in a bag stamped with the <trunc>gree</trunc> with the green line or the brown line <pause dur="short"/> do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so how would that work? Would you <trunc>s</trunc> the three coloured bars are separate to the logo?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0049">the logo is the line <trunc>w</trunc> is is the colour <pause dur="short"/> so for instance when someone buys a candle it comes in the cotton bag <pause dur="short"/> it'll be stamped with the Honest logo but in-between the Honest and the website there's a line <pause dur="short"/> and that will be orange because the candles the home range is orange <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> Um</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">but how do you stamp if you're gonna get a stamp with the logo and three different colour <trunc>li</trunc> lines <pause dur="short"/> ah okay <pause dur="short"/> so you'd <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0049">so you'd choose your colour and then</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="38" who="S0049">so I've gotta see how much <trunc>tha</trunc> that comes back as at <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">have you got a provider for that? Have you got a supplier?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0049">um yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I've just e-mailed them now</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="42" who="S0049">so um I think it'll be about fifteen pounds I think <pause dur="short"/> which isn't bad <pause dur="short"/> and it's gonna be better than printing bags <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be more expensive to print</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0049">the only problem I've got is is the ink going to run into the cotton bag? Cos they're fine on the boxes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is there none</u>
<u n="46" who="S0049">so</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">that you can get that you can iron them and that fixes the ink?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0049">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'll see what she I did  I did  put in the e-mail that um</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="50" who="S0049">tut um that I needed it for cotton bags and boxes <pause dur="short"/> so I'll see what she says anyway <pause dur="short"/> and then on another good note <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at Jigsaw who's my friend has asked me to go in on a Saturday</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0049">in a couple of weeks and be there in the shop <trunc>s</trunc> selling my products</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018">ah fantastic</u>
<u n="54" who="S0049">so that's good <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>sh</trunc> and then Jigsaw will</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">jigsaw clothes shop?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0049">and then Jigsaw will put it on their Facebook and their Twitter and so that's a good thing</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">wow <pause dur="short"/> is that just the one store? Is it a chain?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0049">yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but obviously cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s my friend I'm thinking that she's she's gotta okay it with er upstairs <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="62" who="S0049">so that's a good thing</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018">is that the one in the city centre?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's good</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">are you gonna have enough ingredients to make up enough products?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> well on another note</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0049">I've spoke to a guy this morning who found me on LinkedIn</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0049">he invited me to be to link with him <pause dur="short"/> so I sent him an e-mail because he does manufacturing of small runs of natural products</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/>h</u>
<u n="72" who="S0049">with no chemicals et cetera <pause dur="short"/> so um then he rang me this morning and said he'd give me a quote to make up a hundred of each product <pause dur="short"/> and he's already got all the ingredients</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">fantastic</u>
<u n="74" who="S0049">so er in a way it might be worth me going that way</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0049">so I can be out on the road selling</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0049">than making everything up when he's already got everything <pause dur="short"/> and it might work out a little bit cheaper</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">wow <pause dur="short"/> so what you'd go to his factory? Or has he got er laboratories er?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0049">in Harrogate <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">Yorkshire</u>
<u n="82" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so uh</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">and you'd make all the stuff up</u>
<u n="84" who="S0049">er oh sorry hon <pause dur="short"/> he would um I'd give him my jars and bottles <pause dur="short"/> my formulations <pause dur="short"/> and then he would er make it all and send it back to me</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">brilliant</u>
<u n="86" who="S0049">so that might be</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018">and what does he want in return for that?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0049">I'll obviously pay him <pause dur="short"/> but normally what he does is he he er he's <trunc>p</trunc> in product development <pause dur="short"/> he'll so for instance if I said right say imagine I didn't have enough time to develop my men's range <pause dur="short"/> I could say right this is what I want <pause dur="short"/> this is what I want in it <pause dur="short"/> can you develop it for me? And then he would make it all up and <pause dur="short"/> so he's got a factory <pause dur="short"/> and his website is nice</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018">sounds brilliant <pause dur="short"/> and he just found you on LinkedIn</u>
<u n="90" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">cos he was looking for what was he looking for?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0049">no he just he must have just seen me because</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0049">I do have a lot of people actually I <trunc>h</trunc> I'm I've I'm linked with about a hundred and fifty people</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0049">so he's probably just seen Honest Skincare and read my profile <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>tha</trunc> I thought that was quite good</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> networking</u>
<u n="98" who="S0049">no yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">it's er it's the way to do it though <pause dur="short"/> making contacts</u>
<u n="100" who="S0049">I know <pause dur="short"/> so I'll see what I'm gonna e-mail him er <trunc>h</trunc> him in a bit with um maybe a face cream <pause dur="short"/> a cleanser <pause dur="short"/> um and a body lotion</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0049">and then get a price for a hundred <pause dur="short"/> so then I kinda know <pause dur="short"/> er you know <pause dur="short"/> cos it's gonna huh you know if if someone does invest and say it gives me four five grand to buy all my ingredients it might only cost me two grand to get them made up with him</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> cool <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="104" who="S0049">because I've got all my packaging and stuff as well <pause dur="short"/> so um so that's we'll see</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018">oo don't scratch it</u>
<u n="106" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018">is it painful?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0049">it's so sore <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I keep picking it</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="110" who="S0049">I don't know if it is er I normally get a crack there when I'm like run down <pause dur="short"/> you know cos they say it's lack of vitamin E but I never had a cold sore and I don't I think it is</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="112" who="S0049">I've never had one before</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">have you got any cream to put on it?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've been putting Sudocrem and stuff on <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna go to um tut huh Pilates tonight <pause dur="short"/> the</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0049">huh cos when I took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> swimming the other day it was so cold</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">was it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0049">oh</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018">is that in um</u>
<u n="120" who="S0049">and she was like ruh ruh ruh ruh ruh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">lA Fitness?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> in um Cocks Moor</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="124" who="S0049">so <pause dur="short"/> but to be honest the bus there and back three something <pause dur="short"/> and then swimming was three eighty <pause dur="short"/> so I thought if I did this once a week er I may as well pay for a gym membership</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0049">and then a couple of er of classes <pause dur="short"/> like bums and tums and</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0049">the rest of it</u>
<u n="129" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0018">ah exciting</u>
<u n="131" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">oh it's great that you've got all these um tut possibilities isn't it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0049">yep <pause dur="short"/> and then I was thinking you can buy for bags</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0049">so when someone buys a product instead of having it in a nice luxury bag and everything which are gonna cost a fortune get them to come in brown you know like those sandwich bags?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0049">those folded down with a sticker</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0049">and then stamped logo on</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0049">er Honest on so cos they're cheaper and nice brown paper</u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0049">and then the candles obviously in the cotton bags <pause dur="short"/> and then if anyone wants a bigger bag say they're buying more products I can do them the jute bags in the bigger size</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0049">and they're reusable then aren't they <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna  I'm gonna  do that as well today <pause dur="short"/> and I've put <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s cot on eBay <pause dur="short"/> cos I've gotta buy her a bed</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0049">and it ends in about twenty minutes and I've only got one watcher</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="149" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">er do you know what price that they?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0049">I've put it on <trunc>f</trunc> starting bid at one two five <pause dur="short"/> um but there's only one watcher <pause dur="short"/> so if anything it'll I'll get one two five <pause dur="short"/> and it was about three eighty-three about four hundred pounds for the cot and mattress</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">oh well she's got good use of it hasn't she <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0049"><vocal desc="cough"/> Well not really <pause dur="short"/> been sleeping in my bed every night</u>
<u n="154" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">how is she?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0049">she's fine hon <pause dur="short"/> she's when she went to nursery this morning she went love you</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="158" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">sweetie <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0049">but she goes love you</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0049">like that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Love you</u>
<u n="163" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0018">cool <pause dur="short"/> and when's she back?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0049">Saturday morning <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">is she going to nursery on Mondays as well now?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0049">hm <pause dur="short"/> but I <trunc>li</trunc> I go to stay at my nan's on Saturday because <trunc>sh</trunc> she's in hospital now <pause dur="short"/> she had an operation <pause dur="short"/> so I said I'd go and look after her</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> aw <pause dur="short"/> what's wrong with her?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> they found um a growth inside her which has been growing since she had my mum <pause dur="short"/> so for fifty years</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">oh my life</u>
<u n="171" who="S0049">it's now the size of a grapefruit <pause dur="short"/> which you wouldn't belive cos she's a size six <pause dur="short"/> and she's tiny so you wouldn't even think that was inside her <pause dur="short"/> and um so she's in intensive care now</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">what hospital?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0049">Burton <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>mu</trunc> my mum's there now</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="175" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> so I said I'd go over and just <trunc>lo</trunc> you know look after her and</u>
<u n="176" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0049">for a couple of days</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0049">oh and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s asked me to go to Dubai with him to see his sister</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he'd pay for me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to go</u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="183" who="S0049">I know</u>
<u n="184" who="S0018">what does his sister do in Dubai?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0049">she lives there <pause dur="short"/> she lived there a while now <pause dur="short"/> she but I get on really well with her <pause dur="short"/> she's really nice</u>
<u n="186" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="187" who="S0049">um so I think I might go <pause dur="short"/> it's in July</u>
<u n="188" who="S0018">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> er that'd be cool</u>
<u n="189" who="S0049">I know</u>
<u n="190" who="S0018">how long would that be for?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0049">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> a week maybe <pause dur="short"/> so I think I'll go <pause dur="short"/> I just spoke to my mum about it <pause dur="short"/> so that's a bit of good news</u>
<u n="192" who="S0018">do it <pause dur="short"/> would it be like a holiday? Or has he got</u>
<u n="193" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0018">stuff to do out there?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> a holiday <pause dur="short"/> but um I think we'll see  we'll see  anyway <pause dur="short"/> but for him to um offer to pay um I thought was quite nice</u>
<u n="196" who="S0018">are you cold?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0049">freezing babe</u>
<u n="198" who="S0018">shall we go inside?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind though with er</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="200" who="S0018">so what's happening with eBay?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0049">well <pause dur="short"/> I'll just show you <pause dur="short"/> oh it's mum</u>
<u n="202" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0049">I'll <trunc>ans</trunc> I'll speak to her in a minute <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I'm selling <pause dur="short"/> so let's see <pause dur="short"/> selling <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0018">have you sold those?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0049">oh gosh <pause dur="short"/> that's gone up to ten pound <trunc>f</trunc> I'm selling Ava's baby sling which I've had four bids on <pause dur="short"/> and there's eight minutes left on it</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">oo <pause dur="short"/> exciting <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0049">oh it's gone up to eleven pounds <pause dur="short"/> oh that's good <pause dur="short"/> and then I'm selling um her cot <pause dur="short"/> but it's a shame I've only got one watcher because um tut if there was cos if they're not watching then er it's not gonna sell is it</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0049">Cos they haven't put a bid in</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018">how about taking it off and putting it back on? Or will that cost you more money?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0049">I can <pause dur="short"/> but they've told me off for using my usage <pause dur="short"/> I've just put some things on and um cos I've just put on um this coat <pause dur="short"/> and then I put um tut a lovely which I didn't really wanna get rid of Jigsaw scarf on as well <pause dur="short"/> and then er and then when I put this um tut scarf on it told me that I was up to my limit <pause dur="short"/> so cos I've sold these you see <pause dur="short"/> so I'm not sure</u>
<u n="212" who="S0018">so how does it work? Do you pay for a certain amount of</u>
<u n="213" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018">items?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0049">like for <trunc>i</trunc> it's only gonna cost if you put them on for ninety-nine P it doesn't cost you anything <pause dur="short"/> but if you put say for ten pounds that's gonna cost me about huh I dunno a pound probably <pause dur="short"/> if it sells <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="216" who="S0018">well does it it depends on the price that you sell it for or?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0049">mm? Um no it just um I've just seen here that something's just said awaiting answer for <pause dur="short"/> yeah um on what though?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0018">has anyone messaged you asking you about anything?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0049">messages <pause dur="short"/> inbox <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> No <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0018">what's that question about?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0049">no I've answered all of those</u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="223" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> not sure what that is <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0049">it's very confusing <pause dur="short"/> I'm getting used to it now though</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">and what have you sold already?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0049">I have sold a um let's see <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> tut huh summary <pause dur="short"/> purchase history <pause dur="short"/> oh I've got my rocker there hang on</u>
<u n="228" who="S0018">you're not selling your rocking chair are you?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0049">no er that's what I got that one</u>
<u n="230" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="231" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> I've sold a Nicole Farhi denim jacket for twenty-five pounds</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">bargain</u>
<u n="233" who="S0049">A Jaeger dress for thirty-three pounds <pause dur="short"/> maxmara jumper for twelve ninety-nine <pause dur="short"/> armani two-piece set twenty-one pounds <pause dur="short"/> and a Vivienne Westwood chunky bracelet for forty-three pounds</u>
<u n="234" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="235" who="S0049">yes</u>
<u n="236" who="S0018">gosh <pause dur="short"/> so you've made about a hundred and fifty quid?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0049">yeah but then I think it's a hundred and twenty-three pounds once they take off all the PayPal</u>
<u n="238" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="239" who="S0049">and the eBay thing <pause dur="short"/> so but she hasn't paid <trunc>y</trunc> one of those <pause dur="short"/> um Armani two-piece set <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just looking forward now to watch um tut this go to um so er it should only be here we go <pause dur="short"/> oh there's been five bids now</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">oo</u>
<u n="241" who="S0049">there's four minutes left</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">oo</u>
<u n="243" who="S0049">four minutes</u>
<u n="244" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">exciting <pause dur="short"/> what do you find sells the more quickly? The clothes?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0049">I don't know</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">or the baby stuff?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0049">I think I dunno because the I put this fabric on as well <pause dur="short"/> I had the I've got this Marimekko fabric which is Bo Boo fabric with all cars and things on <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>ha</trunc> I haven't had any watchers or it hasn't sold <pause dur="short"/> so I've took it off</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0049">and you would've thought that would've sold</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">oo I like your rug <pause dur="short"/> that's new</u>
<u n="252" who="S0049">oh I got it from Argos <pause dur="short"/> in fact cos I got the table</u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0049">it was only twenty pounds for the table <pause dur="short"/> er cos I was fed up of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0049">not having anywhere to sit to eat <pause dur="short"/> and the and then I got that cos it was I think that was fifteen <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">it's lovely</u>
<u n="258" who="S0049">it's okay isn't it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0049">and the man walked home with it <pause dur="short"/> I had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the pram and he walked me home</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Nice</u>
<u n="262" who="S0049">with it <pause dur="short"/> so I said I'd I'd write on the Argos website</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0049">and er see what he er <pause dur="short"/> and he said oo if you write something on you might win a thousand pounds <pause dur="short"/> and I said oo okay</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0049">I don't know what's going on here <pause dur="short"/> how do I? How much do you think it's gonna go for then? What do you reckon?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">um how many bids have there been? Four?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0049">five bids <pause dur="short"/> it's now eleven pounds <pause dur="short"/> there's three minutes left</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">what did you put it on for?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0049">I put it on for nine</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">oo <pause dur="short"/> maybe it'll go for twelve</u>
<u n="272" who="S0049">tut <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I think maybe thirteen pounds twenty</u>
<u n="273" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0018">not to put too fine a price on it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0049"><unclear/> funny <pause dur="short"/> so um but basically I lost my bank card</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018">oh God</u>
<u n="277" who="S0049">did I tell you?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0049">so <trunc>h</trunc> went to the bank <pause dur="short"/> cancelled my card <pause dur="short"/> came home <pause dur="short"/> found it in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s kitchen</u>
<u n="280" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0049">was it in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s kitchen?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0049">yeah <trunc>w</trunc> yeah it was in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s kitchen <pause dur="short"/> then um tut so obviously then I had no cash or anything <pause dur="short"/> cos I didn't have my new card <pause dur="short"/> so er it's been a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> so then I've had to change all my PayPal account</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="285" who="S0049">and everything on here</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018">is there no way you could er undo the cancellation?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> you're not you can't</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018">what</u>
<u n="289" who="S0049">and um</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">what's your <trunc>h</trunc> um which bank do you bank with?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0049">HSBC</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0049">oh it's still on two minutes <pause dur="short"/> I think it's gonna be very last minute <pause dur="short"/> everyone's gonna go um</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Can you tell where the bids are coming from?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">I could imagine there are four people around the UK <vocal desc="laugh"/> waiting for two minutes to <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0049">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's funny <pause dur="short"/> still eleven pounds <pause dur="short"/> one minute forty seconds</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">oo <pause dur="short"/> countdown <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0049">normally it's <unclear/> but it's not</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">so what happened with your bank card in the end? Er you sorted it out?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0049">oh so then I picked it up yesterday <pause dur="short"/> and um the new one <pause dur="short"/> and then I've been on the phone to eBay and PayPal this morning trying to tut um change all the details around <pause dur="short"/> which has been a bit of a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> But um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <trunc>s</trunc> um e-mailed me yesterday saying um she was looking forward to coming home <pause dur="short"/> but I don't  I don't  know what she's gonna do for work</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0049">and I spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> today cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was working there two days a week wasn't she</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">oh at Jigsaw? Yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0049">and um</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">oh did she give her job up when she went to Finland?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="309" who="S0049">yep <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know what she's going to do <pause dur="short"/> fifty-five seconds</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">oo <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Is there no work for her at Jigsaw now?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0049">she can reapply for the job</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0049">but I'm not sure</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">wouldn't they let her just take a month out?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> you can't</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0049">Cos I guess if <trunc>sh</trunc> if they let <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did that they'd let the other staff do it or</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> oh she'll find something I'm sure</u>
<u n="319" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hope so</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">or then again it might be good for her to have that <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> you know those two days a week for her to work on her own business</u>
<u n="321" who="S0049">I know <pause dur="short"/> but I think it's money <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what she's gonna do for money <pause dur="short"/> fifteen seconds <pause dur="short"/> and it's still eleven pounds</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ten nine eight</u>
<u n="323" who="S0049">normally it it counts it down</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018">seven six five four three two one</u>
<u n="325" who="S0049">eleven pounds <pause dur="short"/> winning bid <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I thought it would've gone up a little bit more</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> aw</u>
<u n="327" who="S0049">oh well <pause dur="short"/> eleven pounds is still eleven pounds</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">not to be sniffed at <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0049">and they retail I think they're forty-five pounds retail</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0049">so</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">so now you send it to?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0049">so now what I do is um go onto here <pause dur="short"/> your item sold for eleven <trunc>pou</trunc> pounds <pause dur="short"/> send invoice <pause dur="short"/><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> in Newcastle</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0049">so um I'll put here congratulations</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0049">on winning</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0049">my BabaSling</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0049">Smiley face <pause dur="short"/> and then send invoice <pause dur="short"/> so he'll get an e-mail now and then he'll pay me into my PayPal account <pause dur="short"/> if that makes sense?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> and then you send it by normal mail?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well second class I I've put on the thingy <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>n</trunc> I've got another one ending now</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">how much does it do they pay postage and packaging?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">so he's paying eleven pounds plus</u>
<u n="347" who="S0049"><trunc>Pa</trunc> plus yeah packaging</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="349" who="S0049">um and there's thirteen minutes mm left on this cot now <pause dur="short"/> which I really hope someone</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">has nobody <trunc>pla</trunc></u>
<u n="351" who="S0049">oh no twelve minutes</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">has no one placed a bid?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> cos I wanted to buy <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a bed next week <pause dur="short"/> but I'll relist this if it doesn't go <pause dur="short"/> we shall see <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">are you going to buy her a adult-size bed? Or a little one?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0049">I'm going to buy her I think I'm just gonna get her one from IKEA <pause dur="short"/> a wooden one</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0049">I think babe <pause dur="short"/> with um a mattress <pause dur="short"/> because I'm not sure how much they are but um I don't really know where else to get them from <pause dur="short"/> because they're so expensive aren't they</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> haven't your parents got a spare bed or anything?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0049">not for er they've got <vocal desc="cough"/> cos I don't think she she can't go in a single bed yet <pause dur="short"/> she needs to be</u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0049">low doesn't she</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0049">so um</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">see if there's anything on er eBay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0049">bedroom <pause dur="short"/> aw <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> children's beds if I put in here <pause dur="short"/> because then the mattress costs as well doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> mattress</u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0049">are about a hundred pounds</u>
<u n="368" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing with IKEA <pause dur="short"/> they sometimes make you buy the slats</u>
<u n="369" who="S0049">look that's ninety-nine pounds <pause dur="short"/> the white ones are oh that's nice <pause dur="short"/> eighty-nine pounds for that white one</u>
<u n="370" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="371" who="S0049">oh look <pause dur="short"/> forty-nine ninety-nine</u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">bargain</u>
<u n="373" who="S0049">thirty-nine ninety-nine <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0018">even more of a bargain</u>
<u n="375" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> how much are the mattresses? See <pause dur="short"/> guard rails ten pounds <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> forty pounds for the cheapest mattress</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018">that cheap one you could probably paint it <pause dur="short"/> where is it? That one</u>
<u n="377" who="S0049">oh that one</u>
<u n="378" who="S0018"><trunc>S</trunc> you could probably paint it <pause dur="short"/> um cos it's more about important the mattress isn't it <pause dur="short"/> and if you've got a duvet or something that hangs over it you</u>
<u n="379" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0018">don't really see the bed</u>
<u n="381" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're right</u>
<u n="382" who="S0018">click on it and see <trunc>wh</trunc> what it looks like</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="383" who="S0049">hm <pause dur="short"/> aw that's cute</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's got a tut a guard rail there as well</u>
<u n="385" who="S0049">or I go to um Kiddicare <pause dur="short"/> kiddicare <pause dur="short"/> so that's say a hundred pounds isn't it for the bed and mattress <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> cots beds and furniture <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018">is this quite a cheap place?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0049">I think so <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018">have you bought anything from them before?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um cot beds <pause dur="short"/> I don't really want a cot bed <pause dur="short"/> I just wanted a bed <pause dur="short"/> see these are cots that turn into beds</u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0049"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got this <pause dur="short"/> one of these <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">and what about seeing if you can just take the sides off her cot upstairs? Cos it's not that it's too small for her is it?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> no she needs like cos when she lies she like turns the other way</u>
<u n="394" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="395" who="S0049">and the the sides of the <trunc>be</trunc> the thingies pull up and down but they don't come off</u>
<u n="396" who="S0018">oh right <pause dur="short"/> if you could take them off would that be possible</u>
<u n="397" who="S0049">er yeah I think well yeah er probably not big enough actually to be honest now</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0049">she's <trunc>t</trunc> coming up to two now <pause dur="short"/> cos this will last her now till she's five</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="401" who="S0049"><unclear/> a a bed <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="402" who="S0018">is there nothing on eBay? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0049">let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> children <pause dur="short"/> I'll just put on here children's beds <pause dur="short"/> I don't want anyone else's bed though</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0049">is that bad?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018">but you could get the bed frame and buy her a mattress <pause dur="short"/> a new one</u>
<u n="407" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I could <pause dur="short"/> er oh here we go</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018">then again I mean that one for IKEA from IKEA was thirty-nine pounds <pause dur="short"/> it was nice</u>
<u n="409" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0018">it's not too expensive</u>
<u n="411" who="S0049">oh look</u>
<u n="412" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="413" who="S0049">this looks expensive</u>
<u n="414" who="S0018">I'd love to have a little a bed with a little ladder going up to it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0049">cabin beds look</u>
<u n="416" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0049">oh my gosh <pause dur="short"/> four hundred and thirty-five pounds</u>
<u n="418" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> maybe not <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0049">that's terrible <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>m</trunc> I could maybe make her one out of pallets</u>
<u n="420" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">why not? It's the mattress that's important isn't it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0049">here we go <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> so what what's what have you done today?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> I met up with er someone in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then had a driving lesson <pause dur="short"/> and then went to Sainsbury's and er er <trunc>A</trunc> um what was it called? The Co-op to</u>
<u n="424" who="S0049">to get organic water <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0018">to get organic water <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Which doesn't exist</u>
<u n="426" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0049">I know <pause dur="short"/> when she said it I was like are you <trunc>su</trunc> organic water?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Does it have to be organic though that you the ones that you</u>
<u n="429" who="S0049">no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0018">use?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0049">but she said it's best to get organic <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know where what she was thinking though</u>
<u n="432" who="S0018">I guess maybe if it's organic it means it's purer or and you can use them in your products</u>
<u n="433" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna check what this this um how long was left on the um?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0018">twelve minutes <pause dur="short"/> on the cot <pause dur="short"/> how long's left? How <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="435" who="S0049">er</u>
<u n="436" who="S0018">how long is left now?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0049">Seven minutes</u>
<u n="438" who="S0018">huh <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> no bids</u>
<u n="439" who="S0049">no bids</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018">uh</u>
<u n="441" who="S0049">come on guys</u>
<u n="442" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And what happens if it doesn't sell? Do you have to pay er?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0049">you still have to pay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0018">tut</u>
<u n="445" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>chil</trunc> let's type in here children's beds</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018">how much do you have to pay if it doesn't sell?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0049">I think that's gonna be about four pounds</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> er when you said that they um tut they sometimes put them on free? You can put them on for free?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">oh that's a nice bed</u>
<u n="451" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's only fifty pounds</u>
<u n="452" who="S0018"><trunc>W</trunc></u>
<u n="453" who="S0049">that's cute isn't it</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0049">that looks really nice <pause dur="short"/> we'd have a white one of course <pause dur="short"/> let's read</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">oh they're new as well <pause dur="short"/> they're not second-hand</u>
<u n="457" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so um new <pause dur="short"/> a brand new unused unopened and undamaged item in original retail packaging where packaging is <pause dur="short"/> toddler kid solid pine <pause dur="short"/> this is a brand new toddler bed <pause dur="short"/> ideal age of eighteen months to five years <pause dur="short"/> very sturdy beginners' bed at an ideal height <pause dur="short"/> very easily assembled with pictured instructions <pause dur="short"/> the bed oh this will suit a mattress size a hundred and forty by seventy <unclear/> Oh see that's nice isn't it</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> how much extra is it for postage and packaging?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> free postage</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="461" who="S0049">oh well that I really like that <pause dur="short"/> and it's only fifty pounds</u>
<u n="462" who="S0018">just check on IKEA first that you can get a mattress of those dimensions</u>
<u n="463" who="S0049">what was it again? A hundred and forty</u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">A hundred and forty</u>
<u n="465" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0018">by seventy was it? So are you still using the internet from next door? Do they know? No? Oh dear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0049">but um</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">could you cancel the?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0049">I did cancel it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos um but I might just go round and say hey you know what I haven't um <pause dur="short"/> oh look at this</u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">er it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh it's a sticker</u>
<u n="471" who="S0049">I know</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0049">um I might just go round and say do you know what? I cancelled my <trunc>Interne</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've gotta I can't lie to them can I?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="475" who="S0049">I'm gonna have to say that I'm on it</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0049">I'm just gonna watch this now because er how many there's only one available <pause dur="short"/> add to watch list</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe just offer them</u>
<u n="481" who="S0049">in white</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">five quid a month or something for it</u>
<u n="483" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and take them a bottle of wine or something</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0049"><trunc>W</trunc> so the mattress was um a hundred and forty by seventy <pause dur="short"/> mattress <pause dur="short"/> are we okay like this or should I be talking more?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's fine <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0049">mattress <pause dur="short"/> a hundred and forty</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">by seventy <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="489" who="S0049">ah by seventy</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">Will they be new though? Er the mattresses on eBay?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0049">this isn't <trunc>eB</trunc> I've gone onto um Amazon <pause dur="short"/> let's try Amazon <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>thir</trunc> forty quid <pause dur="short"/> cot bed mattress</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">A hundred and forty by</u>
<u n="493" who="S0049">see look</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">oh yeah look you can buy</u>
<u n="495" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">it seems to be a standard size</u>
<u n="497" who="S0049">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh perfect</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">what kind of bed has she got at her dad's?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0049">she's got a cot bed <pause dur="short"/> so the cot she's in there which is a massive cot much probably twice the size of the one I've got</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0049">and the sides come off and it turns into a bed</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018">ah okay</u>
<u n="503" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> and it's new <pause dur="short"/> he he <trunc>n</trunc> he he got that not so long ago <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but there's loads look <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know what mattress you're supposed to have for a child <pause dur="short"/> there's loads</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> I recommend the visco-latex ones <pause dur="short"/> they're so comfortable <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0049">these are the mattress types <pause dur="short"/> open sprung <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>po</trunc> Pocket sprung <pause dur="short"/> memory foam <pause dur="short"/> latex <pause dur="short"/> that is that the one you just said?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the latex and the memory foam are good</u>
<u n="507" who="S0049">and then you've got your comfort grades <pause dur="short"/> mm <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="508" who="S0018">do they do all the different types for children's mattresses though? They might only</u>
<u n="509" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">do certain breeds <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> they're children's mattresses <pause dur="long"/> A hundred and nineteen pounds</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">eek</u>
<u n="513" who="S0049">I'll just see what these are <trunc>m</trunc> are made from though <pause dur="short"/> because er I need an allergy one don't I <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> just like the rest of the kid's bedroom products in our exclusive customized range our bounce mattress is practical but firm <pause dur="short"/> a great night's sleep is essential for growing children and our bounce mattress is designed to give your children's bodies the optimum support and comfort needed for hours of quality rest <pause dur="short"/> the reflex foam in our bounce mattress moulds to your child's shape during the night</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> so it's like latex or memory foam</u>
<u n="515" who="S0049">is that like yours then?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">probably <pause dur="short"/> similar <pause dur="short"/> does that actually say what it's made of though?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">does it say in the dimensions part? Nope <pause dur="short"/> and it gives it in inches <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't give it in <trunc>centimetr</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh yes it does</u>
<u n="519" who="S0049">I'm best getting it off Amazon aren't I babe <pause dur="short"/> now <trunc>sh</trunc> right do you reckon about the cot? Do you reckon they're watching</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">huh</u>
<u n="521" who="S0049">it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">fingers crossed</u>
<u n="523" who="S0049">I think they would've bid though you know by now</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">or maybe they're waiting to see if there's any other bids <pause dur="short"/> how many minutes are left?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0049">please</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Anything?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0049">oh <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> one minute left</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> come on you people</u>
<u n="529" who="S0049">I think they would've bid now <pause dur="short"/> they would've bid one two five</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">how long has it been on?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0049">A week <pause dur="short"/> I had three watchers <pause dur="short"/> then it went down to two <pause dur="short"/> and now I've got one watcher <pause dur="short"/> but normally if they want it they would've bid one hundred and twenty-five pounds</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0049">oh</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0049">I'm gonna have to just put it back on then I think</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">why don't you see what your competition's like for the other cots on there? To see how much</u>
<u n="537" who="S0049">I did <pause dur="short"/> there's no Brio ones on there though</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0049">and the thing is in fact the mattress cos it's the bamboo organic one that was a hundred pounds in itself <pause dur="short"/> so the and the cot was like two ninety</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="541" who="S0049">or something <pause dur="short"/> so you're talking three er four hundred pounds aren't you</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">oof <pause dur="short"/> how expensive to have children <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0049">I know <pause dur="short"/> so I mean I'm thinking that I wouldn't really and because I wanna get her a bed and a mattress for a hundred <pause dur="short"/> I could always put it on for a hundred couldn't I? But then I've gotta buy all the sheets for her bed and</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0049">and I've gotta get <pause dur="short"/> oh that's it <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta get her a duvet and a</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0049">pillow and all <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> so really I need that a hundred and twenty-five pounds <pause dur="short"/> unless I ask my dad to help</u>
<u n="548" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">has it finished already? The bidding</u>
<u n="551" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> where is it? It's gone <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> unsold</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">what a let-down</u>
<u n="553" who="S0049">oh</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">are you disappointed?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0049">I'm gonna relist it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="556" who="S0018">can you just add all the same information? Or do you have to enter it all again?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">so here <pause dur="short"/> insertion fee one pound thirty <pause dur="short"/> buy it now thirty-eight <pause dur="short"/> additional pictures sixty <pause dur="short"/> gallery free <pause dur="short"/> total <pause dur="short"/> so it was two pounds twenty-eight <pause dur="short"/> list your item <pause dur="short"/> so it's back on now anyway <pause dur="short"/> so we'll see <pause dur="short"/> it's another week</u>
<u n="559" who="S0049">did you have more things that you were gonna put on there? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> they won't let me put any more on there now</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="561" who="S0049">I can smell garlic babe <pause dur="short"/> have you been eating garlic?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">um possibly <pause dur="short"/> we had a curry last night <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0049">did you?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">I've brushed my teeth a few times since then though</u>
<u n="565" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0049">how how is it in the house? How's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0018">fine <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen</u>
<u n="568" who="S0049">is he?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0018">a lot of er any of them really <pause dur="short"/> I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last night in the restaurant <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but it's the first time I've seen her for about a week?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0049">really?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0049">she's hardly ever there though is she</u>
<u n="573" who="S0018">well she's been in London on a training course</u>
<u n="574" who="S0049">oh okay</u>
<u n="575" who="S0018">and then she stays at her boyfriend's quite a lot</u>
<u n="576" who="S0049">oh er up the road here?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's</u>
<u n="578" who="S0049">oh of course <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's at number forty? <trunc>For</trunc></u>
<u n="580" who="S0049">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> we went to his house didn't we</u>
<u n="581" who="S0018">that's right</u>
<u n="582" who="S0049">I'm just gonna see how much beds are on Amazon now</u>
<u n="583" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Shopping from home from the comfort of your sofa</u>
<u n="584" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> see I don't really like any of these</u>
<u n="585" who="S0018">are the <trunc>Amaz</trunc> are er the ones on Amazon all um from shops? Like there's no second-hand ones?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0049">hm <pause dur="short"/> I don't want second-hand</u>
<u n="587" who="S0018">no I know but er as are er uh is Amazon usually</u>
<u n="588" who="S0049">er</u>
<u n="589" who="S0018">shop items?</u>
<u n="590" who="S0049">some er yeah most of the time <pause dur="short"/> see there's one there but it's two hundred and twenty-nine <pause dur="short"/> I think that one we saw on eBay's the best <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> well one of my jobs today was to sort <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room out hon because she has got so much stuff</u>
<u n="591" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What clothes?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0049">and er well I <trunc>w</trunc> I <trunc>w</trunc> I went up there earlier and obviously I was getting ready this morning and er when she left I went in her bedroom and it's just like chaos in there</u>
<u n="593" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0049">she's like turned everything upside down</u>
<u n="595" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0049">I was like oh this is ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> so um</u>
<u n="597" who="S0018">streamlining her possessions</u>
<u n="598" who="S0049">I think I need to <pause dur="short"/> because and the other thing is she's got so many toys that she doesn't really play with most of them because she's got so many</u>
<u n="599" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0049">so um I think it's time to make it into a pretty girly room</u>
<u n="601" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> How are you gonna do that?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0049">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I think I've got a lovely chest of drawers at my mum's in the container which is mine <pause dur="short"/> it's white <pause dur="short"/> you know like the and er I love they're white and they've got the patterns on</u>
<u n="603" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0049">so I think I'll get that to come over here <pause dur="short"/> then get her a white bed and we'll have lots of floral things going on <pause dur="short"/> I'll get some flags for around the room <pause dur="short"/> pink</u>
<u n="605" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0018">lovely</u>
<u n="607" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018">are you gonna keep that lampshade though? It's</u>
<u n="609" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018">lovely <pause dur="short"/> really nice</u>
<u n="611" who="S0049">yeah I'd like to put loads of flowers on that <pause dur="short"/> you know like um</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0049">you know like the flowers I've put in the garden on the tree?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0049">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> and now she's got a little table <pause dur="short"/> bless her <pause dur="short"/> it's a chalk table so she can write on it in chalk</u>
<u n="616" who="S0018">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="617" who="S0049">I know</u>
<u n="618" who="S0018"><trunc>W</trunc></u>
<u n="619" who="S0049">bless her</u>
<u n="620" who="S0018">what a novel idea</u>
<u n="621" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0018">can I have a go? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh let me just get that paperwork so you can see it <unclear/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0049">what I've done is I've I've put huh for instance here's all the oils</u>
<u n="626" who="S0018">oh is this for the costing?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>wh</trunc></u>
<u n="628" who="S0018">so these are  these are  broken down by product?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0049">well what I've done so I've put all the ingredients <pause dur="short"/> so these are all the oils</u>
<u n="630" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="631" who="S0049">the size I buy it in</u>
<u n="632" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="633" who="S0049">and the cost</u>
<u n="634" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="635" who="S0049">that's without VAT <pause dur="short"/> my peeling grains <pause dur="short"/> then I've got like my <trunc>f</trunc> these are the fats and preservative <pause dur="short"/> then I've got my vitamins <pause dur="short"/> um more moisturizers <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know if he's gonna understand <pause dur="short"/> because and then I've got essential oils <pause dur="short"/> organic and non-organic</u>
<u n="636" who="S0018">but are those the things that go into <trunc>h</trunc> I mean is that the ingredients for one particular product?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> because what I've done then so I've got all my ingredients <pause dur="short"/> emulsifiers <pause dur="short"/> clays <pause dur="short"/> floral waters <pause dur="short"/> then I've got every single product</u>
<u n="638" who="S0018">ah okay</u>
<u n="639" who="S0049">so I've got body polish <pause dur="short"/> what goes into it</u>
<u n="640" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="641" who="S0049">lips <pause dur="short"/> what goes er <trunc>s</trunc> and the amount</u>
<u n="642" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="643" who="S0049">that goes into it <pause dur="short"/> body lotion <pause dur="short"/> what goes into it <pause dur="short"/> and the amount</u>
<u n="644" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0049">and I've done that for all my products</u>
<u n="646" who="S0018">wow <pause dur="short"/> you've been busy</u>
<u n="647" who="S0049">but I don't know if he's if that's <trunc>i</trunc> I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> really know how else <pause dur="short"/> because what we need to do <pause dur="short"/> we need to take say body lotion</u>
<u n="648" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0049">and we go thistle oil</u>
<u n="650" who="S0018">ah okay <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="651" who="S0049">you get your thistle oil <pause dur="short"/> five hundred mil for five pounds sixty <pause dur="short"/> so you need to work out how much one mil is</u>
<u n="652" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0049">so we need to divide <pause dur="short"/> so get the price for that <pause dur="short"/> and then we need to times it er one mil by four</u>
<u n="654" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0049">which give us the price for the thistle oil</u>
<u n="656" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0049">do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0049">it's gonna it's such a hard long job <pause dur="short"/> it's I think it <trunc>w</trunc>  it <trunc>w</trunc>  definitely I remember when I did it before I I just it's so confusing <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know if that's gonna be enough for him to</u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">I'm sure it will be <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="662" who="S0018">are these in millilitres?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and for instance <pause dur="short"/> everything's in mil</u>
<u n="664" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="665" who="S0049">except for essential oils <pause dur="short"/> so obviously everything's got essential oils in <pause dur="short"/> so on tea tree lavender <trunc>lemo</trunc> lemon essential oils I've got three drops two drops two drops <pause dur="short"/> because this these are all making a hundred mil</u>
<u n="666" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> and how many er?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0049">so they all add up to a hundred</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">so where you've got your for example when you buy your bottles of lemon essential oil how many drops are in each bottle <pause dur="short"/> do you know</u>
<u n="669" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> okay so say let's think about this then <pause dur="short"/> if I bought lemon essential oil <pause dur="short"/> thirty mil is seven pounds ninety <pause dur="short"/> so thirty mil one mil of essential oil is twenty-four drops</u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="671" who="S0049">so</u>
<u n="672" who="S0018">so it's twenty-four times thirty <pause dur="short"/> which is mm seven hundred and twenty <pause dur="short"/> so you get seven hundred and twenty drops out of a thirty mil bottle</u>
<u n="673" who="S0049">I'm sure it's twenty-four drops <pause dur="short"/> because nought point six mil is twelve drops</u>
<u n="674" who="S0018">wait there sorry <trunc>w</trunc> you said a thirty mil bottle <pause dur="short"/> how many drops in one mil?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0049">one mil is twenty-four drops</u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">so it'd be twenty-four times three <pause dur="short"/> two four six <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> seventy-two <pause dur="short"/> add a <trunc>nou</trunc> add a zero on <pause dur="short"/> seven hundred and twenty <pause dur="short"/> no?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0049">oh I dunno babe</u>
<u n="678" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0049">God it's just doing my head in</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018">no but</u>
<u n="681" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="682" who="S0018">I think you've got all the raw data there that he'll need to be able to do the</u>
<u n="683" who="S0049">but this isn't including VAT <pause dur="short"/> I just haven't had time to <pause dur="short"/> and the only other thing the only things I need to do are my three cleansers now</u>
<u n="684" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0049">Cos the formulation's changed <pause dur="short"/> so I've got to do those <pause dur="short"/> but um you know like preservative there I've got nought point six mil of preservative <pause dur="short"/> which is yeah twelve drops</u>
<u n="686" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> eighteen drops of grapefruit <pause dur="short"/> three gram <pause dur="short"/> it's like it's just er it's just <trunc>n</trunc> it confuses me</u>
<u n="688" who="S0018">well as long as you've got on the original sheet how <trunc>w</trunc> the quantities in which you buy it</u>
<u n="689" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="690" who="S0018">and the price of that <pause dur="short"/> I mean he can</u>
<u n="691" who="S0049">so um er the next thing I need to do for him now er is find the prices of my bottles</u>
<u n="692" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="693" who="S0049">and I don't know the <trunc>si</trunc> the price of my labels yet until um</u>
<u n="694" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> of course</u>
<u n="695" who="S0049">it all goes through <pause dur="short"/> and I'm I reckon they'll all be about between nine and eleven P a label</u>
<u n="696" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="697" who="S0049">but I'm not a hundred percent yet <pause dur="short"/> but we can always add that on</u>
<u n="698" who="S0018">so it's you've put the cost and then with VAT VAT? <trunc>H</trunc> is VAT just that <pause dur="short"/> the cost plus</u>
<u n="699" who="S0049">vAT</u>
<u n="700" who="S0018">what is it? Seventeen point point five percent?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so um <pause dur="short"/> and the thing is on some of them they're classed as food so you don't get charged  you don't get charged  VAT</u>
<u n="702" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="703" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> so I've got oils <pause dur="short"/> vitamins <pause dur="short"/> these are like <trunc>m</trunc> um moisturizers <pause dur="short"/> essential oils <pause dur="short"/> organic and non-organic <pause dur="short"/> emulsifiers and clays <pause dur="short"/> floral waters <pause dur="short"/> and for instance I haven't really I should put on the <trunc>w</trunc> on water as well from <trunc>h</trunc> like how much was that water that just cost you?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0018">sixty-eight P</u>
<u n="705" who="S0049">for <trunc>wat</trunc> for one litre of water <pause dur="short"/> so I need to put that on as well <pause dur="short"/> but obviously this doesn't include when Lara did <trunc>m</trunc> some costings for me this doesn't include anything electrical</u>
<u n="706" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0049">anything you know heating <pause dur="short"/> my time <pause dur="short"/> or anything does it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="708" who="S0018">but it's a good idea to get an idea of what the cost is for each particular bottle <pause dur="short"/> for example</u>
<u n="709" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0018">like if you <trunc>s</trunc> say okay I've got a bottle of cleansing lotion <pause dur="short"/> I'm selling it at this price <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="711" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0018">what it takes to make it costs this much</u>
<u n="713" who="S0049">Cos my old cleanser cost me one pound seventy-nine to make <pause dur="short"/> but it only had three ingredients in <pause dur="short"/> cos in this new cleanser's got say ten ingredients in <pause dur="short"/> er so and also all these add up to a hundred <pause dur="short"/> cos I work in a hundred percent <pause dur="short"/> but I sell body polish in two hundred and fifty mil</u>
<u n="714" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="715" who="S0049">I sell my lip balm in fifteen mil <pause dur="short"/> body lotion sells in two fifty mil <pause dur="short"/> do you see what I mean? So it's so if it's body lotion</u>
<u n="716" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0049">it's that times that again times half isn't it</u>
<u n="718" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well maybe what would be a good idea is that when we organize to meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know er to chat about the investment</u>
<u n="719" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0018">that we maybe go and see my dad at the same time <pause dur="short"/> cos he</u>
<u n="721" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0018">just lives round the corner</u>
<u n="723" who="S0049">okay hon</u>
<u n="724" who="S0018">and you can explain all this to him and he can ask you the questions</u>
<u n="725" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0018">that he needs to ask</u>
<u n="727" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="728" who="S0018">to be able to manipulate it all into some kind of <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0049">when do you think er</u>
<u n="730" who="S0018">coherent</u>
<u n="731" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> when do you think we could do that? I'm trying to think</u>
<u n="732" who="S0018">well it'll depend on when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s free <pause dur="short"/> cos I know he's he's busier than</u>
<u n="733" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="734" who="S0018">my dad</u>
<u n="735" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got to  I've got to  give all these costings to that woman in a week and a half</u>
<u n="736" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0049">because I don't want her really going through it because</u>
<u n="738" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="739" who="S0049">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I just don't I'm not comfortable</u>
<u n="740" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> see I can always give it to him next door <pause dur="short"/> because he's said he would do it</u>
<u n="742" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="743" who="S0049">I mean I could give it him and see what <pause dur="short"/> I could photocopy this couldn't I and just see <pause dur="short"/> he might if he's free he might be able to do this in a day</u>
<u n="744" who="S0018">well or if you want I'll <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="745" who="S0049">if he understands</u>
<u n="746" who="S0018">I'll see my dad tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I could give him what you've got</u>
<u n="747" who="S0049">do you think he's gonna understand though if I'm not with if I haven't spoke to him?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0018">well if you phone him?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0049">I'm trying to think if he can um I just hope I've made it clear enough</u>
<u n="750" who="S0018">what else have you got to do tomorrow?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0049">tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I'm just  I'm just  working <trunc>rea</trunc> here really tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I'm just home</u>
<u n="752" who="S0018">Cos if you wanna come over to <anon type="place"/> with me at about midday</u>
<u n="753" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="754" who="S0018">I'm pretty sure he's free tomorrow</u>
<u n="755" who="S0049">is he?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0018">you could sit down and er</u>
<u n="757" who="S0049">go through stuff with him</u>
<u n="758" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> then at least you're on you know you're you can er probably communicate better face to face than over the phone and with some papers</u>
<u n="759" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would be better to see him</u>
<u n="760" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="761" who="S0049">see I could  I could  I was thinking about putting um tut Jane off anyway <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="762" who="S0018">is this the Dragon's Den lady?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0049">but she met my mum last week and she said she's got some really good um she's been speaking to some people and she's er apparently mum said wait till you hear what she's done</u>
<u n="766" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="767" who="S0049">and she's got some er um tut costings from another skincare company er which</u>
<u n="768" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="769" who="S0049">er she <trunc>sh</trunc> it was really hard to get hold of but she's managed to get it <pause dur="short"/> and stuff that so she's really trying to help me</u>
<u n="770" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0049">so</u>
<u n="772" who="S0018">but this stuff's nearly done <pause dur="short"/> don't worry about showing it to her <pause dur="short"/> cos then you know</u>
<u n="773" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0018">probably by next week you can have it all done and dusted and send it off to her before she actually needs it <pause dur="short"/> which will be impressive <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0049">it will won't it babe</u>
<u n="776" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0018">hyper-organized <pause dur="short"/> and then that gives you time to find out you know to price your bottles and</u>
<u n="778" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="779" who="S0018">the pipettes and</u>
<u n="780" who="S0049">that's it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0018">with the labels</u>
<u n="782" who="S0049">I've <trunc>h</trunc> cos I've had a row with who I get my um <vocal desc="laugh"/> um bottles and jars off</u>
<u n="783" who="S0018">I'm not surprised <pause dur="short"/> were they the people that <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="784" who="S0049">they're just a nightmare</u>
<u n="785" who="S0018">they sent you the wrong</u>
<u n="786" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0018">er tops?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0049">but basically <trunc>th</trunc> they're I've had a box waiting for them <pause dur="short"/> they're supposed to pick it up <pause dur="short"/> and they've said they've visited my mum's house five times to collect it and no one's been there <pause dur="short"/> which you can't get into mum's house <pause dur="short"/> it's gated <pause dur="short"/> right? So unless they ring me and say we're gonna come on Monday <pause dur="short"/> don't know what time it'll be <pause dur="short"/> but we're gonna come</u>
<u n="789" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0049">then if I know they're coming then I'll make sure that the driver's got the code to the gate to get into the house <pause dur="short"/> and I could've left the box outside <pause dur="short"/> or <trunc>s</trunc> made sure mum was there or something <pause dur="short"/> and then they said so eventually I get this really snotty um phonecall off um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one of the women there <pause dur="short"/> um basically blaming me <pause dur="short"/> and I said hang on this isn't my fault <pause dur="short"/> you've sent me the wrong products <pause dur="short"/> you've asked to pick the box up but you've just sent a driver <pause dur="short"/> you've not even spoke to me about it <pause dur="short"/> I said you know I'm not there twenty-four seven <pause dur="short"/> and then and now you're telling me that you want me to pay for the postage to send all this back <pause dur="short"/> I said it's gonna cost me about thirty forty pounds <pause dur="short"/> I said no um you know this is your fault <pause dur="short"/> she went it is not our fault <pause dur="short"/> er anyway <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="791" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="792" who="S0049">she was horrible <pause dur="short"/> and er <trunc>sh</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> I felt so horrible the way she was speaking to me <pause dur="short"/> and then um you know when you get all anxious and I couldn't believe</u>
<u n="793" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="794" who="S0049">you know after everything <pause dur="short"/> and then in the end I just bit back and said do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said I've had so many problems um with <unclear/> I said that um you know I said er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has apologized <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s apologized <pause dur="short"/> I said and you're having a go at me <pause dur="short"/> blah blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and I said and you know this isn't my fault <pause dur="short"/> and I said do you know what? I'm sick of this <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="795" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0049">I said um and then she went but there's um there's money outstanding <pause dur="short"/> I was like right okay then <pause dur="short"/> so I took control then <pause dur="short"/> I went tell me how much money's outstanding will you? And tell me <trunc>w</trunc> what for? Because I said I <trunc>pai</trunc> I paid you seven hundred and something pounds a couple of months ago for this that and the other <pause dur="short"/> blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and she went right well let me just see <pause dur="short"/> and they're like really dippy there so</u>
<u n="797" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="798" who="S0049">right so you had some sixty mil jars <pause dur="short"/> and they were blah <pause dur="short"/> I said right okay now I thought you took money for those cos I paid for them over the phone and it went through <pause dur="short"/> oh but we decided not to because um</u>
<u n="799" who="S0018">tut fff</u>
<u n="800" who="S0049">there was this box <trunc>ou</trunc></u>
<u n="801" who="S0018">huh</u>
<u n="802" who="S0049">right okay <pause dur="short"/> so why didn't you tell me? <vocal desc="laugh"/> So and it was just going on and on like this</u>
<u n="803" who="S0018">crikey</u>
<u n="804" who="S0049">and um and in the end I just and I arranged to have the box er I said right then so what day would you like to come and collect this box <pause dur="short"/> and she went well what day suits you?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0049">I said well come on Monday then <pause dur="short"/> I said Monday? And she went yes okay <pause dur="short"/> I said right then Monday it is <pause dur="short"/> I'll make sure it's ready for you <pause dur="short"/> so they picked it up on Monday and I haven't heard anything</u>
<u n="807" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0049">but they're just really dippy <unclear/></u>
<u n="809" who="S0018">and that's crazy blaming you for it <pause dur="short"/> er can you not write a letter of complaint to her</u>
<u n="810" who="S0049">oh</u>
<u n="811" who="S0018">superior?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0049">God <pause dur="short"/> well I know the guy that owns the company <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and he's just as bad <pause dur="short"/> I asked him a year ago over a year ago for a machine right? Because I <trunc>nee</trunc> when my labels come to me now I need something that I can put my bottle in and my label sticks on <pause dur="short"/> because</u>
<u n="813" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="814" who="S0049">to do it by hand I've done it before they're all wonky <pause dur="short"/> they're not exactly the same</u>
<u n="815" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0049">so I heard he had this machine <pause dur="short"/> so I rang him <pause dur="short"/> and er and I spoke to him on the phone <pause dur="short"/> I said you know how much is this machine? He said oh I'll get you the price I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I said right okay fab <pause dur="short"/> I said e-mail me <pause dur="short"/> anyway he never did <pause dur="short"/> babe I musta rang five or six times</u>
<u n="817" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0049">and asked <trunc>f</trunc> for the price of this machine <pause dur="short"/> they never got back to me <pause dur="short"/> and in the end I just gave up</u>
<u n="819" who="S0018">oh God</u>
<u n="820" who="S0049"><trunc>S</trunc> and that was him <pause dur="short"/> the owner <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> argh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0018">what a way to run a business</u>
<u n="822" who="S0049">yep</u>
<u n="823" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So what do you need done with this now? You just basically need er someone to calculate all the different price <trunc>s</trunc> costings of each</u>
<u n="824" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0018">product?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0049">so I guess your dad will say I mean let's just do one for example <unclear/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0049">oh I haven't oh I have got a calculator on here</u>
<u n="829" who="S0018">practice our numeracy skills</u>
<u n="830" who="S0049">because I I've <trunc>d</trunc> I've done my cost my old range I did my costings and it took me forever <pause dur="short"/> but I managed to do it</u>
<u n="831" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0049">with Mike's help <pause dur="short"/> my step-dad <pause dur="short"/> but um I'll just see <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and it was <trunc>rea</trunc> it was really <trunc>m</trunc> especially when you're not mathematical like me</u>
<u n="833" who="S0018">it's just a formula though isn't it <pause dur="short"/> as soon as you</u>
<u n="834" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="835" who="S0018">get the <trunc>s</trunc> formula makes logical sense</u>
<u n="836" who="S0049">just er it's just head doing <pause dur="short"/> it's just really um</u>
<u n="837" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> I find it easier to write it down as well</u>
<u n="838" who="S0049">right <pause dur="short"/> let me get um</u>
<u n="839" who="S0018">if you get some paper we can actually just like er we can probably work it out with a calculator and a pen and a paper</u>
<u n="840" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0018">pen and some paper <pause dur="short"/> how many products have you not</u>
<u n="842" who="S0049">ow <pause dur="short"/> ow</u>
<u n="843" who="S0018">done these for? Was there just two?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0049">how? Er three</u>
<u n="845" who="S0018">three <pause dur="short"/> cos if you want we could do those as well this afternoon <pause dur="short"/> so that you've got at least all your products done</u>
<u n="846" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="847" who="S0018">and then we can put a star by the ones that er are exempt from <trunc>V</trunc> VAT</u>
<u n="848" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm really cold <pause dur="short"/> I need to put um I try not to put the heating on</u>
<u n="849" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> it's a good idea <pause dur="short"/> get a blanket <pause dur="short"/> wear it like a sari <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh is that the <trunc>c</trunc> scarf you're selling?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0018">Don't sell it <pause dur="short"/> it's lovely</u>
<u n="852" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="853" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Aw</u>
<u n="854" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> so um let's just take um</u>
<u n="855" who="S0018">what's?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0049">so these are the ingredients</u>
<u n="857" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="858" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> so you hold the ingredients <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>f</trunc> say we start on um calming face mask</u>
<u n="859" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> so you've got is that camomile water?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so camomile water <pause dur="short"/> floral waters <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got the price for that one</u>
<u n="861" who="S0018">it's not on here?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> because that's a new <pause dur="short"/> let's see how much that is</u>
<u n="863" who="S0018">do you get all your ingredients from the same supplier?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="865" who="S0018">so <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="866" who="S0049">I'll just get the um</u>
<u n="867" who="S0018">do you want me to write it down here?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0049">one litre</u>
<u n="869" who="S0018">wait there <pause dur="short"/> where's the waters? Waters</u>
<u n="870" who="S0049"><unclear/> one litre</u>
<u n="871" who="S0018">how much is one litre?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0049">is eight pounds</u>
<u n="873" who="S0018">so here you've got six millilitres <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="874" who="S0049">six mil <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="875" who="S0018">so how many mil in one litre? A hundred?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0049">A thousand</u>
<u n="877" who="S0018">oh a thousand <pause dur="short"/> I have no idea</u>
<u n="878" who="S0049">A <trunc>thou</trunc> a thousand <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0049">A thousand <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="881" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="882" who="S0049">confused me then <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="883" who="S0018">so if you've got a thousand so it's how much was it?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0049">um er um eight pounds <pause dur="short"/> so a thousand</u>
<u n="885" who="S0018"><trunc>S</trunc> if you do eight pounds divided by a thousand</u>
<u n="886" who="S0049">er <trunc>m</trunc> I need a different <trunc>cal</trunc> er er okay so eight pounds</u>
<u n="887" who="S0018">divided by</u>
<u n="888" who="S0049">divided by</u>
<u n="889" who="S0018">A thousand <pause dur="short"/> and then times it by wait there <pause dur="short"/> what's er six millilitres goes into it does it? Where's the?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="891" who="S0018">oh here <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="892" who="S0049">oh no</u>
<u n="893" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> er oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> here it is <pause dur="short"/> six millilitres <pause dur="short"/> so times that by six <pause dur="short"/> so it costs you nought point nought five P <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> camomile <pause dur="short"/> nought point nought four eight</u>
<u n="895" who="S0018">round it up <pause dur="short"/> just do two digital er two decimal places</u>
<u n="896" who="S0049">so just two <pause dur="short"/> so just</u>
<u n="897" who="S0018">nought point  nought point  nought five</u>
<u n="898" who="S0049">just do <trunc>fi</trunc> five O?</u>
<u n="899" who="S0018">nought point nought five <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0049">nought five?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because cos that's higher than five <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="902" who="S0049">oh okay</u>
<u n="903" who="S0018">put the next number up <pause dur="short"/> in fact we're lower than five</u>
<u n="904" who="S0049">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0018">you'd just keep it to</u>
<u n="906" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="907" who="S0018">nought point nought four</u>
<u n="908" who="S0049">so nought point nought five <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="909" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> the next one is water</u>
<u n="910" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> so um</u>
<u n="911" who="S0018"><trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="912" who="S0049">you just bought that water</u>
<u n="913" who="S0018">er you can get it cheaper though if you buy it in bulk <pause dur="short"/> I reckon</u>
<u n="914" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="915" who="S0018">if you got like er a pack of six <pause dur="short"/> you could probably even get organic water from somewhere if they do</u>
<u n="916" who="S0049">let's just see on here</u>
<u n="917" who="S0018">if they do organic sparkling water <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> I'm sure they must do organic spring water <pause dur="short"/> check out on Asda</u>
<u n="918" who="S0049">oh let's just</u>
<u n="919" who="S0018">maybe they were just um out of</u>
<u n="920" who="S0049">I just I've never really er <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0018">out of stock <pause dur="short"/> oh Highland Spring</u>
<u n="922" who="S0049">if you buy organic water you're a fucking idiot</u>
<u n="923" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Excuse your French <pause dur="short"/> look on Highland Spring <pause dur="short"/> cos they're they were the ones that did the organic sparkling water <pause dur="short"/> so maybe they they do <trunc>s</trunc> still as well <pause dur="short"/> have they got a page for the organic range? What was that there? mm</u>
<u n="924" who="S0049"><trunc>S</trunc> Highland Spring still</u>
<u n="925" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't say if it's organic though <pause dur="short"/> cos they definitely did have a a range of organic waters <pause dur="short"/> check out Highland Spring organic maybe</u>
<u n="926" who="S0049">oh Tesco <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="927" who="S0018">oh yeah look</u>
<u n="928" who="S0049">oh here <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="929" who="S0018">Cos if you buy that in bulk I'm sure it'll cost a lot less than it would if you're buying it bottle by bottle in the supermarket</u>
<u n="930" who="S0049">okay so for five hundred mil sixty-five P</u>
<u n="931" who="S0018">wait there <pause dur="short"/> let me write that down <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="932" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="933" who="S0018">five hundred mil sixty-five P</u>
<u n="934" who="S0049">so just say for a litre it's gonna be one pound twenty <pause dur="short"/> and I reckon we'll get it cheaper than that</u>
<u n="935" who="S0018">litre one pound</u>
<u n="936" who="S0049">one pound twenty</u>
<u n="937" who="S0018">twenty</u>
<u n="938" who="S0049">just to be safe</u>
<u n="939" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> so here you've got forty mils of water <pause dur="short"/> so if one litre is one pound twenty <pause dur="short"/> so divide one <trunc>twe</trunc> one pound twenty by a thousand <pause dur="short"/> and then times it by forty <pause dur="short"/> so that's gonna cost you four point eight P for the water <pause dur="short"/> then the preservative um nought point six mils</u>
<u n="940" who="S0049">see what I should be doing now because preservative is used in all products <pause dur="short"/> instead of keep on doing this</u>
<u n="941" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0049">I've what we should do is um tut we should maybe find out the price for each ingredient <pause dur="short"/> just the price for for one mil</u>
<u n="943" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0049">do you think?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos then you can</u>
<u n="946" who="S0049">and then I can add it up</u>
<u n="947" who="S0018"></u>
<u n="948" who="S0049">that's how I did it before <pause dur="short"/> because otherwise we're gonna keep going back on ourselves aren't we?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="950" who="S0049">because we're gonna have to do preservative twenty-eight times</u>
<u n="951" who="S0018">you see that's where my dad can probably do something nifty with an Excel wordsheet</u>
<u n="952" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="953" who="S0018">er spreadsheet <pause dur="short"/> and um be able to just put in a formula</u>
<u n="954" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="S0018">whereby it'll calculate it all</u>
<u n="956" who="S0049">well we'll keep we'll do this one first babe and see what this one comes out as anyway</u>
<u n="957" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="958" who="S0049">so um water was four point eight <pause dur="short"/> so preservative twelve</u>
<u n="959" who="S0018">where has it got?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="961" who="S0018">wait there <pause dur="short"/> have you got the prices there? Or have I got them here?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0049">um hm</u>
<u n="963" who="S0018">where are they?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0049">oh I'm all confused <pause dur="short"/> right okay so price price</u>
<u n="965" who="S0018">there you go</u>
<u n="966" who="S0049">price</u>
<u n="967" who="S0018">so those are the prices of the</u>
<u n="968" who="S0049">what's that one then?</u>
<u n="969" who="S0018">ingredients</u>
<u n="970" who="S0049">and that's <unclear/> that's <unclear/> Um so preservative twelve</u>
<u n="971" who="S0018">oh well let's just write that <pause dur="short"/> still still um organic water</u>
<u n="972" who="S0049">okay so for for um a hundred mil it's seven pounds ninety</u>
<u n="973" who="S0018">A hundred mil</u>
<u n="974" who="S0049">so what do I do? I go seven pounds ninety</u>
<u n="975" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos if you</u>
<u n="976" who="S0049">divided by a hundred</u>
<u n="977" who="S0018">if a hundred mil is seven pound ninety you wanna find out what one mil is <pause dur="short"/> so you're um divide seven ninety by a hundred</u>
<u n="978" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0018">yeah? And then times it by the amount of millilitres you need in the product</u>
<u n="980" who="S0049">so it's one <pause dur="short"/> so it's that isn't it</u>
<u n="981" who="S0018">preservative twelve that was? No you need nought point six</u>
<u n="982" who="S0049">oh nought point six</u>
<u n="983" who="S0018"><trunc>D</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="984" who="S0049">oh for one mil isn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> nought point six is one mil</u>
<u n="985" who="S0018">nought point six what though?</u>
<u n="986" who="S0049">but then</u>
<u n="987" who="S0018">millilitres?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0049">mil <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so see this is I'm a bit confused now <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> by Aromantic law you're supposed to use er this is nought point six mil but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s changed my um tox reports <pause dur="short"/> so I have to use a mil <pause dur="short"/> but I'm not using a mil because I don't want to</u>
<u n="989" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Why did he say?</u>
<u n="990" who="S0049">just to cover with <trunc>l</trunc> like EU regulations <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="991" who="S0018">well er surely that means you have to use the amount that they specify?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0049">but Aromantic are saying that you don't have to you see <pause dur="short"/> so and <trunc>Aromant</trunc> there's been a big thing er Aromantic have spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about this and they've</u>
<u n="993" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="994" who="S0049">had I dunno what's gone on <pause dur="short"/> but er so</u>
<u n="995" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s the guy that did your tox reports?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="998" who="S0049">so um I can really use up to one percent if I want <pause dur="short"/> so in a hundred percent I'd use <trunc>w</trunc> up to one percent <pause dur="short"/> which would be one mil <pause dur="short"/> so if I say because my mask has got water in it there's more chance of contamination <pause dur="short"/> so I think I should do my pricing all based on one mil of preservative</u>
<u n="999" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0049">just in case</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0049">that's I think that's what I'll do</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a good idea</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0049">do you think?</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0049">because and then if I use less I use less</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0049">but I know that I'm not gonna use any more than one mil don't I?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0049">do you think that makes sense?</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> so that's is that nought point nought?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> so what I'll do then so if I've wrote here</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0018">so it was one millilitre and?</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> I'm confused babe</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0018">was it seven seven pound ninety for one litre?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0049">for a hundred mil</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0018">for a hundred mil?</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0049">so seven pounds</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0018"><trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="1022" who="S0049">ninety</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0018">divided by a hundred</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0049">divided by a hundred</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0018">times one <pause dur="short"/> which is <trunc>ex</trunc> nought</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0049">yeah so so nought point seven nine</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0018">nought point zero eight</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0049">nought point zero eight okay  nought point zero eight okay  Tut</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1030" who="S0049">huh</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0018">next ingredient is white clay</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0018">er where are the clays? Here <pause dur="short"/> so white clay is twenty-five what's that?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0049">two hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0049">grams <pause dur="short"/> one eighty-five <pause dur="short"/> that's just</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0018">two fifty grams <pause dur="short"/> one eighty-five</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0049">so two hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0018">two fifty</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0049">divided by one pound <trunc>f</trunc> eighty-five?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then times the amount you need in the</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0049">that's gone like that though</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0018">product <pause dur="short"/> oh did you</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0018">did you <trunc>ty</trunc> oh no divided by</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0049">one pound eighty-five divided by</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0018">divided by</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0049">two hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0018">and then times it by fifty <pause dur="short"/> nought point three seven <pause dur="short"/> and the last one is apricot kernel oil <pause dur="short"/> six millilitres</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0018">which is apricot kernel oil</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0049">so <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1053" who="S0018">A hundred mil for six twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> six twenty-five divided by a hundred <pause dur="short"/> times six <pause dur="short"/> that's nought point three eight</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> that's it isn't it? That goes into that?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> that's all</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0049">so when we add that up that's hardly anything to be honest <pause dur="short"/> let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0018">do you wanna tell me er?</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0049">nought point</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0018">or shall I?</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0049">nought five</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0018">plus four point eight <pause dur="short"/> plus nought point nought eight <pause dur="short"/> plus nought point three seven <pause dur="short"/> plus nought point three eight <pause dur="short"/> equals five pounds sixty-eight <pause dur="short"/> is that how much it costs? Wait there <pause dur="short"/> no we've done it wrong</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0049">what?</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0018">Cos that er the water wasn't it can't <trunc>b</trunc> ah this is pence</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0018">so</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0049">but no that's not right <pause dur="short"/> four <trunc>pou</trunc> that's not right is it?</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0018">four point eight pence <pause dur="short"/> you've got a dot between you've got a point <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0049">four four point eight <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0049">so I've got nought point</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0018">nought five</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0049">nought five</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0018">plus</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0049">plus</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0018">four point eight</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0049">that seems a lot <pause dur="short"/> four point eight doesn't it? For water</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0018">but you needed wait there</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0049">no it can't be right</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0018">you needed forty millilitres <pause dur="short"/> and one litre  one litre  was one pound twenty was it? No <pause dur="short"/> one litre was wait there <pause dur="short"/> I wrote it down <pause dur="short"/> one litre was one pound twenty</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and if the camomile's only nought point nought five</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0018">are you sure there's only are you sure there's a thousand</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a thousand mil</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0018">millilitres in a litre?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0049">thousand mil in a litre</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0018">that would make sense</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0049">Cos five hundred mil is a bottle like this</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that would make sense</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0049"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0018">cos it's millilitre isn't it <pause dur="short"/> mil means thousand</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0018">so what's?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0049">so um</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0018">so</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0049">so if um the water let's just tut</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0018">the water was one pound twenty for a litre <pause dur="short"/> so one twenty times by</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0049">one pound twenty</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0018">er divided by a thousand <pause dur="short"/> timesed by</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0049">forty</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> forty <pause dur="short"/> equals nought point nought <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="1100" who="S0049">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0018">five <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0018">so put nought point nought five</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0049">nought point again you see that's er the same as that isn't it?</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0049">oh okay babe <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1108" who="S0049">nought point nought five</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0018">plus</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0049">plus nought point nought five</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0018">plus nought point nought eight</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0049">nought point nought eight</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0018">plus nought point three seven <pause dur="short"/> plus nought point three eight <pause dur="short"/> equals</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0049">ninety-three P <pause dur="short"/> that's more like it</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0018">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> phew <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1116" who="S0049">so that's for ingredients <pause dur="short"/> then I've got bottle</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0049">I mean tut um jar <pause dur="short"/> lid <pause dur="short"/> label <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so that's how we'd work it then</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so what you really need is each ingredient divided by <vocal desc="cough"/> the number of millilitres that it comes in</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see um</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0018">but again you can do that on Excel really easily <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0049">Cos I've got my laptop working now</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0049">so I could get the um that would be easier for your dad <pause dur="short"/> in fact we could work this out <pause dur="short"/> I could do this today</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0018">yeah but I mean he do you know how to <trunc>f</trunc> er make formulas for different columns of er of data?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0049">no</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0018">you see my dad's brilliant at stuff like that</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0049">is he?</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0018">or what what we could do</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0049">well I could shall I um</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0018">what we could do is do it with him <pause dur="short"/> so he can</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0018">teach us how to do it <pause dur="short"/> and then you know if you had to change anything you'd be</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0049">Cos what I might just</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0018">in the know</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0049">quickly <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> Are we still recording?</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0018">huh? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1138" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="1139" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1140" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0018"><vocal desc="cough"/> But it is a monumental task <pause dur="short"/> that's why I think it's much better if if dad finds a way</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0049">Cos especially with his um especially um with the <trunc>la</trunc> with the um tut labels and stuff</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0049">Cos I'm just thinking that almond oil <pause dur="short"/> I could do some of these <pause dur="short"/> it gives me it helps me as well you see if I can</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0049">so a hundred mil <pause dur="short"/> three pound ten <pause dur="short"/> so I'd er just put three pound ten divided by a hundred</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0049">so it costs me nought point do I have to have the nought?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0018">er</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0049">or just put nought point nought <trunc>thr</trunc> would I put that to thirty?</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0018">what do you mean? Sorry</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0049">would I have nought point nought three O? If we were rounding it off</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0018">if you er you you have to round it you can't round it up because that last digit is not higher than five</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0018">so what you just do is get rid of that last digit</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0049">oh okay babe</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0018">so it's nought point nought three</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0049">so you'd have nought point nought three <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna do this <pause dur="short"/> nought point nought three <pause dur="short"/> for one mil</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0018">so what's that? Nought point nought three pence?</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0018">so put</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0049">for one mil</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0018">put P next to it <pause dur="short"/> just so that you</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0018">you got it clear what it is</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> if I can just do some of these and then I'll shall we have a drink?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you want do you wanna cuppa tea?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0049">A cuppa tea</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0018">shall I put the kettle on? Or would you prefer coffee?</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0049">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I might have a coffee actually <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna make it? Or do you want me to make it?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0018">no no no <pause dur="short"/> I'll make it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1172" who="S0049">what about this?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0018">no it's fine</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0018">it's fine <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1176" who="S0049">it'll be funny though <trunc>lis</trunc> listening back to um</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1178" who="S0049">like did you listen back to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s conversation?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0018">no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I just um listened to it quickly to just to work out what um the topics were <pause dur="short"/> cos I have to write a list of what topics</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0049">what was he talking about?</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0018">gosh we were talking about loads of things</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1183" who="S0018">lots of different things <pause dur="short"/> tV programmes <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0049">he's quite interesting isn't it</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no he's a good good talker</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0049">so on this one would I take away the five or have it nought point six three?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> well basically how many decimal places do you want after the dot? Two? No? Cos it's easier to work your head <pause dur="short"/> cos we're talking about pence</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0049">I <trunc>d</trunc> I so don't understand babe <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0018">so you just have two decimal places after the point <pause dur="short"/> yeah? So if you wanted to round it up to three you'd round it up to nought point nought six three <pause dur="short"/> cos that's five or above</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0018">and so if you got nought point nought six three you wouldn't round the six up to seven because the three</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0049">right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0018">is below five <pause dur="short"/> so it would be nought point nought six</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> nought point nought six</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> so I need to just really take off these two</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0049">off er off all the ones that I do</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but be careful because if you you can take them off but make sure you change that figure up one if the one next to it is is <trunc>m</trunc> more than five</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0049">more than five <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0018">but it's not gonna make a huge difference <pause dur="short"/> cos you're you know even if you just make a mistake with a couple of them it's not gonna make a huge difference to your costing</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0018">but it's good to be precise <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1204" who="S0049">yes <pause dur="short"/> so six pounds ninety divided by a hundred <pause dur="short"/> see the other thing is if I was to buy a litre of almond oil I'd save pounds</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0049">but because um these are like smaller</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0049">like the clay <pause dur="short"/> because I'm buying two hundred and fifty grams it's er a lot cheaper</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0018">so how much if a hundred millilitres of almond oil is three pound ten how much would like</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0049">A litre be</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0018">a litre be?</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0049">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> you <trunc>sa</trunc> but you would save cos on the  on the  on your pricing you've got thirty mil <pause dur="short"/> a hundred mil <pause dur="short"/> um two fifty mil <pause dur="short"/> five hundred mil <pause dur="short"/> a thousand <pause dur="short"/> for all different prices <pause dur="short"/> and then each one <pause dur="short"/> so imagine if I was buying that in litres</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0049">you'd save so much money wouldn't you</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0018">you'd probably be buying it at a quarter of the price wouldn't you <pause dur="short"/> per millilitre <pause dur="short"/> but you'll get there <pause dur="short"/> you'll get bigger <pause dur="short"/> you'll start making more profit and it'll start costing you less to make them</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0049"><trunc>S</trunc> so that's gonna be nought point nought seven</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0018"><trunc>W</trunc></u>
<u n="1218" who="S0049">isn't it</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0049">you can tell I didn't pass maths at school</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know why <pause dur="short"/> you're learning quickly</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1223" who="S0018">then again I can't believe I'm teaching <vocal desc="laugh"/> maths <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0049"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're a teacher</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0018">yeah I know but English not maths</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1227" who="S0018">I'm awful  I'm awful  with numbers</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0049">oh no er you're clever you are</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0018">my dad'll probably turn around and say you've done this all wrong <pause dur="short"/> you told her to divide it by a hundred and you needed</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0049">no</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0018">to times it by a hundred <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1232" who="S0049">no you did it right</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No what it is is I used to get paid by the hour</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0018">so I'd always be working out how much I'd get paid <pause dur="short"/> and I'd do different types of classes which were charged at different rates</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1237" who="S0018">and then I'd have to work out the um the tax that I'd have to pay and</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1239" who="S0018">so it was all about</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0049">what's that one babe? I am listening to you</u>
<u n="1241" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> you tell me</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0049">one nought point one seven</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> you only round it up <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't er</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0049">nought point two</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0018">you wouldn't round <vocal desc="cough"/> you wouldn't round it down <pause dur="short"/> start with like the the third figure <pause dur="short"/> is it above five?</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0018">so what do you do to the second figure?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0049">so it'd be nought point one seven</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta get the gist of this</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0018">but why why would you <trunc>rou</trunc> why would you make that six</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0049">because that's</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0018">into seven?</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0049">because the eight is higher than five</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0018"><vocal desc="cough"/> That's the only logic you need to apply</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0049">how am I gonna teach Ava when she goes to school?</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Hopefully they'll have teachers</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1262" who="S0018">that are pretty competent</u>
<u n="1263" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1264" who="S0049">God babe I can really smell garlic</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0018">huh huh</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0049">what did you eat?</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> what was it? Chicken</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0049">was it nice?</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0018">something? Oh it was gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it had ginger <pause dur="short"/> garlic</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0018">as you can smell <pause dur="short"/> tomato <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0049">have you seen um tut Ruchi?</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she was out last night <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0049">was she? Aw</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0018">she's better <pause dur="short"/> her hands are awful <pause dur="short"/> they're</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0049">are they?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0018">now they're a lot better now they've they're not as swollen <pause dur="short"/> but they're all cracked and dry and</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0049">see mine have come up</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0018">oo <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0049">but</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0018">painful</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0049">they're not um this is good really</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0049">but they're but I've noticed my hands are drier <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's the change in weather?</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0049">because your your skin does change <pause dur="short"/> and when you've got dermatitis your skin changes <pause dur="short"/> and hormones <pause dur="short"/> but I wonder why hers are so bad? Cos they were quite bad last time I saw her</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0018">well it was cos she had er I think she had a bit of eczema under her wedding ring</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0049">she's er allergic to her wedding ring isn't she?</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0018">I don't know whether it is that or whether it was just because the eczema was under a ring it started to fester <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1290" who="S0049">Cos the the um <trunc>s</trunc> people with dermatitis shouldn't wear any jewellery</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0049">even earrings</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0049">because of the metal <pause dur="short"/> or like my engagement ring was platinum and I <trunc>d</trunc> I didn't <trunc>re</trunc> er react to it <pause dur="short"/> but that's why I don't wear any jewellery <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>h</trunc> haven't even got my ears pierced</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0049">so she shouldn't wear any jewellery <pause dur="short"/> that's gonna affect it definitely</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well she had to wrap her hands in cling film every night</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1300" who="S0049">aw that's what I had to do</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0018">tut aw</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0049">oh bless her</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0018">but she's got steroids and antibiotics</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0049">tut</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0018">and it's taken away the infection um but</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0049">it's the worst thing you know</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0018">now her hands you know are</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0049">it's the worst thing to have</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0018">after you've had like swollen tut infections</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0049">are they weeping as well? With water?</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0018">not anymore <pause dur="short"/> I think they were <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0049">oh God I feel so sorry for her <pause dur="short"/> er there's nothing she can do either</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0049">but she definitely shouldn't you should tell her not to wear a wedding ring <pause dur="short"/> honestly hon</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> and do you know like the past two months my hands haven't flared up <pause dur="short"/> and I think is she a <trunc>w</trunc> is she a worrier? Does she worry? Is she anxious?</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> not any more than er</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0049">than normal</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0049">then that says because they er they reckon hand dermatitis is er and foot dermatitis is down to stress</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0049">the main thing <pause dur="short"/> and then if you're stressed and then you use something like you could even use lavender</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0049">and you'd still react</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0049">oh I feel so sorry for her <pause dur="short"/> and really when I <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to wrap my hands up at night in cling film and cream <pause dur="short"/> and when I'd wake up in the morning the my hands were soaking wet with water because my hands couldn't breathe</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0049">so in a way I er maybe I should speak to her <pause dur="short"/> she should put bandages on</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0018">gauze?</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0018">or something like that</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0049">but I've got these lovely gloves from the doctors <pause dur="short"/> they're fifty pounds a pair</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0018">are they silk?</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0049">they're beautiful babe</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1336" who="S0049">so if she goes to the doctors and I went and said you know I've heard about these gloves <pause dur="short"/> and she checked the book <pause dur="short"/> she went God <pause dur="short"/> and they were fifty pounds <pause dur="short"/> so she gave me two pairs <pause dur="short"/> but I've I don't know er otherwise I could <trunc>sh</trunc> I could give her a pair <pause dur="short"/> I've only got one pair at the moment cos I don't know where the other pair are <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a look in a minute <pause dur="short"/> and they're lovely <pause dur="short"/> you put them on and you just put your cream on and you can do lots of things round the house <pause dur="short"/> they're not like the cotton gloves <pause dur="short"/> because the cotton ones fall off <pause dur="short"/> they go baggy</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1338" who="S0049">but these ones are really nice</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0018">oh I'll tell her</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0049">I'll try and find them in a minute</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0018">what are they made out of?</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> they are a bit silky <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where they are <pause dur="short"/> they might be in the kitchen <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a look</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't imagine cling film would be the the best thing <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1344" who="S0049">Cos cos it's hot <pause dur="short"/> makes you hot</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it sweats it all</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0049">and with dermatitis you <trunc>s</trunc> you and er what happens is you itch it <pause dur="short"/> the blisters come up <pause dur="short"/> then it swells <pause dur="short"/> so the skin looks swelled</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0049">and then <trunc>f</trunc> for er for it to get better you have to pop the blisters</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0018">urgh</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0049">for the skin to come off to reheal <pause dur="short"/> so it's like um a vicious circle <pause dur="short"/> so they say to put steroid cream on and put the cling film on because it's gonna burst the blisters <pause dur="short"/> but it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> it didn't work for me at all <pause dur="short"/> but the dermatologist they have to tell her that because the next step if it gets worse is she'll go to the skin hospital and then that's their that's what they do <pause dur="short"/> you have to go through the process</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0049">and then what they do at the skin hospital is you take in every single product that you use <pause dur="short"/> whether it be washing up <pause dur="short"/> skincare <pause dur="short"/> shower gels <pause dur="short"/> whatever <pause dur="short"/> and you go in this room and they put a tiny blob on your back</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0049">and they cover it with tape <pause dur="short"/> and you're wrapped up in tape <pause dur="short"/> and you leave it on for a week</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0049">so you can't shower for a week <pause dur="short"/> and then cos you can't get this these things wet <pause dur="short"/> and then they write on your back what what they are</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> God <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1358" who="S0049">and then you go back in a week's time and they take it all off <pause dur="short"/> and like with me I took all the Dr <pause dur="short"/>Hauschka products <pause dur="short"/> cos that's what I was using</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0049">and I reacted to er nearly every single one <pause dur="short"/> my skin had risen</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0018">huh</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0049">it was all red <pause dur="short"/> and my back was bad for months</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0049">after it had all come off <pause dur="short"/> cos I just wouldn't heal <pause dur="short"/> and then they show you then <pause dur="short"/> and then the <trunc>w</trunc> so the one she'll react to they'll know which product it is <pause dur="short"/> then they'll take that product <pause dur="short"/> they'll get</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0049">the ingredients from that product <pause dur="short"/> so even like lavender <pause dur="short"/> people think oh you won't react to lavender <pause dur="short"/> but I react to lavender</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0049">because lavender's got geranial in it <pause dur="short"/> which is a perfume</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0049">and geranial is an irritant for people with eczema and dermatitis <pause dur="short"/> so it doesn't necessarily say</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0018">but isn't lavender oil just pure lavender oil?</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0049">no it's got it's obviously got things in it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0049">and that's like on my products I've got lavender <pause dur="short"/> but on my tox report <pause dur="short"/> my incy on my labels there's geranial <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> and geranial's one of the things I reacted to</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0049">do you see what I mean? So</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0018">tut <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0049">Cos it's the components <pause dur="short"/> there's probably a thousand components in lavender oil</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0049">probably more than that</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0049">and they take out the strongest ones <pause dur="short"/> so like on my tox report and on my label there's for lavender I've got a list of things</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0049">and the percentages <pause dur="short"/> and I've got those on my labels for my <trunc>writi</trunc> for my label <pause dur="short"/> cos er</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0018">you would've thought that lavender essential oil would just in just</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0049">hm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0018">contain lavender oil pressed from the flowers <pause dur="short"/> no?</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then it's still got lavender's still got things in like I can <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="1389" who="S0018">oh the</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0049">it's still got you know</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> the er</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0049">and um</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0018">the components of the oil</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0049">I'm trying to think <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and also like I'm trying to think <pause dur="short"/> like on um <pause dur="short"/> but it is only in essential oils <pause dur="short"/> even camomile has got geranial in it</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0018">really? So what is gernial? Is it a?</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0049">it's a <trunc>perf</trunc> it's a perfume <pause dur="short"/> it's a  it's a  part</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0018">A <trunc>natu</trunc></u>
<u n="1398" who="S0049">it's a component of camomile</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0018">so it's a natural perfume?</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but again it's an irritant <pause dur="short"/> so on my in my calming scrub and in fact my calming facial oil on my tox report and on my labels it says geranial</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0049">you know <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>b</trunc> and it by law it has to go on there</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0018">oh well <pause dur="short"/> at least people can</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0049">so</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0018">people who are <trunc>aller</trunc></u>
<u n="1406" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0018">allergic to it can see what's in it</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0049">but I was shocked because I couldn't understand with all this Hauschka business <pause dur="short"/> and I was like right so my main er ingredient er the hospital have said is geranial <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> then I get all my tox reports back and I've got geranial in my products</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0018">but the</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0049">so er so I'm like hang on so I'm like what the hell? This is what I've reacted to <pause dur="short"/> geranial <pause dur="short"/> from Dr <pause dur="short"/>Hauschka <pause dur="short"/> so and this is how I've learnt in the whole process is because I learnt that you know about all these components in all these essential oils</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0049">so that's why my <trunc>f</trunc> in my <trunc>f</trunc> calming cleansing cream I've got no essential oils</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0018">ah okay</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0049">so I've got nothing in there that would harm</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0049">so if I went if that's why I use my calming cream <pause dur="short"/> because I know I <trunc>w</trunc> will not react to er to it</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0018">but do you react to your products</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0049">I could do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0018">that have got geranial in?</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0049">I could do <pause dur="short"/> not at the moment <pause dur="short"/> but I could <pause dur="short"/> if say my hormones change</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0049">and say I'm not very well <pause dur="short"/> and my skin's a bit sensitive <pause dur="short"/> like my skin's sensitive at the moment <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't reacted to anything</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0049">but if my hormones change and I use something then maybe yeah <pause dur="short"/> probably would</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0049">but my calming range I wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> my balancing range and my nourishing range I would <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos of the essential oils <pause dur="short"/> but in a way there's lots of products out there which say they're calming</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0049">but I can't use them</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's just probably marketing purposes though <vocal desc="laugh"/> isn't it</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0018">that they name it in a certain way</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0049">so it just <trunc>ma</trunc> just makes me angry <pause dur="short"/> because er the stuff that is in and then you've got all that with paraben <pause dur="short"/> sulphates <pause dur="short"/> alcohol <pause dur="short"/> can you imagine?</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0049">the um what people are putting on their skin</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0049">that's a bit noisy <pause dur="short"/> did you hear that babe?</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0018">I know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1438" who="S0049">this guy came down the road earlier <trunc>h</trunc> honking his horn going rah rah rah <pause dur="short"/> have you heard them?</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0049">picking up the um your fridges and your</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0049">freezers and your metal</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0018">the scrap metal guys</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> made me</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the ones that go round <trunc>ou</trunc> our neighbourhood have got like a little flute <pause dur="short"/> and they</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0049">oh really</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0018">they play a little melody <pause dur="short"/> the same one every time so you know it's them <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1448" who="S0049">aw</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0018">crazy crazy</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0049">right <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna pop to the loo babe</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0049"><unclear/> I'm supposed to be going to Cafe <anon type="place"/> tonight but</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0018">to where?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0049"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1455" who="S0018">where's that?</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0049">in town</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0018">who are you going there with?</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0049"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's just text me actually <pause dur="short"/> um yes babe</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0018">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0049">oh he's a really really old friend <pause dur="short"/> he's um tut he's um he owns um tut Temple Gym in town <pause dur="short"/> you know Temple Gym? By the um</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0049">God um I've he's been my friend for about since I was about eighteen</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0018">can't you get a free gym membership with him then?</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0049">oh God <pause dur="short"/> it's like a bodybuilding thing</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1466" who="S0049">the <trunc>w</trunc> the women in there are all like muscley and</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1468" who="S0049">but one thing he's doing in the summer he's <trunc>p</trunc> he puts on a show <pause dur="short"/> he did one last year <pause dur="short"/> where the X Factor's held</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0049">and it's his show and he has people pay to have their stands <pause dur="short"/> and he's given me a stand for free</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0018">ah fantastic</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0049">so I'm really looking forward to that</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0018">when's that?</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0049">I'm not sure yet <pause dur="short"/> it's in the summer some time <pause dur="short"/> but I'll speak to him about it tonight <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm gonna get some nice things</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0018"><trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="1476" who="S0049">made and</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0018">it's not when you're thinking of going to Dubai is it?</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0049">I think it's September you know <pause dur="short"/> I think it's the beginning of September <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure when it is <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure last <trunc>y</trunc> or was it October? Could be October actually babe</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0018">cool <pause dur="short"/> you'll have <trunc>anyth</trunc> everything up and running by then</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's gonna be really good for me to do</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0018">where did you meet him?</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0049">um he's from <anon type="place"/> so er where I used to live <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and he's he paid my deposit for my old apartment</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> which then I bought <trunc>s</trunc> obviously it wasn't as much as here but and he said just keep it <pause dur="short"/> just have it</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0049">which was really nice</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0018">did he set up his own business from scratch?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's loaded babe <pause dur="short"/> he's I'd say he was a millionaire <pause dur="short"/> he's I even spoke to him on the phone the other day about him giving me some money for this</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0049">but the thing is I didn't really wanna ask him</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0049">because he's a friend and he cos he gave me my deposit like I I just feel a bit bad <pause dur="short"/> but he did mention it so</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0018">or er tut</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0049">you know</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0018">view it as a loan? And give it him back</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> but um but he's a nice guy <pause dur="short"/> he's Chinese</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> is it like martial art gym?</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> he's um well what he did he um he open he had a gym in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then um <trunc>t</trunc> then they were doing like you know bodybuilding and all this kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> then he closed that one <pause dur="short"/> then he <trunc>ha</trunc> Dorian Yates who's a famous guy <pause dur="short"/> have you heard of him?</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0049">he's like in that industry <pause dur="short"/> he's like I used to massage him at Hotel du Vin <pause dur="short"/> he's very er he's known for his supplements and</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0049">he sells products with his name and stuff on <pause dur="short"/> it was his gym <pause dur="short"/> temple Gym <pause dur="short"/> and he gave it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos they're very close friends</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0049">and er or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was working or doing something anyway <pause dur="short"/> and now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s took over that gym <pause dur="short"/> and now he's not there anymore cos he's doing these shows or something <pause dur="short"/> but he's er he's done well for <trunc>w</trunc> you know for er for the amount of time</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0049">and I think he's doing supplements and things like that <pause dur="short"/> my <trunc>s</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he's friend with my sister as well <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0018">so what time are you gonna meet him?</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0049">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I was just texting him now <pause dur="short"/> cos um it's half five now <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realize how</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0018">is it?</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0049">late it was <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0018">blimey <pause dur="short"/> it's late</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0049">and I don't mind really <pause dur="short"/> I could always meet him tomorrow <trunc>ni</trunc> cos I wanted to go and do um bums and tums tonight</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1514" who="S0049">but I've got no trainers <pause dur="short"/> that's what I was gonna say <pause dur="short"/> I've got no</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0049">trainers <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but Pilates <pause dur="short"/> I could've done Pilates <pause dur="short"/> there's a class at seven</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0018">where's that?</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0049">at <trunc>m</trunc> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I nearly <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0049">I nearly said more cocks</u>
<u n="1521" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1522" who="S0018">little Freudian slip there</u>
<u n="1523" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1524" who="S0018">how do you get there from here?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0049"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The bus <pause dur="short"/> could walk I guess</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0018">is that <trunc>Ac</trunc></u>
<u n="1527" who="S0049">but I don't know if I can be bothered</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0018">is it Acocks Green?</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> it's only like three stops down</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0049">it's um past um so you go down <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> High Street</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0049">past the lights <pause dur="short"/> keep going  keep going keep going  Down the hill <pause dur="short"/> and it's down there</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0049">before you get to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But I dunno if I wanna be bothered to go out</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's it's always difficult isn't it</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0049">it's cos it's so light <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>n</trunc> normally it'd be dark now wouldn't it</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> seasons are changing <pause dur="short"/> we could do a bit of stretching here</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1541" who="S0049">could couldn't we babe</u>
<u n="1542" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1543" who="S0049">just go to the loo <pause dur="short"/> and I'll just take</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll put the kettle on</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0049">alright hon</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="1546" who="S0049">just see if um</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0018">so how much are the bags?</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0049">apparently he rang me back <pause dur="short"/> well the bags</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1549" who="S0018">which ones are these? Are they the the brown paper ones? Or the <trunc>ju</trunc> jute ones?</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> both <pause dur="short"/> they're um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1551" who="S0018">are they from the same supplier?</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0018">oh they're lovely</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0049">have you seen the cotton bag in there?</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the the kind of</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0049">so</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0049">well these are the ones I really liked <pause dur="short"/> but they're too much really <pause dur="short"/> cos er ten for five ten um hang on <pause dur="short"/> they're the jute <pause dur="short"/> cotton <pause dur="short"/> here we go <pause dur="short"/> cotton bags</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0018">is it the raw cotton ones? The the kind of stiff ones?</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0049">these are them</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0018">they're lovely</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> so for a pack of ten I think they're six seventy for the size I want <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but really I don't know what to do <pause dur="short"/> what do you think? Because I'll show you these paper bags <pause dur="long"/> So imagine those <pause dur="short"/> and then <trunc>y</trunc> you'd put your products in and then you fold it over and put a sticker on <pause dur="short"/> and then you just stamp the bag with the stamp</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0049">and I think that looks it's nice isn't it <pause dur="short"/> but then that's fine if someone buys er one cleanser or one moisturizer <pause dur="short"/> but if someone buys a cleanser a toner and a moisturizer they need a proper bag</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0049">because that's just not gonna they need to carry it</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0018">can you not have bags like that er just with the little loops on the top?</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0049">they're not strong enough</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0049">for instance my body scrubs are big glass</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0049">um five hundred mil jars</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0049">and they're really heavy <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> those would have to go in a see the other bags I don't everyone else does these bags and I don't</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0018">which ones? <pause dur="long"/> Are they paper or material?</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0049">ah <pause dur="short"/> they are these</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0049">but I just think they're a bit er</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0018">but why would those be strong enough if the brown paper bag wouldn't be?</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> the brain brown paper bag er isn't strong enough cos they're like paper</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0049">but these bags are really expensive</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0018">ah they're glossy so they're really</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0049">and they're a bit <trunc>ta</trunc> er they're not what mm what I like <pause dur="short"/> so that's why I'm thinking these cotton bags</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0049">if I got two sizes</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1587" who="S0049">tut</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0018">is it the same ones as <trunc>y</trunc> the one that you've</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0018">got in the the other room?</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see that you know the Hessian-y one?</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0049">that's really nice <pause dur="short"/> it's just but I want <trunc>s</trunc> people to reuse it <pause dur="short"/> otherwise I go for a <trunc>pr</trunc> you know a one of these</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0049">but they're expensive <pause dur="short"/> thirteen ninety-five for ten look</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0018">phew</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0049">well it'd be that one</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0018">oh those are the jute ones? And how much are the cotton ones?</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0049">tut <pause dur="short"/> so hang on <pause dur="short"/> so they're <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>tw</trunc></u>
<u n="1600" who="S0018">ah they're <trunc>e</trunc></u>
<u n="1601" who="S0049">twenty-five for eight ten?</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> that can't be right if it's ten for eight forty-five?</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0049">that doesn't make sense does it?</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0018">it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> then again if you buy them now at that price <pause dur="short"/> cos they've got that price advertised <pause dur="short"/> it's a legal requirement that they sell it</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0049" trans="overlap">let's just put in there twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> see what it says <pause dur="long"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0018">huh <pause dur="short"/> oh no er look total</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0049" trans="overlap">oh God</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0018">two hundred and two <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh no just put oh er no it's says a pack of ten <pause dur="short"/> ah okay <pause dur="short"/> so if you buy twenty-five packets of</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0049">oh God</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0018">ten the price is reduced <pause dur="short"/> that's probably what it means <pause dur="long"/> Just put one in <pause dur="short"/> see how much they charge you for one</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0049">mm God what am I doing? I just wanna see <pause dur="short"/> I wish I could show you <pause dur="short"/> let me see if I can get it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1612" who="S0018">you see these ones are really I mean I <trunc>pr</trunc> I think I prefer the cotton ones</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I do babe <pause dur="short"/> I'll just show you <unclear/></u>
<u n="1614" who="S0018">are the cotton ones cheaper than the jute ones or the Hessian ones?</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0049"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1616" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I just think they look a bit more classy</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0049">the cotton?</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're more er more organic more in the lines of your range</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0049">see and the other thing is right so</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0018">and they can reuse those as well <pause dur="short"/> the the jute ones are</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0049">problem is I would've liked them white but it doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/> but this isn't the box but I need to find a box this size in white</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0049">and they open it and this is to send out samples <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna have the cleanser <pause dur="short"/> the toner <pause dur="short"/> the facial oil <pause dur="short"/> a mask <pause dur="short"/> and a moisturizer</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0049">and then that will go <pause dur="short"/> be stamped</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0049">with Honest <pause dur="short"/> with my business card</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0018">lovely</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0049">and that's why I want white <pause dur="short"/> cos that  And then I'd like it to go into a bag <pause dur="short"/> not that one obviously <pause dur="short"/> but the next size up <pause dur="short"/> and then I'll post and this'll be stamped with Honest on</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0049">and then I'll post that <pause dur="short"/> because I think it's first impressions that if someone's gonna open that aren't they go nice bag</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1633" who="S0049">nice box</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1635" who="S0049">nice products</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1637" who="S0049">it's simple <pause dur="short"/> so I like that size box <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0018">have you bought boxes before?</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta find some <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but again this box is flimsy <pause dur="short"/> I want something that says</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0049">you know cos it's er <trunc>thi</trunc> this it's first impression so I've got to</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0018">have you tried Alibaba dot com?</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a <trunc>n</trunc> it's a nightmare babe <pause dur="short"/> you need to buy five ten twenty thousand of things</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1645" who="S0049">it's an absolute nightmare <pause dur="short"/> but um they have <trunc>ni</trunc> they have things on there that you'd I'd really like</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0049">but I just can't afford to buy in packs like that <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0018">what what are the pricings for like a thousand?</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0049">um well it's just I dunno but it's um hang on <pause dur="short"/> er I'll just bring them in</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0018">Cos if it wasn't more <trunc>expensi</trunc> I don't know how much more economical it is to buy something from a um a wholesaler? I mean even if you've got more than you need <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether er that would would that work out cheaper than buying from? Cos these aren't wholesalers are they? Or are they?</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0049">um yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've they're e-<trunc>mai</trunc> cos I've spoke to them on the phone</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> see really I could do with a box probably that size couldn't I really?</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0049">Cos I don't wanna send out too many products do I?</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> cos especially if they're just samples <pause dur="short"/> you don't wanna be wasting too much of your products</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0018">giving them out free</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0049">that's what I mean</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0018">have you not got sample sized like little small? Can or isn't there some kind of machine that makes foil packages of?</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0049">oh God yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's so babe it's so <trunc>exp</trunc> this is honestly the cheapest way <pause dur="short"/> I've been down that route <pause dur="short"/> it's just ridiculously expensive <pause dur="short"/> and then to get all your your label your branding on there</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0049">like for instance to send a cleanser in that size that's thirty mil <pause dur="short"/> obviously with a white lid <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> and the other thing you see <pause dur="short"/> my the printers I'm not doing um labels for these because it's gonna cost me a lot of money again <pause dur="short"/> so on my DYMO in there</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0049">on my printer really I've got to make my own labels that look really professional</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0049">just to send out samples</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0018">I'm sure that there's some kind of er thing in Word</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0049">really?</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0018">with which you can do labels <pause dur="short"/> cos the where I was teaching there was um the language department had a secretary</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0018">and she did all the the admin work <pause dur="short"/> and she made out labels to stick in the pupils' books <pause dur="short"/> like if you're marking their homework</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0049" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0018">and very good work or <trunc>y</trunc> your target is to lay out your work</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0049">so you can put your logo on there?</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can put anything on there <pause dur="short"/> she used to put like little er little pictures of the Eiffel Tower and <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1677" who="S0049">oh really? Aw that's</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0018">actually I think I've still got some <pause dur="short"/> I should I'll hunt them out and show you how</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0018">professional they can look <pause dur="short"/> cos they they really did look</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0049">like good <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I'm sure you can do that in labels in Word</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> well that would be brilliant</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0018">if it is just on the <trunc>nor</trunc> it's er just on normal white sticky labels isn't it?</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0018">just um rectangular?</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0049">okay</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0018">and you can do them as small or as large as you need them</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0049">that's what I need to do then <pause dur="short"/> cos really on here I just want a label with Honest my logo and then the name of the product then it just say sample</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0049">so I don't really need a box <pause dur="short"/> I could do if I had another <trunc>li</trunc> little one there I could send just that out couldn't I?</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0049">Cos the mask isn't gonna cost me much to send <pause dur="short"/> obviously my moisturizers are a lot more</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0018">what's the cheapest products that you have to make?</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> I think it's probably my toners</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0018">so you could maybe stock up on the toners in the samples <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And leave the <trunc>th</trunc> or make the</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0049">the thing is when er I need to send out really um</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0018">that kind of works doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0018">is the lid on that top one properly?</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0049">on that one? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0018">no that's not gonna close</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0049">or if I had tissue paper printed with Honest on</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0049">then that would take up space <pause dur="short"/> and then I could have it folded <pause dur="short"/> and then with a little sticker I can do on my Dymo saying Honest</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0049">could undo the sticker <pause dur="short"/> unwrap it <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1708" who="S0018">how about a little candle? You know the tea light</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0018">size? That would fill</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0018">the space</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0018">then again those are more expensive aren't they</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and everyone does those as well <pause dur="short"/> cos I I wanna I don't wanna come across as um what are these? As like everybody else <unclear/></u>
<u n="1716" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the tissue paper idea'd be good</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos that'd be easy <pause dur="short"/> I mean I can get printed ribbon for <trunc>h</trunc> you know a pound a metre or something <pause dur="short"/> that's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0018">well why not just get um in that case tissue <trunc>pa</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> don't worry about the box <pause dur="short"/> tissue paper with the logo on</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0018">A bit of ribbon with the logo on and just tie it around</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I did think about that</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0018">pop it in a bag</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0049">or I don't even have to have a box</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0049">do I?</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> you could just put them all in the bag <pause dur="short"/> er maybe you know that um tut like the cardboard coloured er very thin strips of paper?</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0018">which you could probably do in a</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0049">look</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that'd be fine</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0049">could just have that in the post couldn't you</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you wanted to pack it out with the <trunc>s</trunc> tut the shredded bits of paper or something <pause dur="short"/> or tissue paper</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0018">what did you do for <trunc>Lon</trunc> for the Paris Fashion Week? Or was it London Fashion Week? How did you present?</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0049">oh I just had lots er just gave her loads of these <pause dur="short"/> posted her these and she put them in her own bags</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0018">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> did you have any</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0049">no</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0018">feedback from them?</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0049">oh er no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>p</trunc> she er she sent me an e-mail saying she was gonna let me know what people thought <pause dur="short"/> but she <trunc>ha</trunc> she didn't <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I need to contact her really <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't had any</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0018">who did she give them to?</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0049">just people that were looking at her show that but she did say that um she was gonna give them to the best people <pause dur="short"/> but you I don't think she was just saying that <pause dur="short"/> but to be honest hon they were I wasn't ready <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> I did the labels myself with just Honest on</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0049">you know <pause dur="short"/> they were just <pause dur="short"/> do you know I don't I think I'm just best sending that in the post with my logo on</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that's a good idea <pause dur="short"/> cos boxes are <trunc>j</trunc> it's just another hassle to to find them <pause dur="short"/> and it's another cost <pause dur="short"/> and you gotta find one that's</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0049">would've been nice</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0018"><trunc>s</trunc> fits perfectly <pause dur="short"/> and now you can get the smaller sized bag as well</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0049">would've been nice to have um that with Honest ribbon <pause dur="short"/> there's this guy <pause dur="short"/> he sold er</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0018">can you not rethread them?</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0018">you could do</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0049">I could do <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> could have Honest ribbon couldn't I? Through there</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how many are you thinking of sending out?</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0049">tut well <pause dur="short"/> my list of salons is endless</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1755" who="S0049">there's huh so far my list of salons I have over three hundred</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0018">phew</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0049">but</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0018">that's a lot <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1759" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna but obviously I can't do it all at once <pause dur="short"/> so mm this woman we're getting together the best list of the best spas <pause dur="short"/> and then for instance <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> she's um she <trunc>m</trunc> messaged me <pause dur="short"/> her website's really nice <pause dur="short"/> about my products <pause dur="short"/> so and she um is it recording?</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0049">she said I'll just show you her website <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> so I look when she messaged me I looked at her website <pause dur="short"/> and it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> it's perfect for like where I wanna be <pause dur="short"/> see she sells all nice <pause dur="short"/> she even sells um it's a bit like fusion I guess <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0018">well is it interior?</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0018">oh er it's er lots of different things</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0049">she even sells Tonfisk <pause dur="short"/> which is my you know my um tut tea-pot and</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0049">um cup?</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's lovely</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0049">so she sells all really nice things <pause dur="short"/> and someone like her would be perfect to stock my products</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0018">does she already have <trunc>s</trunc> beauty products on there?</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0049">no</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0018">nice <pause dur="short"/> all very design</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she's like a perfect customer really <pause dur="short"/> like she even sells the tea lights I've got</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1775" who="S0049">and there's my Tonfisk</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1777" who="S0049">there are my cups look <pause dur="short"/> they're so beautiful <pause dur="short"/> one broke <pause dur="short"/> I was gutted</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1779" who="S0049">Cos they're so expensive <pause dur="short"/> forty quid look <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1780" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0049">I know <pause dur="short"/> I was gutted when it broke</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0018">is it wood?</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0049">for one</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0018">er</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0018">oh only the handle</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0049">er and my actual tea-pot which is that one <pause dur="short"/> a hundred and fifty quid look <trunc>f</trunc> just for that</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0018">huh</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0049">and I'd got er I've got that</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0018">oh my God</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0049">and I've got one of those and I've got that</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1793" who="S0049">but um and I was hoping that she had seen my picture on Twitter <pause dur="short"/> because I've got that in my Twitter in my picture haven't I <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0049">my tea my tea-pot</u>
<u n="1796" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1797" who="S0049">so someone like her is perfect to have <unclear/></u>
<u n="1798" who="S0018">how did you get in touch with her?</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0049">she got in touch with me <pause dur="short"/> she <trunc>f</trunc> she follows me on Twitter</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0049">tut so if I ordered some of these <pause dur="short"/> get my stamp <pause dur="short"/> then inside would go um a business card <pause dur="short"/> and a brochure on the top <pause dur="short"/> and then I'd just mail it out <pause dur="short"/> I think that's enough isn't it</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0049">instead of wasting it on packaging</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0049">Cos <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> which is what I was before <pause dur="short"/> these are the boxes we used with our logo on</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0049">that's why I've still got that one <pause dur="long"/> Well that's</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0018"><trunc>W</trunc></u>
<u n="1809" who="S0049">sorted that so</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0018"><trunc>D</trunc> I think if you're gonna put stuff in a bag er you don't need a box as well <pause dur="short"/> er it's kind of</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0018">er too much packaging <pause dur="short"/> it kind of goes against your</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0018">ethos as well doesn't it</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0049">so in which case hon that's <trunc>m</trunc> gonna be my sample bag and my candle bag</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0049">I'm trying to think if I can use it for anything else <pause dur="short"/> and I don't even know what size that is</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0018">the bag?</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to measure it <pause dur="short"/> so that will be my sample bag <pause dur="short"/> candle bag <pause dur="short"/> let's just <trunc>p</trunc> you don't mind me doing this do you while you're here?</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> not at all</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0049">let me just try this candle</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0018">have you got a tape measure?</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll get it <pause dur="short"/> hang on</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0018">do you know where it is? Er is it in the kitchen?</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0049">tut um yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll just put the</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0018">have you checked the candle fits okay? Yeah</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0049">perfect</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0018">perfectly</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0049">so my candle bag</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0018">lovely <pause dur="short"/> it looks er it looks really professional as well</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0049">do you think babe?</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0049">I'm trying to think if I can use that for anything else <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0018">oh these candles smell so good <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1835" who="S0049">I know <pause dur="short"/> they're gorgeous aren't they</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0018">are they two toned?</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0049">no</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0018">the colours?</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0049">it's just from the wax when it's um</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> oh cos it's against the glass</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0049"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1842" who="S0018">oh it smells so good</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0049">is it centimetres? That's centimetres there isn't it?</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's eight</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0049">so it's nine</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0018">nineteen</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0049">nine centimetres by huh</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1849" who="S0049">sorry</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0018">that's alright</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0049"><trunc>T</trunc> um</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0018">it's nineteen</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0049">it's nineteen by</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0018">fourteen</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0049">nineteen by fourteen</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0018">ah it smells so good <pause dur="short"/> what's it got in it? Lemongrass <pause dur="short"/> lavender <pause dur="short"/> and geranium <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0049">it's nice isn't it <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> sample bag and candle bag <pause dur="short"/> then I would have so now I've just gotta decide what bag to have <pause dur="short"/> so imagine you go to Caroline McGrath's shop</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0049">and you buy one moisturizer</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1861" who="S0049">you <trunc>y</trunc> you'd have it in this or you'd have it in that paper bag</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0049">the paper bag's gonna work out cheaper</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0018">if I were you I'd keep the cotton bags for the the samples you send out to people that you want to be making orders with you</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0049">and the candle <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1866" who="S0018">and then when people actually buy retail</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0018">keep them in the paper bags</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0049">okay <pause dur="short"/> so then the paper bags will be for <trunc>w</trunc> so I'll have one size <pause dur="short"/> so if a customer only buys one or two products <pause dur="short"/> but then if a customer's buying cleanser toner and a moisturizer which at a spa she would <pause dur="short"/> tut or for instance when I used to work at Hotel du Vin well we had to sell our retail <pause dur="short"/> so people would go away with four or five products <pause dur="short"/> and they came in bags then <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to have a proper bag</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0049">or if someone's going into a shop and buying a candle <pause dur="short"/> a scrub <pause dur="short"/> and a moisturizer <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna need a stronger bag aren't I</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0049">so I either sell it in</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0049">well in which case er they would have tissue to wrap up the products and then one of those jute bags</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0049">kinda thing in cotton</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="long"/> And maybe just like um actually if you  if you  got the printed ribbon with the logo you wouldn't need to print the tissue paper <pause dur="short"/> you could just get some cheap tissue <trunc>pap</trunc> well not cheap but <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0049">tut um</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0018">not not stuff that looks cheap <pause dur="short"/> the stuff that costs</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0049">tissue paper</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0018">that costs less</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0018">or <trunc>w</trunc> some that's got like flecks in</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0049">no I just want plain white really with probably just plain white tissue</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0049">and then on my Dymo I've got labels that big I print off with Honest on</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0049">they're like that big</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0049">so the <trunc>s</trunc> the they will have a sheet of labels and then cos when you're in a shop they can then just wrap the product up</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0018">yeah um yeah</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0049">put a sticker on and put it in the bag</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0049">Cos especially cos some of them are glass and some are plastic</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0018">Good idea <pause dur="long"/> <trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="1897" who="S0049">so in which case cotton bags <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0018">are you sure you can't find them cheaper on er other sites?</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0049">tut yeah oh babe honestly I've done so much research with these guys <pause dur="short"/> but they I don't have them for they give me I'll find the e-mail in a minute <pause dur="short"/> they give me they're not at this price <pause dur="short"/> they're only a little bit cheaper</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0049">but you can get <trunc>ni</trunc> er cotton bags like this but they're not as um they're not as nice cos I've had so many samples sent to me</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0049">and some of them were like really cheap</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0049">like looking</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0018">oh you don't want cheap looking</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0049">see they do backpacks as well look</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Aw <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> How much are they?</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0049">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> five hundred by seven <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>hundre</trunc> oh God they've done it in <trunc>m</trunc> in um in <trunc>mi</trunc> millimetres <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0018">uh</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0049">oh gosh <pause dur="short"/> what would <trunc>mil</trunc> <trunc>millim</trunc> what would that one be then? Would that be a hundred and forty by two hundred?</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0018">how many millimetres does it say?</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0049">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0018">it's forty-five by thirty</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0049">five pounds twenty for ten <pause dur="short"/> but I'll check my e-mail <pause dur="short"/> so they're five pounds twenty <pause dur="short"/> but bearing in mind the shops pay for their bags</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0049">so salons will buy a pack of bags</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0049">if they want them</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0049">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0049">otherwise if not then I'll just give them tissue paper</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0049">and they'll the clients will put it in the bag or whatever <pause dur="short"/> but most spas will buy their own <trunc>b</trunc> will buy their bags <pause dur="short"/> five twenty for ten <pause dur="short"/> so fifty-two P each <pause dur="short"/> so it just has to go into my costing doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> for the candles</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0049">and then my stamp's not <trunc>gonn</trunc> gonna <trunc>co</trunc> cost much is it? Cos of the ink and well the stamp's gonna be I reckon it'll be about fifteen pounds <pause dur="short"/> but it's gonna last me isn't it <pause dur="short"/> so the and then <trunc>pape</trunc> um tut so really a bag <pause dur="short"/> two hundred and fifty-one so that's twenty-five centimetres by three hundred</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0018">by thirty <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0049">that's enough for like a couple of products isn't it?</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's probably the biggest you're gonna need</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0049">Cos the next size up then is three hundred by</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0018">unless you buy the backpacks</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0049">four fifty</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0018">they're cool <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1935" who="S0049">which is like that big</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0049">which is way too big</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0018">no that's too big <pause dur="short"/> unless somebody buys a lot of products</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0049">well no people everyone walking round with Honest <unclear/></u>
<u n="1940" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1941" who="S0049"><unclear/> backpacks <unclear/></u>
<u n="1942" who="S0018">that's the aim <pause dur="short"/> if everyone can buy ten products each they can have a backsack free <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1943" who="S0049">well this is perfect</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0049">in fact I really like this bag</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0018">but it'll be difficult to stamp it won't it</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0049">it's like I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="1948" who="S0018">then again</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0049">but you know like potato bags?</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0049">you buy your potatoes in <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0018">well you could huh</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0049">I don't know which ones I prefer</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0018">do you definitely wanna stamp the bag with the logo?</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's gotta be <pause dur="short"/> cos I can't afford to get them printed <pause dur="short"/> prints I got a quote</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0018">but you definitely want the logo on the bag?</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0049">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos it's um</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0018">but will you be able to get er a logo on that bag? Cos it's quite rough material isn't it</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0049">tut it's <trunc>prob</trunc> it's gonna cos I want people to reuse <pause dur="short"/> I want people to be proud of their bags as well</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Aw <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1961" who="S0049">do you know what I mean? Like if I had a bag like that I'd reuse it for in my bathroom or something</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well maybe</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0049">I don't know <trunc>re</trunc> I don't know</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0018">uh</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0049">which one do you prefer?</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0018">come here <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's lovely isn't it <pause dur="short"/> and actually it's it's heavier duty <pause dur="short"/> so it would be better as you say if someone's buying the glass tut containers <pause dur="short"/> I like both of them <pause dur="short"/> but er I think it will be easier to stamp the logo on the cotton</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0018">but</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0018">I mean there's</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0018">no reason why you couldn't maybe get some of this material <pause dur="short"/> stamp the material <pause dur="short"/> and then just like er sew it on</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0049">oh God babe <pause dur="short"/> you're joking</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1975" who="S0049">um</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0018">can give your nan something to do</u>
<u n="1977" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1978" who="S0018">nan <pause dur="short"/> I need you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1979" who="S0049">I think they're the same price</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0018">they are lovely though <pause dur="short"/> but I like tut</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're the same price</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0018">they both say the same thing <pause dur="short"/> they're both very organic materials and</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0018">nice and pure</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0049"><vocal desc="cough"/> See I <trunc>cou</trunc> I could mm I don't know if I wanna keep changing though and have three different bags <pause dur="short"/> but I could have candles and samples in there <pause dur="short"/> and then these bags <pause dur="short"/> heavier ones <pause dur="short"/> for when people buy</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0049">you know a scrub or in actual fact if someone buys a scrub and they're in these these are gonna be loads better aren't they</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they'll protect the glass better as well <pause dur="short"/> well maybe in that case don't stamp the those bags with the logos <pause dur="short"/> put the ribbon through the</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0049">Cos that's a scrub in there <pause dur="short"/> obviously a lot heavier cos it's gonna be full of products <pause dur="short"/> see?</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it does need something more heavy-duty doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> hm <pause dur="short"/> and the scrub's gonna be heavier isn't it <pause dur="short"/> cos this is empty</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0049">it's gonna be <trunc>f</trunc> yeah really heavy <pause dur="short"/> because it's full of salts and and it's in a box <pause dur="short"/> they come in a box as well</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0018">well in that case you're definitely gonna want a bag that's more heavy-duty so that especially well if it's in a <trunc>ba</trunc> if it's in a box that'll probably protect it</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0049">in fact</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0018">quite well <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0049">I know this isn't full and it's not got salt in but this is just oil</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really heavy</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0049">so with salt in as well or sugar it's gonna be even heavier</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it will be</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0049">um put that in the bag</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0018">let's see how it feels <pause dur="short"/> why don't you put a candle in as well? Just in case</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0049">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0018">people buy two glass things</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna have to be this bag <pause dur="short"/> see?</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0018">lovely <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice little shopping bag <pause dur="short"/> it looks like the um the you know the baguette bags that the French carry around <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2005" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what? That's the bag I'm having</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0049">so that's a decision made <pause dur="short"/> and really er to do my branding it doesn't matter that I've got different ones</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0049">I think it's quite nice</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0018">they do complement each other as well <pause dur="short"/> they could be used together</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0049">so the size of that one is thirty-five <pause dur="short"/> so three hundred and fifty by a hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0018">so how much are those?</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0049">they are <pause dur="long"/> oh no <trunc>f</trunc> four hundred by five hundred <pause dur="short"/> is it that one? Three fifty by four hundred</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0018">yeah that's what it was</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0049">well that's <trunc>twent</trunc> mm no so that's not it either</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0018">how big is it? Thirty? What was it?</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0049">er <pause dur="short"/> this one's thirty-five <pause dur="short"/> so three fifty</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0049">that way <pause dur="short"/> and then two</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0018">three fifty by</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0049">twenty</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0018">twenty-two</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0049">two hundred and sixty</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0018">isn't it two twenty-six? Cos it's twenty</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0049">yeah</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0018">six</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0049">but two hundred and sixty millimetres that is isn't it</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0018">isn't it two hundred and twenty-six? How many centimetres is it?</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0049">it's um tut twenty-six</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> so it would</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0049">so it's two hundred and sixty</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0018">two hundred and sixty millimetres <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> do they not have that size on the webpage?</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> which is weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0018">very bizarre <pause dur="short"/> they sent you that as a sample?</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0049">mm</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0018">let's see</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0049">ah <pause dur="short"/> two hundred and thirty by three hundred</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0018">that's definitely not</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0049">uh <pause dur="short"/> bizarre</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0018">how very weird <pause dur="short"/> so how much are those anyway?</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0049">um they are five ten for ten no four eighty-five for ten</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0018">that's okay <pause dur="short"/> it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="2043" who="S0049">which is cheaper than the smaller ones</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0049">large jute bag which I've got in there is seven ten for ten <pause dur="short"/> so the large ones <pause dur="short"/> let me just measure that large one <pause dur="short"/> I know it's too big but just to see if the measurements <unclear/></u>
<u n="2046" who="S0018">well maybe they're in the medium size one maybe they're talking about the one that you were calling large?</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0049">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0018">Cos other er</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0049">this is the large</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0018">oh that is very large isn't it <pause dur="short"/> that'd be just yeah too big <pause dur="short"/> how long is it?</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0049">well that would be nearly five hundred by</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0018">five hundred <pause dur="short"/> wait there <pause dur="short"/> I'll just</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0049">five hundred mil by three hundred mil</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0018">mil <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2055" who="S0049">mil <pause dur="short"/> m M</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0018">five hundred by three hundred <pause dur="short"/> where's the size of that one?</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0049">four hundred by five hundred</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0018">how bizarre</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0049">really bizarre</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0018">maybe they've just sent you a different cos that actually looks a bit darker than these ones</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0049">no it's the same</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0018">very strange</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0049">let me see what their small one is</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0018">have you got a small one here?</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0049">I've got that <pause dur="short"/> which is that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0018">er but are they?</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0049">oh no <pause dur="short"/> look</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0018">are they the same sizes? The different</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0049">well he said because I wanted all of them he said he sent me a bit of both <pause dur="short"/> because they were all the same</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0049">um <pause dur="short"/> so that would be a hundred and five <pause dur="short"/> so oh I know what he's done</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0018">what's he done?</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0049">so there's a smaller one <pause dur="short"/> this is smaller <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh well <pause dur="short"/> well when I speak to him I can ask him</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0049">but I think that's the way to go</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0018">well it's just a rough idea of the price anyway <pause dur="short"/> even if the centimetres are out</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0049">well what I'll do is I'll wait till my stamp arrives <pause dur="short"/> and then I'll stamp them and see which is best</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0018">did you order the stamp already?</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0049">no <pause dur="short"/> she hasn't e-mailed me back <pause dur="short"/> I said can you let me know <trunc>t</trunc> by today</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0018">how long will it take to arrive?</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0049">tut um</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0018">or don't you know?</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0049">probably have it by next week</u>
</body>
</text>
