<text id="SBYQ">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:31:12</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0082 S0086</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Politics, charity, friendships</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0082">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Mordern, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0086">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cuckfield, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0086">he didn't say how it was but he didn't complain about it <pause dur="short"/> so although</u>
<u n="2" who="S0082">I think that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> if if it was it's it's it's so disagreeable</u>
<u n="3" who="S0086">yeah well yes I know cos you were complaining quite loudly about it</u>
<u n="4" who="S0082">I mean I don't think you realise how I mean it really was awful</u>
<u n="5" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've had it happen to me before but I suppose because it wasn't  it wasn't  happening to me on that phone</u>
<u n="6" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0086">it wasn't that bad</u>
<u n="8" who="S0082">em</u>
<u n="9" who="S0086">so</u>
<u n="10" who="S0082">well I've had it a little bit at other times</u>
<u n="11" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0082">but it was so bad <pause dur="short"/> it was just like hearing my voice like as loud as I am now</u>
<u n="13" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0082">um and then you've got the delay and I wasn't sure whether you what you were hearing or what</u>
<u n="15" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0082">it was so bad <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> you couldn't help saying something <pause dur="short"/> so if if somebody doesn't say anything I think you can assume that it's not there</u>
<u n="17" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0082">I mean it I I'd been speaking to you for a while before I actually realised that I hadn't heard it and</u>
<u n="19" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0082">you know</u>
<u n="21" who="S0086">well fingers crossed maybe that's what it takes to take the sim card out again</u>
<u n="22" who="S0082">I mean I don't see</u>
<u n="23" who="S0086">maybe it wasn't quite in</u>
<u n="24" who="S0082">how these things work but um why that would make a difference</u>
<u n="25" who="S0086">ah when I leave I'll call you from the car</u>
<u n="26" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes do that <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<u n="27" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0082">it's got an amazing cast but I think it's probably not a terribly good film</u>
<u n="29" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's looks like the sort of thing where they put the best</u>
<u n="30" who="S0082">it's a bit cheesy</u>
<u n="31" who="S0086">bits like in the trailer</u>
<u n="32" who="S0082">yes and it's terribly cheesy I'm sure</u>
<u n="33" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0082">oh</u>
<u n="35" who="S0086">it's going to be a little bit on the patronising side I think</u>
<u n="36" who="S0082">oh yes</u>
<u n="37" who="S0086">ah aren't these Indian people lovely?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0086">they're not uncivilised at all <vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I was having a very strange conversation with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last night where she really sort of flagged up her ignorance of some areas</u>
<u n="40" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0086">she she I think because she's she's twenty-four but because she fell out with her parents when she was quite young she moved out when she was sixteen <pause dur="short"/> so she grew up quite quickly</u>
<u n="42" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0086">so she gives  she gives  the big I am <pause dur="short"/> she is quite mature</u>
<u n="44" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0086">and she's very fiercely independent</u>
<u n="46" who="S0082">right</u>
<u n="47" who="S0086">but at the same time we were having a conversation and she was saying she's on some charity board at work you know as a way of sort of getting further ahead in the company and get involved in stuff</u>
<u n="48" who="S0082">right</u>
<u n="49" who="S0086">and then but she was saying but our charity this year is something to do with Africa and I said oh what is it? Is it CAFOD or you know Oxfam or</u>
<u n="50" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0086">she said is it one of those big ones? What is it? Amnesty you know? What is it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0086">she like oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> water Aid? You know naming as many as I could <vocal desc="laugh"/> she's like oh I don't know yeah probably one of those <pause dur="short"/> save The Children? Oh I don't know then she said you know I'm going to sound really stupid but it's they're like aliens to me? It's so far away and I said</u>
<u n="54" who="S0082">right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0086">but the  But the  surely right like now that <trunc>cu</trunc> current day because of the fact that the world does seems smaller all the time you know in the way that we communicate and the way that we are seeing people in other countries</u>
<u n="56" who="S0082">yes</u>
<u n="57" who="S0086">in television or other kinds of media <pause dur="short"/> it's sort of making it seem smaller not further away</u>
<u n="58" who="S0082">yes I</u>
<u n="59" who="S0086">but the gulf between</u>
<u n="60" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0086">how we live and how they live is growing all the time</u>
<u n="62" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0086">you know they're they're getting poorer</u>
<u n="64" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0086">as we get</u>
<u n="66" who="S0082">yes</u>
<u n="67" who="S0086">richer effectively the west as a whole <pause dur="short"/> and um she was saying I just can't understand it I'd rather give money <pause dur="short"/> not I'd rather look after my own but she said at least I can see a direct um consequence to us donating money <pause dur="short"/> I think she's <trunc>prob</trunc> it's sounds like they probably just haven't explained where the money is actually gonna go because</u>
<u n="68" who="S0082">but that's pathetic though</u>
<u n="69" who="S0086">well I agree <trunc>y</trunc> and I did talk her down and I said she did I did say well they probably someone you know and they give clean needles they provide clean water or you know</u>
<u n="70" who="S0082">uh mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0086">they probably do a multitude of things <pause dur="short"/> um and she said no I can't just I just can't see how it's actually going to help people <pause dur="short"/> I said well that's that's silly <pause dur="short"/> I said it a lot of it has to do with the <trunc>de</trunc> desensitisation of the television as well</u>
<u n="72" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0086">like you see these images and it's completely heartbreaking and then it's gone and then you've got a car car advert</u>
<u n="74" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0086">you know it does sort of it only stays with you for a matter of moments <pause dur="short"/> I said don't you remember like the Live Aid you know that was only a few years ago <pause dur="short"/> and their campaign was the fact that you know in Africa a child dies every three seconds</u>
<u n="76" who="S0082">uh mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0086">she like yeah oh yeah I'd forgotten all about that <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking well yeah like out of sight out of mind <pause dur="short"/> that's the problem isn't it?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0082">it very much is</u>
<u n="79" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0082">in fact <trunc>y</trunc> yes <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="81" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0082">that's that's certainly the case but <pause dur="short"/> to feel that they're so far away so it has no impact so and and</u>
<u n="83" who="S0086">so therefore you might as well not doing anything</u>
<u n="84" who="S0082" trans="overlap">and and and also the idea that you wouldn't give to charity if you couldn't see where it</u>
<u n="85" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0082">what it was doing</u>
<u n="87" who="S0086">that was her <pause dur="short"/> and actually that's your own ignorance because you don't understand something <pause dur="short"/> cos I said well in that case why don't you find out much more about it? Cos it's probably doing a good thing</u>
<u n="88" who="S0082">exactly</u>
<u n="89" who="S0086">like can't you see it's a charity and it's helping people</u>
<u n="90" who="S0082">yes</u>
<u n="91" who="S0086">so why if you're on the board and you didn't know why didn't you ask?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0082">it would take  it would take  five minutes on Google to find out what the charity is and</u>
<u n="93" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0082">what it's doing</u>
<u n="95" who="S0086">or ask the people if they were making the announcement in the meeting</u>
<u n="96" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0086">right this is going to be a charity <pause dur="short"/> why not say okay well I'm sorry I don't know who they are</u>
<u n="98" who="S0082">tell us more about it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0086" trans="overlap">and what they're doing</u>
<u n="100" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0086">it does seem very strange</u>
<u n="102" who="S0082">yes</u>
<u n="103" who="S0086">and she said why don't they help themselves? And I thought right don't <pause dur="short"/> you sound like a Daily Mail reader now</u>
<u n="104" who="S0082">ooh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0086">she said well then how come we've got so civilised in the west and they haven't got <trunc>civilisa</trunc> <trunc>civili</trunc> <trunc>ov</trunc> civilised there?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0082"><vocal desc="gasp"/> Oh god</u>
<u n="107" who="S0086">and I thought oh god</u>
<u n="108" who="S0082">oh my god</u>
<u n="109" who="S0086">oh no <pause dur="short"/> so I had to you know sort of talk her down <pause dur="short"/> but I think the worry is with her is she just  she just  you know she <trunc>ju</trunc> if she can't see it <pause dur="short"/> then she doesn't want to understand it</u>
<u n="110" who="S0082">that's that's well that's the case with a lot of people I think</u>
<u n="111" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0082">and there is this perception which the west has done nothing to try and challenge that the west is civilised</u>
<u n="113" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0082">and everybody else isn't</u>
<u n="115" who="S0086">well that's what I said did you not see soldiers going into countries now and pillaging and raping? Nothing's has really changed <pause dur="short"/> when what makes us <trunc>w</trunc> what how does that make us humane?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0086">than people in those countries</u>
<u n="118" who="S0082">what's what's civilised about that?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0086">and in fact we actually all come from Africa we come from them</u>
<u n="120" who="S0082">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0086">you know and the reason is we've we've <pause dur="short"/> she said well why is their land so uninhabitable? That's their own fault they should move <pause dur="short"/> and I said well not really <pause dur="short"/> actually they're really poor they've got nowhere to move to <pause dur="short"/> that is their land <pause dur="short"/> and if we helped them</u>
<u n="122" who="S0082">also the fact  the fact  that um a lot of Africa was fertile land</u>
<u n="123" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0082">um and it's become lesser because um if land is cleared</u>
<u n="125" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0082">um then you get um what do they call it? Um <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what they call it now um <pause dur="short"/> but when it does rain it actually <trunc>wash</trunc> washes all the top soil away because there's no vegetation</u>
<u n="127" who="S0086">oh god <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0082">or there's very little because it's all been um I mean you know we're talking about decades of drought</u>
<u n="129" who="S0086">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0082">where it used to be fertile</u>
<u n="131" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0082">um but with um <pause dur="short"/> where land was cleared for grazing</u>
<u n="133" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0082">and then you had drought and then when you have rain it washes the top soil away <pause dur="short"/> so there's nothing you have you haven't got sort of um fertile land for things to grow on to sort of recover from that</u>
<u n="135" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0082">so um it's there's a  there's a  whole range of things</u>
<u n="137" who="S0086">well absolutely <pause dur="short"/> and plus I mean she said why they don't do anything to help themselves <pause dur="short"/> I said well actually you know there there is</u>
<u n="138" who="S0082">and and that's not true</u>
<u n="139" who="S0086">that's not true <pause dur="short"/> and also you know the problem is you see this thing this with charities all over the place where the money is just actually not filtering down and that's because the charities aren't actually being regulated in the same way that maybe they should be <pause dur="short"/> look at the funds of money going to Haiti</u>
<u n="140" who="S0082" trans="overlap">also you do have to deal with  you do have to deal with  corrupt</u>
<u n="141" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0082">um governments</u>
<u n="143" who="S0086">well in Cuba the money never actually <pause dur="short"/> the majority of money that actually goes into the country doesn't reach the people but they're all catered for</u>
<u n="144" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0086">they've all got a basic living allowance but they could have more</u>
<u n="146" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0086">but because they they live in a socialist country</u>
<u n="148" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0086">their their government the people the clothes they're getting for example and then they sell them off</u>
<u n="150" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0086">to another third world country and make profit and then keep the money for themselves</u>
<u n="152" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0086">in Haiti they're still living in shanty towns <pause dur="short"/> new Orleans they're still living in shanty towns</u>
<u n="154" who="S0082">I know</u>
<u n="155" who="S0086">they're still living in tents under the subway</u>
<u n="156" who="S0082" trans="overlap">because the money the money isn't going to where it should</u>
<u n="157" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> it's not <pause dur="short"/> and you think well that's the big reason <pause dur="short"/> it's it's</u>
<u n="158" who="S0082">corruption is is a huge thing <pause dur="short"/> it it will always happen <pause dur="short"/> vested interests you know</u>
<u n="159" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0082">so <trunc>w</trunc> when you do get a disaster the money that goes in will be  will be  put into projects that you know um government or big corporations or you know developers</u>
<u n="161" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0082">will have a vested interest in in choosing this route</u>
<u n="163" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0082">rather than you know just actually kind of handing it over and helping the people that really need it <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's always a kind of <trunc>t</trunc> there's always an element of that</u>
<u n="165" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0082">so the people on <trunc>t</trunc> the ground don't actually benefit from that</u>
<u n="167" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0082">and that  And that  happens whether it's you know America or Africa</u>
<u n="169" who="S0086">oh absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0082">so there's no difference there <pause dur="short"/> there's corruption everywhere <pause dur="short"/> there's vested interests everywhere</u>
<u n="171" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's what I was pointing out about New Orleans</u>
<u n="172" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0086">and trying to make it so that it's not them and us</u>
<u n="174" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0086">you know <pause dur="short"/> I think a lot of it is just ignorance and I</u>
<u n="176" who="S0082">mm it is</u>
<u n="177" who="S0086">you know I'm ignorant to a lot of I as well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0086">but I think I try and read about stuff at the same time</u>
<u n="180" who="S0082">well yeah and be open to it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0082">absolutely</u>
<u n="183" who="S0086">I reckon I'm a bit of a goldfish <pause dur="short"/> if I watch something or read something in the newspaper I think oh I don't really understand that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0086">I try and investigate it I might read a book or I might go online or I might <trunc>r</trunc> read the paper and in that period of time I try and understand it and then I think or then something else comes along</u>
<u n="186" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's the same as all of us</u>
<u n="187" who="S0086" trans="overlap">that's sort of the nature of it <pause dur="short"/> but this idea that oh I don't understand it therefore I don't want to engage with it</u>
<u n="188" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0086">they're far away therefore</u>
<u n="190" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0086">I shouldn't give them money <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0082">there's also um you've got things like small farmers who try and sell <trunc>a</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> this is quite a big thing that that was <pause dur="short"/> um we were sort of things were explained to us at the time of remember the <trunc>d</trunc> drop the debt thing in two thousand?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0082">um the World Health Organisation and the World Trade Organisation people like this you know they're set up to sort of provide um kind of help and sort of</u>
<u n="195" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0082">an overseeing kind of role</u>
<u n="197" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0082">but they're hugely corrupt as well</u>
<u n="199" who="S0086">mm hm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0082">and and and even if they're not you know the balance is is out</u>
<u n="201" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0082">I mean they're there to sort of oversee like fair trade and trade agreements between countries and continents</u>
<u n="203" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0082">but actually the balance is always tipped in favour of the rich countries <pause dur="short"/> the the western countries</u>
<u n="205" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0082">and the very large corporations I mean Monsanto has a huge clout</u>
<u n="207" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0082">in places like this <pause dur="short"/> so all the markets where you know the small farmers would want to bring their produce and trade them</u>
<u n="209" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0082">and which has been done for centuries <pause dur="short"/> they're actually having to compete now with European or American um goods that are imported into into Africa</u>
<u n="211" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0082">and sold at a fraction of the price in African markets where their own farmers can't sell their own stuff</u>
<u n="213" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0082">because it's all to do with um trade balances and the <trunc>g</trunc> trade agreements you must allow um the US and Europe to um export to you <pause dur="short"/> you must have you must take these in</u>
<u n="215" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0082">in order to um you know <pause dur="short"/> all these trade agreements are set up</u>
<u n="217" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0082">so they're having to accept cheap imports which means that their their own farmers can't sell their own produce</u>
<u n="219" who="S0086">oh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0082">in order to make a living <pause dur="short"/> it's completely ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> outrageous</u>
<u n="221" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0082">but it's all to do with this you know we must have trade <pause dur="short"/> trade is good but who has the power to say what this trade agreement is you know?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0082">you must accept X Y and Z and we will take A B and C</u>
<u n="225" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0082">and it's it's the corporations and it's the  it's the  UK and <trunc>U</trunc> US and European governments</u>
<u n="227" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0082">who make who have the power to say to to the WTO</u>
<u n="229" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0082">you must you know this is what we're gonna do and you've got to agree to it</u>
<u n="231" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0082">and they do and you know the poorer countries have no say in the matter</u>
<u n="233" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0082">they have to accept it</u>
<u n="235" who="S0086">it's all run by money isn't it?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0082">because they want to be able to trade</u>
<u n="237" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0082">but it's the balance is wrong <pause dur="short"/> so even even if they're doing okay and they're producing goods you know they're up against the west in in that respect <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="239" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0082">it's not like they can actually help themselves because they're always coming up against</u>
<u n="241" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0082">more powerful and richer governments and corporations well</u>
<u n="243" who="S0086">bloody hell</u>
<u n="244" who="S0082">they're the same thing these days</u>
<u n="245" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0082">so it's it's like it's it's not even possible to do that even even if it  if it  had been in the past</u>
<u n="247" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as you said who actually regulates that?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0082">most destitute people</u>
<u n="249" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0082">are those who can't even feed you know if if they  if they  weren't growing enough to to be able to trade to sell it at least they could actually just feed themselves and their families but they can't</u>
<u n="251" who="S0086">but they can't do that</u>
<u n="252" who="S0082">because they live in the poorest areas where you know</u>
<u n="253" who="S0086">they can't grow anything</u>
<u n="254" who="S0082">there's there's no water and the the land is is poor and won't you know they can't grow anything so</u>
<u n="255" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0082">if they  If they  had money and could live somewhere else they could do it but they don't I mean they're at the bottom of the pile they have nothing <pause dur="short"/> how can they help themselves if they have nothing?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's sickening isn't it?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's <trunc>y</trunc> you know they say always if you work hard you can get on with your life <pause dur="short"/> when you've got nothing you know</u>
<u n="259" who="S0086">and you've just got nothing and</u>
<u n="260" who="S0082" trans="overlap"><trunc>Y</trunc> you don't even have a a a cow or you know a house <pause dur="short"/> if you're living in a  in a  tin shack or you know</u>
<u n="261" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0082">how if you if you're that poor how can you work harder to get on?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> and you're up against such opposition as well</u>
<u n="264" who="S0082">these people</u>
<u n="265" who="S0086">as you say</u>
<u n="266" who="S0082">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> they they work so hard for nothing</u>
<u n="267" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0082">for no return <pause dur="short"/> for you know how how are they supposed to get on?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0086">I know</u>
<u n="270" who="S0082">that's a it's a ridiculous thing to even say</u>
<u n="271" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0082">anyway well good for you for challenging her but</u>
<u n="273" who="S0086">well I'm not as um well read on the subject either <pause dur="short"/> but um it <trunc>d</trunc> it did make it did alarm me <pause dur="short"/> just the I do want to challenge that attitude</u>
<u n="274" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0086">like if it's not my country but it's not in front of me if I can't see the direct impact my money's going to give me</u>
<u n="276" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0086">I'm not gonna engage with it <pause dur="short"/> if I don't understand it then I'm not gonna try</u>
<u n="278" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0086">and understand it <pause dur="short"/> cos she gives it the big I am oh I always I've got on of those brains like a really enquiring brain and I know how things work <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that's actually the case <pause dur="short"/> and particularly worrying because she wants to join the navy <vocal desc="cough"/> which she will be great at actually <pause dur="short"/> but the worrying thing is if she is quite closed minded about other cultures and other people and what's going on in other countries</u>
<u n="280" who="S0082">that's the</u>
<u n="281" who="S0086">you can't be in the Navy</u>
<u n="282" who="S0082">that's the kind of person they want</u>
<u n="283" who="S0086" trans="overlap">but that's what they like</u>
<u n="284" who="S0082">that is they don't want people to question things</u>
<u n="285" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="286" who="S0082">if you see soldiers start to question things that's when they have breakdowns and that's when they leave and they</u>
<u n="287" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0082">have to do something else</u>
<u n="289" who="S0086" trans="overlap">they drill that out of you <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically they don't want people to think for themselves</u>
<u n="291" who="S0086">no they want sheep</u>
<u n="292" who="S0082">yes</u>
<u n="293" who="S0086">even officers <pause dur="short"/> cos officers</u>
<u n="294" who="S0082">oh yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0086">officers don't have to be told what to do it just cascades down</u>
<u n="296" who="S0082">well <trunc>off</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well officers are usually from a class where they have that sense of superiority anyway that's kind of natural to them so</u>
<u n="297" who="S0086">well yeah because they're this is  this is  why she is doing it now this is the last year she can do it cos she's five years out of university</u>
<u n="298" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0086">you can only be an officer if you're within that five years</u>
<u n="300" who="S0082">oh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0086">because I think that um you know you've got those life skills that you would need</u>
<u n="302" who="S0082">right</u>
<u n="303" who="S0086">to go to university therefore you must be a cut above which is what they call ratings which is your cannon fodder</u>
<u n="304" who="S0082">yes</u>
<u n="305" who="S0086">so if you're out if I wanted to apply which obviously I would never do I would go in as ratings</u>
<u n="306" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0086">but the I mean the money's ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> I mean she goes in when she's training for the first three months she's on twenty-seven thousand and after that she's on forty</u>
<u n="308" who="S0082">oh</u>
<u n="309" who="S0086">disgusting isn't it? And there's people out</u>
<u n="310" who="S0082">Good god</u>
<u n="311" who="S0086">out in Afghanistan with you know malfunctioning kits and you think they're actually paying people around forty grand a year <pause dur="short"/> it's ridiculous and then they're but they're  but they're  um <pause dur="short"/> they're you know they're firing lots of people aren't they? They're cutting back</u>
<u n="312" who="S0082">they are cutting back</u>
<u n="313" who="S0086">within the services</u>
<u n="314" who="S0082">absolutely</u>
<u n="315" who="S0086">so it seems strange</u>
<u n="316" who="S0082">I know</u>
<u n="317" who="S0086">why you would look at everything just across the board</u>
<u n="318" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0086">but she had her entry exam the other day and she passed <pause dur="short"/> so at this point she only has to do the medical which she thinks she'll probably pass</u>
<u n="320" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0086">even though she's got she's long sighted or is she short sighted? Is it when you can see you can't see here but you can't see over there that's short sighted?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0086">yeah so she's short sighted <pause dur="short"/> um but the fitness thing is a bit of a worry cos she's she's not big but she just carries a few extra pounds</u>
<u n="324" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0086">probably a size fourteen but she's been trying to lose weight for ages and she can run</u>
<u n="326" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0086">and when she went for the entry exam the guy said right at this point you know those of you have passed need to do this and this to get ready for your fitness <pause dur="short"/> then he said you should be aiming to run a mile and a half in sixteen minutes well she's running it in fifteen and a half</u>
<u n="328" who="S0082">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's very good</u>
<u n="329" who="S0086">and you should be swimming once a week and you should be  you should be  doing weight training <pause dur="short"/> she said I've already been doing that for three months because she knew that is what they would require</u>
<u n="330" who="S0082">okay</u>
<u n="331" who="S0086">and he said okay so how fast are you running it? And he she said fifteen and a half and he said and I don't mean to be rude but how heavy are you? And she said however heavy she is maybe like thirteen fourteen stone <pause dur="short"/> and he said I cannot believe you know I trust what you're saying</u>
<u n="332" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0086">but I cannot believe that you at your weight can run and your heart can take it</u>
<u n="334" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0086">he said if you turned up for your medical now you wouldn't pass <pause dur="short"/> like if you sent in your <trunc>med</trunc> cos you have to send in a medical slip and then they look at it before they get you in</u>
<u n="336" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0086">and if they saw that she was fourteen stone but running it at fifteen and a half minutes they'd think she was lying and dismiss her out of hand <pause dur="short"/> so she so he said I'm not saying this but you should lie and put down your the weight that you're aiming for and then push and the longest you can leave it at this point is six weeks</u>
<u n="338" who="S0082">right</u>
<u n="339" who="S0086">before having to actually have the fitness <pause dur="short"/> I mean it sounds mad and then  and then  at that point you have to do this um these practical</u>
<u n="340" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0086">training situations because she's going in as an officer with problem solving and you've got to get your team of across</u>
<u n="342" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0086">some issue and then you've got to go out running around in your pack <pause dur="short"/> but we watched the propaganda DVD that they sent through and it horrifies me <pause dur="short"/> everyone's running around and I think the thing is what concerns me is she's not engaging with the fact that she will potentially go to war</u>
<u n="344" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0086">if you're in the services obviously</u>
<u n="346" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0086">that's what you have to prepare yourself for</u>
<u n="348" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0086">she said no no no</u>
<u n="350" who="S0082">she could be going over to the Falklands <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> again <pause dur="short"/> cos she was saying um oh I just want to be on the boat I just want to work in logistics and I just I'll be safe on the boat <pause dur="short"/> and I said you're a sitting target <pause dur="short"/> boats you know there were boats targeted</u>
<u n="352" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0086">um there have been and there will be um</u>
<u n="354" who="S0082">so just tell her to look up I can't remember his name <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> something</u>
<u n="355" who="S0086">who is he?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0082">um he was terribly burnt um</u>
<u n="357" who="S0086">oh yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0082">in one in in one of those ships that was hit during the Falklands</u>
<u n="359" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0082">it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> something <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember his name</u>
<u n="361" who="S0086" trans="overlap">I know who you mean <pause dur="short"/> yes I've seen an interview with him</u>
<u n="362" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um I can't remember what the name of the boat was</u>
<u n="363" who="S0086">did it begin with B?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0082">no that was the that</u>
<u n="365" who="S0086">that was the Argentine</u>
<u n="366" who="S0082">the Argentinean one that that we blew up as it was sailing away</u>
<u n="367" who="S0086">yeah and then she said it was a danger</u>
<u n="368" who="S0082">Maggie lied</u>
<u n="369" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0082">she lied through her teeth <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="371" who="S0086">disgusting</u>
<u n="372" who="S0082">eR the Belgrano that was</u>
<u n="373" who="S0086">oh that was that's it yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0082">um I can't remember what the ship was called</u>
<u n="375" who="S0086">well I think she's she's not being very realistic of what they're expecting</u>
<u n="376" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0086">she's got no idea about <trunc>m</trunc> modern history at all</u>
<u n="378" who="S0082">the thing is in the Middle East um you know where where the tensions are in the Straits of Hormuz</u>
<u n="379" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0082">that's where Iran is blocking the shipping</u>
<u n="381" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0082">so if the tension ratchets up there</u>
<u n="383" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0082">more <pause dur="short"/> then we'll be sending ships there</u>
<u n="385" who="S0086">it will be the Navy <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="386" who="S0082">so tell her that</u>
<u n="387" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0082"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0086">you're going to Iran <pause dur="short"/> enjoy <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't imagine anything worse</u>
<u n="390" who="S0082" trans="overlap">I don't like people who just accept what their told why you know</u>
<u n="391" who="S0086">well that's</u>
<u n="392" who="S0082">we should all think for ourselves</u>
<u n="393" who="S0086">well that's the thing about her I would never have pegged her as somebody <pause dur="short"/> I mean she's she's not you know <pause dur="short"/> she has a bit of a um an authority issue</u>
<u n="394" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0086">but I think she thinks that she's going in as a as an officer she could tell everyone else what to do but it's not going to work like that <pause dur="short"/> because ultimately you're within the regime</u>
<u n="396" who="S0082">uh</u>
<u n="397" who="S0086">so I don't know <pause dur="short"/> the good thing is you get three months and at that point at the end of the three months you get to decide whether you sign up</u>
<u n="398" who="S0082">she'll probably love it</u>
<u n="399" who="S0086">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I mean she's decided because she loves water and she likes technical things and she's speaks four languages</u>
<u n="400" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0086">that she that it will be the perfect job but in theory</u>
<u n="402" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0086">if she was more engaged with what she was actually going to be doing I'd think yeah fine</u>
<u n="404" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0086">go right ahead <pause dur="short"/> but the fact that she's just not</u>
<u n="406" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0086">being realistic <pause dur="short"/> she's being quite naive</u>
<u n="408" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0086">sort of worries you a little <pause dur="short"/> although it would be a bad thing if she does move out of the house <pause dur="short"/> I like the girl and I'll miss her but it's all kicking off with the Spanish girls</u>
<u n="410" who="S0082">is it?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0082">why?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0086">well a couple of weeks ago she and I went out drinking and we came home quite late and we woke everybody up</u>
<u n="414" who="S0082">that's right you you did yes</u>
<u n="415" who="S0086" trans="overlap">and it was awful and I was really embarrassed</u>
<u n="416" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0086">and I had never done it before</u>
<u n="418" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="419" who="S0086">and eh we apologised to everyone in the house the next day</u>
<u n="420" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0086">and we felt very guilty <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately a couple of days before we put a signs up on the kitchen door to ask everyone to shut it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0086">behind them and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s boyfriend was leaving really early so that was the point</u>
<u n="424" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0086">where it's it all we had a conversation with her about it</u>
<u n="426" who="S0082">it got tense yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0086">yeah and it's been a bit frazzled ever since</u>
<u n="428" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s since then a new Spanish girl's moved in you <trunc>Car</trunc> oh yes so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there that was her first week</u>
<u n="430" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0086">and she is incredibly heavy footed</u>
<u n="432" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0086">bangs around everywhere</u>
<u n="434" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0086">um and her room is above <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room <pause dur="short"/> so I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hears her quite a lot and they have very different hours <pause dur="short"/> she's in quite late because she works in the college as well</u>
<u n="436" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0086">so she's in at half nine and cooks dinner at ten o'clock just like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't think that ten o'clock to cook dinner is late</u>
<u n="438" who="S0082">no</u>
<u n="439" who="S0086">and she doesn't think that eight o'clock in the morning is early</u>
<u n="440" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0086">and doesn't</u>
<u n="442" who="S0082">well you know eight o'clock isn't early</u>
<u n="443" who="S0086">well no but it is <pause dur="short"/> if it's the weekend</u>
<u n="444" who="S0082">well the weekend I suppose is different yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0086">so the point is the door should be closed up until ten o'clock which is what put on the door</u>
<u n="446" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0086">from ten PM unto ten AM</u>
<u n="448" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0086">because you can all agree that that's you know if you want to have a lie in</u>
<u n="450" who="S0082">that's fair enough</u>
<u n="451" who="S0086">that's fair enough</u>
<u n="452" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0086">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> never shuts the door behind her so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if she's on late shift <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> starts at ten</u>
<u n="454" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0086">she might have a lie in the morning and so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wakes her up <pause dur="short"/> and every morning she's gone in and said look can you keep the door closed? Um and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes yes <pause dur="short"/> so this morning she went absolutely mental because again about half eight <trunc>A</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was up and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and they talk so loudly together</u>
<u n="456" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was up so I don't really know why she kicked off but she text me texted me saying are you awake? And I said yeah but you know I wake up quite early <pause dur="short"/> I was awake at eight</u>
<u n="458" who="S0082">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0086">and she's stormed out of her room said to the Spanish girls why don't you keep the door closed? People are trying to sleep <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is probably asleep even though I wasn't</u>
<u n="460" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0086">and she said no she's awake and she said well you know she might not be you don't know that and keep the door closed and it went and it just got really nasty</u>
<u n="462" who="S0082">no</u>
<u n="463" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> started shouting back and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went mental and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> started shouting and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> started shouting</u>
<u n="464" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0086">and I thought I'm not gonna wade in <pause dur="short"/> luckily <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone away for the weekend <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um but uh yeah it's pretty tense in the house now</u>
<u n="466" who="S0082">oh dear</u>
<u n="467" who="S0086">it's hard and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s living out some sort of Jeremy Kyle-esque drama <pause dur="short"/> have I told you?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0082">no</u>
<u n="469" who="S0086">he started seeing a girl about a month less than a month ago and he was there every night for a week <pause dur="short"/> she's got two kids <pause dur="short"/> she's twenty-nine and he's twenty-six</u>
<u n="470" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0086">it turns out the father of her two children her ex husband had an affair with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fiancee <vocal desc="laugh"/> He knew that she'd obviously his fiancee had an affair didn't know who the bloke was</u>
<u n="472" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0086">turns out it's this fellow <pause dur="short"/> this girl's ex husband <pause dur="short"/> so that's weird in itself</u>
<u n="474" who="S0082">that's so <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0086">weird <pause dur="short"/> weirder still the the new girl hired the ex fiancee and they worked in the salon together <pause dur="short"/> so they knew each other when the Craig's fiancee was having an affair</u>
<u n="476" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0086">with her boss's husband <pause dur="short"/> and now</u>
<u n="478" who="S0082">okay</u>
<u n="479" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dating this this girl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's a little bit on the edge</u>
<u n="480" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0086">I think she's got some quite dark issues <pause dur="short"/> she's got quite a troubled past</u>
<u n="482" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0086">um and she just called it a day a couple weeks ago and now they're back together again <pause dur="short"/> but the but it's not even a month <pause dur="short"/> and he was saying to me yesterday in the kitchen oh blah we were talking about weddings and I say I've got a few coming up yeah I said yeah I've got a few in July <pause dur="short"/> and I probably I've got to pick a room at the hotel <pause dur="short"/> oh though oh that would be nice you know</u>
<u n="484" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0086">double <trunc>b</trunc> double room <pause dur="short"/> he said yeah I've got the kids to consider <pause dur="short"/> and I was like what do you mean? He said well you know it's not just me and Jenna now it's <trunc>u</trunc> it's us and I was like what are you talking about? It's been a matter of weeks</u>
<u n="486" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0086">the fact that she so quickly and so readily allowed you to meet the kids <pause dur="short"/> he stayed over on the sofa one night and they just bowled in and he and that was after the first week</u>
<u n="488" who="S0082">some women are just they just don't <trunc>ca</trunc> seem to care and they don't</u>
<u n="489" who="S0086">I think</u>
<u n="490" who="S0082">it doesn't bother them that their kids have a succession of uncles</u>
<u n="491" who="S0086">it's really bad</u>
<u n="492" who="S0082">but think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s it's quite rare in that  in that  respect</u>
<u n="493" who="S0086">well I thought that would be the standard you know that you'd put your kids first</u>
<u n="494" who="S0082">some women are just some women don't</u>
<u n="495" who="S0086">if you that desperate for a bit of male attention?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0082">I think so</u>
<u n="497" who="S0086">that you lurch from bloke to bloke <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying he gets really annoyed that lots of the ex men in her life are still good friends with her and they come around for wine of whatever and I said if you don't  if you don't  trust her then it's game over from the beginning</u>
<u n="498" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0086">you're gonna have to trust her or</u>
<u n="500" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0086">if you think there's something not to trust have it out with her</u>
<u n="502" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0086">but the fact that she's so willingly allowed her kids to meet him</u>
<u n="504" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0086">is a bit concerning <pause dur="short"/> and how many blokes have there been before?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0082">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="507" who="S0086">you know when it's just you that's fine <pause dur="short"/> you're a single woman you can do what you like but if you've got kids it's</u>
<u n="508" who="S0082">no it's different</u>
<u n="509" who="S0086">it's very different <pause dur="short"/> I mean I you know I don't want to judge but it seems a bit</u>
<u n="510" who="S0082">it's a bit weird</u>
<u n="511" who="S0086">it seems a bit strange <pause dur="short"/> so it's like Jeremy Kyle</u>
<u n="512" who="S0082">yeah it is yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0086">every day I would get a new instalment <pause dur="short"/> I don't need to watch TV ever <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me the other day what are you going to do when you move out? You're going to have nothing to talk about <vocal desc="laugh"/> basically just live tenuously through the dramas in my house</u>
<u n="514" who="S0082">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0086">it's quite nice not to be at the centre of any of the dramas</u>
<u n="516" who="S0082">yeah I mean it must be a bit wearing</u>
<u n="517" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos you wanna just come home in the evening and not worry that people aren't talking to each other</u>
<u n="518" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> quite <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="519" who="S0086">turns out that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told the plumber he's not even a plumber I don't think he's qualified with anything <pause dur="short"/> eh to take the regulator out of the shower a few weeks ago which is why it has been running scaldingly hot she told us yesterday</u>
<u n="520" who="S0082">why?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0086">A few weeks ago um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and the other young girl who used to live there Grace said that it was running cold</u>
<u n="522" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0086">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to come and have a look at it</u>
<u n="524" who="S0082">yeah and took it out</u>
<u n="525" who="S0086">and it seemed to be better <pause dur="short"/> I mean I never noticed a problem with it</u>
<u n="526" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0086">so he came and made it warmer or whatever <pause dur="short"/> I didn't think anything of it</u>
<u n="528" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0086">and then recently it's been running really hot</u>
<u n="530" who="S0082">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0086">if you're the first person it's fine but after that it's just it's really really really hot</u>
<u n="532" who="S0082">and you can't adjust it?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0086">no you have when you turn it right down it doesn't go down <pause dur="short"/> so I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she came over yesterday I said it was running really hot and she said well what am I supposed to do? One week it's cold one week <pause dur="short"/> well then it's probably an issue and can you get somebody</u>
<u n="534" who="S0082">and it's a crap shower</u>
<u n="535" who="S0086">who's actually qualified to come round and have a look at it? He said she said well it's very hard you know? What I'm I supposed to do? Fix it?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0082">yes</u>
<u n="537" who="S0086">Don't moan to me well you know I had to get Clive to take the coil out and I said what's the coil? And she said oh the regulator <pause dur="short"/> then no wonder it was bloody burning everyone's skin off</u>
<u n="538" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0086">she's a horror and she it's just the fact that she makes out to be your fault when there's an issue</u>
<u n="540" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0086">you think actually love this is what you get when you have the houses for rent</u>
<u n="542" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0086">you've got issues</u>
<u n="544" who="S0082">exactly</u>
<u n="545" who="S0086">I do resent having to pay rent when there's you know faulty</u>
<u n="546" who="S0082">exactly</u>
<u n="547" who="S0086">faulty amenities</u>
<u n="548" who="S0082">well maybe you should look around?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0086">yeah I always keep my eyes peeled</u>
<u n="550" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0086">I mean it is cheap and it does mean at the moment actually I'm doing better about paying my overdraft off than I thought I would be</u>
<u n="552" who="S0082">mm hm good</u>
<u n="553" who="S0086">um particularly with this recording of the conversations <pause dur="short"/> I do think that this is really helping <pause dur="short"/> because it if for every hour that I record I get paid eighteen pounds</u>
<u n="554" who="S0082">do you now?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0086">yes <pause dur="short"/> I'll take you out for dinner when I get my first payment <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um I'll bring you round some chocolates</u>
<u n="556" who="S0082">oh that's not bad</u>
<u n="557" who="S0086">yeah it's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="558" who="S0082">eighteen Pounds an hour?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0086">eighteen Pounds an hour</u>
<u n="560" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0086">but that includes all the documents you have to fill out as well</u>
<u n="562" who="S0082">okay</u>
<u n="563" who="S0086">I have to get you to sign a consent form <unclear/> to me <pause dur="short"/> and for each recording you have to fill in a a a <trunc>sh</trunc> accompanying sheet that says what type of conversation you had where it was recorded and who was involved</u>
<u n="564" who="S0082">okay</u>
<u n="565" who="S0086">what your opening lines were was it was it a discussion? Was there anecdote telling?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0082">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="567" who="S0086">you know <trunc>w</trunc> what formed the base of the conversation? All of it helps when the authors are going in and looking at the research to find out how people actually speak English</u>
<u n="568" who="S0082"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0086">bless you</u>
<u n="570" who="S0082"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0086">bless you</u>
<u n="572" who="S0082">oh dear</u>
<u n="573" who="S0086">more and more of our books in our corpus informed <pause dur="short"/> so it's all one of our biggest USPs</u>
<u n="574" who="S0082">okay</u>
<u n="575" who="S0086">so you're helping innit?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0082">um yes so it's just a one off though?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0086">oh good <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="578" who="S0082">I hope it was</u>
<u n="579" who="S0086">you haven't got the plague</u>
<u n="580" who="S0082">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="581" who="S0086">my penicillin is starting to really kick in now</u>
<u n="582" who="S0082">sorry?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0086">my penicillin is really kicking in now</u>
<u n="584" who="S0082">Good</u>
<u n="585" who="S0086">or whatever it is they gave me <pause dur="short"/> amoxicillin must be</u>
<u n="586" who="S0082">it is yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0086">some sort of</u>
<u n="588" who="S0082">it is penicillin</u>
<u n="589" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0082">it's just the broad broad spectrum as they call it</u>
<u n="591" who="S0086">maybe that's what it is then <pause dur="short"/> maybe cos they say you'll get a rash and maybe it's an amoxicillin</u>
<u n="592" who="S0082">that's not a rash though</u>
<u n="593" who="S0086">um no</u>
<u n="594" who="S0082">that's not a rash</u>
<u n="595" who="S0086">oh right <pause dur="short"/> that's too small to be a rash</u>
<u n="596" who="S0082">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think so</u>
<u n="597" who="S0086">Cos there's there's there's a lot of them <pause dur="short"/> well no there's not a lot</u>
<u n="598" who="S0082">it's not</u>
<u n="599" who="S0086">there's probably about three four</u>
<u n="600" who="S0082">they're not very big or either so</u>
<u n="601" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="602" who="S0082">I don't know  I don't know</u>
<u n="603" who="S0086">then it's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> it's just if I develop meningitis etcetera <pause dur="short"/> not that I'm a drama queen</u>
<u n="604" who="S0082">I think you might be</u>
<u n="605" who="S0086">well I think we can tell that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't come here then</u>
<u n="606" who="S0082">no</u>
<u n="607" who="S0086">I mean it does take half an hour to cycle</u>
<u n="608" who="S0082">I know but that's <pause dur="short"/> I know but that's quite a while ago</u>
<u n="609" who="S0086">but what time did dad say he left? Did he leave just after me?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0082">about five minutes before</u>
<u n="611" who="S0086">you called</u>
<u n="612" who="S0082">I called him whenever that was</u>
<u n="613" who="S0086">five twenty-four or five past two er one</u>
<u n="614" who="S0082">mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0086">he's at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0082">yeah he's he's he's gonna come round but he said in about an hour um</u>
<u n="617" who="S0086">right</u>
<u n="618" who="S0082">but um I mean we could pop out <pause dur="short"/> are you? You still haven't finished it?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0086">no but look I might I thought</u>
<u n="620" who="S0082">oh you were really</u>
<u n="621" who="S0086">well I'm bringing the other one back for <trunc>im</trunc> for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0082">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0086">so I might as well bring this one back at the same time</u>
<u n="624" who="S0082">yeah and finish it off that's fine</u>
<u n="625" who="S0086">but really um it's been great <pause dur="short"/> it's really good</u>
<u n="626" who="S0082">I think it's really good</u>
<u n="627" who="S0086">yeah it's really well written <pause dur="short"/> well there's a few things I don't know if I agree with but it's certainly sort of food for thought isn't it?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0082">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="629" who="S0086">it makes you think like um</u>
<u n="630" who="S0082">have you read about the births?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0086">put me off for life</u>
<u n="632" who="S0082">it did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0086">Christ</u>
<u n="634" who="S0082">well shall we  shall we  pop out for a bit?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0086">yeah shall we? Let's do that</u>
<u n="636" who="S0082">it would be quite nice just to</u>
</body>
</text>
