<text id="SC7H">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0088 S0136</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Bottisham Village College, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>Food, children, hobbies, work</topics>
		<activity>Two colleagues having a chat during lunchtime break.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0088">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Cover supervisior</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; Spanish -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0136">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Tomsk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Russia</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Eastern European</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Reprographics, IT administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2>Russian</l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0088">if they did food you wouldn't want to eat it <vocal desc="laugh"/> basically <pause dur="short"/> and the people were so strange <pause dur="short"/> there was nobody else there walked in and they were em why it was so weird? It was weird so obviously I just <unclear/> up yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0136" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so but it's a much better place now isn't it? The park?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0088">I haven't been there  I haven't been there  so I don't know but I should imagine they've done a lot yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0136">me neither <pause dur="short"/> cos we were just thinking uh over the weekend cos it's Mothering Sunday <pause dur="short"/> uh I was probably just thinking about like doing a takeaway or something cos we don't really know any pubs in this area <pause dur="short"/> eh we've only been here for a year and my in-laws have only just literally moved to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so you know</u>
<u n="5" who="S0088">so you will you if you would you go out for something to eat then if it if you knew a few places that were places you might like to go?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0136">if we knew beforehand then yeah but the trouble is</u>
<u n="7" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0136">it's all going to be absolutely booked up because it's Mothering Sunday</u>
<u n="9" who="S0088">that's true  that's true  It is all booked up isn't it really? The only place I could think of that might not be is do you know  do you know  the um <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0136">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's uh I've never been there but I know about the place</u>
<u n="11" who="S0088">Cos they're always I mean to me they seem they're hunting customers really</u>
<u n="12" who="S0136">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0088">so that might be somewhere to go <pause dur="short"/> I might pop along there <pause dur="short"/> so it's this Sunday isn't it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0136">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0136">yeah my son made me a card at playgroup <pause dur="short"/> eh well I'm saying he made it he just stuck some kind of you know stickers and that cos it was already made you know but still it was quite sweet really you know</u>
<u n="17" who="S0088">that was really sweet</u>
<u n="18" who="S0136">yeah he made it yesterday with when he went to the mother and toddler group with my mother-in-law <pause dur="short"/> so it was quite cute</u>
<u n="19" who="S0088">my daughter made you know she'd made she got she thought it was last Sunday</u>
<u n="20" who="S0136">mm hm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0088">so she thought Mother's Day was last Sunday <pause dur="short"/> so I woke up on Sunday to find this card all made for me and she had inside the card she had made these like mock envelope and in the envelope were these tokens three three no five tokens three cleaning tokens and two she does nail varnish so she's going to do my nails</u>
<u n="22" who="S0136">ah that's quite sweet really yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0088" trans="overlap">that's really sweet isn't it? So she hasn't been to the shops or anything she just got these little tokens <pause dur="short"/> so I have to make use of that this weekend to do my work for me</u>
<u n="24" who="S0136">oh I look forward to the time when my son can give me tokens for hoovering and cleaning if it ever happens <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it will though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0088">so how old is your kid?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0136">well his uh a twenty-one month old so</u>
<u n="27" who="S0088">oh yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0136">he's quite small <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's gonna be two in June</u>
<u n="29" who="S0088">so the hoover is probably still quite interesting</u>
<u n="30" who="S0136">oh yeah he's fascinated by it <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0088">fascinated</u>
<u n="32" who="S0136">just every time I hoover he just you know he just wants to grab it and just do it all himself <pause dur="short"/> maybe I should buy him a toy one or something</u>
<u n="33" who="S0088">I remember that <pause dur="short"/> I remember my son used to <pause dur="short"/> he was so interested in the hoover <pause dur="short"/> he also used to pull it out all the time pull it out of the plug and um and then it's kind of changed you know the hoover goes on it's like shut up I want to watch the TV  I want to watch the TV</u>
<u n="34" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0136">how do things change? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was quite concerning actually cos we usually take him to Early Learning Centre or something like that and just let him you know choose whatever toys he wants</u>
<u n="36" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0136">just to see what he would play with naturally</u>
<u n="38" who="S0088">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0136">and sadly so far it's always been cleaning equipment <pause dur="short"/> is there some sort of toy set for like cleaners there was I was sort of you know this cleaning trolley with like you know sort of you know brushes and that sort of thing</u>
<u n="40" who="S0088">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0136">he seems to enjoy playing with that</u>
<u n="42" who="S0088">so you just take him somewhere and just let him <trunc>nat</trunc> just see what he would choose</u>
<u n="43" who="S0136">just out of interest really we don't necessarily buy it for him but you know just just to see what he would be interested in you know</u>
<u n="44" who="S0088">that's that's good cos my son was pretty similar <pause dur="short"/> he liked cleaning things <pause dur="short"/> things that do something</u>
<u n="45" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0088">like a hoover or a brush or a <trunc>s</trunc> anything that was to do something</u>
<u n="47" who="S0136">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's copying adults as well isn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0136">it's like if you if he watches adults doing something he wants to do the same thing you know</u>
<u n="50" who="S0088">I seem to remember tool kits as well</u>
<u n="51" who="S0136">oh yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0088">he loved tool kits</u>
<u n="53" who="S0136">yeah we tried to hide the one that's uh <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> uses</u>
<u n="54" who="S0088">does he try and get in it? Does he try?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0136">yeah very much so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0088">have you tried buying him little plastic tools and things but they're just not the same are they? They want the real thing</u>
<u n="57" who="S0136">he knows  He knows  they're not real so he wants to play with the actual grown-up toys and obviously the the iPhones and iPads and things like this you know he just loves it yeah <pause dur="short"/> he keeps playing with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>' iPhone because there's you know this program with all the animal voices he loves it <pause dur="short"/> um like just  like just  a little app thing you know</u>
<u n="58" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0136">and the same on the iPad as well it's got different apps for like you know piano and you know drums that sort of thing</u>
<u n="60" who="S0088">I bet he's just so he that age it's quite  it's quite  intense isn't it? It's quite full on</u>
<u n="61" who="S0136">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah it's a shame really that I don't get to see it you know fully because you know he's like with a childminder some days and with my mother-in-law other days yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0088">but it does give you that break as well doesn't it?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0136">uh if you call it a break <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's work</u>
<u n="64" who="S0088">mental difference isn't it? It's just a <trunc>men</trunc> it's a break in terms of you're not doing <pause dur="short"/> I always find doing the same thing all the time is quite hard</u>
<u n="65" who="S0136">I think so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0088">even though it's something you enjoy I mean like spending time with your son is is enjoyable</u>
<u n="67" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0088">but doing that all the time can get a bit too intense</u>
<u n="69" who="S0136">hmm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0088">like when I was <trunc>lit</trunc> when the kids were little</u>
<u n="71" who="S0136">well maybe</u>
<u n="72" who="S0088">I was really keen to to just mix and match up my life a bit as well so that um I had that adult time as well as being with them and</u>
<u n="73" who="S0136">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know the way I feel now I just really want to go to you know uh play groups with him and do activities and things and I've I never get to do it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0088">hmm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0136">you see?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0088">oh yeah see that's that's something that you <pause dur="short"/> it is a good good times aren't they? The good times</u>
<u n="77" who="S0136">yeah definitely but then you know I wish I could sort of you know maybe go part time or something like that but it's not the right job to go part timing sadly</u>
<u n="78" who="S0088">it isn't really is it?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0136">no well <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0088">no but it's because it's a day in day out job isn't it really? It's not gonna that's what I like about mine <pause dur="short"/> I've got three days and I can <pause dur="short"/> I see my way through three days but by Friday I feel like I've done you know I feel like I've done a full a week really</u>
<u n="81" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0088">and also at the moment it's been very full-on cos we've been looking for new staff but luckily we've got two new staff starting so yeah you should have an easier time</u>
<u n="83" who="S0136" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> brilliant yeah <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know that they were going to appoint like two people cos I thought it was just one</u>
<u n="84" who="S0088">me too <pause dur="short"/> I thought there was just one as well but um there were two starting at the same time <pause dur="short"/> I think it is good in some way two starting at the same time means they get all the training out the way um we've got Easter coming up then after Easter it will be you know we're working as a team then it will be good because it's been me and Sam Thursdays and Fridays</u>
<u n="85" who="S0136">hmm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0088">and they hardly take any new supply in on now</u>
<u n="87" who="S0136">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well supply are expensive aren't they really?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0136">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my husband was actually thinking about doing supply cos he's on a temporary contract at the moment</u>
<u n="90" who="S0088">hmm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0136">eh he's a primary school teacher</u>
<u n="92" who="S0088">hmm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0136">and what he did when we first moved into this area from <anon type="place"/> is that he took like a long-term supply for about eight weeks or something uh in a school in <anon type="place"/> and I think he really enjoyed it actually</u>
<u n="94" who="S0088">hmm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0136">so he wouldn't mind doing some more supply cos he's um he's temporary now and he's got another temporary one uh starting from Easter as well</u>
<u n="96" who="S0088">hmm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0136">he'd love it to become permanent but if it doesn't he would be quite happy to just uh do supply or something you know <pause dur="short"/> actually he really enjoyed that um that first supply he did in <anon type="place"/> because on the third day of him working there he actually saw the Queen in the the <anon type="place"/> Gardens</u>
<u n="98" who="S0088" trans="overlap">hmm <pause dur="short"/> did he? <vocal desc="laugh"/> How come? Was she just there on a visit? Just</u>
<u n="99" who="S0136">I think there was some sort of new building and you know she just opened that new building or something</u>
<u n="100" who="S0088">she was just there for yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0136">yeah he said she looked exactly the same as she normally looks like on the photos and that</u>
<u n="102" who="S0088">she incredible I find cos she's a very <pause dur="short"/> I mean she <trunc>m</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I'm not quite sure how old she is but she's you know she's she's quite an old lady really</u>
<u n="103" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0088">and she always looks very um fit and um well you know her she looks really great really I think</u>
<u n="105" who="S0136">well I think she's doing brilliant <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0088">mm <pause dur="short"/> the same with me I went to <anon type="place"/> Abbey <pause dur="short"/> I haven't been to <anon type="place"/> Abbey for years and years</u>
<u n="107" who="S0136">right</u>
<u n="108" who="S0088">and years and I said uh I'm going to meet my friend there why don't we go there? So we went there <pause dur="short"/> I said oh the car park's quite full <pause dur="short"/> you know it not usually like this on a weekday <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0088">and it seemed to be all the sort of plant pots on the outside and it was all looking lovely and Prince Charles was there</u>
<u n="111" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0136">amazing I actually live next to <anon type="place"/> Abbey <pause dur="short"/> cos I live in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0136">and we just walk there you know it's brilliant</u>
<u n="115" who="S0088">it's lovely isn't it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0136">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're building a new car park there as well</u>
<u n="117" who="S0088">they're extending it a lot aren't they?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0088">and um I <pause dur="short"/> in the last couple of years it's got really popular <pause dur="short"/> I think there was you know the snowdrop season?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0136">yeah of course yeah that's</u>
<u n="121" who="S0088">it became a national thing because in the papers it was there at a time every paper was talking about the snowdrops at <anon type="place"/> Abbey</u>
<u n="122" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0088">and how many different varieties of snowdrop there are and did you know that there are this type and that type and <pause dur="short"/> and then from that point when it became like this public thing all these cars turn up at the weekend <pause dur="short"/> they must be doing really well</u>
<u n="124" who="S0136">I think so</u>
<u n="125" who="S0088" trans="overlap">they've extended their um cafeteria as well haven't they?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0136">they did yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0136">yeah they do photo walks and all sort you know when it's the snowdrop snow drop season</u>
<u n="129" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0136">you know <pause dur="short"/> so yeah it's quite popular</u>
<u n="131" who="S0088">I've never been on I've just been on the walks or have I? I haven't been on a guided walk or anything like that but I've been around the gardens</u>
<u n="132" who="S0136">well you don't really to you just kind of have to go and explore at your own leisure really you know?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0136">my husband normally just um takes my son on Sunday you know and goes to <anon type="place"/> Abbey with him you know to just give me a bit of a break really you know? So it's nice</u>
<u n="135" who="S0088">what a nice place to live though just down there</u>
<u n="136" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0088">just down on your doorstep isn't it?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0136">yeah we were quite lucky actually <pause dur="short"/> cos we've got um we've got a very small house but we've got a small house in a very nice village <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="139" who="S0088">yeah so you can just you can  you can  the whole village is</u>
<u n="140" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0088">I've got friends there um you might know them actually</u>
<u n="142" who="S0136">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I know a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who lives right next to me the teaching assistant</u>
<u n="143" who="S0088">does she? There's another teaching assistant who lives there as well</u>
<u n="144" who="S0136">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0088">no <pause dur="short"/> my friends live just next door so it's the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0136">um no I don't know them yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0088">they live well it would be a <trunc>f</trunc> a door away from where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives um</u>
<u n="148" who="S0136">oh in one of the big houses?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0136">alright <pause dur="short"/> I live the other side of  Close literally the last house in the close and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives just opposite of me literally</u>
<u n="151" who="S0088">oh I didn't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lived there are well</u>
<u n="152" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0088">I've not seen her around there</u>
<u n="154" who="S0136">yeah her cats keeps coming round to my garden <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>n</trunc> no not that I mind cos I've got a cat myself and uh I think they're just trying to sort out their territorial issues really you know if that's right</u>
<u n="155" who="S0088">cats meet up don't they the cats?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0136">they do yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0088">they've got their own thing going on</u>
<u n="158" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0088">you just don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0136">yeah there's a like in the car park next to my house there's always like a cat party every every evening that sort of thing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0088">we have a cat we our our cat and she doesn't particularly like going out to the front so she's not really on the road at all and she's not on the front garden <pause dur="short"/> but the cat across the road this big lovely black cat and she or he comes over to try and it seems to me try and uh get our cat to come out and you know join in</u>
<u n="162" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0088">and have some fun and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well our cat she's called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she sits in the window just sort of like looking like this saying oh here she comes again not bothered and it's a cat thing but obviously waiting like almost like a friend you know like when you were a kid</u>
<u n="164" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0088">and your friends come over and knock knock for you to come and play and she's not having it <pause dur="short"/> she just doesn't you know she's so disinterested and this poor little black cat or big black cat comes over every day with you know</u>
<u n="166" who="S0136">wow</u>
<u n="167" who="S0088">wanting to have some fun <pause dur="short"/> I'm a bit worried though because um she has to cross the road each time and I think one day she's not gonna make the right decision and you know the</u>
<u n="168" who="S0136">well cats are clever</u>
<u n="169" who="S0088">they're very clever</u>
<u n="170" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0088">they are clever</u>
<u n="172" who="S0136">we're quite lucky in this respect because we haven't got any major roads or anything next to our house</u>
<u n="173" who="S0088">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0136">so our cat just goes over the fence and there's a graveyard behind our house and then there's like um um a patch of allotments and things like these and she just goes exploring really <pause dur="short"/> she nearly brought in a mouse the other day</u>
<u n="175" who="S0088">did she?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0136">it was horrible I hate mice <pause dur="short"/> I absolutely hate mice</u>
<u n="177" who="S0088">actually I don't mind them really</u>
<u n="178" who="S0136">really?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0088">no I don't mind them <pause dur="short"/> I might not particularly want to have them regularly or anything but I don't mind mice <pause dur="short"/> I feel all really sad when our cat gets one cos she just <pause dur="short"/> she brings them in and she shows us it's a big deal you know like come and look at this mouse I've killed for you and</u>
<u n="180" who="S0136">wow</u>
<u n="181" who="S0088">to go through the wow wow you've brought a mouse in but <pause dur="short"/> um no I don't know it's a bit sad really and you'll try and hide them and then she'll go and find them again</u>
<u n="182" who="S0136">wow I'll call you the next time she brings in a mouse I hate mice</u>
<u n="183" who="S0088" trans="overlap">yeah I honestly don't mind them  don't mind them</u>
<u n="184" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0088">I don't like spiders but or flies but luckily she she will eat flies <pause dur="short"/> she's great in the summer <pause dur="short"/> she'll be by the window eating flies</u>
<u n="186" who="S0136">hmm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0088">probably not good for her but it is great for us</u>
<u n="188" who="S0136">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0088">I'm going to have to call it a day because I've got a lesson to go to</u>
<u n="190" who="S0136">yeah that's fine okay</u>
<u n="191" who="S0088" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well thank you very much</u>
<u n="192" who="S0136">that's okay</u>
</body>
</text>
