<text id="SCEL">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:44</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-01-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Knitting, baby clothes, comedy, Mighty Boosh, panel shows.</topics>
		<activity>Knitting, baby clothes, comedy, Mighty Boosh, panel shows.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">what are you making?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">well I was thinking about making a little hat <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>um</trunc></u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">the problem with me is that</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115" trans="overlap">such as that one? Yeah it looks very stripy and complicated</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">I don't really like the pointy bit on the end of that though I think it looks a bit stupid <pause dur="short"/> Do you know what I mean? Can</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">like like a  like a  pixie or something</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">but the problem is like I <trunc>n</trunc> like <pause dur="short"/> cos I like <trunc>littin</trunc> knitting on these needles <pause dur="short"/> these don't <pause dur="short"/> like when you when your knitting needles I'll have like um an end on them <pause dur="short"/> like normal knitting needles <pause dur="short"/> they tell you what size they are <pause dur="short"/> so like can see the needles in the jar <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> in the jar</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">uh yeah I can see some one with ones with a point and I can see some ones with obviously the flat bit at the end <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah and I see that one there is uh is double pointed at both ends yeah?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so like those ones <pause dur="short"/> so those ones tell you what size they are but these ones don't so <pause dur="short"/> I think you can get like er um</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes it's six <trunc>m</trunc> six millimetres that one</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">so you can get like a gage but I haven't got one where you can put your needle in and it tells you what size you're knitting on</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's the <trunc>th</trunc> the diameter</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">but I haven't got one yet so I just try and find ones that look about right</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">like this one says use three and three quarter <trunc>nee</trunc> needles <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know what size that needle is <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I've bought that many</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115">well if this is six point six then <pause dur="short"/> so if this is six then that this one that one's probably like sort of half it's probably three isn't it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> but they go in like I I know but they go in like quarter <pause dur="short"/> like three and three and three quarters three and one quarter three and a half</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> you can't do the precise</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's like you can't tell <pause dur="short"/> anyway as a</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you can actually <pause dur="short"/> but you'd have to get sort of measure it across with a</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I need one of those what are they called? Me dad's got one like um</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115" trans="overlap">not not a <trunc>r</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> not just a ruler? A ruler wouldn't do it then?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">no it's like a pincer thing do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">oh those things yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">it's like for measuring really small</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">but um <pause dur="short"/> you could sort of hold it above the ruler and look</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">be pretty hard though</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115" trans="overlap">be a bit  be a bit be a bit  annoying</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just to see like a quarter of a millimetre <pause dur="short"/> You know whatever it is</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115">yeah you'd have to be very uh</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037" trans="overlap">three and a quarter millimetres versus three and a half <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you'd have to hold it very <trunc>c</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and I just sort of tend to start and then just see like is it does it look right? That's why the things always come out a tiny bit different to how they look in the picture</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and so you think that that one <trunc>th</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">and I never buy the right wool like you're supposed to knit it in like really</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">yeah all <trunc>d</trunc> different <trunc>asp</trunc> uh yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037" trans="overlap">all different like <trunc>th</trunc> thicknesses and stuff I just have what <trunc>s</trunc> use what ever I've just whatever I've just got hanging around</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you <pause dur="short"/> so that's uh that's a baby's hat is it?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">so I was thinking about knitting a little hat so I've done booties and a jumper</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you've done a  you've done a  hoodie?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and booties</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you've done boots and you've got a hat</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> there's loads of really lovely patterns like hang on where's that one?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">then you need some trousers</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's a <trunc>real</trunc> there's a really nice like <pause dur="short"/> like there's not that much stuff for little little babies so I might have to start knitting bigger things but <pause dur="short"/> there's stuff where it's like um really nice but it's quite girly <pause dur="short"/> like them for example <pause dur="short"/> they're really pretty but</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">like if it's a boy they're not gonna like <pause dur="short"/> and like that as well like that's a lovely little cardigan can</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">but like <pause dur="short"/> You know what I mean?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's a pink uh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">can you see like the details? It's all pink and like ribbons and <trunc>f</trunc> like lacey bits like?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">yeah that's got a lot of  lot of  bits hasn't it?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if it's a little boy he's not gonna be <pause dur="short"/> not gonna be dressing him in that are they?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> no they wouldn't unless unless they were short of</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so I'm just sticking to like bright colours for now anyway</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115" trans="overlap">unless they were short of clothes</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">well yeah but</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">and that's so like that's another thing <pause dur="short"/> I'm just knitting in like bright colours or white really so <pause dur="short"/> it's um</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but it's alright <pause dur="short"/> but some of <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="67" who="S0115" trans="overlap">works with both doesn't it? Yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's some really good stuff like I <trunc>w</trunc> looked at some like websites and there's like um <pause dur="short"/> there's ones where it's like um like Goth knitting and like um really sort of weird uh like um <pause dur="short"/> how can I <trunc>c</trunc> say? Like alternative baby knitting like jumpers with spiders knitted on the front and like</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">punk like little so like you know those little booties that I knitted?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">I saw a pattern for like Doctor Marten like knit little <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>f</trunc> like Doctor Marten imitation ones?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so if you have like a punk baby <pause dur="short"/> yeah like punk baby I suppose</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah um</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">that would be pretty cool</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115"><unclear/> so it's uh pretty popular then is is the knitting uh for babies? I mean do do do all babies have uh stuff knitted for them? What what happens if?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't know about <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's no one knitting anything?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I mean like my family knit a lot like that's why I knit</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">but I don't know about other people</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos it's popular</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">I mean some people think it's chavvy <pause dur="short"/> like I was telling you like</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">some people <trunc>w</trunc> don't want <trunc>knit</trunc> knitted fancy baby knitted things cos they think it makes their baby look like a baby chav <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but I would've thought that that</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like those lazy socks as well do you know those?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">wouldn't wouldn't a sort of peasant baby be less likely to have uh like <trunc>clo</trunc> clothes that its family had made I mean</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> but maybe it's just at home like maybe it's just like in Sunderland like some of the babies like you know you see tiny babies with ears pierced for example or like um</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">alright</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">those socks on you know those socks those really frilly socks with loads of lace?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">like that was really chavvy or like</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">yeah I mean just a bit over the top <pause dur="short"/> so and I sort of see the point like it can look a bit like rough but</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <trunc>n</trunc> no I don't think that knitted clothes look in the slightest bit um either poor or garishly uh</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037" trans="overlap">maybe you need to <pause dur="short"/> if you saw them in the context <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think so either</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115" trans="overlap">or <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>ch</trunc> sort of uh um urban slum dwelling babies I don't think <trunc>u</trunc> to me uh knitting doesn't look uh chavvy at all so</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no well I don't think so but I think it depends</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">I think like anything could look chavvy though couldn't it really?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115" trans="overlap">not things that are sort of frumpy uh so much</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115"><trunc>N</trunc> not so <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> it I mean it <trunc>w</trunc> suppose it <pause dur="short"/> if you're  if you're  talking about poor</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do you think boys wear?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you're talking chavvy is it talking chavvy meaning poor or if you're talking chavvy meaning um uh garish <trunc>l</trunc> sort of wealthy but ignorant sort of different sense of the word</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do you think boys wear hats? I mean <pause dur="short"/> boys wear hats? Do you think boys wear purple? I mean I like it but do you think there would?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> it depends doesn't it I mean why? Because?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do you think it's suitably like unisex?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos <pause dur="short"/> well the babies wear <trunc>ev</trunc> everything don't they cos they just get they just wear what they're given don't they?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know but</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean  I mean  they people aren't always that choosy about what they put on a baby are they? Or are or some of them might be I mean</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> is it not because like sometimes when babies are first born they just look like <trunc>any</trunc> like you can't tell what sex they are so like their mams and dads dress them in like blue so it doesn't go isn't he lovely? and then they have to go it's a girl <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">yeah well I think</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">but someone was telling me <pause dur="short"/> don't know if this is right but in the Victorian times they were the other way around like boys wore pink</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">oh yeah is that sort of something like I think it was QI was it or was it?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037" trans="overlap">was it you telling me that?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">uh where they said that yeah it used to be men <trunc>u</trunc> uh boy uh they considered pink more masculine <pause dur="short"/> perhaps cos it was red I don't know</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">and then blue uh more feminine in uh Victorian times according to think it was QI</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">uh-huh</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">um which is surprising for a lot of people now <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing about QI it gives you things that it sort of likes to go against your expectations doesn't it</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">uh urban myths or uh commonly held misconceptions or whatever that um that uh that's the point of QI but uh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">it'd be good to be a researcher wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I I don't really understand how they why they always have fixed colours for for different you know things but</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">I I think everyone should wear every colour but  that's just  that's just me <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">yeah but I mean</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">there's a lot of  there's a lot of  crazy possibilities I suppose <pause dur="short"/> you don't wanna be too too bright brightly coloured</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I like the brightly coloured things like the jazzy stuff but I mean I don't know if <pause dur="short"/> I suppose babies just be sick and do poos all the time I mean I suppose  I suppose  people don't they'll just need lots of stuff won't they?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">yeah I guess they um they have loads and loads of <trunc>cha</trunc> they have <trunc>man</trunc> multiple changes <trunc>in</trunc> per day</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">so um <pause dur="short"/> it's not like a sort of older um child maybe or not a teenager where they would only need like one thing to wear or uh plus plus the school school uniforms and</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know everyone likes a bit costume change Lady Gaga style <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">yeah I don't know much about Lady Gaga really</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">I don't</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">like she wore meat meat one time didn't she?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just that she's weird <pause dur="short"/> meat dress</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">uh very strange sort of haircuts and things <trunc>u</trunc> um</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">I think like</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115" trans="overlap">really sort of <pause dur="short"/> attention seeking <vocal desc="laugh"/> extremely</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> she's obviously like got it right though <trunc>ma</trunc> she must've made a like a million billion pounds</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">well it's a good sort of she sort of blend of uh Madonna type image with um</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">oh there's definitely a lot of Madonna in there <trunc>sh</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115">with a sort of Marylin Manson type image or something</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">or something strange uh that I don't really</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">I don't really follow her I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> I've only seen her like on</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Don't understand that but <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">if she's been on like Jonathan Ross or something</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">oh yeah <unclear/> uh</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">one of them shows</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">yeah I've been uh <pause dur="short"/> I watched the last Jonathan Ross um <pause dur="short"/> and it uh and uh but it's repeated <pause dur="short"/> it's on Saturday but it's repeated on some other times I think but <pause dur="short"/> on Friday it is</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Friday is it not on on the?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like Friday it is it's on sort of late at late on Friday</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um so I think I watched last the last one repeated last Friday</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> there was uh Noel Fielding was there yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">he's weird like have you seen <trunc>every</trunc> did you catch any of that new comedy one he's doing? What's it called?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">oh yeah it's it's called uh <trunc>N</trunc> Noel Fielding's Luxury Comedy or something it's him and his brother</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's right yeah <pause dur="short"/> have you seen any of it?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037" trans="overlap">did <trunc>e</trunc> uh I didn't know if it's been on yet</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>N</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> no no just sort of just a few clips on the uh the thing with um Jonathan Ross <pause dur="short"/> but no there there's no cos uh it it would be different without Julian Barratt cos I I liked Mighty Boosh so <pause dur="short"/> I saw um</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah he was really good he was the best <pause dur="short"/> I liked him better than Noel Fielding I think <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what's happened to him?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they definitely had a good they got they had a good sort of dynamic together <pause dur="short"/> that um obviously that that gave them a sort of distinctive sort of style</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">uh but but also the one they had others there um <pause dur="short"/> cos in The Mighty Boosh they got there's sort of five of them aren't there? I mean there's there's the brother there's also the</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well there's the guy who plays <trunc>r</trunc> the bear the bear?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">there's the the gorilla</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037" trans="overlap">gorilla <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">yeah his name's something something brown or something</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">or the bear</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">and then there's</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">he's called Matt as well isn't he?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">I don't know</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">I think so</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">and uh there's um and then there was uh Brian <trunc>F</trunc> is it Brian Fulcher or something?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">uh and he's uh I I last saw him on an advert on an obscure advert</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037">he's been on a few things <pause dur="short"/> I've seen him a few times</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">and <pause dur="short"/> but there but also yeah the music of uh Mighty Boosh was very good and <pause dur="short"/> as well as the visual sort of stuff</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> crimp <pause dur="short"/> Do you remember?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> But um <trunc>c</trunc> uh cos I guess Noel Fielding was doing a lot of the visual stuff and the costumes but um Julian Barratt I guess was doing the music</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">composition or something</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I suppose we'll have to see like this new one and see how much music's in it and stuff and like if it's all just like spangly one pieces and like cakes and that</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there's definitely I've seen clips and it's definitely got the the trademark um Noel Fielding strange costumes strange makeup</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">Cos what's that uh?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">some of the strange voices that he does the <trunc>so</trunc> sort of uh strange scenes the surreal</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">events um <trunc>s</trunc> surreal characters</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they have some good characters like do you remember that one that was just a head? And he was like</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">just a hedge?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">and he was <pause dur="short"/> head</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">head <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah you mean uh</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's like I've got a crate of poppers</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">you mean Tony Harrison?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">Tony Harrison <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">he's uh he's a sort of uh pink head with no hair and little sort of octopus tentacles coming at the bottom but</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah that was pretty weird</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">and they and they travelled around on a carpet a lot <pause dur="short"/> uh that was in the the the wizards uh</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">that's right the other wizards yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the brother uh Noel Fielding's brother was was a wizard or something called Naboo or something</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">and uh</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">do you think they'll make another series of that?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure uh but I suppose Julian</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos they did like a stage show</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Julian Barratt's um Julian Barratt's obviously busy with something else maybe maybe he's got a family or something <pause dur="short"/> or he's just bored of uh just bored of Noel Fielding I don't know</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">uh they've got like a <trunc>s</trunc> they had like a stage show didn't they? They did it live</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">yeah that was  that was  really good um we had that DVD but it disappeared uh</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">I wonder where it's gone</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">um it's it's in  it's in  <anon type="place"/> somewhere</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> think we know where</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">I don't know if you know</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's probably lost forever now</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's just <trunc>mi</trunc> misplaced or</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">I'm not sure</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">I would've</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">I've got the box <pause dur="short"/> I found the box at Christmas <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't even mine you know? That was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we <trunc>al</trunc> we always had  we always had  the box but it's just that we</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">that belonged to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that wasn't even mine</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">I thought that that that the <trunc>C</trunc> <trunc>e</trunc> we got the CD B but we lost CD A <pause dur="short"/> I thought CD A or DVD A uh was in <trunc>y</trunc> your parents' house</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">maybe it is</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> cos that's where the box was <pause dur="short"/> but then there sort of</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">I know but</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">there was a chance that it might've got lent to your brother</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">but I don't know if it was ever taken out of your parents' house <pause dur="short"/> so it should  it should  possibly be</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">in in um your parents' house but</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">but but if we did get that that was  that was  a good video but uh <pause dur="short"/> I guess we'll get get that again actually</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">could probably download it from somewhere</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> could get a copy of it of that there <pause dur="short"/> they the <trunc>d</trunc> the live show was in some ways even better than the uh the series or something</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the filmed one?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">although I liked  I liked  like Tundra and um there were some really good episodes like that Wild West one <pause dur="short"/> Do you remember that one?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">yeah I think there was <trunc>u</trunc> there was a <trunc>Be</trunc> Beta Max and that yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037" trans="overlap">beta Max</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">um yeah yeah some of the episodes are very good uh uh I think there was what was it? There was the first <trunc>s</trunc> series in a zoo and then there was a second series um they're sort of in a house and then there's</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah where they they had like The Emporium</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">the third series they had a shop <pause dur="short"/> uh the third I didn't like the third series as much but um</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">where was the second series?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">in a  in a  <trunc>h</trunc> in their house in a flat</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah they had like a <pause dur="short"/> that's right</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">uh where they lived with uh you know Noel and Julian lived with the gorilla and the uh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">his brother</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">brother and and they uh they <trunc>j</trunc> just go on adventures um from that</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">I'd totally forgotten about that until the other day <pause dur="short"/> that I had even had that CD I mean</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I think the second one actually had the best uh my my favourite episodes I think then the second one</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">but <pause dur="short"/> yeah there was Tundra I think <pause dur="short"/> is that the one with the sort of yeti things? Um</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">oh yeah and they like <pause dur="short"/> is that? No that's a different one</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and then there's</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037">they sort of <pause dur="short"/> I'm terrible at remembering episodes like they all kind of blur</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">some of them and then often they're good at  good at  music <pause dur="short"/> I think the most <trunc>no</trunc> maybe maybe one of the most famous ones is the one with um with sort of they go out on to the lake and</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">oh Black Lake</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">and then they uh</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037">when he's like have you ever drank Baileys from a shoe?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115">and they they go down the sort of they go fishing in the lake in the middle of the night and the</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">there's a lot <pause dur="short"/> they were talking in a  in a  <trunc>i</trunc> in a little inn with loads of sort of drunken locals or something</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the <trunc>fisher</trunc> fishermen?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115">yeah and then then they go out onto the lake to look for the um big black monster or something this big</u>
<u n="272" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">sea that lives under the uh sorry monster that lives under the sea and then <pause dur="short"/> they uh they go out and they they sort of get caught don't they and then they get you <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="274" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he gets dragged to its lair</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And then she falls in love</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what was the name of the? I don't know</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037" trans="overlap">falls in love with</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115">it falls in love with Noel or the other way round</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">no no no the <trunc>oth</trunc> uh the other one</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it falls in love with with uh Julian</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">his name was <pause dur="short"/> what were their names uh Vince Noir and uh</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">he his Julian's name was Vince Noir and then um</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">I don't know I haven't see it for so long</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um so they they get dragged to the <pause dur="short"/> yeah he has to get rescued uh um <pause dur="short"/> but that that does the that has that song um very famous song <pause dur="short"/> uh sort of about love games I think there's a song there's a song called Love Games</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">that's probably the best song that that they've</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">uh oh I forgot about that</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">uh that that they did from that <pause dur="short"/> cos they they had a song in every episode <pause dur="short"/> but it was a good idea um uh</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">yeah there was a few I</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but I like like that was one of my favourite comedy programmes and also I like Peep Show as well</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">but uh</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">do you think they'll do another series of that?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> peep Show's been Peep Show's done about six or seven series or something like that</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> but do you think like is it finished now?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">what?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">like sorry is it finished though?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115" trans="overlap">peep Show? Peep Show?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">or do you think they'll like?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">peep Show will probably  probably keep going for a  probably keep going for a few more wouldn't wouldn't it or?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">Don't know</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">wouldn't they sort of? Cos I I imagine that um <pause dur="short"/> uh what's the names now? Can't remember uh Mitchell and Webb <pause dur="short"/> I imagine Mitchell and Webb have got a lot of spare sort of they would be eager to do it</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">uh they they they doing <trunc>l</trunc></u>
<u n="308" who="S0037" trans="overlap">although he's in everything now isn't he that David Mitchell?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they've done</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">in fact when does that thing start?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115"><trunc>Y</trunc> yeah but he's <trunc>alr</trunc> he's prolific isn't he I mean David Mitchell</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037" trans="overlap">when does that new you know with Lauren Laverne when does that start again?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he he he'd definitely  he'd definitely  say yes I think he just wants to keep doing stuff <pause dur="short"/> think he's uh</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">is he really going out with Victoria Coren?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">well <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's just a a rumour isn't or or or is it not a rumour?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is that a rumour?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">but well I no I thought it was really really plausible because I thought the two of them were so similar like to the point of</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037" trans="overlap">did you read that? Yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">they almost like <pause dur="short"/> she's like the female version of him in some ways</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well he's a bit funny like I mean he's not my cup of tea <pause dur="short"/> I like him but</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">he's a bit funny <trunc>th</trunc> or? You mean ha ha funny or?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">no not ha ha funny</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">or ooh funny</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">like ugh like he's a bit sort of <trunc>s</trunc> like swotty and like smart-arsey isn't he?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">like he would get on you nerves <pause dur="short"/> if you were like ooh do you want some?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>Sort</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I dunno but he he uh isn't he more he's more in barrister territory <pause dur="short"/> he's more like Clive Anderson</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">but do you not think?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">an authoritative barrister</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but <trunc>y</trunc> that's not what you want when you're like having a cup of tea and just like</u>
<u n="331" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you don't  you don't  want Clive Anderson?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0115">after a hard day at work come home and you'd be like ooh I'm really tired <pause dur="short"/> and he'd be like well actually you know like you don't want someone <pause dur="short"/> I mean maybe he's not like that maybe that's just his stage persona</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> I think he does that you know for the for for a joke but I don't think he'd actually be doing that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">might be though</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">I think he performs really <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> it's like a barrister I mean <pause dur="short"/> they they do  they do  the being a barrister wouldn't have to be a barrister but uh I suppose they're not always in that sort of defending the the client mode that <pause dur="short"/> or prosecution mode or like cross questioning</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">cross <pause dur="short"/> whatever the word is <pause dur="short"/> socratically cross questioning them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah uh examining cross examine them</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cross uh yeah different words there <pause dur="short"/> um I don't know what Socratic cross cross questioning means</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">socratic <trunc>cwo</trunc> cross questioning</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">I don't know I just <vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't know I just said it uh</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> have you just made that up?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115">no uh I remember Boris Johnson said it said it once <pause dur="short"/> I think it's</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">oh well he probably just made it up then <pause dur="short"/> good old Boris</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115">uh it's just it's something it's the sort of expression you'd know if you if you've come gone to the kind of school that Boris Johnson went to I'd imagine</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037">did Boris Johnson go to Eton then?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115">um I think so cos there was a programme about him with at the Bullingdon Club wasn't there with um</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so you can only be in the Bullingdon Club if you go to Eton then?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> actually that was at <trunc>Ox</trunc> that was set at Oxford wasn't it?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037">no but I mean like you obviously had to</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is the Bullingdon Club located in? Where is it?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's at the University yeah but you must've have to have some pedigree to go to get in <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they just let like plebs in</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115" trans="overlap">in Oxford <trunc>Univers</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> exclusive Bullingdon Club <pause dur="short"/> so no I don't know for certain that um Johnson was at Eton <pause dur="short"/> he he may have been at one of the other ones but uh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I was saying sorry <trunc>c</trunc> cross questioning um and I was talking about uh <trunc>barrist</trunc> uh like David Mitchell being like a typical barrister and uh I suppose that</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115">A lot of them those sort of comedians that actually may've been barristers if it wasn't for the opportunities these days there's a big market for comedians stand-up comedians</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">um <trunc>a</trunc> and general <trunc>s</trunc> uh panel monkeys or whatever the</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037" trans="overlap">tomfoolery</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115"><trunc>Pa</trunc> panel people people that go around doing the panel</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's so many of them panely games on</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115"><trunc>S</trunc> many many ones I mean and you used to just have like you know in the eighties well it <trunc>w</trunc> it was just Have I Got News For You <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I still like that though <pause dur="short"/> I still don't</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115" trans="overlap">then then there was Shooting Stars</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115">in the mid nineties</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but they scrapped that that's shocking isn't it?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> it had been going for a long time <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but it was good like</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think <pause dur="short"/> no it had</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">think it was just the same stuff?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it had done  it had done  enough of it like I'd rather see more from Reeves and Mortimer <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather see them doing doing something</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like do sketch shows or something or?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115">well they've done a few different sketch shows <pause dur="short"/> I mean <pause dur="short"/> my favourite thing that they ever did was The Smell of Reeves and Mortimer</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> the Smell they started off with the the sort of stage show um <pause dur="short"/> vic Reeve's Big Night Out <pause dur="short"/> that was a long time ago</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037">me dad  me dad  really likes that sort of thing</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115" trans="overlap">then they did a few things like Randall And Hopkirk Deceased and</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115">that that one that was kind of like Phoenix Nights but before Phoenix Nights</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">oh Baron's Baron's Nightclub</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> um they could've accused Peter Kaye of copying that</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">yeah you can't  you can't  like accuse one of just copying a nightclub of having a <trunc>rub</trunc> the idea of having a rubbish nightclub like</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">I think it was the format of it being sort of um <pause dur="short"/> it is a <trunc>mocku</trunc> something <trunc>mocku</trunc></u>
<u n="390" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or like <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> mockumentary yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115">it's not a mockumentary it's a mockudrama or something like uh spoof</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">spoof comedy but staged as a drama so that sort of  sort of  a bit like <pause dur="short"/> no I don't know it it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> it was kind of like a sort of a comedy or <pause dur="short"/> I don't know the technical term for what that was <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">Cos that <trunc>w</trunc> whatever what's Alan Partridge? That's sort of mock something isn't it? That's like a spoof</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's awful <pause dur="short"/> it's so cringey <pause dur="short"/> I still haven't like</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">spoof</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">got <trunc>r</trunc> you know I watch it but I still find it really hard to watch <pause dur="short"/> like still think it's really sort of um really cringey <pause dur="short"/> and even worse than that like beyond beyond <trunc>w</trunc> like Alan Partridge is like <trunc>Bor</trunc> Borat <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well yeah Borat took took that sort of cringe to the  to the  <trunc>f</trunc> furthest I've ever seen go as far as Borat</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037">oh it was so bad</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> but my favourite's probably Alan Partridge <pause dur="short"/> I think it's just  it's just  sort of <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> some of the scenes in it are just sort of <pause dur="short"/> the effortlessness of uh Coogan to play such a unpleasant person but the in in a very effortless</u>
<u n="402" who="S0037" trans="overlap">think I've made a <trunc>mi</trunc></u>
<u n="403" who="S0115">have you made a mistake with your knitting then?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think so <pause dur="short"/> I'm I'm supposed to be doing two knits and but the  but the  <trunc>pat</trunc> like but it's asking</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">so is it hard to talk and knit at the same time?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037">no not not really <pause dur="short"/> I'm just uh</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115" trans="overlap">because but you started it so you're doing a technical procedure aren't you?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I I just <trunc>knit</trunc>  I just <trunc>knit</trunc>  No I just knitted two together there at the start like <pause dur="short"/> I just a few <trunc>kni</trunc> a few stitches ago</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's  it's not  a serious mistake then?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> a few stitches ago I thought like oh are they two stitches? Are they one? And I just knitted them together and thought muh but that was the wrong thing <pause dur="short"/> I should've just checked <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> more fool me really but the I'm only on like the first tiny bit so <pause dur="short"/> it's always hard starting like at the start it normally just looks like a lot of knots <pause dur="short"/> and then eventually <vocal desc="laugh"/> Out of the knots sort of comes something that looks a <trunc>lit</trunc> bit less like just knots</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037">but you know <pause dur="short"/> it's alright <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115" trans="overlap">accident yeah but so</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037">sorry please carry on</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115">so what you got? Cool Knits For Kids what was that? But um</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115">yeah so we were <trunc>t</trunc> uh <pause dur="short"/> what was I saying? I was talking about <pause dur="short"/> we were talking about Borat or something</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you were saying that Alan Partridge was your favourite <pause dur="short"/> and I said that I hated Borat</u>
<u n="419" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> that's my that's that's my favourite of of the cringe  of the cringe  comedies that we've had a lot of recently <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="420" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> but also the</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it was so bad I honestly thought like I would've just <trunc>l</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> if I hadn't been there with you I think I would've just left the cinema</u>
<u n="423" who="S0115">for Borat? Some of it's hard <pause dur="short"/> some of it's really I thought it was really good but I think it went too far</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037" trans="overlap">about that bit when he like</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115">I think it did go <trunc>t</trunc> uh most people would probably say it <trunc>d</trunc> it went too far in in places <pause dur="short"/> but some of it was staged wasn't it so</u>
<u n="426" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think because it <pause dur="short"/> yeah some of it was but some of it wasn't and some of it was just like real people</u>
<u n="427" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you know <pause dur="short"/> yeah well he got people sacked didn't he I mean?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0037">like people prosecuted him and</u>
<u n="429" who="S0115">yeah he</u>
<u n="430" who="S0037">all kinds of things</u>
<u n="431" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there were  there were  people getting sacked for for having him um</u>
<u n="432" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0115">uh for having him do <pause dur="short"/> I I could talk about comedy for uh a long time though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
</body>
</text>
