<text id="SCG9">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:43</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-05-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Kitchen, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Stories we are creating, Linton Book Festival, Helen Moss stories</topics>
		<activity>Family talking about stories</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0653">so I've just told you about some of the plot for the new story I'm writing erm and yeah so this man <pause dur="short"/> the bit that's relevant is the man in a sweet shop that's for adults only is secretly using hamster poo</u>
<u n="2" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0653">and it's actually making everybody ill but he's trying to frame people that work in the circus <pause dur="short"/> now what was your question? no what you had something to say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> didn't you have something to say?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0654">yeah yeah mum after they like blew their cover</u>
<u n="5" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0654">then</u>
<u n="7" who="S0653">oh they'll try and dispose of the evidence won't they?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0654">no like say they could they could still make you if they could like hide it but still make it in a different product</u>
<u n="9" who="S0653">they might do</u>
<u n="10" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and like and like say oh <vocal desc="gasp"/> look if they didn't get sick they must have done it let's get them</u>
<u n="11" who="S0653">yep so he he's obviously trying to put the blame on somewhere else but yeah the kids that are investigating it have got to keep a sample <pause dur="short"/> and prove that it's got hamster poo or guinea pig poo or whatever it in it erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> yeah so <trunc>w</trunc> that's that's as far as I've got to in my thinking of it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you had a question</u>
<u n="12" who="S0655">if you get if you get the book er published then</u>
<u n="13" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0655">why can't I illustrate it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0653">because erm publishing but did you not hear what they said in author's panel yesterday? anyway erm but I knew this basically publishing houses have publish erm authors and they also have illustrators so they will decide who is going to illustrate the book <pause dur="short"/> I don't I won't have a say over it</u>
<u n="16" who="S0655">what if you want to illustrate it yourself and then actually give the job to me?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0653">well I'd they've have they still <trunc>ha</trunc>have to like the illustrations so you could still you could <trunc>s</trunc> you know do them and they could see if they liked them</u>
<u n="18" who="S0655">yay</u>
<u n="19" who="S0653">but as I said if they didn't I mean in the imaginary world of me actually writing it and finishing it and sending it and getting published if you if they didn't like them you could still do stuff for the website cos Helen Moss has got lots of stuff I was I was meaning to say to you the other day we should look on the Helen Moss website cos there's actually loads of stuff for fans on there and I think there's</u>
<u n="20" who="S0655" trans="overlap">are there games?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0653">I think I don't know but there's definitely other stories that fans have written and all that kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> so it'll be worth you going on there</u>
<u n="22" who="S0655">but anyway I'll try the illustrations</u>
<u n="23" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0655">although</u>
<u n="25" who="S0653" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="26" who="S0655">someone else can do the front cover</u>
<u n="27" who="S0653">okay <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just</u>
<u n="28" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I could do the sweet shop on the front cover actually</u>
<u n="29" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh my goodness stop interrupting me so</u>
<u n="30" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0653">yes so that's what I've got to so far in my plan so there are some other things that needed to happen and obviously one of the characters Ashad or whatever his name is when I rename him you know his dad is</u>
<u n="32" who="S0654" trans="overlap">how about Tony?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0655">Michael</u>
<u n="34" who="S0653">no it's got to be an Asian name cos it's going to be like Ashad</u>
<u n="35" who="S0655" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0653">and it's important for there for there to be Asian characters in stories so that <pause dur="short"/> people feel <pause dur="short"/> that they are included in stories</u>
<u n="37" who="S0654"><unclear/> so like they think their mum is kind of erm a bit crazy but they actually think or they actually find er they own the best mum in the world and <pause dur="short"/> like when the circus</u>
<u n="38" who="S0653" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> slow down</u>
<u n="39" who="S0654">comes to town</u>
<u n="40" who="S0653">sorry? when the circus comes down?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0654">yeah but she didn't have the one thing cos they</u>
<u n="42" who="S0653" trans="overlap">can hang on I can't understand anything you're saying</u>
<u n="43" who="S0654" trans="overlap">she doesn't tell them she doesn't tell them one thing cos she thinks they're bored circus</u>
<u n="44" who="S0653">she does get that chip off your head</u>
<u n="45" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0653">she doesn't tell them one thing what do you mean?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0654" trans="overlap">erm like the family</u>
<u n="49" who="S0653">that they don't know she does the hoop do you mean?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0653">yeah well I I think they're kind of they kind of think she's quite cool but they're not really they're just used to her being as she is so they don't know that she was in the circus erm but they're kind of not really surprised and the Ashad character like really likes their mum and thinks she's really really cool but Teejay and Katy really like Ashad's mum and she's going to be based on my er student Sumi and she's like really quiet and lovely and keeps the house really clean and bakes for them all the time and Teejay and Katy kind of think oh that would be really cool to have a mum like that I mean they do like their mum but erm yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0655">the grass is always greener on the other side</u>
<u n="53" who="S0653">exactly but Sumi Ashad's mum is a little bit kind of taken aback by Teejay and Katy's mum so whenever they see whenever they meet each other <pause dur="short"/> you know Katy and Teejay's mum is always doing something crazy and Sumi just thinks oh my goodness me what is this lady doing? so one thing that I do know is that the woman the wife of the nasty man that owns the sweet shop just for adults and is selling stuff with hamster poo in it</u>
<u n="54" who="S0654">erm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0653">she is going to er actually train to do the aerial hoop in secret <pause dur="short"/> and then she's gonna leave him and run off to the circus at the end of the book</u>
<u n="56" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0654">yeah but maybe erm find out</u>
<u n="58" who="S0653" trans="overlap">can you</u>
<u n="59" who="S0654">what she wants to do and then go <pause dur="short"/> oh I know I know I can teach you</u>
<u n="60" who="S0653">yes she's gonna teach her</u>
<u n="61" who="S0654">and erm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0653" trans="overlap">can you stop using your hands? because you've got a perfectly good fork and knife thank you yes so she the mum is gonna teach her how to do the aerial hoop and she's gonna be like a quite a big lady like a large lady who does <trunc>ea</trunc> no no not fingers erm but she's still gonna do erm a hoop performance in the grand finale before the circus leave town which think'll be quite cool and she's gonna wear like a big pink dress that looks a bit like a blancmange and look a bit</u>
<u n="63" who="S0654" trans="overlap">what's a blancmange?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0653">a sort of wibbly wobbly dessert so any suggestions of other bits of the plot <pause dur="short"/> would be useful</u>
<u n="65" who="S0655">erm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0654">I <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="67" who="S0655">it could be that the man erm I mean the owner of the sweet shop</u>
<u n="68" who="S0653">uhu</u>
<u n="69" who="S0655">tries to like get rid of his wife well not kill her <pause dur="short"/> but like erm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0653">mm he might do</u>
<u n="71" who="S0655" trans="overlap">maybe just</u>
<u n="72" who="S0654">mm get erm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="74" who="S0654">erm I think</u>
<u n="75" who="S0653" trans="overlap">stop using your hands</u>
<u n="76" who="S0655">erm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0653">yes?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0655"><trunc>mayb</trunc></u>
<u n="79" who="S0653">gets your hands away</u>
<u n="80" who="S0655" trans="overlap">cos she might report him to the police</u>
<u n="81" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0655">and</u>
<u n="83" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I don't think he's I don't think he's nasty nasty nasty like that yes is what is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0654">erm maybe he could like think wait erm if she's er really she could run off and tell the children cos he was <unclear/> in his sweet shop</u>
<u n="85" who="S0653">I don't think he thinks she will tell but I don't think they're very happy and what's gonna happen is he's going to get eventually find out cos the kids are going to <pause dur="short"/> reveal everything and everyone's gonna say sorry to the circus for being mean to the so they're gonna like do it in an exclusive newspaper article so that means that Ashad's dad will still have a job cos he's got like an exclusive er scoop for that and then he's gonna end stop using your hands use your fork and knife then erm the man is gonna end up in prison in jail for you know illegally using hamster poo however a bit at the end of the story will be that another company decide erm that actually it's got loads of health properties and that it was the way that he was treating it that he should have done something to them I dunno like bake them or something erm and then all the bad stuff goes so there <trunc>s</trunc>some some company is going to go and sell hamster poo chocolate and charge a fortune for it erm and with all these health properties and so he could have in fact have become very rich if he'd done it properly instead of an underhand sneaky way and I think that's quite a good kind of revenge thing on him that he if only he'd done it in a a sensible good way rather than deceiving everybody <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I can see you're using your fingers and I would like you to stop that cos that's why you get ill quite a lot isn't it?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when you er <trunc>s</trunc>said stop using your fingers use your fork</u>
<u n="87" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="88" who="S0655">it sounded like this stop using your fingers use your fork</u>
<u n="89" who="S0653">yes I was doing a robotic voice</u>
<u n="90" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I'm mm <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="91" who="S0653">and</u>
<u n="92" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no you weren't</u>
<u n="93" who="S0654">no <trunc>wel</trunc></u>
<u n="94" who="S0653"><trunc>y</trunc>yes I was</u>
<u n="95" who="S0654">welcome to King's Cross station</u>
<u n="96" who="S0653" trans="overlap">stop using your fingers use your fork and the other thing</u>
<u n="97" who="S0655" trans="overlap">welcome to King's Cross station <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0653" trans="overlap">that that he wanted to do but then he didn't get round to doing was that he was planning on erm using slugs in jellies</u>
<u n="99" who="S0655">oh</u>
<u n="100" who="S0653" trans="overlap">little jelly sweets that sort of thing so that shop ends up closing down and it could be that if we did another story then that's shop could open as something else and that could be another story</u>
<u n="101" who="S0654">yeah but erm eventually</u>
<u n="102" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0654">the could be a shop</u>
<u n="104" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and it and it's about</u>
<u n="105" who="S0653" trans="overlap">hang on don't talk over <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0654">but maybe there could eventually become a shop which just <pause dur="short"/> sells antiques</u>
<u n="107" who="S0653">no cos there's an antique shop next door</u>
<u n="108" who="S0654">I know but erm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0653" trans="overlap">run by the annoying man</u>
<u n="110" who="S0654">the antiques actually like <pause dur="short"/> they never never never never break so it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0653" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0654">you know how antiques are really fragile?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0653">yeah some of them are</u>
<u n="114" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and that can like be they can maybe out of plastic and like and</u>
<u n="115" who="S0653" trans="overlap">well no cos <trunc>ant</trunc></u>
<u n="116" who="S0654" trans="overlap">everybody starts to like that one cos they're really cool and they</u>
<u n="117" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh a rival?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0654">and they want to overthrow that one</u>
<u n="119" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0654" trans="overlap">but then erm the only reason which happens is you have to say I like antique shop next door because everybody really likes you and if and and if that happens you could get end up with a dodgy boyfriend but obviously it would be okay cos you like that man</u>
<u n="121" who="S0653">well I like that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I like there being a rival and then they have to come to the rescue <trunc>perha</trunc></u>
<u n="122" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and then then that</u>
<u n="123" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I mean you can't get plastic as antiques but perhaps they sell fake antiques</u>
<u n="124" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0653">you know or they're taking er they're they're making people sell their antiques for not much money whereas actually they're worth a lot of stuff so it could be like a wheeler dealer that someone that sell that buys stuff that could be a good idea</u>
<u n="126" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0653" trans="overlap">for another story and as you say the man that runs the antique shop he's not <trunc>m</trunc> like he you know he's quite nice he's nice he just he just shouldn't fancy their mum cos they're just not very compatible stop</u>
<u n="128" who="S0654">oh</u>
<u n="129" who="S0653">using your fingers</u>
<u n="130" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0653">if I see you using them again I will take your food away from you and you will have to go hungry okay?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0653">so erm yeah so there might be some stuff that happens in school</u>
<u n="134" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0653">oh and yeah so some of <trunc>th</trunc> that's why some of the kids were sick cos some of them were kind of pilfering their parents' sweets cos they wanted to try them and they taste disgusting it's just that adults think that you know oh it's a special adult thing so they kind of pretend that they like them and then there's one grandma that always like lets her kid eat whatever she likes and lets her get away with stuff and she buys them for her and that's where she gets it all and she's really mean erm she's not a very nice kid so</u>
<u n="136" who="S0655">oh we could do it that that girl is the next door neighbour and in the second or third book</u>
<u n="137" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0655">wait let's say there's a like really old next door neighbour and when they move out they like to see their family more</u>
<u n="139" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0655">cos they're quite old and they can't really do many visits</u>
<u n="141" who="S0653">uhu</u>
<u n="142" who="S0655">and then she moves in like to get closer to get like further way from school so he she has an excuse of being late instead of what <trunc>sh</trunc> instead of saying oh my TV show was very long and then <pause dur="short"/> she is like really annoying and always catapults her dog's poo over the fence</u>
<u n="143" who="S0653">well that was our other story that we had wasn't it?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0654">yeah the dropping</u>
<u n="145" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah but we haven't made it yet</u>
<u n="146" who="S0654" trans="overlap">we were dropping pot of</u>
<u n="147" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="148" who="S0654">erm what's their name? what shall we do? there oh</u>
<u n="149" who="S0653">we could</u>
<u n="150" who="S0655" trans="overlap">we</u>
<u n="151" who="S0653">we could combine</u>
<u n="152" who="S0655" trans="overlap">great idea <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0653">that story with the we could combine that story with the other one perhaps</u>
<u n="154" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then I make a little erm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0653" trans="overlap">don't use your finger</u>
<u n="156" who="S0654">catapult for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then she shoots some with the <trunc>c</trunc> and then</u>
<u n="157" who="S0653">it's not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's Teejay and Katy</u>
<u n="158" who="S0655">er yeah and then I <trunc>sh</trunc> make a little catapult for Katy and she has a pillow on her back and when she lands she takes the pillow off and chucks it down with the and then chucks it over with a stone I mean the just chucks it over and then I know she's okay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0653">uhu</u>
<u n="160" who="S0655">and then she <trunc>s</trunc> and like puts the catapult so that it when she does it it flings into <trunc>h</trunc> a window</u>
<u n="161" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0655">and then I <trunc>mea</trunc> and the windows and then she opens the window</u>
<u n="163" who="S0653">uhu</u>
<u n="164" who="S0655">and then both and then pulls a face at the girl</u>
<u n="165" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0655">and then she goes back and keeps sort of jumping up in the <unclear>face</unclear> and saying <unclear>hello hello hello</unclear></u>
<u n="167" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0655">and then she shoots the catapult and it lands <vocal desc="laugh"/> in her <trunc>win</trunc> in her room house and then the dog goes yap yap yap yap yap to try and get the poo back as <unclear>its fetch</unclear></u>
<u n="169" who="S0653">we could well maybe</u>
<u n="170" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0653">but in that story that we did</u>
<u n="172" who="S0655">bad</u>
<u n="173" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0653">the sister was much younger cos you are going to be a <trunc>li</trunc> you know Teejay's gonna be like eleven</u>
<u n="175" who="S0655" trans="overlap">twelve?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0653">and and Katy's going to be nine so you're <trunc>onl</trunc> they are only gonna be a little bit older than you guys</u>
<u n="177" who="S0654">erm yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0655">it would be <trunc>funn</trunc> it would be cool er if I was like twelve and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was something like three but I just</u>
<u n="180" who="S0653" trans="overlap">but if you want</u>
<u n="181" who="S0655">brought her up so <trunc>per</trunc> I just brought her up so well cos you brought me up well I kind of learnt on my own in that book <pause dur="short"/> so Teejay would have brought Katy up so well</u>
<u n="182" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0655">so well that she could like walk and was a very fluent talker and then she was like this ah and then pretended to be a baby when she was around everyone and pretended she couldn't talk</u>
<u n="184" who="S0653">oh that's a nice idea</u>
<u n="185" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and then she would be like this na-du-ba and then everybody thought she was really cute and then she was like this is really well</u>
<u n="186" who="S0653">can you speak that not whisper it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and then she goes and then she whispered to me this is going really well</u>
<u n="188" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0655">people won't suspect me if I do anything</u>
<u n="190" who="S0653">that would be a good different story yes for sure</u>
<u n="191" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0653">I like that</u>
<u n="193" who="S0655">but she pretends she's like that to loads of people but only</u>
<u n="194" who="S0653" trans="overlap">and then she can get away with stuff</u>
<u n="195" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0653">I like it</u>
<u n="197" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and that's exactly how me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> get the sweets from the shop she calls in going doba-da and then the man</u>
<u n="198" who="S0653" trans="overlap">well no nobody's going into a sweet shop for that one or is this a different story now?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0654">erm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0655">erm or she could just go into sweet shops and then goes do-go-ba and then</u>
<u n="201" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0655">or</u>
<u n="203" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and then she and then she makes them erm cry <unclear>really cruel</unclear> to the downstairs <unclear/> while the man is still waiting for someone to go in cos he is erm looking over and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> she just crawls in</u>
<u n="205" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0655">and then a door opens but she plan but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> planned it so well that someone else is coming in she well she waits so she has the door open for her to crawl in</u>
<u n="207" who="S0653">uhu</u>
<u n="208" who="S0655">and then she gets some sweets and packs them in her little bib and then goes ma-na-ma</u>
<u n="209" who="S0653">I like it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and then she</u>
<u n="211" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0655">goes and when someone's going out of the sweet shop she gets out and goes go-gu-ba</u>
<u n="213" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and when you pass her by</u>
<u n="215" who="S0653" trans="overlap">you would totally do this if you could wouldn't you? in real life</u>
<u n="216" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah no-gu-ba</u>
<u n="217" who="S0653">mm I like it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and then she would just get her taxi and go no-gu-ba <vocal desc="laugh"/> taxi taxi</u>
<u n="219" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0655">and then er he was like right got any money? ganja <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0655">but erm have you got any money I'll give you a gumdrop it's worth a tenner</u>
<u n="223" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="224" who="S0655" trans="overlap">okay I have this gumdrop and where do you want to go? my house but your house is pretty much</u>
<u n="225" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0655">but your house is just around the corner ganja</u>
<u n="227" who="S0653">so what did you learn</u>
<u n="228" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0653">yesterday?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0655">gumdrop</u>
<u n="232" who="S0653">at</u>
<u n="233" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0653">the <anon type="place"/> book festival? what was your favourite bit?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0655">erm well I had er I liked a gumdrop</u>
<u n="236" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0655">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> Shine was an interesting thing</u>
<u n="238" who="S0653">the book about the story called Shine?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0655">cos Shine's an interesting name for a book about a kind of girly vampire</u>
<u n="242" who="S0653">mm <pause dur="short"/> well she's a monster I'm not sure what that means cos I I've gotten the book but I haven't read it yet</u>
<u n="243" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0653">but there she did a good talk about story structure didn't she?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0655">uhu</u>
<u n="246" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0655">a thousand faces of</u>
<u n="248" who="S0653">The Hero with a Thousand Faces by Joseph Campbell</u>
<u n="249" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah he yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0653">yeah it's</u>
<u n="251" who="S0654" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0653" trans="overlap">good to for you guys to know about that</u>
<u n="253" who="S0655">it's funny that she was like and there's actually and I didn't know that until I found out there's actually a book that tells you exactly how to write a story</u>
<u n="254" who="S0653">it does I mean it's it it is a really good book a really interesting book and it goes through classic stories and films like style I mean that is what George Lucas who wrote Star Wars he did use that book The Hero with a Thousand Faces to base the <trunc>st</trunc> the <trunc>i</trunc> the plot and it's very successful that plot isn't it Star Wars?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0655">uhu</u>
<u n="256" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0654">erm Luke Skywalker is like Dorothy</u>
<u n="258" who="S0653">like the The Wizard of Oz indeed and lots and lots and lots of really good films and stories <pause dur="short"/> are based on that key plot structure</u>
<u n="259" who="S0655">is Maleficent on it?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0653">I would imagine so <pause dur="short"/> cos that's a very good story isn't it?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0655">is your story based on it?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0653">well I've always known about the Joseph Campbell thing what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna plan out my story and then I will check against The Hero with a Thousand Faces hero structure to see if it kind of roughly follows it I think that will make it successful</u>
<u n="263" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0653">uhu</u>
<u n="265" who="S0654">can I ask a question mum?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0654">erm the bit where Helen was answering my they asking for my quench my question in that room that was my best bit</u>
<u n="268" who="S0653">that was great so that was a panel of authors wasn't it?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0653">talking about their writing process</u>
<u n="271" who="S0654">yeah it's like erm from</u>
<u n="272" who="S0653" trans="overlap">and what was your question?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0654">what did it feel like when your book got published?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0653">mm <pause dur="short"/> and it was nice that for her to check what you meant</u>
<u n="275" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0653">by asking you and it was it was interesting wasn't it?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and she was like erm where's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and I and we're like me and everyone was like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0653">and also Helen <pause dur="short"/> although she didn't didn't get time to read out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s question she said that it was a very good question that you had as well</u>
<u n="279" who="S0655" trans="overlap">uhu and I if I ever get a chance I will ask the authors that question</u>
<u n="280" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0655">what was the question again?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0653">yours?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0653">out of the books they've written which is their favourite?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0655">oh yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0653">which is a good question but always a hard one erm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0653">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s it was</u>
<u n="289" who="S0655" trans="overlap">what's the favourite book they've written?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0655">yeah what's the favourite book they've written?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0655" trans="overlap">ever</u>
<u n="294" who="S0653">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s question was interesting because <pause dur="short"/> many of them said that when they first found out they were getting published they were really excited and then lots of them said there was such a long time to wait</u>
<u n="295" who="S0655">isn't it a year and a half?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0653">yeah a year and a half two years some of them that they were actually quite nervous I thought Hilton Pashley who got to see his book being produced in the factory I thought that was really cool to see that erm <trunc>t</trunc> and to touch a book that was still warm <trunc>l</trunc>literally hot off the press that's what that phrase means of your own book that's very very cool he only lives in <anon type="place"/> you know? they're all local authors all of those people <pause dur="short"/> but I've er I've never met him before I've had this book for ages erm and when we went last to <anon type="place"/> cathedral his book is in <trunc>c</trunc> the <anon type="place"/> cathedral and erm I tweeted him last night saying oh look there is your book which I forgot to bring to get signed and it's a hardback one and he said oh wow they're actually quite rare those hardbacks cos not very many of them were made and I got that when I was working at <anon type="place"/> so that's pretty cool isn't it?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0655">yeah hardbacks are annoyingly more expensive than paperbacks</u>
<u n="298" who="S0653">they're a lot more expensive</u>
<u n="299" who="S0655" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0653">I don't really know why people bother to have things in hardback any more I think it must've been</u>
<u n="301" who="S0655">it's cos it's</u>
<u n="302" who="S0653">important originally but er it's a bit pointless now isn't it?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0653">cos you know why</u>
<u n="306" who="S0655" trans="overlap">it only makes them</u>
<u n="307" who="S0653"><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="308" who="S0655" trans="overlap">like waterproof but</u>
<u n="309" who="S0653">no it's not different it's just literally got a hard back and a</u>
<u n="310" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0653">a wraparound cover they don't tend to do it for every book now they'll only do it for the really successful ones like Harry Potter</u>
<u n="312" who="S0654" trans="overlap">like Diary of a Wimpy Kid</u>
<u n="313" who="S0655">and Diary of a Wimpy Kid</u>
<u n="314" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0654" trans="overlap">cos erm like it's</u>
<u n="316" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I have two hardbacks</u>
<u n="317" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0655"><unclear>on that</unclear></u>
<u n="319" who="S0653" trans="overlap">well and that's what why they do it I think cos they know</u>
<u n="320" who="S0655">oh yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0653">that you you can't wait <trunc>unti</trunc> you know <trunc>c</trunc> you're gonna have to get hardback because you you don't want to wait for the paperback to come out but then it usually means <pause dur="short"/> and this is what I have with my Harry Potters is that four of them are paperback and three of them are hardback and it's really annoying isn't it? cos you think I want a whole row of either paperbacks or hardbacks so people end up buying a whole nother set of <trunc>st</trunc> of books just so that they they all match but most of my the series of books I've got there's always at least one that's hardback which is kind of annoying isn't it? cos then they don't match but yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you've got the same thing with Diary of a Wimpy Kid</u>
<u n="322" who="S0655">yeah two hardbacks every single one that's been out I have</u>
<u n="323" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0655">it started off as a <trunc>s</trunc> at the dance fair where I got Diary of a when I got the first one and then I read it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0653" trans="overlap">where? where?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0655">erm at my dance thing erm the <trunc>f</trunc> a fair</u>
<u n="327" who="S0653">oh right</u>
<u n="328" who="S0655">yeah and</u>
<u n="329" who="S0653" trans="overlap">is that what happened?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0655">yeah and then I read it and I really liked it so</u>
<u n="331" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="332" who="S0655">dad got the second one</u>
<u n="333" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0655">and then the third</u>
<u n="335" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0655">and then the fourth</u>
<u n="337" who="S0653">well then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got you lots for your</u>
<u n="338" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and you got <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="339" who="S0653" trans="overlap">birthday and Christmas er</u>
<u n="340" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and you got some</u>
<u n="341" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0655">yeah I think my personal favourite I don't really have one cos I've lost count</u>
<u n="344" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0654">erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0655" trans="overlap">where he can become a millionaire</u>
<u n="347" who="S0654" trans="overlap">what about the last one?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0653">he probably is a millionaire</u>
<u n="349" who="S0655">no he probably can become one because he has a ring that's worth a load of money</u>
<u n="350" who="S0653">who? Jeff Kinney?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0655">er no</u>
<u n="352" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="353" who="S0655"><trunc>Dia</trunc> erm Greg Heffley</u>
<u n="354" who="S0653">oh really?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0655">yeah he found a ring in the Easter egg</u>
<u n="356" who="S0653">right</u>
<u n="357" who="S0655" trans="overlap">there is a family heirloom but in <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="358" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0655">but he's ever er gets a really big urge to get a jetpack or something</u>
<u n="360" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0655">then he might want to</u>
<u n="362" who="S0653">does he know it that it's definitely valuable?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0654">cos it's a real diamond</u>
<u n="366" who="S0653">but why has he got the ring?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0654">because</u>
<u n="368" who="S0655" trans="overlap">because he found it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0654">yeah because erm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0653">was he meant to find it though?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0655">erm it wasn't</u>
<u n="372" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no because erm they had a great great great great grandma and</u>
<u n="373" who="S0653">right</u>
<u n="374" who="S0654">at her funeral</u>
<u n="375" who="S0653">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0654" trans="overlap">he found out she wasn't wearing her diamond ring</u>
<u n="377" who="S0655">and apparently and and it was worth a huge amount</u>
<u n="378" who="S0653">so has why has he not told his parents that he's got it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0654">because they'll just want</u>
<u n="380" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><trunc>b</trunc>because then they'll just</u>
<u n="381" who="S0653">is he just</u>
<u n="382" who="S0655" trans="overlap">cos</u>
<u n="383" who="S0653">keeping it for a rainy day?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0655" trans="overlap">because his mum would like to give it back but as they found out in in like an thing she was wearing</u>
<u n="385" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0655">a ring</u>
<u n="387" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0655" trans="overlap">the ring when she was baking an apple pie</u>
<u n="389" who="S0653">oh okay</u>
<u n="390" who="S0655">it wasn't on there when she was putting it in the when she was putting stuff in the Easter eggs</u>
<u n="391" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0654">and they <unclear>absolutely fought for</unclear></u>
<u n="393" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and then they knew what it meant that whoever got the Easter egg with it in would have the ring and it would be bestowed to them</u>
<u n="394" who="S0653">so how many books has he had has he kept the ring for?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0655">erm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0654">er er</u>
<u n="397" who="S0655" trans="overlap">only like one</u>
<u n="398" who="S0654">a lot because it was in well</u>
<u n="399" who="S0653">quite an early one?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0655">quite an early one</u>
<u n="401" who="S0654" trans="overlap">which one? was it in the blue one?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0655">er no it was in the light green one? hardback</u>
<u n="403" who="S0654">oh</u>
<u n="404" who="S0655">it's quite a late one although I've lost track I think it's the fourth one?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0653">but it didn't think he didn't he didn't think at all that he should tell his parents?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="407" who="S0655" trans="overlap">that he didn't think</u>
<u n="408" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0655" trans="overlap">at all</u>
<u n="410" who="S0654">cos basically they are grown-ups</u>
<u n="411" who="S0655">oh I think it's</u>
<u n="412" who="S0654" trans="overlap">so I think he thought</u>
<u n="413" who="S0655" trans="overlap">the fifth one</u>
<u n="414" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="415" who="S0655">erm no</u>
<u n="416" who="S0654">if the grown-ups thought</u>
<u n="417" who="S0655" trans="overlap">er sorry</u>
<u n="418" who="S0654"><unclear>if he might have got that</unclear> we'll do it but if <trunc>h</trunc></u>
<u n="419" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah they would give it back to</u>
<u n="420" who="S0654" trans="overlap">if his mum</u>
<u n="421" who="S0655">their his great granny but they wouldn't just trade it for loads of money</u>
<u n="422" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0655">or even keep it save they'd just give it to a they'd say I think this should be given to granny and then</u>
<u n="424" who="S0653">well it should really</u>
<u n="425" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and then loads of people would sell it</u>
<u n="426" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mum mum</u>
<u n="427" who="S0653" trans="overlap">cos she does own it</u>
<u n="428" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mum can I finish</u>
<u n="429" who="S0655">no to like their granny not their great granny</u>
<u n="430" who="S0653">oh I see</u>
<u n="431" who="S0655">cos she's next in line</u>
<u n="432" who="S0653">oh okay</u>
<u n="433" who="S0655">they might</u>
<u n="434" who="S0654">mum can I</u>
<u n="435" who="S0653">can you</u>
<u n="436" who="S0654">can I please to have a dessert?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0653">yeah I was surprised you wanted rice as well as chips</u>
<u n="438" who="S0654">can I have a dessert?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0653" trans="overlap">can yeah but can I just say one of the things I really like about the Helen Moss books</u>
<u n="440" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0653">is that every <trunc>epis</trunc> er every book they either get some money or something of value don't they?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0654">yeah like on the</u>
<u n="443" who="S0653" trans="overlap">cos they got a hundred pounds each</u>
<u n="444" who="S0655"><trunc>n</trunc> two <trunc>hun</trunc></u>
<u n="445" who="S0653" trans="overlap">from the film person</u>
<u n="446" who="S0655" trans="overlap">a hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="447" who="S0653">was it? <pause dur="short"/> cos that's a lot of money</u>
<u n="448" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and and then they got something</u>
<u n="449" who="S0655" trans="overlap">the film person?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0654">from finding the treasure</u>
<u n="451" who="S0655">oh yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0653" trans="overlap">they got to keep one of the coins which is</u>
<u n="453" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and they got up to one hundred and fifty wait a hundred for the film</u>
<u n="454" who="S0654" trans="overlap">what about the thing with the piglet?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0655" trans="overlap">oh yeah they did get a hundred</u>
<u n="456" who="S0653">oh they got a little they did get a reward from the British Museum</u>
<u n="457" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0653">so they've got some really cool stuff haven't they?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0655">yeah and they got like a certificate and</u>
<u n="460" who="S0653" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="461" who="S0655">free passes for the circus</u>
<u n="462" who="S0653">oh did they?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0655" trans="overlap">in yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0653">I <trunc>th</trunc> I was sleeping through most of that book</u>
<u n="465" who="S0655">in the <trunc>r</trunc> in The Cursed Ruby</u>
<u n="466" who="S0653">oh wow</u>
<u n="467" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and what did they get in The Missing Masterpiece?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0653">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know</u>
<u n="469" who="S0654">erm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0653">maybe they didn't get anything that time</u>
<u n="471" who="S0655">well they <pause dur="short"/> and they knew what she got an adventure</u>
<u n="472" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0654">no they did get something</u>
<u n="474" who="S0653">did they?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0654">yeah they did get something</u>
<u n="476" who="S0655">Helen had</u>
<u n="477" who="S0653" trans="overlap">was it more money? or was it a painting?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0654">erm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0653">I can't remember now</u>
<u n="480" who="S0655">they could have</u>
<u n="481" who="S0653" trans="overlap">don't tap that cos that's the thing that's recording <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't tap anything I can't remember we'll have to double check that's like <pause dur="short"/> the one before the circus isn't it?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0654"><vocal desc="gasp"/> mm mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0653">what is it? what do you want?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0655" trans="overlap">oh I know what Jack got</u>
<u n="487" who="S0654">I can't reach the cake</u>
<u n="488" who="S0653">you can't have any more cake cos you had some for lunch</u>
<u n="489" who="S0655">I know what Jack and Emily got</u>
<u n="490" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I so want them</u>
<u n="491" who="S0653">hang on what?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0655">erm they got an awesome ride down into that hole erm to where the pig was to hide the painting</u>
<u n="493" who="S0653" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0655">remember when</u>
<u n="495" who="S0653" trans="overlap">that was a bit scary though</u>
<u n="496" who="S0654">er</u>
<u n="497" who="S0655">but but they loved it it was like wee</u>
<u n="498" who="S0653">Scot didn't like it</u>
<u n="499" who="S0654">mm he didn't even go there</u>
<u n="500" who="S0653">oh didn't he?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0654">he he went to</u>
<u n="502" who="S0655">yeah he went to get the horses to go</u>
<u n="503" who="S0653">oh yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0654">and he was</u>
<u n="505" who="S0655" trans="overlap">to tell her</u>
<u n="506" who="S0654" trans="overlap">an official member of those</u>
<u n="507" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0654">he's official member of the</u>
<u n="509" who="S0653">of the gang?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0654">member</u>
<u n="511" who="S0655">wait maybe the got like something like free passes to the museum</u>
<u n="512" who="S0654" trans="overlap">just</u>
<u n="513" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0654">just one tiny piece</u>
<u n="515" who="S0653">you can't have a piece of cake you had how many pieces did you have for lunch?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0654">one</u>
<u n="517" who="S0653">did you?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0653">so there will be one left over then</u>
<u n="520" who="S0654">why?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0653">because I packed two</u>
<u n="522" who="S0654">well why did you drink <unclear>give me the then</unclear> water then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0655">I gave you some water</u>
<u n="524" who="S0653">did you eat one or two pieces today? <pause dur="short"/> so there should be one in your bag still</u>
<u n="525" who="S0654">zzz</u>
<u n="526" who="S0655">my bag?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0653">in your packed lunch if there isn't it means you've eaten two</u>
<u n="528" who="S0655">psst psst</u>
<u n="529" who="S0654">I haven't eaten two can I please have a dessert now?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0653">what do you want as a dessert?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">a Fru</u>
<u n="532" who="S0653">you can't have a Fru because you had one for lunch</u>
<u n="533" who="S0655" whoConfidence="low">may I have some cake?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0654">I definitely know I didn't eat two</u>
<u n="535" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I don't remember I don't think I ate all of it or ate any of it</u>
<u n="536" who="S0653" trans="overlap">you can have some grapes or some strawberries</u>
<u n="537" who="S0655">erm or cake if there's still some left</u>
<u n="538" who="S0654" trans="overlap">can you wash this so I can have it tomorrow?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0653">just have a but what are you having for now?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0654">I don't know because I did only have one cake</u>
<u n="541" who="S0653">I packed two little slices</u>
<u n="542" who="S0655" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0653">did you eat them both?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0654">I didn't</u>
<u n="545" who="S0653">oh have some cake for goodness sake</u>
<u n="546" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0653">I even rhymed didn't I?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0653">did you eat all of yours <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0655">let's see</u>
<u n="551" who="S0653">just a small slice because you did do a very good job of making it so</u>
<u n="552" who="S0655">oh</u>
<u n="553" who="S0654" trans="overlap">how many slices did you get?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0653">come here you're just gonna have one piglet</u>
<u n="555" who="S0655"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0654">I'm asking</u>
<u n="557" who="S0653">he got the same as you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0655">cake cake <shift new="singing"/> that's what I got <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0653">there you go</u>
<u n="560" who="S0655"><shift new="singing"/> I got some cake <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0653" trans="overlap">have a small slice please oh my goodness there's only four pieces left and you are the only people that have eaten this cake</u>
<u n="562" who="S0655">yo</u>
<u n="563" who="S0653">there were twenty slices</u>
<u n="564" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0653">crikey</u>
<u n="566" who="S0654">a good cake</u>
<u n="567" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0654" trans="overlap">which is actually a good sign because we like it</u>
<u n="569" who="S0653">it is a good sign that you like it cos normally you don't like any cakes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0654">but that is</u>
<u n="571" who="S0653" trans="overlap">cos you're a complete</u>
<u n="572" who="S0654">a lovely</u>
<u n="573" who="S0653">that's lovely</u>
<u n="574" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I like most cakes</u>
<u n="575" who="S0653">try not to stamp when I as I said the icing is particularly nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0655">uhu yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like how dark it is</u>
<u n="577" who="S0654"><shift new="singing"/> yo yo my name is Joe <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0653" trans="overlap">well it's a fudge icing so</u>
<u n="579" who="S0654"><shift new="singing"/> I broke <unclear/> and I eat <shift new="normal"/> I'm glad erm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0653" trans="overlap">it's not really dark</u>
<u n="581" who="S0654">we taste it and it wasn't and we found out it was too dark</u>
<u n="582" who="S0653">so you add well it wasn't quite sweet enough so we added a little bit more of golden syrup and now it's perfect</u>
<u n="583" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0653">right I think you've got enough there on your plate there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0654">I think it's the sprinklies</u>
<u n="586" who="S0653">you don't need any more</u>
<u n="587" who="S0654">I need the sprinkles</u>
<u n="588" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="589" who="S0655">well to be more <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="590" who="S0653" trans="overlap">don't take them from other slices though</u>
<u n="591" who="S0655">well to be more accurate</u>
<u n="592" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="593" who="S0655">it had a bitter aftertaste</u>
<u n="594" who="S0653">but it then it didn't</u>
<u n="595" who="S0655">erm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0653">when you put the golden syrup in <pause dur="short"/> is that right?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0654">uhu</u>
<u n="599" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0653">yeah do you know what? I'm like so kinda oh it's nearly half term I've no idea why I think that cos there's gonna be three weeks of hell of exam marking it's going to be horrible <pause dur="short"/> but I'm just</u>
<u n="601" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I think er is it gonna be half</u>
<u n="602" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0654">er</u>
<u n="604" who="S0653">what?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0654">er is it gonna be half term before we</u>
<u n="606" who="S0653" trans="overlap">it's half term it's half term next week isn't it? so you're off on Friday <pause dur="short"/> and there's a bank holiday Monday so erm <pause dur="short"/> and then it will be</u>
<u n="607" who="S0655" trans="overlap">ten days off</u>
<u n="608" who="S0653">then it'll be June yes June next week now</u>
<u n="609" who="S0655">June?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0653">yeah cos it's the end of May</u>
<u n="611" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="612" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0653">so on</u>
<u n="614" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0653"><trunc>Fri</trunc> on Thursday you're going to dad's he's picking you up and he you're gonna be with him from Friday to Monday</u>
<u n="616" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0653">because I'm gonna do one erm <trunc>s</trunc> meeting of exams on Friday at home on the computer <pause dur="short"/> and then on Saturday I'm driving a long long way away to do the other exam meeting and then I've got to wait for the exam scripts to arrive from the A level because they're all taking the exam on the Friday so then they've all got to be posted and I expect that will take quit a long time cos of the bank holiday weekend so I think we'll have all of the scripts will arrive by the Friday and then I've got to get on and be clear to mark and start marking from that Friday which is the day before <anon type="place"/> fair but for the exam the GCSE <pause dur="short"/> I think I can start as soon as I've <pause dur="short"/> been cleared cos it's all online now</u>
<u n="618" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0654"><unclear/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0653">wa-wa-wa-wa-wa what?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0654" trans="overlap">erm is the Friday with the <anon type="place"/> fair next week?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0653">first of all it's the Saturday but yes it's the following week</u>
<u n="624" who="S0654">good</u>
<u n="625" who="S0653">so you're with dad this weekend coming</u>
<u n="626" who="S0654">erm</u>
<u n="627" who="S0653">and then you're with me for the <anon type="place"/> fair</u>
<u n="628" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0655" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="631" who="S0653">cos otherwise you wouldn't be with me to watch me perform as a bird on the on the hoop <pause dur="short"/> my lime green leotard is arriving soon <pause dur="short"/> I've got to think about how I can make it look like a bird <pause dur="short"/> but I've got my bright bright pink hair haven't I?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0653">which will look good look okay</u>
<u n="634" who="S0654">what are you gonna</u>
<u n="635" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I know exactly what you could do</u>
<u n="636" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0655">you could get some like <pause dur="short"/> erm <trunc>wi</trunc> fake wings to erm go out from it</u>
<u n="638" who="S0653">I can't get any fake wings because they'll get in the way of the hoop won't they?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0655" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0653">I can't have anything that's gonna get in or me all tangled up</u>
<u n="641" who="S0654">ah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0653">so I might get a little bit or netting or a tiny bit of material to hang off it but I can't have any big wings or anything</u>
<u n="643" who="S0654" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0655" trans="overlap">wait you could have something like erm a wing going like that and then it's really stretchy so you could bend</u>
<u n="645" who="S0653">maybe</u>
<u n="646" who="S0655">and do the wings</u>
<u n="647" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah I might try and get some feathers that I can have as cuffs around my hands</u>
<u n="648" who="S0654">erm excuse me I've finished</u>
<u n="649" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="650" who="S0655">and what</u>
<u n="651" who="S0653">you're finished? okay</u>
<u n="652" who="S0655">finished please can I get down?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0653">erm hang on a moment you need to first of all sort out your packed lunches and do the stuff in the dishwasher</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
