<text id="SCQC">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:32:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0264 S0265</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Dinner at participants' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Arrangements for birthdays, postcard of recent holiday, Scottish independence</topics>
		<activity>Arrangements for coming weekends </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, announcing, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0264">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crickhowell</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Wales/Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>tutorial fellow</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Dutch -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0265">
				<exactage>56</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harworth, Nottinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>e_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>technical analyst</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0264">you don't know if it's <pause dur="short"/> done erm anyway you might have already can I have some yoghurt please?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0265">yes help yourself</u>
<u n="3" who="S0264">er <pause dur="short"/> did you see that other yoghurt is there so you just need to check dates</u>
<u n="4" who="S0265">yes I <trunc>d</trunc> I did check the dates yes <pause dur="short"/> no I saw that was opened anyway so</u>
<u n="5" who="S0264">that fruit actually lasted pretty well but I just had to throw away one peach I think yeah or one or might might have been one nectarine that had gone</u>
<u n="6" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0264">horribly mouldy and one pear I think that had gone funny</u>
<u n="8" who="S0265">oh this is quite sour</u>
<u n="9" who="S0264">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's tart</u>
<u n="10" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0264">mm and then you know I was thinking <pause dur="short"/> what about the birthdays?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0265">about</u>
<u n="13" who="S0264">well <pause dur="short"/> er it's a bit boring isn't it to go to that pub?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0265">yes well no</u>
<u n="15" who="S0264">well</u>
<u n="16" who="S0265" trans="overlap">which <trunc>pu</trunc> do you mean the one on <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0264"><trunc>ye</trunc> no not that one that was awful because it took about two hours to get served</u>
<u n="18" who="S0265">oh you mean the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0264">yes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0265">well we've we we've done that a few times haven't we?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0264">well there's the gardens in <anon type="place"/> or the gardens in <anon type="place"/> or erm <pause dur="short"/> there's <anon type="place"/> where I can get a Campari and soda</u>
<u n="22" who="S0265">oh yes</u>
<u n="23" who="S0264">but <pause dur="short"/> well what about that then for the weekend?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0265">Campari and soda in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0265">well I don't no I don't know I no we'll just do something here <anon type="place"/> is fine</u>
<u n="27" who="S0264">it's depressing though</u>
<u n="28" who="S0265">well <anon type="place"/> maybe there's somewhere nice in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0264">that's even more depressing <pause dur="short"/> anyway I've just remembered I can't because I'm I'm working all those Saturdays</u>
<u n="30" who="S0265">couldn't</u>
<u n="31" who="S0264">mm?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0265">Sunday</u>
<u n="33" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0265" trans="overlap">couldn't do a Sunday?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0264">yeah well it would have to be somewhere <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather maybe go somewhere like <anon type="place"/> though isn't there a castle there?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0265">I think so</u>
<u n="37" who="S0264">mm did we go there once?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0265">I don't I don't think so I don't think I don't think I've ever been to <anon type="place"/> is it er <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0264"><anon type="place"/> I think we could go to <anon type="place"/> castle</u>
<u n="40" who="S0265">oh now that's somewhere I'd like to go <pause dur="short"/> cos it always looks very very nice it's surrounded by water</u>
<u n="41" who="S0264">mm <pause dur="short"/> and then erm there's another one you know where erm <pause dur="short"/> one of those Henry the eighth queens was erm brought up <pause dur="long"/> I dunno whether it was Anne Howard or somebody</u>
<u n="42" who="S0265">I don't know</u>
<u n="43" who="S0264">well that's somewhere near there as well I think <pause dur="long"/> but we're talking about a week <pause dur="short"/> sunday</u>
<u n="44" who="S0265">which would be the seventeenth</u>
<u n="45" who="S0264" trans="overlap">or in your case er next Sunday</u>
<u n="46" who="S0265">I'm not gonna be here this Sunday</u>
<u n="47" who="S0264">why not?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0265">I'm going up to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0264">how can you do that when you've just been away for a week holiday?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0265">er well I I'm going up on Thursday</u>
<u n="51" who="S0264">mm oh <trunc>y</trunc> how can you take a day off again?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0265">I'm taking three days off</u>
<u n="53" who="S0264">you keep saying you don't have leave</u>
<u n="54" who="S0265">well I'm using this this is a bit of a combination of flexi and leave</u>
<u n="55" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0265">I'm going up to erm a a friend of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s seventieth birthday celebrations <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I'm going up Thursday and coming back on Monday <pause dur="short"/> and then I'll be back at work on Tuesday <pause dur="long"/> so yes the weekend Saturday the</u>
<u n="57" who="S0264">by train?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0265" trans="overlap">so Sunday the seventeenth will be fine</u>
<u n="59" who="S0264">I don't know how you can take all by train?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0265">what? train</u>
<u n="61" who="S0264">to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0265">yes I'm taking the train yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0264">how much is that?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0265">erm advanced ticket so I can't remember it's not not a lot</u>
<u n="65" who="S0264">sixty quid I bet</u>
<u n="66" who="S0265">yeah about that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0264">and what about the hotel and stuff?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0265">er no hotel it's just staying at friends <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0264">that's August bank holiday weekend isn't it?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0265">no that's the er twenty-fifth twenty-sixth</u>
<u n="71" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> and then your your mother is coming isn't she?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0265">erm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> two weeks after that isn't it?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh that's gonna be a nightmare</u>
<u n="74" who="S0265">and you're going away around about the same time</u>
<u n="75" who="S0264">I'm coming back or going away <pause dur="short"/> all sorts of things yes because of work and <pause dur="long"/> and that reminds me any day now there's gonna be another commission coming through the letter box and I haven't sorted out the last one properly</u>
<u n="76" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="77" who="S0264">and I think there isn't much <pause dur="short"/> well I've got that sorted out anyway sort of that one <pause dur="short"/> there's never time to get things properly finished or <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0265">what are those postcards?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0264">they're the ones from Skye</u>
<u n="80" who="S0265">oh are they?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0264">they got wet in Skye but they seem to have dried out but that's <pause dur="long"/> could send them to somebody</u>
<u n="82" who="S0265">mm I don't remember too er Portree looking like looking like that do you?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0264">where's Portree?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0265">that was that erm <pause dur="short"/> well you know where Portree is on Skye it's that that place where we</u>
<u n="85" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh yes it was <trunc>wh</trunc></u>
<u n="86" who="S0265" trans="overlap">we stayed at</u>
<u n="87" who="S0264">it's because we didn't go to the water much because it was raining all the time</u>
<u n="88" who="S0265">yeah it was quite misty as well</u>
<u n="89" who="S0264">ah I didn't see <pause dur="short"/> well this is obviously taken from a ship</u>
<u n="90" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah we did walk we walked down to that one that's painted white cos I think it's been repainted pink now</u>
<u n="92" who="S0265">well there was a all I remember at Portree down by the harbour was that row of terraced houses</u>
<u n="93" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0265" trans="overlap">all painted in bright colours</u>
<u n="95" who="S0264">yeah well that they weren't all you're <trunc>thinki</trunc> you're getting confused with Tobermory that's what this row here is <pause dur="short"/> er these cards are probably decades old</u>
<u n="96" who="S0265" whoConfidence="low">could be</u>
<u n="97" who="S0264">like that like those ones that we got from like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> say ninety-three</u>
<u n="98" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0264">I wouldn't have sent those if I'd realised <pause dur="short"/> and look at that little place there what <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc>that nobody could live there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="100" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0264">maybe it's a boathouse</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="102" who="S0265">I don't know I can't quite place it</u>
<u n="103" who="S0264">yeah cos we didn't walk that oh I know that white place is <trunc>act</trunc>actually a hotel <pause dur="short"/> and I think maybe the pink place <pause dur="short"/> is to the left of the picture where it is sort of pinky <pause dur="long"/> it's all depressing I don't I don't know what people saw in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> apart from those mountains that looked they looked quite nice from that island what was it called?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0265">yes erm well we went past on the boat they looked very dramatic didn't they?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0264">yeah it looked they looked better from er from those other islands was it mm <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0265">erm <pause dur="short"/> er I can't remember is this erm <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> wasn't it?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0264">yeah but we didn't go there we went to the other one</u>
<u n="108" who="S0265">no we went we sailed past them</u>
<u n="109" who="S0264">yes and we went</u>
<u n="110" who="S0265" trans="overlap">and then <anon type="place"/> was on the</u>
<u n="111" who="S0264">but as we were</u>
<u n="112" who="S0265" trans="overlap">the right hand side</u>
<u n="113" who="S0264">yes exactly and and so you could see the mountains but then</u>
<u n="114" who="S0265" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0264" trans="overlap">when you actually got to <anon type="place"/> you couldn't see anything</u>
<u n="116" who="S0265">no <pause dur="short"/> not where we went <pause dur="long"/> you know it's a bit of a funny shaped island wasn't it? it was like</u>
<u n="117" who="S0264">there was a play on the radio actually set on erm Raasay I think it's called</u>
<u n="118" who="S0265" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0264" trans="overlap">that that long thin island</u>
<u n="120" who="S0265">Raasay yes yes</u>
<u n="121" who="S0264">about somebody who'd built a road <pause dur="short"/> by himself</u>
<u n="122" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="123" who="S0264" trans="overlap">on what do you know about that?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0265">yes erm <pause dur="short"/> I think you mentioned them <pause dur="short"/> about this building this road all the way around the island or something</u>
<u n="125" who="S0264">I don't know about all the way around it was <pause dur="short"/> probably to the to the ferry port <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0265">where from?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0264">I don't know from where they lived I suppose <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0265">I don't think there's much on it anyway</u>
<u n="129" who="S0264">no it's probably like that one <pause dur="short"/> we went on last of all opposite <pause dur="short"/> oban</u>
<u n="130" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0264">that was a bit of a waste of time</u>
<u n="132" who="S0265" trans="overlap">oh yes yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0264">I wonder if they will <pause dur="short"/> I don't suppose they'll take the initiative and vote for independence <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0265">who would?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0264">Scots</u>
<u n="136" who="S0265">well</u>
<u n="137" who="S0264" trans="overlap">I looked at the map and it is much smaller than Norway but maybe the population is roughly the same size</u>
<u n="138" who="S0265">mm I think it is about the same isn't it? it's about</u>
<u n="139" who="S0264" trans="overlap">which</u>
<u n="140" who="S0265">is it four million or something?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0264">well probably</u>
<u n="142" who="S0265">very small</u>
<u n="143" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't see what that's got to do with it I don't <pause dur="long"/> I I don't think they'll do anything that's interesting I suppose anyway <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0265">I can't see them voting yes</u>
<u n="145" who="S0264">why not? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0265">well I can't really see any any <pause dur="short"/> strong argument</u>
<u n="147" who="S0264">well I can't see any strong argument for not voting yes quite honestly apart from negative ones <pause dur="short"/> I was surprised by that bloke on the boat do you remember? did you talk to him?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0265">no you spoke to him though</u>
<u n="149" who="S0264">I thought his er reasoning was very childlike childish too actually</u>
<u n="150" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0264">did you erm did you feel <pause dur="short"/> vindicated or did you feel embarrassed that we didn't get in the car? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0265">oh erm er that chap from St Andrews</u>
<u n="153" who="S0264">yes</u>
<u n="154" who="S0265">no because I I wasn't erm party to that conversation was I?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0264">yeah but were you happy that were you still happy when we saw him again in Portree that we hadn't accepted the lift or did you feel guilt?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0265">no I didn't feel any guilt no I well I mean why should why should I feel guilty I mean yes he he he offered to give us a lift erm but we have every right to say yes or no</u>
<u n="157" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I keep on</u>
<u n="158" who="S0265" trans="overlap">and and and <pause dur="short"/> we were quite happy just taking the bus so</u>
<u n="159" who="S0264">I keep remembering a bloke in Munich <trunc>off</trunc>offering me a lift to Vienna <pause dur="short"/> when I was <pause dur="short"/> mm on a trip <pause dur="short"/> from my from <anon type="place"/> actually</u>
<u n="160" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0264">and I think that's looking back I think that's highly suspicious</u>
<u n="162" who="S0265">yeah I think when you're by yourself you've got to be more wary</u>
<u n="163" who="S0264">exactly but he seemed all very very pleasant at the time I happened to say I was going Vienna next erm <pause dur="short"/> and erm and then and then he said er he was going there on Sunday and he'd give me a lift</u>
<u n="164" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0264">it was quite tempting cos I think I don't know how I knew but I think he seemed to have quite a nice car <pause dur="short"/> anyway the I think the main reason why I didn't was because I had an aeroplane ticket and I <trunc>w</trunc> I fancied <pause dur="short"/> going by plane</u>
<u n="166" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0264">yeah it was <trunc>qui</trunc>quite horrible thinking back thinking like what would have what might have happened if I had accepted</u>
<u n="168" who="S0265">mm and and the other thing is when when you're travelling in in someone's car you feel obliged to make conversation all the time which can be quite tiring and <trunc>pr</trunc>probably impossible for me with my hearing <pause dur="long"/> cos I can't hear very well in cars as you know</u>
<u n="169" who="S0264">well he <trunc>ju</trunc> he just didn't seem a terribly social person to me so I couldn't imagine how he would enjoy it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0265">no <pause dur="long"/> mm good point</u>
<u n="171" who="S0264">I mean it's a funny thing to do as well to go <pause dur="short"/> for your holidays on</u>
<u n="172" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yes he was he was just kind of</u>
<u n="173" who="S0264">drifting</u>
<u n="174" who="S0265">drifting yeah taking it as it comes like <pause dur="long"/> it was very strange</u>
<u n="175" who="S0264">but what do you think about that other bloke that artist that furniture person <pause dur="short"/> was that drifting?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember his</u>
<u n="177" who="S0264" trans="overlap">the <trunc>onl</trunc></u>
<u n="178" who="S0265" trans="overlap">background but why</u>
<u n="179" who="S0264" trans="overlap">the <trunc>ans</trunc> yes</u>
<u n="180" who="S0265">he he was doing something that he'd done several times before</u>
<u n="181" who="S0264">plus he'd hired a cottage or he'd <pause dur="short"/> been lent a cottage or something near Mallaig</u>
<u n="182" who="S0265">oh I can't remember that</u>
<u n="183" who="S0264" trans="overlap">outside Mallaig he had a car he had a car as well I think <pause dur="short"/> and there were other people that were gonna join him so it a bit of a different kettle of fish I think it was family or people were coming up <pause dur="long"/> did I tell you that I I wrote and erm reviewed his website and he wrote and thanked me?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0265">no you didn't</u>
<u n="185" who="S0264">ah a cursory acknowledgement and erm that was a but <trunc>d</trunc> you I don't I'm not surprised because probably people don't like to be given feedback on their websites</u>
<u n="186" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0264">cos you it's odds on it's quite likely you'd say the wrong thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0265">so did you did you so you you emailed him?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0264">yeah I told him</u>
<u n="190" who="S0265" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0264" trans="overlap">he needs some I think I probably said what what I <pause dur="short"/> said on the boat I think I I said you he needed some text I mean <pause dur="short"/> all that I could see unless he'd sent me not the correct links were pictures <pause dur="short"/> I think he called it a blog I <trunc>th</trunc> or I wouldn't I didn't see how it was a blog</u>
<u n="192" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0264">I probably said all the same things that I said on the boat that <pause dur="short"/> he needed to offer some tips and tell people something like how he chose his raw materials or how he approached <pause dur="short"/> a project just to give people an insight into <trunc>wh</trunc>what</u>
<u n="194" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0264" trans="overlap">he did</u>
<u n="196" who="S0265">yes <pause dur="long"/> and how long ago was was it when you sent him that email?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0264">oh I don't know probably when we got back</u>
<u n="198" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="199" who="S0264">the nineteenth of June</u>
<u n="200" who="S0265">well maybe he's changed it</u>
<u n="201" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I couldn't well I haven't got time to <pause dur="short"/> don't even know where the car or anything where <pause dur="short"/> not interested</u>
<u n="202" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0264">you can go you can check if you want</u>
<u n="204" who="S0265">well if if you can give give me the website and I can have a look</u>
<u n="205" who="S0264">are you really interested?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0265">no well <pause dur="short"/> sort of</u>
<u n="207" who="S0264">you wouldn't know it if</u>
<u n="208" who="S0265" trans="overlap">but but I wouldn't know what's erm what it looked like before</u>
<u n="209" who="S0264">no <pause dur="short"/> oh well yeah but you would know if there was any text there</u>
<u n="210" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="211" who="S0264">anyway I <trunc>wou</trunc> I'd be very surprised cos I I don't think he's the kind of person that takes advice from people <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0264">I think <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would and that prom that I heard on the radio the other night <pause dur="short"/> I think he must but yeah I think maybe he went for Richard Strauss cos I turned it on when I was eating it must have been the weekend and I cos I caught the end of er like Elgar's second symphony but it was conducted by some Russian and <pause dur="short"/> I did think it was a very strange interpretation I thought</u>
<u n="214" who="S0265">oh <pause dur="long"/> I don't know the second symphony I don't know much Elgar at all</u>
<u n="215" who="S0264" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc>you you would <trunc>recogni</trunc> well you'd <trunc>l</trunc>I thought the Dream of Gerontius was your favourite piece</u>
<u n="216" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's about the only</u>
<u n="217" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0265">Elgar I know well apart from the really popular</u>
<u n="219" who="S0264">well I think you'd recognise</u>
<u n="220" who="S0265" trans="overlap">Pomp and Circumstance</u>
<u n="221" who="S0264">well I think you'd <pause dur="short"/> he said that he heard that er played in a church in Sicily when he and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were there on holiday</u>
<u n="222" who="S0265">what Dream of Gerontius?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0264">er?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0265">which one?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0264">Pomp and Circumstance</u>
<u n="226" who="S0265" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0264">he thought it was for a wedding he thought it was very inappropriate</u>
<u n="228" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0264">do you think he meant the Land of Hope and Glory bit? do you is that what he means do you think?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0265">I don't know there are several of them aren't there?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0264">well I don't know</u>
<u n="232" who="S0265">so it depends</u>
<u n="233" who="S0264">I think that colours your thing cos he dismissed the second symphony and I said it's actually quite poignant because it's a sort of farewell to empire <pause dur="short"/> cos it's all very well saying er <trunc>yea</trunc> it it might pay lip service <pause dur="short"/> to those times that but I think the <trunc>v</trunc> the very spooky ending <pause dur="short"/> I think is an an acknowledgement that it's all over</u>
<u n="234" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0264">you well you'd you <trunc>wou</trunc> you would recognise it I'm sure you'd know what <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0265">mm I think</u>
<u n="237" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it's a hardly it's hardly a triumphant ending quite the opposite</u>
<u n="238" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/> yeah I'll have to listen to it at some time it's probably on Youtube</u>
<u n="239" who="S0264">everything is on Youtube I don't see how they can be on Youtube actually must be illegal on phones <pause dur="short"/> in people's pockets</u>
<u n="240" who="S0265">yes well all that copyright business seems to have just gone by the wayside <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0264">well I'm sure that I'm sure if people wanted to they could they could get in touch with Youtube and get these things taken off couldn't they?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0265">mm I don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0264">I'm I'm sure you I'm sure you can</u>
<u n="244" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it it's <pause dur="short"/> how how it how it works whether it's just when one person that <pause dur="short"/> has to request it to be removed or</u>
<u n="245" who="S0264">no well it it would be whoever is the copyright holder if it's a piece of art <pause dur="short"/> in the case of a concert I don't know maybe it's the concert organiser the promoter</u>
<u n="246" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0264">but that that could include the copyright holder I mean supposing Elgar's got family do they <trunc>b</trunc> er <trunc>i</trunc>is Elgar out of copyright? it's seventy years I suppose he would be <pause dur="short"/> does that mean that people can just print the music? <pause dur="long"/> copyright doesn't last it's finite you know</u>
<u n="248" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/> well the copyright is</u>
<u n="249" who="S0264">I think it's different in</u>
<u n="250" who="S0265" trans="overlap">acquired by the publisher isn't it?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0264">what you mean normally?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0265" trans="overlap">and and it's <trunc>n</trunc> probably fifty years or something like that is it?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0264">are you sure it's acquired by the publisher? because I thought it was the author <pause dur="long"/> look here's a book <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0265">I always thought it was the <trunc>publish</trunc></u>
<u n="255" who="S0264" trans="overlap">copyright Stephen Pinker so it's</u>
<u n="256" who="S0265" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="257" who="S0264" trans="overlap">so it's the author and it says <pause dur="short"/> nineteen ninety-four anyway I think it's probably life plus some years</u>
<u n="258" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0264">but then I'm sure things pass to your heirs</u>
<u n="260" who="S0265">mm I don't know no idea</u>
<u n="261" who="S0264">and also it's different in the USA I think actually it's shorter <pause dur="short"/> there</u>
<u n="262" who="S0265">oh is it?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0264">I think so <pause dur="short"/> I've got the word I've got the figure seventy-seventy years in my mind for the UK <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know if that's music or everything <pause dur="long"/> must read all this stuff</u>
<u n="264" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> and it would be a good thing as well like if tidy up all these all these <pause dur="short"/> books off the table</u>
<u n="266" who="S0265">yes</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="267" who="S0264">did you see about those seagulls in Rome by the way attacking er when the pope?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0265">no</u>
<u n="269" who="S0264">you must have read it it's on the BBC there's a thing on the BBC page</u>
<u n="270" who="S0265">oh that'll be on Youtube</u>
<u n="271" who="S0264">well it might be but they they released two doves and a seagull attacked one of the doves and what I didn't realise was they eat them</u>
<u n="272" who="S0265">oh gosh</u>
<u n="273" who="S0264">so they're beyond the pale as far as I'm concerned now they hit the the seagull got the dove but by er tail feathers and so the dove escaped minus a few feathers <pause dur="short"/> but then the second <pause dur="short"/> dove was killed by a crow</u>
<u n="274" who="S0265">oh gosh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0264">imagine the symbolism of that I mean how and it's very embarrassing as well imagine you're the pope <pause dur="short"/> and you're and you're there presumably on the balcony or whatever it was and this thing happens in front of what are you supposed to do?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0265">mm you'd think they'd have people to take care of that sort of thing and make sure there are no birds around</u>
<u n="277" who="S0264">how can they?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0265">well</u>
<u n="279" who="S0264" trans="overlap">but yeah apparently that's</u>
<u n="280" who="S0265" trans="overlap">scare them off or something</u>
<u n="281" who="S0264">that's a point of this report by a journalist BBC journalist whatever or a correspondent that it Rome has been overrun with these wretched what are they called? mackerel gulls? herring gulls</u>
<u n="282" who="S0265">herring gulls yes yes</u>
<u n="283" who="S0264">which are which are what these are</u>
<u n="284" who="S0265">these are yes</u>
<u n="285" who="S0264">they're horrid vicious things and you can tell about the way they're screaming and they're <unclear/> they've got slightly better but they're still ridiculous</u>
<u n="286" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0264">and anyway so I've got no <trunc>i</trunc> just fed up with them now that I know that they kill other birds like that <pause dur="long"/> I mean some other birds I know they don't they they just ignore them cos I've seen them I've seen jackdaws or crows and they just ignore the seagulls I mean</u>
<u n="288" who="S0265">well <trunc>th</trunc> I've I've heard that <trunc>s</trunc>seagulls don't like crows and they will stay away so if the if the the crows are nesting they will keep their distance</u>
<u n="289" who="S0264">not much though cos the on campus there's a there's a rookery and</u>
<u n="290" who="S0265" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0264">they've both flying there</u>
<u n="292" who="S0265" trans="overlap">mm yes well they I'd I <trunc>th</trunc> I think what's happened is that that cos there used to be a rookery up I the <anon type="place"/> for years</u>
<u n="293" who="S0264">has it gone?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="295" who="S0264">why?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0265">I don't know they probably just moved on and I think it's since they've gone that we've got the seagulls</u>
<u n="297" who="S0264">but it isn't yeah but the it isn't just in the close that they're nesting they're nesting</u>
<u n="298" who="S0265">yeah they're probably nesting in the vicinity or they were</u>
<u n="299" who="S0264">well it's a very large vicinity because on parallel streets they they are around and I doubt whether our little tiny rookery was influencing a couple of roads away or a couple of streets away er have you <trunc>deci</trunc> have you thought about the implications if they try to nest on the roof?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0264">you have? those flat bits</u>
<u n="302" who="S0265">yes yes well I mean lots of people they end up putting barbed wire or mesh up don't they to to keep them off their chimney stacks and <pause dur="short"/> stuff like that they like to nest <pause dur="short"/> between chimney stacks</u>
<u n="303" who="S0264">I don't cos er cos when I run past that house by the path into the park at the sort of bottom of <anon type="place"/> avenue I think <pause dur="short"/> why has that household holder allowed? cos they they must be able to nest up there cos they're always guarding they're always perching up on those roofs have you seen have you seen them?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>wh</trunc>which house is it?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0264">oh it one it it's it's near the path into the park</u>
<u n="306" who="S0265">right</u>
<u n="307" who="S0264">er it</u>
<u n="308" who="S0265" trans="overlap">it right next to the path</u>
<u n="309" who="S0264">it's before the turn in the road goes</u>
<u n="310" who="S0265" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="311" who="S0264">haven't you noticed them?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0265">no no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0264">anyway <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how that householder house owner tolerated them there</u>
<u n="314" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="315" who="S0264">but it isn't just me cos I've had <trunc>conversa</trunc> I've had a conversation with one person that obviously lives in the next street or lives around there about them oh that was about another lot that were that were there nesting in a different street but I've seen people who look up anyway <trunc>a</trunc>about the ones that we're talking about <pause dur="short"/> so I think it's a lot of <trunc>pea</trunc> and er <pause dur="short"/> rubbish is one thing but <vocal desc="sigh"/> cos they're pecking into plastic bags aren't they?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0265">mm oh they will do yes <pause dur="short"/> they create a lot of litter as well</u>
<u n="317" who="S0264">well that's certainly</u>
<u n="318" who="S0265" trans="overlap">a lot</u>
<u n="319" who="S0264">I've that's what's happening on the campus I'm sure that they are <pause dur="short"/> there's loads of junk junk food and <pause dur="long"/> I think they can make a concerted effort to get rid of them maybe put some <pause dur="short"/> poison down or something</u>
<u n="320" who="S0265">I think they have to do it more humanely that that <pause dur="short"/> well it the best thing is to er break their eggs isn't it?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0264">well <pause dur="short"/> that's I suppose what happened that year that that ridiculous seagull built the nest on the flight of steps</u>
<u n="322" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0264">and they were the flight of steps were cordoned off but eventually the nest <trunc>disa</trunc> I <trunc>ima</trunc><trunc>ima</trunc> they disappeared and I imagine it was a fox or some other rodent <pause dur="short"/> because it was just on the ground so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0264">what other what other apart from foxes? well it could be any wildlife in that area <pause dur="short"/> is it stoats and weasels?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0265">mm I dunno</u>
<u n="327" who="S0264">they all maybe they all go for eggs</u>
<u n="328" who="S0265">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0264">but it's er something's got to be done because as one of my colleagues said <pause dur="short"/> you are encouraged to shoot rabbits it's your duty well we all know that <pause dur="short"/> but the seagulls are protected <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0264">well <pause dur="short"/> that doesn't seem to make sense I'm not saying it's the seagulls' fault it's obviously cos human beings have been</u>
<u n="332" who="S0265">well it's it's the human</u>
<u n="333" who="S0264" trans="overlap">messing</u>
<u n="334" who="S0265">I think it's a human</u>
<u n="335" who="S0264">yeah because</u>
<u n="336" who="S0265" trans="overlap">that we caused it</u>
<u n="337" who="S0264">yeah probably by taking too much fish out of too many fish out of the sea so they've got nothing to live on where they should be living on them and so they've moved</u>
<u n="338" who="S0265">yeah and and we we leave too much too much food out rubbish and they scavenge</u>
<u n="339" who="S0264">but that doesn't give them an excuse to start pecking and killing other birds</u>
<u n="340" who="S0265">well that's just their nature <pause dur="short"/> that's that's <trunc>prob</trunc> they've probably always been like that <pause dur="short"/> but they are very vicious <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0264">reptilian <pause dur="long"/> yeah I wouldn't be surprised if they're around after human beings have gone</u>
<u n="342" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/> and maybe they could be quite adaptable <pause dur="short"/> as a species</u>
<u n="343" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/> maybe their stupidity is less stupid that human beings' stupidity <pause dur="short"/> in a way</u>
<u n="344" who="S0265">mm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
