<text id="SCQS">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:14</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0251 S0252</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living room in Malton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Oatcake experiment</topics>
		<activity>Oatcake</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0251">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>North Ferriby, East Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>GCSE Maths Examiner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0252">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>York</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0251">right so we're ready yeah so this'll be fun for the academics I think I'll make a nice change for them we're going to do the oatcake test now so I've got two plates of oatcakes one is the Morrisons brand and one is the Nairn's brand and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is going to see if he can determine which is which now what do you think about the appearance?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0252">erm well I think one is slightly darker than the other as in er the er type of oats used</u>
<u n="3" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0252">er the one that is using a darker complexion also a erm has a darker edge</u>
<u n="5" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0252">that's the other one erm is a lighter colour and a lighter edge in terms of roughness they're relatively similar and in terms of depth er the lighter one is just very slightly thinner</u>
<u n="7" who="S0251">okay then <pause dur="short"/> right so what about the taste?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0252">right the taste <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0251">do you think it's quite crisp that one?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0252">another the darker one has quite a a crunch</u>
<u n="11" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0252">erm relatively floury in <pause dur="short"/> taste <pause dur="short"/> erm er getting oat tastes and relatively crunchy for an oatcake</u>
<u n="13" who="S0251">right do you like that one?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0252">erm er er it's not a bad oatcake</u>
<u n="15" who="S0251">how many marks out of ten would you give it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0252" trans="overlap">er you can see the layers which is</u>
<u n="17" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="18" who="S0252">a good sign</u>
<u n="19" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0252">erm the I'd say it's er seven out of ten</u>
<u n="21" who="S0251">seven out of ten okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="23" who="S0251">now try the next one don't take a really huge bite</u>
<u n="24" who="S0252">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0251"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0252">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0251">so how do you find that one? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0252">not as crunchy</u>
<u n="29" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0252" trans="overlap">as the other one</u>
<u n="31" who="S0251" trans="overlap">not as crisp</u>
<u n="32" who="S0252">that's not quite as floury as the other one</u>
<u n="33" who="S0251">mm is that a good thing?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0252">in a <pause dur="short"/> slightly positive way erm the layers are still relatively well defined</u>
<u n="35" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="36" who="S0252">the it's like a little bit sweeter</u>
<u n="37" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0252">and that's</u>
<u n="39" who="S0251" trans="overlap">do you prefer it a little bit sweeter?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0252">slightly more oatier</u>
<u n="41" who="S0251">yes so how many marks out of ten for that one?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0252">er I think that's perhaps more of an eight and a half</u>
<u n="43" who="S0251">mm so you think that one's a superior product?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0252">I do</u>
<u n="45" who="S0251">so which one do you think is the Morrisons one and which one do you think is the Nairn's?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0252">I think the darker one is the Morrisons one</u>
<u n="47" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="48" who="S0252">and I think the lighter one is the Nairn's</u>
<u n="49" who="S0251">alright so let's turn the plates over <pause dur="short"/> that's the Nairn's</u>
<u n="50" who="S0252" trans="overlap">Nairn's is the dark one and Morrisons</u>
<u n="51" who="S0251" trans="overlap">that's the Morrisons one</u>
<u n="52" who="S0252" trans="overlap">is the lighter</u>
<u n="53" who="S0251">so are you right?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="55" who="S0251">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> so are you going to review your buying policy? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0251">are you surprised?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0252">I am a little bit surprised <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> I'd say</u>
<u n="59" who="S0251">do you think the labels are on the wrong dishes?</u>
<u n="60" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0252">er</u>
<u n="62" who="S0251">always a possibility</u>
<u n="63" who="S0252">yes yeah well I must admit I'm the ones that I've seen of Nairn's in the past have they looked more like that</u>
<u n="64" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0252">than that one</u>
<u n="66" who="S0251">it could be just a dark batch do you think?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0252">mm it could be a one-off</u>
<u n="68" who="S0251">quite a good snap</u>
<u n="69" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="70" who="S0251">mm that's good interesting so did you recognise your regular brand?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0252">seemingly not</u>
<u n="72" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0251">when we were small me and my sister we used to go to my uncle and auntie's on a Boxing Day</u>
<u n="74" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="75" who="S0251">my uncle used to do what was called the Smartie test</u>
<u n="76" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0251">and we used to blindfold him <pause dur="short"/> and then we used to feed him Smarties and he reckoned that he could detect which was the orange Smartie because in those days all the Smarties had milk chocolate in the middle but the one that was orange had orange flavoured chocolate in</u>
<u n="78" who="S0252">oh</u>
<u n="79" who="S0251">you know like a Terry's Chocolate Orange sort of taste</u>
<u n="80" who="S0252">oh right</u>
<u n="81" who="S0251">so we used to feed him the Smarties and he used to have to have a little sip of sherry in between each one just to cleanse the palate you know</u>
<u n="82" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0251">well it was Christmas wasn't it? and er we used to think that was great fun so we didn't know how happy we were you don't get uncles like that any more do you?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0252">not in</u>
<u n="85" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="86" who="S0252">not really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0251">no I don't think you've had an uncle like that have you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0251">we were quite lucky with uncles in those days</u>
<u n="90" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0251">mm and we had another uncle <unclear>not only</unclear> like that he took us to the zoo and erm I had this packet of ginger biscuits and we were feeding them to the elephants and I never knew that elephants really like ginger biscuits</u>
<u n="92" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0251">but they do</u>
<u n="94" who="S0252">I don't think you'd get away with that nowadays</u>
<u n="95" who="S0251">probably not it would say do not feed the animals</u>
<u n="96" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0251">health and safety regulations</u>
<u n="98" who="S0252">and what do you think er</u>
<u n="99" who="S0251" trans="overlap">and you</u>
<u n="100" who="S0252" trans="overlap">was the big attraction for the elephants to have the ginger biscuit?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0251">I don't know they'd probably got fed up of his normal I don't know what elephants normally eat</u>
<u n="102" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0251">what do they eat?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0252">bamboo sticks</u>
<u n="105" who="S0251">that's pandas isn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/> so probably a nice change to get something sweet</u>
<u n="106" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0251">and erm I heard it said that the way to have a happy and fulfilled life apart from having uncles that do a Smartie test and let you feed ginger biscuits to elephants is to plant a tree</u>
<u n="108" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0251">to have a son and to write a book <pause dur="short"/> so we how many trees have you planted?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0252">I've planted five trees I've planted an apple tree a plum tree erm a pear tree er a cherry tree and er another apple so that's one dessert apple and one cooking apple</u>
<u n="111" who="S0251">mm and have they brought you happiness?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0252">er no I don't really in some ways it's er the performance with trees is erm very varied erm think one delight that is more or less guaranteed every year is that erm the trees blossom which er</u>
<u n="113" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0252">they have very delicate and intricate flowers</u>
<u n="115" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah they're beautiful aren't they?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0252">but er in terms of fruits it's a bit less predictable</u>
<u n="117" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0252">er perhaps so far as the saying you can't count chickens until the eggs have hatched</u>
<u n="119" who="S0251">that's right</u>
<u n="120" who="S0252">erm that er frosts and disease and pest attacks</u>
<u n="121" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0252">can affect the crop</u>
<u n="123" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0252">once the er blossom has set so</u>
<u n="125" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I think once you get the blossom they are quite vulnerable aren't they?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0251">and although they had a lot of blossom on all of the trees</u>
<u n="128" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0251">the pear for instance I think</u>
<u n="130" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I think two</u>
<u n="131" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I think there's only about two pears</u>
<u n="132" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="133" who="S0251">and I don't mean four I mean four I mean two</u>
<u n="134" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0251">pears</u>
<u n="136" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="137" who="S0251">not bad on the plums had quite a lot of plums this year</u>
<u n="138" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="139" who="S0251">we've made plum jam</u>
<u n="140" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="141" who="S0251">and plum chutney and I've been able to put lots of plums in the freezer for crumbles and things</u>
<u n="142" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0251">in the winter</u>
<u n="144" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="145" who="S0251">so I think they've been quite a joy don't you?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0251">and picking the apples climbing up the ladder and <pause dur="short"/> getting all the best ones which are always at the top aren't they?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0252">yes and the erm extender the like a net on a pole is quite a good buy</u>
<u n="149" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah that's been really invaluable hasn't it?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0252">but I'm very tall so that helps</u>
<u n="151" who="S0251">true I've also had quite a good harvest of brambles</u>
<u n="152" who="S0252">yes it's been a bit of a surprise that has</u>
<u n="153" who="S0251">I think the good thing about brambles is they're not hard to grow</u>
<u n="154" who="S0252">they're not hard to grow</u>
<u n="155" who="S0251" trans="overlap">they're more or less a weed I think <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0252" trans="overlap">but they are expensive to buy</u>
<u n="157" who="S0251">they are expensive they are very dear</u>
<u n="158" who="S0252">yes so say compared to an apple or a</u>
<u n="159" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0252">plum</u>
<u n="161" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0252">which maybe twenty or thirty pence each a punnet of blackberries could easily be two or three pounds</u>
<u n="163" who="S0251">yeah and picked about two ice cream boxes of brambles this year haven't we?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="165" who="S0251">I think we've done well and there's still some to pick aren't there cos some</u>
<u n="166" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0251">are not quite ripe yet</u>
<u n="168" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="169" who="S0251">so there's</u>
<u n="170" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0251" trans="overlap">some more to pick for next week</u>
<u n="172" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I'd say because it's on a a little bit of a slope</u>
<u n="173" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0252" trans="overlap">they're gonna like that because</u>
<u n="175" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm well drained</u>
<u n="176" who="S0252" trans="overlap">this should be well they'll be well drained</u>
<u n="177" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="178" who="S0252">and they're <unclear></unclear> as well</u>
<u n="179" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think it's probably quite an old saying because I think it will be considered a bit unfair to say that just a son will make you happy and fulfilled I think any child really has potential</u>
<u n="180" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm that's</u>
<u n="181" who="S0251" trans="overlap">whether it's a boy or a girl but I think it's a bit like the Christmas carol it's all your hopes and all your fears when you have your baby and watch them grow up cos somehow it's more heightened the sensation for instance when you've been doing your exams I've been much more perplexed and really felt for you more so than when I did them myself I think you take it more in my stride I think</u>
<u n="182" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="183" who="S0251">but er it seems more important when it's your own child I think and really it's your life's work watching your child grow up and it's all your effort trying to make it right and trying to make it erm better than it was for you and make you</u>
<u n="184" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="185" who="S0251">more successful and that you erm get the benefit of what I've learnt</u>
<u n="186" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0251">and my education so that you know the benefit trickles down the generations</u>
<u n="188" who="S0252">yes I think perhaps books are a bit more of a a tricky aspect I suppose one thing is erm everyone well most people would have the ability to be able to write a book but it's</u>
<u n="189" who="S0251" trans="overlap">well I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0252" trans="overlap">but it's it's quite another thing getting it published and</u>
<u n="191" who="S0251" trans="overlap">true</u>
<u n="192" who="S0252">into a a shop</u>
<u n="193" who="S0251">yes well we've got quite a few stories that we've written down haven't we?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="195" who="S0251">but just because we haven't got them published it just means that they're going to be within the family aren't they? so</u>
<u n="196" who="S0252">mm yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0251" trans="overlap">in some ways it sort of keeps it private doesn't it? and they're our special stories</u>
<u n="198" who="S0252">yes certainly</u>
<u n="199" who="S0251">that we'll still have to share won't we? you think what <pause dur="short"/> there is the common factor between all those things is that it's something that is going to live after you've gone it's like a little bit of a legacy</u>
<u n="200" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0251">the trees'll be still there for some time</u>
<u n="202" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="203" who="S0251">after we've all grown old and <pause dur="short"/> your children are there mostly unless there's an accident after you've gone <pause dur="short"/> and your work really what you've written <pause dur="short"/> could be I suppose these days people write blogs don't they?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0251">erm I suppose in the old days you used to write a diary</u>
<u n="206" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="207" who="S0251">and they were meant to be private they were often sold with a little key or a little padlock on</u>
<u n="208" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="209" who="S0251">because they were private and secret and confidential but nowadays people seem to put the blogs on the internet</u>
<u n="210" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0251">for everybody to share and everybody to read</u>
<u n="212" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="213" who="S0251">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> there seems to be a difference in attitude doesn't there? about whether it's</u>
<u n="214" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="215" who="S0251">private or whether it's something that you're going to share with anybody who cares to read your diary</u>
<u n="216" who="S0252">I think there are a number of downsides to that is that people are posting things every twenty minutes or</u>
<u n="217" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="218" who="S0252" trans="overlap">every hour or something that when if you meet that person erm face-to-face you you don't actually have anything to discuss</u>
<u n="219" who="S0251" trans="overlap">new to say <pause dur="short"/> well you could talk about what they've already said</u>
<u n="220" who="S0252">yes but then</u>
<u n="221" who="S0251" trans="overlap">in the diary but there isn't any news is there? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it's nothing <unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0251">no there isn't anything new to tell you cos you already know it all</u>
<u n="224" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0251">and another thing is that things might be said that you wish you hadn't said</u>
<u n="226" who="S0252">I know</u>
<u n="227" who="S0251">that you want to change and there's this controversy about whether you can hide things that have been put on the internet for instance</u>
<u n="228" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="229" who="S0251"><unclear/> retract them <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know that it's possible is it?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0252">well I think er the European Union er the court rulings have erm tried <trunc>t</trunc> made it possible for people to block er results from when you search their own name erm in the key search engines</u>
<u n="231" who="S0251">right I believe that people who are looking to recruit or employ people for jobs can check Facebook accounts</u>
<u n="232" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0251">and things see if there's any silly photographs or compromising</u>
<u n="234" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="235" who="S0251">photographs and so on that they probably wish they hadn't put on</u>
<u n="236" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0251">if they're applying for a serious job</u>
<u n="238" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I don't think it would really help you</u>
<u n="240" who="S0252">no so at least one advantage of not having a Facebook account</u>
<u n="241" who="S0251">yes I don't think it's something that really appeals to me I think if I want to tell a friend something or if I want to tell my family something then I'd rather meet them and tell them personally</u>
<u n="242" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0251">or tell them over the telephone rather than just put it out there and then you have to er look on the Facebook account if you find out if I've got any news to tell you</u>
<u n="244" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes but er some might say it's a way of keeping in contact with perhaps your extended family or friends</u>
<u n="245" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="246" who="S0252" trans="overlap">that you haven't met for a long time</u>
<u n="247" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes or maybe some people are are more private than others</u>
<u n="248" who="S0252">unless I suppose it's because it's a reflection of individual personalities</u>
<u n="249" who="S0251">yes yes <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0252">one thing that really I've not done er for I don't think we've ever done it is made marmalade with them whilst we've made chutney and we've made</u>
<u n="251" who="S0251" trans="overlap">true</u>
<u n="252" who="S0252" trans="overlap">er jams but no</u>
<u n="253" who="S0251" trans="overlap">and lemon curd</u>
<u n="254" who="S0252">and lemon curd</u>
<u n="255" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I love your lemon curd you have to have that or it wouldn't be a real Christmas would it?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0251">if you didn't have lemon curd tarts</u>
<u n="258" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0251">mince pies but grandma makes it doesn't she?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0252">she does</u>
<u n="261" who="S0251">both grandmas actually</u>
<u n="262" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="263" who="S0251">have made it</u>
<u n="264" who="S0252">they have</u>
<u n="265" who="S0251">but it think it's become something that is being consumed mainly by the older generation</u>
<u n="266" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0251" trans="overlap">the <trunc>gen</trunc> grandma generation</u>
<u n="268" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0251">we don't really have it</u>
<u n="270" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="271" who="S0251" trans="overlap">apart from at Christmas</u>
<u n="272" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0251">but that's when we have the grandparents visiting</u>
<u n="274" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0251" trans="overlap">but we do eat it then don't we?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0252">yeah erm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0251">I don't dislike it</u>
<u n="278" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="279" who="S0251">but we don't really have it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="281" who="S0251">during the year somehow</u>
<u n="282" who="S0252">also erm I sometimes use it in my ginger parkin recipe</u>
<u n="283" who="S0251">yes that's true</u>
<u n="284" who="S0252" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="285" who="S0251">yes when we make that at Halloween time</u>
<u n="286" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="287" who="S0251">with a spoonful of marmalade can help you make it nice and moist can't it?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0252">yes <pause dur="short"/> are there any other er condiments or preserves that you would ever consider making?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0251" trans="overlap">erm well we've made two jams haven't we raspberry jam cos we went raspberry picking didn't we?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="291" who="S0251">and the plum jam which we made as the kind of it's supposed to be Christmas in a jar jam plums <pause dur="short"/> er orange juice and orange rind spices like cinnamon and some port I think that was really nice</u>
<u n="292" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="293" who="S0251" trans="overlap">and it's very good for them cold winter mornings isn't it to have toast and that jam and the lemon curd I'm not really thinking of any more cos I don't think we could eat much more jam really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0251">the next thing I'll be thinking about making is erm Christmas puddings</u>
<u n="296" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0251">and then we're going to make the Christmas cakes maybe September October time</u>
<u n="298" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0251">to give them plenty of time to mature ready for Christmas</u>
<u n="300" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0251">and then keep feeding them with brandy putting the little holes in the bottom and</u>
<u n="302" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="303" who="S0251">feeding them up so they're nice and moist</u>
<u n="304" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="305" who="S0251">I think we've had quite a good success on that</u>
<u n="306" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0251">and it's a little tradition that we've built up together isn't it?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm the one thing we have yet to do is to erm get a a mixer that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="310" who="S0252">is fully capable of er</u>
<u n="311" who="S0251" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="312" who="S0252">meeting the er demanding requirements at this time of year</u>
<u n="313" who="S0251">quite I think the food mixer we've got is really past its best isn't it?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0252">it is</u>
<u n="315" who="S0251">it's on its last legs and</u>
<u n="316" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it's making a lot of noise and I think the</u>
<u n="317" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it's making a lot of noise and</u>
<u n="318" who="S0252">er the motor <unclear>clogs</unclear> are not quite catching are they?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yeah no they're not and there's a bit of a strange rubbery smell when it er</u>
<u n="320" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0251">it's been running for some time so</u>
<u n="322" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yeah so are you planning to get a another hand mixer or are you thinking about more like a a chef's mixer with a</u>
<u n="323" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0252">a bit of a large bowl and spinning</u>
<u n="325" who="S0251">yeah I would like that because I think it will be easier for me because I find it quite heavy now doing the mix there</u>
<u n="326" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="327" who="S0251">especially if it's butter as opposed to margarine it's quite stiff to get it erm nice and soft so if you had a mixer with the stand I think that will be easier</u>
<u n="328" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="329" who="S0251">but the downside is they are quite a lot more expensive</u>
<u n="330" who="S0252" trans="overlap">they are</u>
<u n="331" who="S0251">aren't they?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="333" who="S0251">so we'd have to do a bit of research I think <pause dur="short"/> erm and see if we could find one at a good price maybe if</u>
<u n="334" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="335" who="S0251">John Lewis have a sale or something</u>
<u n="336" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="337" who="S0251">we could er get one there that would be suitable</u>
<u n="338" who="S0252">yes but by the look of it a suitable replacement does need to be found within the next</u>
<u n="339" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0252">three weeks perhaps</u>
<u n="341" who="S0251">true because we need to get these Christmas cakes started and</u>
<u n="342" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="343" who="S0251">yeah I know</u>
<u n="344" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="345" who="S0251">I don't know what we'll do</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
