<text id="SCWJ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:51:38</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-02</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0517 S0518</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Fradley, Staffs</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Death, cancer, health (mental and physical), family, children.</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about family members and health issues.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, Inquiring, Advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0517">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sutton Coldfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Self employed - marketing &amp; Proofing services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- working knowledge; German -- Working knowledge</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0518">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Staffordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services Team Leader</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0518">erm no I think it's fine well I say I think it's fine <pause dur="short"/> we had a chat this morning he's gone to London</u>
<u n="2" who="S0517">how long's he gone for?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0518">till I think he's <trunc>c</trunc> I think he'll come back Wednesday night cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got this sixth form open <trunc>epen</trunc>evening</u>
<u n="4" who="S0517">oh are you going to that?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0517">so are you not running?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0518">well you can't can you?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I was gonna talk to you about that?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0518">haven't you got <pause dur="short"/> something?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I <pause dur="short"/> well I probably could but erm <pause dur="short"/> I've just <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>erm</unclear></u>
<u n="11" who="S0518">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> right well we won't talk about that at the moment <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0518">erm in my mind I was thinking you were busy that day <pause dur="short"/> and then it was the sixth form open evening which starts at half six</u>
<u n="14" who="S0517">oh is it half six?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0517">I thought it was <trunc>se</trunc> er said seven on the website</u>
<u n="17" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="18" who="S0517">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been asked to erm <pause dur="short"/> go to it you know as a sixth-former</u>
<u n="19" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="20" who="S0517">so <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>s</trunc> but either way I did think oh I bet you're going and I bet we're not running on Wednesday</u>
<u n="21" who="S0518">he erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it starts at half six but he said he would find out more details today</u>
<u n="22" who="S0517">so what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> done going to do? how's he getting home or do you want me to drop him home?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know because <pause dur="short"/> I thought <pause dur="short"/> I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I'll probably come back on Wednesday so I said <pause dur="short"/> can you try to come back for half six because it's the sixth form open evening? <pause dur="short"/> so he said yes <pause dur="short"/> and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you won't be able to do football training that night <pause dur="short"/> because you'll be at that but</u>
<u n="24" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="25" who="S0518" trans="overlap">obviously <pause dur="short"/> so will quite a few of his <pause dur="short"/> team <anon type="place"/> City</u>
<u n="26" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0518">involved in that erm <pause dur="short"/> and then I was just thinking depending on what time it ended <pause dur="short"/> I would just <trunc>sai</trunc><trunc>said</trunc>say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> can <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just walk into it? <pause dur="short"/> like can he just go and find us there?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> see when I went last year <pause dur="short"/> the talk was at the beginning in the theatre</u>
<u n="29" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0517">and then after that you just <trunc>wal</trunc> you just walked around to the various departments that interested you in you know the A levels they wanted to do <pause dur="short"/> and just spoke individually to the teachers so that bit was really informal <pause dur="short"/> so after the theatre talk which</u>
<u n="31" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0517">he'll miss cos he'll be doing football training he can just come in and find you</u>
<u n="33" who="S0518">that's what I wondered</u>
<u n="34" who="S0517"><unclear>but</unclear> just in classrooms</u>
<u n="35" who="S0518">because obviously I got your <pause dur="short"/> text and I thought <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>h</trunc> it probably sounds like you won't be running on Wednesday anyway <pause dur="short"/> and then I was thinking oh do you need somebody to ring <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="37" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh</unclear></u>
<u n="38" who="S0517">no no <unclear>but I</unclear> can drop <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> home if he doesn't come in to you <pause dur="short"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="39" who="S0518">haven't run together for so long have we?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0517" trans="overlap">we haven't I know I know <pause dur="short"/> no ages</u>
<u n="41" who="S0518">well I'm sure we will get back into it</u>
<u n="42" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we will</u>
<u n="43" who="S0518">it's just been <pause dur="short"/> summer holidays we were away you were away <pause dur="short"/> er you know after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whatever whatever whatever</u>
<u n="44" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know and then since then it's just been</u>
<u n="45" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0517">been <trunc>play</trunc></u>
<u n="47" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0517">anyway so</u>
<u n="49" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think he's okay <pause dur="short"/> he's worried because he hasn't had a big <pause dur="short"/> full-on</u>
<u n="52" who="S0518" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="53" who="S0518">cry but I said to him you're not that sort of person <pause dur="short"/> and I said you're <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>em</trunc>emotionally you're very calm anyway so</u>
<u n="54" who="S0517">so <trunc>di</trunc> was he told over the phone then that his?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0517">dad had died oh</u>
<u n="57" who="S0518">so I'd spoken to the hospital that day</u>
<u n="58" who="S0517">right?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0518">and erm <pause dur="short"/> basically <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know if you know any of this do you know that we were going to a wedding reception last Saturday and then we got a call?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0517">yeah yes you put that in a text to me</u>
<u n="61" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="62" who="S0517">and then he he ended up going to London and you</u>
<u n="63" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went so we were literally we were all dressed up <pause dur="short"/> I felt stupid because <pause dur="short"/> I put a picture of me on Facebook with my rollers in</u>
<u n="64" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's what I saw <pause dur="short"/> I did see that yes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0518">to my sister-in-law because erm she we have this joke that whenever I'm whenever I'm going out <pause dur="short"/> I put my rollers in you see</u>
<u n="66" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="67" who="S0518">and she was like oh auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you haven't been out for so long like this <pause dur="short"/> so I put this picture on like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm going out <pause dur="short"/> and then a few people commented like somebody from work oh are you going out out? and erm a few you know <pause dur="short"/> er different people contact me <trunc>ab</trunc>about it <pause dur="short"/> and later on they said erm <pause dur="short"/> oh did we saw your picture did you have a nice evening? where did you go? was it <trunc>rea</trunc> and then I had to sort of say well we didn't go in the end</u>
<u n="68" who="S0517">oh so what time did he get the call?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> erm well we we were going <pause dur="short"/> we were literally getting into the car and it was about half past seven <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> had been to the hospital that day so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lived in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> he had gone with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and his two children and we were a bit worried about the children going to be honest but he said no I want them to go</u>
<u n="70" who="S0517"><trunc>w</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> was he taking them to say goodbye or just to see <trunc>th</trunc> see their grandad or?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm yeah well <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>s</trunc> he said dad's gonna be in dad's gonna go downhill in the next few months <pause dur="short"/> and I'd rather that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> see him <pause dur="short"/> while he's still himself <pause dur="short"/> but I'd seen him on Tuesday and I said he isn't</u>
<u n="72" who="S0517">he's not himself</u>
<u n="73" who="S0518">he's like a corpse oh <pause dur="short"/> shouldn't</u>
<u n="74" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0518">he's like he is though he's like a corpse to be honest and erm <pause dur="short"/> he's really confused and it's</u>
<u n="76" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0518">quite scary it's upsetting for me as an adult</u>
<u n="78" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>h</trunc>how old are their children?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s four months younger than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fifteen and erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is er <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> er twelve</u>
<u n="80" who="S0517">mm I mean I know you you know they're old enough to to to understand and appreciate and er but it it will stick with you and it's not nice to see them like that it's not nice</u>
<u n="81" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>erm</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are you sure? and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went ah yeah yeah I want them to see him while he's still okay and I and I said he isn't he looked really really <pause dur="short"/> ill this week really ill <pause dur="short"/> and it was weird <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because <pause dur="short"/> when I said goodbye to him I said goodbye to him because I</u>
<u n="82" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0518">the this feeling came over me and I just thought</u>
<u n="84" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was that last? last Tuesday?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0518">the <trunc>Tue</trunc> yeah the</u>
<u n="86" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0518">I'm not coming back here again it's funny how you get those feelings isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> I just thought I'm not I don't think I'm coming back here again <pause dur="short"/> and erm so I <pause dur="short"/> when I said my goodbye to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said my goodbye <pause dur="short"/> and erm and I walked along the edge of the hospital and I just sort of looked up and I just thought yeah I just got a funny feeling but anyway <pause dur="short"/> got on the train and everything <pause dur="short"/> but he looked bad <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to take them he wanted to take them so then I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well in that case maybe we ought to give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the option we shouldn't decide for them</u>
<u n="88" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0518">anyway they both said no they didn't want to <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had seen <pause dur="short"/> grandad only a few weeks ago and he said <pause dur="short"/> he hugged me goodbye and went oh lovely to see you good luck with your football and your <unclear>kids</unclear></u>
<u n="90" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and that and that's how he <trunc>want</trunc></u>
<u n="91" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0517">wants to remember him <unclear>yes you know</unclear></u>
<u n="93" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and he said I want to <trunc>kee</trunc> I want us to keep like that <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> which you know was fi= that was fine and er <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and the children on the Saturday <pause dur="short"/> they literally <pause dur="short"/> just got back to <anon type="place"/> so they driven down <pause dur="short"/> hospital visited <pause dur="short"/> turned around <pause dur="short"/> went back to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a call from the hospital to say <pause dur="short"/> erm he's really deteriorated <pause dur="short"/> he's had erm <pause dur="short"/> a choking attack <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't seem to be able to swallow <pause dur="short"/> erm his breathing's altered and we think that <trunc>i</trunc> you know? he <trunc>s</trunc> doesn't have much time so can he come to the hospital? <pause dur="short"/> then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> rang us and said we've been called to the hospital <pause dur="short"/> so I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like we'll all go and he said I don't know <pause dur="short"/> no cos I don't know what I'm gonna find I don't know if it's too late I just don't know</u>
<u n="94" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0518">we just don't know</u>
<u n="96" who="S0517"><unclear>oh</unclear></u>
<u n="97" who="S0518">so then I was a bit in shock because I didn't know what to do cos literally got this gift in my hand and we're all dressed up and all of this so I said <pause dur="short"/> I think I need to go and <pause dur="short"/> see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and just <pause dur="short"/> wish them a happy day and give them the gift but also <pause dur="short"/> strange wedding anyway</u>
<u n="98" who="S0517">oh was it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0518">yeah because they don't have any money so they'd <trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> organised this wedding <pause dur="short"/> they'd only literally got their family and the best man in the day <pause dur="short"/> and their friends invited at nighttime and said <pause dur="short"/> rather than giving us a gift <pause dur="short"/> like can you <pause dur="short"/> we had to bring food <pause dur="short"/> so we all</u>
<u n="100" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really? oh that is a strange wedding oh gosh</u>
<u n="101" who="S0518" trans="overlap">we organised our own food</u>
<u n="102" who="S0517">where was it at?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0518">it was at and it was really pretty actually <pause dur="short"/> at <anon type="place"/> Hall <pause dur="short"/> it's on the A5  is it <anon type="place"/>? going out <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> it's that road that goes up <pause dur="short"/> behind the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you can</u>
<u n="104" who="S0517">oh what out towards <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and <pause dur="short"/> yeah that one that building</u>
<u n="106" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes I know I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it goes out through <anon type="place"/> we passed a pub called the <anon type="place"/> Arms <anon type="place"/> is on your left</u>
<u n="108" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I know that yes yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0518">and it's just on the edge of the road <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="110" who="S0517">okay I know where you are yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0518" trans="overlap">sort of opposite the <trunc>t</trunc> crossroads where you would go to <anon type="place"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> erm football training ground <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but anyway that's <pause dur="short"/> where it was so they'd all said can you bring your own food? and one of our friends works at the <anon type="place"/> so she had organised <pause dur="short"/> all these platters of food <pause dur="short"/> including gluten-free options and stuff for the boys as well <pause dur="short"/> and we were all paying her a contribution</u>
<u n="112" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="113" who="S0518">so I was like saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know even though they said no gifts and we'd got them a card and <pause dur="short"/> something anyway and erm <pause dur="short"/> we'd done all the food and I said I haven't paid <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <pause dur="short"/> I oh even if if I text that'll be like really <pause dur="short"/> rude and it'll still be a shock and <trunc>u</trunc>upset people so it's better if I just go in person but not stay and</u>
<u n="114" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="115" who="S0518">I just didn't know he just went</u>
<u n="116" who="S0517">did he drive then? but oh okay</u>
<u n="117" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I was worried about him cos it's half past seven <pause dur="short"/> by the time he got his sleeping bag and his overnight stuff he was setting off it was like eight o'clock probably</u>
<u n="118" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0518">and he was gonna meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at the house then they were gonna go to the hospital so they weren't gonna get there till half ten</u>
<u n="120" who="S0517">what about <pause dur="short"/> the other brother?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0518">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was already there</u>
<u n="122" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0518">but he didn't wanna go on his own so he was gonna meet</u>
<u n="124" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="125" who="S0518">they were gonna pick him up as well</u>
<u n="126" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0518">so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> by the time they got to him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he was three sheets to the wind <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0517">oh what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <trunc>w</trunc> oh really?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0518">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had to say <pause dur="short"/> have you been drinking? <pause dur="short"/> said well I had a glass of wine and you know and ah and the rest</u>
<u n="132" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0518">said he practically fell over getting into the car <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh no</u>
<u n="135" who="S0518">but erm so yeah so he went off and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I don't want to I want to just I <trunc>h</trunc> I <trunc>h</trunc> I wanna stay here I wanna stay here so he was just upset and wanted to stay at home <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <pause dur="short"/> I want to stick with you <pause dur="short"/> I don't want you to drive out into the night on your own dad's driven out I don't want you to drive out so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came with me <pause dur="short"/> so we went to the village hall it looked beautiful it was so pretty <pause dur="short"/> wished them a happy day apologised they just said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad's not very well so he's not able to come <pause dur="short"/> and I'm only just gonna stay a few minutes and go but I just wanted to see you <pause dur="short"/> erm but then like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there and a few of our other friends they were really nice and okay <pause dur="short"/> look a bit shell-shocked what's happened? right <pause dur="short"/> just go home <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said you're not paying me for the food <pause dur="short"/> you're not gonna even gonna eat it just go just go <pause dur="short"/> so I went and got a Chinese takeaway for the boys I didn't have anything and then erm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="137" who="S0518">that that's what happened that night <pause dur="short"/> forgotten <unclear>whilst I say all this</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> erm and the next day was my parents' golden wedding party</u>
<u n="138" who="S0517">oh you said you were going to that</u>
<u n="139" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh and it was a church service</u>
<u n="140" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>di</trunc> when did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come back?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0518">he didn't get back till the evening</u>
<u n="142" who="S0517">on Sunday?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="145" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but he came to their house and just had some cake and champagne because <pause dur="short"/> he <pause dur="short"/> he missed the lunch he missed the <trunc>s</trunc> the mass</u>
<u n="146" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0518">he missed everything else <pause dur="short"/> but he did that which he didn't have to do <pause dur="short"/> but he did do it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0517">so this is a <pause dur="short"/> is this a week ago Saturday?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's last weekend</u>
<u n="150" who="S0517">right okay</u>
<u n="151" who="S0518">because basically they got there and his dad was <pause dur="short"/> still</u>
<u n="152" who="S0517">no no the weekend just gone this <trunc>was</trunc>wasn't it?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0518">no <pause dur="short"/> no <trunc>th</trunc> it was</u>
<u n="154" who="S0517">I've lost track cos when did you send me a text saying could I have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you might be going to London?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0518">this weekend <pause dur="short"/> but that was because he was still with us</u>
<u n="156" who="S0517">oh <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="157" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so this all happened the weekend before the twenty-something <pause dur="short"/> of</u>
<u n="158" who="S0517">yes start of half-term wasn't it?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0518" trans="overlap">twenty-four <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes I remember now sorry yes yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0518" trans="overlap">anyway that's that's fine and erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> but they <trunc>c</trunc> ended up coming <pause dur="short"/> staying the night going back the hospital the next day <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> being told that erm <pause dur="short"/> the doctors were in of two minds <pause dur="short"/> one set of doctors thought that there was hope and the others basically didn't <pause dur="short"/> erm they're gonna try him on a different</u>
<u n="162" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0518">antibiotic <pause dur="short"/> his breathing was still really laboured and shallow <pause dur="short"/> he'd got pneumonia they'd put <pause dur="short"/> a <pause dur="short"/> chest <pause dur="short"/> lung pump into him <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> that was pumping the fluid off the lungs to try and keep them clear <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just said look whatever you're gonna do don't prolong his dying <pause dur="short"/> if you think there's a chance that a different antibiotic will</u>
<u n="164" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0518">bring him round then do so but <trunc>pl</trunc> don't just prolong</u>
<u n="166" who="S0517">no well not at <trunc>nine</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> ninety-four?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0518" trans="overlap">three yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0517">ninety-three</u>
<u n="169" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you don't want that do you?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="172" who="S0517">you just</u>
<u n="173" who="S0518">so they said we're in two frames of mind</u>
<u n="174" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="175" who="S0518">but <pause dur="short"/> you can't set up camp here <pause dur="short"/> you you need to go home you can't this <pause dur="short"/> last night was critical <pause dur="short"/> he's he's <pause dur="short"/> still with us he's hanging on <pause dur="short"/> you know it could be three months it could be three days we don't know <pause dur="short"/> so that's why they came home on the Sunday</u>
<u n="176" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="177" who="S0518">and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone in every day and then I've rung the hospital and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s rung the hospital and then Tuesday we're told <pause dur="short"/> nothing else they could do <pause dur="short"/> he was being put into the palliative care team <pause dur="short"/> so that just makes his last few days comfortable <pause dur="short"/> they've</u>
<u n="178" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0518">taken out erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> the antibiotic they've taken out the lung pump <pause dur="short"/> they <trunc>d</trunc> weren't doing any more obs so they were doing no more blood pressure or anything like that <pause dur="short"/> they weren't feeding him cos they were feeding him intravenously so they'd taken away all fluid all food <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> basically they were turning him and swabbing his mouth and that's what they were gonna do</u>
<u n="180" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0518">so I rang the hospital on the Thursday <pause dur="short"/> and obviously he was still <pause dur="short"/> there <pause dur="short"/> and I said <pause dur="short"/> the fact that he's still going <pause dur="short"/> do you think that he could that he is strong enough to pull through? <pause dur="short"/> and she didn't say yes and she didn't say no she just said <pause dur="short"/> he hasn't responded to any treatment and she said we are no longer treating him</u>
<u n="182" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="183" who="S0518">and that was on Thursday morning and then Thursday at ten fifteen <pause dur="short"/> the hospital rang <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and said <pause dur="short"/> he's just passed away <pause dur="short"/> peacefully <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> rang <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I was at a drama rehearsal but then I literally just walked through the door after he'd finished on the phone call so I'd missed the call by a few minutes <pause dur="short"/> just looked at his face and he just went like this so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> I said I'm so sorry and I had I just cried straightaway cos that's just me <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and the boys were just sitting there in silence really and I said have you hugged your dad? and they said no <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="184" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> but what are they like boys? I mean mine would</u>
<u n="185" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0517">my two would <pause dur="short"/> be the same they just</u>
<u n="187" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came in the kitchen he said I didn't know what to do mum I didn't know what to do and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a bit later hugged <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me <pause dur="short"/> I keep all emotions inside he said I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what to do but then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me later in fairness he said <pause dur="short"/> we were expecting the call <pause dur="short"/> they already the knew the situation</u>
<u n="188" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0518">he said I didn't know what to do <pause dur="short"/> I just said <pause dur="short"/> that was uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know unfortunately grandad's <pause dur="short"/> passed away <pause dur="short"/> and he said they kinda looked at me for a reaction</u>
<u n="190" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah cos they don't know <pause dur="short"/> how to react so they're waiting</u>
<u n="191" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0517">and I suppose it is at the first <pause dur="short"/> family</u>
<u n="193" who="S0518">well nana died but they that was seven years ago so they were younger</u>
<u n="194" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so they were much younger <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0518">they were younger <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> they didn't go to the funeral for that <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <pause dur="short"/> he suddenly he sat down and just put the computer on his lap so in a way he <pause dur="short"/> shut shut them out</u>
<u n="196" who="S0517" trans="overlap">shut them out really and said</u>
<u n="197" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0518">whereas I just come in and just barge straight</u>
<u n="200" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0518">move the computer <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0517">group hug</u>
<u n="203" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="204" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="205" who="S0518">but erm <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="206" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so have they said much since the boys?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> well <pause dur="short"/> that night yeah so that night <pause dur="short"/> they went to bed I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are you alright? he said yeah I just said I just <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather just say my own prayer <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> I just <pause dur="short"/> just keep my emotions inside</u>
<u n="208" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0518">that's fine and we're all different and I said if you want to talk about anything or ask anything you can <pause dur="short"/> so I said okay <pause dur="short"/> and I could just and he was just subdued he was subdued</u>
<u n="210" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0518">and they were last Saturday subdued and on Sunday they kept saying when's dad coming home? when's dad coming home? will <trunc>w</trunc> will he be back soon is he coming soon? <pause dur="short"/> and when he got back they were all over him <pause dur="short"/> you know they'd just</u>
<u n="212" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0518">both of them wanted to just sit all over him really</u>
<u n="214" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0518">erm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0517">bit big for that</u>
<u n="217" who="S0518">well yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0518">but you know</u>
<u n="220" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like</u>
<u n="222" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's nice though</u>
<u n="223" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sort of give me a piggyback you know just rough and tumble and everything <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0518">so but they were subdued and then <pause dur="short"/> we were just sitting downstairs and we just had a glass of wine and we're just talking and I'm saying like how do you feel? and <pause dur="short"/> how was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and all of this <pause dur="short"/> and could hear <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming downstairs</u>
<u n="226" who="S0517"><vocal desc="sigh"/> oh no</u>
<u n="227" who="S0518">can't get to sleep <pause dur="short"/> so he sat so we all sat on the sofa till about one o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="228" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="229" who="S0518">and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was just asking lots of questions really <pause dur="short"/> and that's him <pause dur="short"/> talk talk it out</u>
<u n="230" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0518">wasn't wasn't crying or upset or scared or anything <pause dur="short"/> just wanted to know lots of things <pause dur="short"/> what was gonna happen to the house? what was gonna happen to the things in the house? and</u>
<u n="232" who="S0517">I mean that's the next big thing isn't it? that's a four-bedroom house in London they've got to sort out</u>
<u n="233" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I mean it's in London as well <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="234" who="S0517">that's gonna be horrendous</u>
<u n="235" who="S0518">and it's got a massive garden <pause dur="short"/> and er it's got like erm <pause dur="short"/> a huge greenhouse <pause dur="short"/> and a shared <pause dur="short"/> and it's got like erm <pause dur="short"/> out</u>
<u n="236" who="S0517" trans="overlap">are they are they all full all these things?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0518">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0517">gosh</u>
<u n="241" who="S0518">and there's things like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s made a list of <pause dur="short"/> all of the the different things that we need to contact there's over ninety and that's not including people these are</u>
<u n="242" who="S0517">utilities and</u>
<u n="243" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the Blind Society and you know? the people who put the handrails in and the mobility scooter people and the <pause dur="short"/> papers and the milk and the duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh and the <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> the deaf people and the people he sees for his eyes and the people he sees for his ears and the people he sees for his leg and the duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh <unclear>you know?</unclear></u>
<u n="244" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> so that's before friends?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0518">yeah but</u>
<u n="246" who="S0517" trans="overlap">have you got a list of his friends?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0518">yes but he hasn't got that many left <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <pause dur="short"/> he googled and found this this thing Tell Us Once <pause dur="short"/> and you can register somebody's bereavement somebody's death and then they will contact a lot of the you know? the gas electricity the</u>
<u n="248" who="S0517">oh <pause dur="short"/> how do they know who to contact though?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0518" trans="overlap">doctors <pause dur="short"/> think we need to supply I think we give them a <trunc>l</trunc> I think we give them the list and they do it</u>
<u n="250" who="S0517">right <pause dur="short"/> well that would be easier I remember when my dad died but it was a hassle for mum she kept having to provide the <pause dur="short"/> death certificate</u>
<u n="251" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="252" who="S0517">to a lot of places</u>
<u n="253" who="S0518">well <unclear><trunc>obvious</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="254" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mind you some of that was <pause dur="short"/> banking and they had joint accounts and things like that but I know <pause dur="short"/> stuff that was in his name <pause dur="short"/> that she just wanted to transfer to hers</u>
<u n="255" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="256" who="S0517">was in joint and she wanted to transfer to her name <pause dur="short"/> she had to provide death certificates all the time and</u>
<u n="257" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="258" who="S0517">sometimes they had to be originals <trunc>a</trunc> it was a it was a pain <pause dur="short"/> it was a pain</u>
<u n="259" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay well we'll see</u>
<u n="260" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0518">that's good good to know</u>
<u n="262" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but you've gotta empty all the house before you can even put it on the market</u>
<u n="263" who="S0518">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a brief chat and said <pause dur="short"/> you know should we <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>r</trunc>renovate it? should we put a new kitchen and bathroom in and stuff? my feeling is <pause dur="short"/> because it's it's dated you know? it's got like this avocado bathroom suite</u>
<u n="264" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0518">but erm <pause dur="short"/> my feeling is that erm we should just empty it <pause dur="short"/> clean it <pause dur="short"/> and then it's an empty shell for someone to come in and yes they won't like the pattern carpet <pause dur="short"/> oh no actually that's gone <pause dur="short"/> oh no it's plain in the hall stairs and landing it's still patterned in the lounge <pause dur="short"/> although they won't like the pattern carpet although they won't like the avocado bathroom suite <pause dur="short"/> they will come in and say</u>
<u n="266" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>wa</trunc> they'll want to do their own <trunc>thi</trunc> yes yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0518" trans="overlap">just gut it <pause dur="short"/> they will <pause dur="short"/> somebody's died <pause dur="short"/> it's a house with no chain or whatever you know up a chain <pause dur="short"/> and it's empty and if it's just empty and clean then people will see <pause dur="short"/> the potential in it</u>
<u n="268" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0518">and they will</u>
<u n="270" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they'll want to do what they want with it you know? if you chose a <trunc>bath</trunc> a new bathroom or kitchen suite</u>
<u n="271" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> they will</u>
<u n="272" who="S0517">it might end up getting ripped out again cos it's not the choice of the <pause dur="short"/> buyers</u>
<u n="273" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> that's what I think and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is saying no no but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said just put like a bland just plain white one in I said yes I know <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is then someone else else comes in and I said</u>
<u n="274" who="S0517">and wants a wood one</u>
<u n="275" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0518">or you know in the bathroom they <pause dur="short"/> don't like those tap fittings or they actually</u>
<u n="278" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0518">want to make it into a wet room or something you know?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0517">it might be worth getting the advice of the estate agent</u>
<u n="281" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said</u>
<u n="282" who="S0517" trans="overlap">because they <trunc>mu</trunc> they must <pause dur="short"/> they must come across us all the time and they must know whether</u>
<u n="283" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0517">whether the expense you'd go to</u>
<u n="285" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0517">would be worthwhile <pause dur="short"/> er but frankly you've got you've got to be there managing it</u>
<u n="287" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I don't think he will <pause dur="short"/> and I said who's gonna do that?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and you <trunc>n</trunc> you're not local</u>
<u n="289" who="S0518">no <pause dur="short"/> I said who's gonna do it? <pause dur="short"/> I said I'm worried about just clearing the place out let alone anything else</u>
<u n="290" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0518">and erm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0517">you've gotta be there for quotes and people coming round and the workmen being there</u>
<u n="293" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="294" who="S0517">it's just</u>
<u n="295" who="S0518">I know <pause dur="short"/> well just getting the hall stairs and landing is bad enough but</u>
<u n="296" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0518">you know? <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> I I my feeling is</u>
<u n="298" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0518">that yes you can do things to sell a house you can put in <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> neutral bathrooms and et cetera et cetera</u>
<u n="300" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0518">you can do that <pause dur="short"/> but when it's a property and somebody <pause dur="short"/> has died and this is it's got it it's a desirable property</u>
<u n="302" who="S0517">where is it?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0518">it's in erm <anon type="place"/> it's on the edge of <anon type="place"/> North London</u>
<u n="304" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="305" who="S0518">so it's all of the houses round there are are big <pause dur="short"/> they're very expensive <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> a lot of them have been modernised <pause dur="short"/> and the one opposite was modernised and it <pause dur="short"/> and it went up for sale and it sold for five hundred and something thousand pounds <pause dur="short"/> but I think it had five bedrooms <pause dur="short"/> and it had got a new bathroom and</u>
<u n="306" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0518" trans="overlap">et cetera <pause dur="short"/> and new double <trunc>glaz</trunc> I mean it's all double glazed it's for central heating and everything so it's not <pause dur="short"/> in bad repair <pause dur="short"/> but the decoration is old-fashioned</u>
<u n="308" who="S0517">you might they find though that by the time they've finished emptying it and going through it all they just want rid</u>
<u n="309" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="310" who="S0517">but that that in itself is gonna be so time-consuming</u>
<u n="311" who="S0518">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="312" who="S0517">that by the time they a four-bedroomed house with a garage and an attic and a <pause dur="short"/> shed oh</u>
<u n="313" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0517">that's not even your stuff</u>
<u n="315" who="S0518">I know</u>
<u n="316" who="S0517">you <trunc>do</trunc> oh no that's gonna be so time-consuming for them</u>
<u n="317" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0517">they might just want rid by then so I shouldn't even worry about it until they've done that <pause dur="short"/> first step</u>
<u n="319" who="S0518">on</u>
<u n="320" who="S0517">cos that could take</u>
<u n="321" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="322" who="S0517">weeks</u>
<u n="323" who="S0518">I think it was just them in their talking you know like</u>
<u n="324" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0518">you talk about stuff don't you? and they were just</u>
<u n="326" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0518">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh you know do you think we need to? <pause dur="short"/> god we're gonna have to sell the house do you think we need to</u>
<u n="328" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0518">decorate it? do you think we need to <trunc>r</trunc>refurbish it? <pause dur="short"/> I my feeling is just no</u>
<u n="330" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> do your <trunc>s</trunc> do your own <trunc>fi</trunc> <unclear>you know</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as <pause dur="short"/> as <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc>sell it site as seen <pause dur="short"/> people buying it will know</u>
<u n="332" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0518">there is no upward chain the person that lived here has died it was an elderly gentleman <pause dur="short"/> it is in good repair the kitchen's only a few years old and that is just a very <pause dur="short"/> neutral cream kitchen</u>
<u n="334" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's all it's all <pause dur="short"/> it'll be all cosmetic anyway the you know the <pause dur="short"/> refurb won't it so?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well it will and I just think because it is in a desirable area and it is a desirable property potentially anybody buying it <pause dur="short"/> probably want to totally modernise it <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they'll want to just <pause dur="short"/> put a new kitchen and bathroom in</u>
<u n="336" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="337" who="S0518">I think they will want to <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="339" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just</u>
<u n="340" who="S0517" trans="overlap">make it their own yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0518"><unclear>really</unclear> do everything <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0517">oh gosh <pause dur="short"/> so where how long is he going down for now? do you is it <trunc>w</trunc>were his were his dad's affairs in order? will that be straightforward at least?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0518" trans="overlap">the same <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah so that's brilliant absolute blessing to us all</u>
<u n="344" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh that's good</u>
<u n="345" who="S0518">because erm <pause dur="short"/> so then he came back last Sunday and then obviously this week we've just been waiting every time the phone goes every time his phone rings at work and all of this <pause dur="short"/> but then Thursday that happened Thursday night <pause dur="short"/> he didn't go to work on Friday <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> but we got tickets for the theatre Friday night which we did go to <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I said I'd asked the box office <pause dur="short"/> could I just? <pause dur="short"/> you know not have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as if it came to it but he said he would go <pause dur="short"/> because he said I will just sit there it's not like chatting to people</u>
<u n="346" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0518">my sister had got a Halloween party on <pause dur="short"/> the Saturday night <pause dur="short"/> which he didn't go to</u>
<u n="348" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="349" who="S0518">but I took the children <pause dur="short"/> just because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was looking forward to it and</u>
<u n="350" who="S0517">yeah cos she's still young isn't she? and she wanted the boys yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I wanted the boys just to be kind of normal I didn't want to sit round go oh</u>
<u n="352" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0518">because we had a chap ninety-three years <pause dur="short"/> you know? fifty-odd years of happy marriage</u>
<u n="354" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0518">lovely career</u>
<u n="356" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0518">family home great children grandchildren</u>
<u n="358" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0518">nothing really to be sad about</u>
<u n="360" who="S0517">no nothing no no</u>
<u n="361" who="S0518" trans="overlap">at all nothing to be sad</u>
<u n="362" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="363" who="S0518">lived completely independently till the end</u>
<u n="364" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0518">you know so <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="366" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0518">everything to celebrate <pause dur="short"/> so we've had that chat so we <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stayed at home because he was concerned he had not <pause dur="short"/> properly cried at all his eyes had filled up a bit but he hadn't had a good cry and it's because he hadn't had any space around him</u>
<u n="368" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="369" who="S0518">because <pause dur="short"/> been at work then come home then obviously he'd had Friday off we'd all been there cos it was half-term and I was off work</u>
<u n="370" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0518">and then we were all there on Saturday and so he just wanted a few hours on his own <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> he wanted to get ahead with all his TMA marking because <pause dur="short"/> his first lot of assignments are coming in</u>
<u n="372" who="S0517">oh so he's got all that new work to do</u>
<u n="373" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so he's got all of that marking to do</u>
<u n="374" who="S0517">and that's all new to him isn't it?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so he wanted just time to do that <pause dur="short"/> so he did he did that spent a few hours doing that <pause dur="short"/> we went out at six <pause dur="short"/> thought we back about nine didn't get back till eleven so that was quite good it gave him all that time</u>
<u n="376" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0518">and then <pause dur="short"/> nothing could be done over the weekend so <pause dur="short"/> they've gone down today to London <pause dur="short"/> for</u>
<u n="378" who="S0517">he and his brother?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0518">he he's gone down <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone down</u>
<u n="380" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0518">they're meeting at the house <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got the death certificate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went into hospital <pause dur="short"/> they took the body to the mortuary at midnight on Thursday night <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went Friday morning they gave him personal belongings and the death certificate and a whole load of paperwork of stuff that you need to do <pause dur="short"/> couldn't register the death until <pause dur="short"/> today I think <pause dur="short"/> so you have to ring up and make an appointment</u>
<u n="382" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> yes yeah we yes</u>
<u n="383" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0517">I remember we had to go in <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0517">we <trunc>w</trunc>when dad died we had to go into the <pause dur="short"/> what's it called? the registrar to yeah in in in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0518" trans="overlap">registrar of births marriages yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0518">so they've got an appointment to do that today and then he said are his affairs in order? he in his office he'd got all of his files <pause dur="short"/> and one said will one said funeral plan <pause dur="short"/> and he</u>
<u n="390" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh so he's</u>
<u n="391" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0517">got his funeral plan?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0518">yeah it's all done it's all paid for they've got an appointment at the funeral director tomorrow</u>
<u n="394" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="395" who="S0518">and it says erm I wish to be cremated <pause dur="short"/> erm this is the name of the <pause dur="short"/> funeral director <pause dur="short"/> erm and he's basically paid for the crematorium the <unclear>whole thing</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> cars</u>
<u n="396" who="S0517" trans="overlap">god when did he do all that? <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="397" who="S0518">erm <pause dur="short"/> years years ago I think</u>
<u n="398" who="S0517">gosh</u>
<u n="399" who="S0518">I don't know it's all it's all in order <pause dur="short"/> so in the will folder it says <pause dur="short"/> this is the last will and testament these are the executors this is a solicitor it's very simple it's all laid out <pause dur="short"/> erm and then the funeral plans</u>
<u n="400" who="S0517" trans="overlap">gosh</u>
<u n="401" who="S0518">so so we're really lucky</u>
<u n="402" who="S0517">yeah that that is that's</u>
<u n="403" who="S0518" trans="overlap">really lucky</u>
<u n="404" who="S0517">that's a massive weight off everybody's mind that that's all done</u>
<u n="405" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> rang the funeral director he</u>
<u n="406" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0518">said yeah come in half past ten tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> and he said I'll go through the plan I'll tell you exactly what your dad's erm put in place what he's been <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>pay</trunc> I don't know if he paid in one lump or if he's been paying by direct debit or quite whatever happens I don't know <pause dur="short"/> and I know the cost of things go <pause dur="short"/> up <pause dur="short"/> so maybe</u>
<u n="408" who="S0517">maybe there'll be a bit to pay or something</u>
<u n="409" who="S0518" trans="overlap">maybe <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="410" who="S0517">so have you got a date? <pause dur="short"/> for the funeral?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="412" who="S0517">no?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0518">because that's what they'll do tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> they'll go and</u>
<u n="414" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0518">so they'll register the death and they'll go and see the funeral director <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc> and then obviously he'll say when he can <pause dur="short"/> do it to fit in with the crematorium so</u>
<u n="416" who="S0517">that's what I've heard crematoriums seem to have a backlog at the moment</u>
<u n="417" who="S0518">ah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I heard somebody I <trunc>d</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> forget who it was now and they were having to wait three weeks for the funeral because of the crematorium being busy</u>
<u n="419" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> his mum you see she was religious so we had a church service for her <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't want that <pause dur="short"/> and then went to a crematorium but <pause dur="short"/> they picked this crematorium miles away <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> erm called <anon type="place"/> and one <trunc>o</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would say why why? <pause dur="short"/> it's very pretty</u>
<u n="420" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="421" who="S0518">and it's more out in the country so we don't know if that's why but he said <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0517">how how many people do you think <pause dur="short"/> will be there? will it mostly be family?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0518">yeah because they'll</u>
<u n="424" who="S0517">all of his friends have <pause dur="short"/> already gone have they I suppose <trunc>we</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> ninety-three</u>
<u n="425" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean there's some neighbours</u>
<u n="426" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0518">that</u>
<u n="428" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0518">will come <pause dur="short"/> and there are maybe some friends of <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that will come <pause dur="short"/> like the girls they used to play with at the bottom of the garden who are all grown up who are in touch now <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s best friends erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> they've got erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who <pause dur="short"/> we're in touch with and so like every <pause dur="short"/> year or something we'll say we'll have a day out to London we'll meet you at the Science Museum or something</u>
<u n="430" who="S0517" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> oh so there are</u>
<u n="431" who="S0518">so</u>
<u n="432" who="S0517">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he they will <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> are <trunc>d</trunc> are dead but the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s counterparts</u>
<u n="434" who="S0517">right yes yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0518" trans="overlap">are still alive so I think they will probably come <pause dur="short"/> and but</u>
<u n="436" who="S0517">will you take the boys down?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0518">yes</u>
<u n="438" who="S0517">so that'll be</u>
<u n="439" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0517">well it'll be a weekday won't it?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0518">I think they do</u>
<u n="442" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I don't think they do them all weekends</u>
<u n="444" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't think they do no no</u>
<u n="445" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> so they might have to have time off school <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0518">oh what was I gonna say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether to have the <trunc>crema</trunc> the cremation at the same place as mum's <pause dur="short"/> but when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was cremated <pause dur="short"/> we didn't even go back for a sprinkling of the ashes <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is very <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> she's gone you know I she's here in my heart now and <pause dur="short"/> they can just put the ashes where they want</u>
<u n="448" who="S0517">oh he didn't even pick them up?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="450" who="S0517">gosh</u>
<u n="451" who="S0518">so he just gave he just said to them <pause dur="short"/> when they're done you just sprinkle them in the gardens of remembrance or whatever <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>they said</unclear> do you want an inscription in the book? would you like a plaque? would you like they've got like a stained glass window thing?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0518">would you like erm <pause dur="short"/> bit of a window? <trunc>n</trunc>no nothing <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't really happy about that</u>
<u n="454" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0518">and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know what do you think? and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> we won't ever go back and visit there <pause dur="short"/> so he said I'm a bit like dad he said to me my memory of my mum is with me</u>
<u n="456" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and he said and in photographs and memories and stories and things he said I'm not gonna drive out to some remote crematorium <pause dur="short"/> to</u>
<u n="458" who="S0517" trans="overlap">just to look at a a stained glass window or?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0518" trans="overlap">look at yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0517">yeah well and he's got a very good point I suppose hasn't he?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="462" who="S0517">but everybody's different with how they want to <pause dur="short"/> remember it aren't they?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0518"><trunc>a</trunc> er <pause dur="short"/> anyway but there we go so that's that</u>
<u n="466" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right well at least he's got a plan of what he wants and that makes it easier for you</u>
<u n="467" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0517">so you've just gotta wait for the date now <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="469" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> yeah and and you know if it is at that crematorium <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> when can they fit us in and everything?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0518">stuff and I don't know what to do about going back to work cos</u>
<u n="472" who="S0517">well yes</u>
<u n="473" who="S0518">I don't want to go back in the middle of a bereavement</u>
<u n="474" who="S0517">what <vocal desc="sigh"/> so you're supposed to go back next</u>
<u n="475" who="S0518">Tuesday</u>
<u n="476" who="S0517">oh Tuesday? okay</u>
<u n="477" who="S0518">got a meeting tomorrow with my manager</u>
<u n="478" who="S0517">mm?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0518">and she knows what's happened</u>
<u n="480" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="481" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because I was late sending off my final sick note because I obviously I I got my final sick note <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> or the the latest sick note <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> we got all of this news about <pause dur="short"/> well I and then I went down to <anon type="place"/> and <pause dur="short"/> saw how poorly he was and that was the week when everything went up and down <unclear>here and I</unclear> completely forgot to send it off <pause dur="short"/> on the day that I got it <pause dur="short"/> so I sent it a few days later</u>
<u n="482" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0518">and I just wrote a letter and said I'm <pause dur="short"/> really sorry <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>f</trunc> we've had erm <pause dur="short"/> you know a bad week with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad and it's sort of been a bit touch and go <pause dur="short"/> and erm it just went out of my head <pause dur="short"/> she texted me and said I've got your sick note I'm really sorry to hear about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad <pause dur="short"/> and just er keep me updated and if Tuesday's meeting is just too much for you we'll rearrange there's there's absolutely no urgency</u>
<u n="484" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="485" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and I thought</u>
<u n="486" who="S0517">who had er who had instigated the meeting? they had?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0518">no I did</u>
<u n="488" who="S0517">you had? oh okay</u>
<u n="489" who="S0518">because last time I went back to the doctor I said <pause dur="short"/> I I I don't want to go back to work in half-term because my manager's off and the other team leaders are off I'll be going back into <pause dur="short"/> a war zone I haven't been there for how <trunc>man</trunc>many weeks I <trunc>d</trunc>I don't even know what my job role is and I don't know where my desk is or anything I I just don't feel that's the right time to go back</u>
<u n="490" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0518">so he said I absolutely agree <pause dur="short"/> I'll sign you off for half-term <pause dur="short"/> and the week after <pause dur="short"/> and erm <vocal desc="misc"/> and I said in that week I'd like to arrange a meeting with my manager to talk about coming back to work how I come back to work exactly what's expected of me where I'm gonna be sitting <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc>what's been told to the team <pause dur="short"/> you know all of this sort of thing</u>
<u n="492" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0518">because I've got <pause dur="short"/> I know I've been a bit off the rails but I have got erm <pause dur="short"/> you know I have got a sensible attitude and I've got quite a proactive <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> mindset towards it</u>
<u n="494" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0518">and er the whole being off <trunc>s</trunc>sick bit <pause dur="short"/> so I contacted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and just said you know I've been signed off until da-da-da however <pause dur="short"/> in that week I want to make an arrangement</u>
<u n="496" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="497" who="S0518">to come and see you <pause dur="short"/> she said that's great that's really good <pause dur="short"/> and I'll get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's my HR partner to be there <pause dur="short"/> and because we can talk about a <trunc>ph</trunc>a phased return or fewer hours or fewer days</u>
<u n="498" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0518">if you want <pause dur="short"/> I was like <pause dur="short"/> to myself oh no if I'm going back I'm going back</u>
<u n="500" who="S0517" trans="overlap">going <trunc>b</trunc> well <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>you know</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I'm better <pause dur="short"/> I'm going back</u>
<u n="502" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you're better yes yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0518">but er <unclear/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0517" trans="overlap">have they have they you know when they when you went to the consultant last time they he changed the <trunc>prescr</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> the drugs has that made a difference? has that helped?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes definitely</u>
<u n="506" who="S0517">oh good</u>
<u n="507" who="S0518" trans="overlap">definitely <pause dur="short"/> erm I've been running with not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I've been running with stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> twice a week</u>
<u n="508" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0518">that's another story <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> he said to me <pause dur="short"/> er he said I can't tell you how overjoyed I am he said to see such he said you're like a different person <pause dur="short"/> and I am I feel</u>
<u n="510" who="S0517">feel better</u>
<u n="511" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0517">good <pause dur="short"/> so are they? <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <trunc>w</trunc> are all the side effects still there as bad as they were? or has that has it got better?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no that's why that's why I feel better <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0517">oh that's good</u>
<u n="515" who="S0518">because <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> having said that <pause dur="short"/> last night I <trunc>c</trunc> was struggling to get to sleep cos I felt <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> like I couldn't breathe properly and er today I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I feel really <trunc>o</trunc>on edge really apprehensive really panicky but I think that was because <pause dur="short"/> of the situation and because he's going to <anon type="place"/> for three days and I know why he's going and</u>
<u n="516" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0518">I don't know I know you're used to being without <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I I'm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0517">er well it's <trunc>ta</trunc> took a little <pause dur="short"/> while to adjust to it when he first started working away <pause dur="short"/> it did so I can understand that</u>
<u n="519" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you feel like the weight's on your shoulders don't you?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah you've gotta keep everything</u>
<u n="521" who="S0518"><trunc>t</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0517">everybody in the right place at the right time and they yeah yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the children seem okay but what if they're not? and</u>
<u n="524" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="525" who="S0518">you know what</u>
<u n="526" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0518">anyway but that's er I wasn't actually thinking about that but I wondered <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc>was that part yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0517" trans="overlap">subconsciously was that yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0517">bothering you</u>
<u n="531" who="S0518">but the panic attacks the palpitations <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> the nausea <pause dur="short"/> all of that is greatly reduced</u>
<u n="532" who="S0517">and do you think that's just cos he changed the dose?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he didn't change the tablet did he?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0518">no but he's changed it</u>
<u n="536" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh well that's good news though</u>
<u n="537" who="S0518">it was the strongest amount and he's halved the strength <pause dur="short"/> and it was every day <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="538" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0518">he's put it every other day so it's effectively he's quartered the amount</u>
<u n="540" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="541" who="S0518">the the downside is that most well quite a lot of nights I have woken up in really bad pain <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> that's come come back <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and for the first week when I was on the reduced dose had absolutely <pause dur="short"/> massive swollen up eyes like really</u>
<u n="542" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0517">did he say that might happen?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0518">no but erm <pause dur="short"/> they've gone down <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> the tummy aches have become less so <pause dur="short"/> every night he was waking up <pause dur="short"/> at the same time between four or five o'clock <pause dur="short"/> really really bad pain like he was in labour that sort of <pause dur="short"/> strength of pain</u>
<u n="546" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="547" who="S0518">not being able to get comfortable just having to take painkillers lying up the stairs lying on the <trunc>flo</trunc> you know that just for a <trunc>f</trunc> couple of hours or whatever till morning really <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> and that was because <pause dur="short"/> where the where it was on the strong dosages of drugs it was helping that but even the other things so reducing it that came back</u>
<u n="548" who="S0517">that came back but the side effects went</u>
<u n="549" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>mental</trunc>ly I was so much better <pause dur="short"/> wasn't crying all the time you know?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad has died I've cried about that but it's being appropriately upset where I was just crying about everything</u>
<u n="552" who="S0517" trans="overlap">before yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0518">you know? <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't stand anybody hugging me or touching me could I? and erm <pause dur="short"/> I had to just go <pause dur="short"/> take a deep breath when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to hug me like this is my child it's okay but</u>
<u n="554" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0518">when it was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> coming near me I was oh keep away keep away keep away you know and all of that <pause dur="short"/> couldn't stand it but erm <pause dur="short"/> so that's all</u>
<u n="556" who="S0517">so that's</u>
<u n="557" who="S0518">normal yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>u</trunc> I <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know you might not want to know the details of this</u>
<u n="558" who="S0517" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0518">er <trunc>con</trunc> er basically I had a constant period <pause dur="short"/> for the whole of the time</u>
<u n="560" who="S0517">how many weeks is that <unclear/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear/> weeks and <trunc>may</trunc> I've had like a few</u>
<u n="562" who="S0517">since since you had the <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>opera</trunc> the <trunc>l</trunc> the operation or since the since the drugs?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no no since I've been on the well yeah no I didn't put two and two together <pause dur="short"/> cos I just thought</u>
<u n="564" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay okay</u>
<u n="565" who="S0518">oh bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> on top of everything else <pause dur="short"/> like this oh must be my age</u>
<u n="566" who="S0517">right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="567" who="S0518">and I know I joked to you and said I've put on loads of weight when I've been off and you said no you haven't you've been eating lots of lunches or whatever it is</u>
<u n="568" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0518">and these tablets have put on weight but my tummy has been really <trunc>ha</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> really has been bloated <pause dur="short"/> and then obviously this <pause dur="short"/> and it hasn't caused me any distress other than oh for goodness sake</u>
<u n="570" who="S0517">yeah for weeks and weeks you don't need that and have they said that's another side effect of the drug or they don't know cos they're new?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0518" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> I yeah I hadn't thought about it <pause dur="short"/> but then I went for this smear test and it was like well when do I book it in</u>
<u n="572" who="S0518" whoConfidence="low">don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0518">you know?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0517">oh yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and it <pause dur="short"/> so the nurse said well we'll just have to go <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0517" trans="overlap">just do it <unclear>or</unclear></u>
<u n="577" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and to see what happens so <pause dur="short"/> then she said to me I'm not really happy about this because she said I don't think it is your age she said I think it's erm <pause dur="short"/> she said did you say when you saw the consultant and you told him about all the other side effects did you mention this? I said <pause dur="short"/> no cos I thought this was my age <pause dur="short"/> she said <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it is she said I think it it might be because of these drugs and she said erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm <pause dur="short"/> if you'd've said it <trunc>sh</trunc> cos it's a new drug she said if you'd've said and it would've been noted down and then someone else had said it and someone else <pause dur="short"/> that's how you build up what the side effects are</u>
<u n="578" who="S0517">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0518">so she said I want you to do <trunc>s</trunc> I want to have some blood tests and discuss it with the doctor <pause dur="short"/> she <trunc>s</trunc> oh poor you this is awful I said well it isn't actually to be honest it isn't <pause dur="short"/> awful it isn't that awful</u>
<u n="580" who="S0517">well you're used to it but <trunc>y</trunc> I mean you know you're used to getting a bit of a break aren't you? like weeks and weeks of it's a pain</u>
<u n="581" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and I don't have any problems and I don't stop running and I don't stop swimming</u>
<u n="582" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="583" who="S0518">and just carry on</u>
<u n="584" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0518">and I don't have mood swings and anything like that</u>
<u n="586" who="S0517">so</u>
<u n="587" who="S0518">but obviously my <pause dur="short"/> I just feel like my tummy's constantly really sticking out and <pause dur="short"/> and and that's just keeps happening so <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="588" who="S0517">so has she sent the <trunc>b</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> has she taken the blood?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0518">no so she</u>
<u n="590" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="591" who="S0518">said book in <pause dur="short"/> so then she did the smear test <pause dur="short"/> that I had a letter back saying that was normal <pause dur="short"/> and no untoward cells or anything so thanks very much come back in three years' <pause dur="short"/> time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> then <pause dur="short"/> the very day I got the letter <pause dur="short"/> the surgery rang me and said oh Mrs <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> have you erm had your letter back regarding the smear test results? I said yes <pause dur="short"/> and they <trunc>s</trunc> I said said it was normal and they said well <pause dur="short"/> yes the cells are the normal but we have found <vocal desc="laugh"/> a few other things I was like <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="592" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="593" who="S0518">so the doctor wants to see you <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh god so she said <pause dur="short"/> shows that you've got thrush <pause dur="short"/> I said <pause dur="short"/> I've never had thrush before in my life <pause dur="short"/> I said <pause dur="short"/> what will the symptoms be because I have no symptoms? <pause dur="short"/> so she told me what they'd be and I said oh I <trunc>m</trunc> definitely haven't got those symptoms so she said well it it's showing up and the doctor does want to treat it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="594" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so is that another possible side effect of the drugs? oh my goodness</u>
<u n="595" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> because I went to the dentist on Thursday and they said <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> your gums are bleeding <pause dur="short"/> and normally I have like really good teeth and gums <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> you're not taking any medication <pause dur="short"/> are you at the moment? I said well I am actually <pause dur="short"/> and then of course that <pause dur="short"/> has maybe caused thrush and then</u>
<u n="596" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="597" who="S0518">he said what is the medication? <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>sai</trunc> told him and he said it's a nerve stimulant <pause dur="short"/> and it's for your gut and he said anything to do with the gut relates to the mouth</u>
<u n="598" who="S0517">does it? <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="599" who="S0518">apparently so <pause dur="short"/> he said mouth and gut are related so he said I wouldn't be surprised if <pause dur="short"/> this is all <pause dur="short"/> related <pause dur="short"/> so now having blood tests on Wednesday and then I've got an appointment to talk through the doctor with the doctor because they've <pause dur="short"/> said <pause dur="short"/> we don't know whether it's affected your thyroid <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> these drugs whatever they are</u>
<u n="600" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="601" who="S0518">are horrible <pause dur="short"/> they're horrible</u>
<u n="602" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it does <trunc>sou</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> how many people are on these drugs?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I <unclear>I'm not</unclear></u>
<u n="604" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I mean I know you said they were new how many people have they told you any of that?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="606" who="S0517">cos that does sound</u>
<u n="607" who="S0518">but</u>
<u n="608" who="S0517">that's a lot of <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> that's a lot of side effects</u>
<u n="609" who="S0518">you know if you go to the doctor and you say oh I'm taking <pause dur="short"/> penicillin or <vocal desc="laugh"/> antibiotic? <pause dur="short"/> or I'm taking</u>
<u n="610" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you say you're taking this and they've not heard of it?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0518">they go oh</u>
<u n="612" who="S0517">and they get their book out</u>
<u n="613" who="S0518">they get the book out and look all through <pause dur="short"/> and then they'll <trunc>s</trunc>so they they don't really know what it is and then they find it <pause dur="short"/> now it's listed in the two thousand and fifteen book <pause dur="short"/> so it's listed <pause dur="short"/> and this book comes out every six months <pause dur="short"/> but then there's a great big erm <pause dur="short"/> sheet of paper paper that you can print off and erm they print off the computer and it's also inside my drugs <pause dur="short"/> and basically when I went back to Dr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he prescribed it he said <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna have to check on these on this drug he said cos I know it's got a side effect but I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> what we know of it so far <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> one in ten people which is quite high<pause dur="short"/> one in ten people experience these commonly <pause dur="short"/> palpitations nausea <pause dur="short"/> panic attacks <pause dur="short"/> erm headaches</u>
<u n="614" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="615" who="S0518">vomiting</u>
<u n="616" who="S0517">god</u>
<u n="617" who="S0518">haven't had vomiting luckily <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so one in ten is quite high</u>
<u n="618" who="S0517">I think that's high</u>
<u n="619" who="S0518">and it</u>
<u n="620" who="S0517">ten percent</u>
<u n="621" who="S0518">and it's <pause dur="short"/> because normally <pause dur="short"/> it's erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> if you look at normal <pause dur="short"/> they list all the side effects but it's like <pause dur="short"/> one in ten experience heart attacks due to this <pause dur="short"/> or one in a hundred experience this or</u>
<u n="622" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="623" who="S0518">one in <pause dur="short"/> ten thousand experience this</u>
<u n="624" who="S0517" trans="overlap">experience this</u>
<u n="625" who="S0518">but on this it's one in ten experience</u>
<u n="626" who="S0517" trans="overlap">ten experience</u>
<u n="627" who="S0518">quite serious side effects</u>
<u n="628" who="S0517" trans="overlap">a lot</u>
<u n="629" who="S0518">a lot of side effects</u>
<u n="630" who="S0517">so how <trunc>l</trunc> how long do they I don't suppose we know do we? how long do they test it for before they say?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I think it's tested <pause dur="short"/> it's tested <pause dur="short"/> on erm <pause dur="short"/> but it says this has only been tested <pause dur="short"/> and is only available for use for <pause dur="short"/> erm women of a certain age group which is my age group <pause dur="short"/> it cannot be used on young young people <pause dur="short"/> or younger women as it's not been tested on them yet <pause dur="short"/> and it can't be used on men</u>
<u n="632" who="S0517">well I wonder if that's because it would affect their fertility I mean if you've</u>
<u n="633" who="S0518">don't know</u>
<u n="634" who="S0517">yeah if it's obviously <trunc>u</trunc>upsetting your cycle isn't it?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="636" who="S0517">er it might affect their fertility if it was younger women perhaps I don't know</u>
<u n="637" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it might do it might do <pause dur="short"/> I mean it does it does say <pause dur="short"/> don't take if you're pregnant or breastfeeding <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="638" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos you wouldn't you wouldn't entertain the idea though would you if you were pregnant or breastfeeding but erm?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no but and also would you be in my I don't know when it says my age group I don't know what the age group the age group might range from <pause dur="short"/> thirty-five to fifty-five so you might be coming to breastfeeding at thirty-five I don't know</u>
<u n="640" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0518">but erm <pause dur="short"/> so it's very <pause dur="short"/> good because normally when when nerves are dead they're dead <pause dur="short"/> and this drug obviously has been proven to be able to help <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="642" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to stimulate?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0518">which it is</u>
<u n="644" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0518">but <pause dur="short"/> alongside of that</u>
<u n="646" who="S0517">you've got all this</u>
<u n="647" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0517">so <pause dur="short"/> so the <pause dur="short"/> the blood tests you'll discuss with the doctor but what about the consultant that's prescribing them?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0518">okay</u>
<u n="650" who="S0517">don't you need to go and <pause dur="short"/> back and see him?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh er <pause dur="short"/> january I've got an appointment with him but I've <pause dur="short"/> he's written a letter <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> after our two hour <pause dur="short"/> I told you all about that <unclear>haven't I?</unclear></u>
<u n="652" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yes you did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and <trunc>we</trunc> he's written a letter which he's sent me a copy of which is a very nice letter and it says in it you know? <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has experienced really bad side effects <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> what I've done is and he's explained <pause dur="short"/> and he said I wanted to persevere on these drugs because there is some evidence that they are helping however <pause dur="short"/> erm he said <pause dur="short"/> I don't want her to continue if the side effects continue to this degree and and <pause dur="short"/> we may just have to go back to square one <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> in the background though there are a lot of other things <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know whether this is also <pause dur="short"/> adding to it</u>
<u n="654" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0518">erm so he's listed and he says to the GP which you may or may not be aware of <pause dur="short"/> and he lists all these various other things <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know stress-<trunc>r</trunc>related things such as <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> she has elderly parents who <pause dur="short"/> are not well who are reliant on her they can't <pause dur="short"/> spread the burden with her sister cos her sister's <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> a blind diabetic</u>
<u n="656" who="S0517" trans="overlap">also? <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0518" trans="overlap">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> effectively <pause dur="short"/> erm her father-in-law's recently been taken seriously ill <pause dur="short"/> he lives a distance away and erm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0518">she's not very settled at home at the moment <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> there's also</u>
<u n="660" who="S0517" trans="overlap">there's a whole load you can't just take it on its own can you? and say</u>
<u n="661" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0517">like the drugs are doing this and this because there's so much else</u>
<u n="663" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0517">going on</u>
<u n="665" who="S0518">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="666" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0518">you know I want to persevere on the drugs because there is some improvement <pause dur="short"/> now he's changed the dose <pause dur="short"/> I obviously feel mentally a lot better <pause dur="short"/> there are obviously some other stuff going on <pause dur="short"/> but the blood tests that they're doing <pause dur="short"/> are very specific which will say <pause dur="short"/> is it <pause dur="short"/> the early onset of menopause <pause dur="short"/> or <pause dur="short"/> it <pause dur="short"/> it it it these tests will tell you whether it is or isn't</u>
<u n="668" who="S0517">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="669" who="S0518" trans="overlap">erm apparently and also they're doing anaemia because <pause dur="short"/> of just <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0517" trans="overlap">constant blood loss I assume</u>
<u n="671" who="S0518">and erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>of</trunc> some very specific thyroid ones because she said I'm not sure whether <pause dur="short"/> it's actually affected your thyroid <pause dur="short"/> just because</u>
<u n="672" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I'm never really sure what your thyroid is <pause dur="short"/> does</u>
<u n="673" who="S0518">well <pause dur="short"/> on Jeremy Vine <pause dur="short"/> I was listening</u>
<u n="674" who="S0517">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0518" trans="overlap">they were talking about anaphylactic shock <pause dur="short"/> and things that cause people to have anaphylactic shock to things <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> they were explaining that the whole body goes into overdrive</u>
<u n="676" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="677" who="S0518">not just like if you have an insect bite I'm allergic to it <pause dur="short"/> and then your adrenaline rushes to that spot and creates a reaction and that's why I get that massive <pause dur="short"/> huge blister <pause dur="short"/> and that's erm <pause dur="short"/> what is it? antihistamine isn't it? your natural antihistamine reaction</u>
<u n="678" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0518">well in anaphylactic shock your whole body reacts <pause dur="short"/> and then they were saying <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>l</trunc> it's like an exaggerated version of somebody that's got either <pause dur="short"/> an overactive or an inactive thyroid <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> so with somebody that's got a problem with their thyroid it's like <pause dur="short"/> their body attacks themself <pause dur="short"/> and I was like <pause dur="short"/> oh?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0517"><unclear>erm</unclear></u>
<u n="681" who="S0518">really? <pause dur="short"/> okay well I hadn't really realised that but</u>
<u n="682" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="683" who="S0518">that's what they were saying it's just like er</u>
<u n="684" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="685" who="S0518">your own body reacts to <pause dur="short"/> against your own self</u>
<u n="686" who="S0517" trans="overlap">against it?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0517">well you don't want that do you?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0518">no so</u>
<u n="690" who="S0517">gosh there's a whole list of what a</u>
<u n="691" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I have to say <pause dur="short"/> I wish I hadn't bothered <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I wish I'd just stayed as I was <pause dur="short"/> for</u>
<u n="692" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0517">do you though?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="697" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I couldn't because if you remember</u>
<u n="698" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no you couldn't you were in a lot of pain</u>
<u n="699" who="S0518">well and the thing that started it off was that day at work</u>
<u n="700" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="701" who="S0518">when I was put with and you I told you and said <pause dur="short"/> you need to go to</u>
<u n="702" who="S0517">er yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0518">because imagine if that had been something <pause dur="short"/> far more serious</u>
<u n="704" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh absolutely you did need to go to the doctor and at least</u>
<u n="705" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0517">well <pause dur="short"/> when was that though? how long have we how long have we <trunc>be</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/>? <pause dur="short"/> how long have we been going through this process now?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0518"><vocal desc="misc"/> since er January I would say</u>
<u n="708" who="S0517">oh right so the best part of a year</u>
<u n="709" who="S0518">because I remember</u>
<u n="710" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="711" who="S0518">going to see Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> for the first time in February <pause dur="short"/> so I had to see the consultant <pause dur="short"/> then obviously had to get er</u>
<u n="712" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0518">an appointment</u>
<u n="714" who="S0517">see it's a long I mean it is a long <pause dur="short"/> long time <pause dur="short"/> I suppose once they've <pause dur="short"/> and and that and I think that's probably why they won't send you back to work yet because they're <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> they're still doing all these tests <pause dur="short"/> I mean and also they've you don't wanna go back to work <pause dur="short"/> and then be off <pause dur="short"/> off for a funeral off for blood tests</u>
<u n="715" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no for I know</u>
<u n="716" who="S0517">off for appointments with the consultant off for this off for that because <pause dur="short"/> mentally you won't be back at work yet will you? you're</u>
<u n="717" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="718" who="S0517">still dealing with everything going on I</u>
<u n="719" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="720" who="S0517">I think they'll</u>
<u n="721" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I feel much now I feel well enough to go back to work I do feel well enough to go back to work <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know what whether I will when I'm back at work</u>
<u n="722" who="S0517" trans="overlap">thing is though when you're at work <pause dur="short"/> especially with you cos you're very conscientious <pause dur="short"/> and up until this point where you hadn't had any time off sick <pause dur="short"/> you didn't like to take time off</u>
<u n="723" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="724" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> it would bother you <pause dur="short"/> if you were off work so if you suddenly <pause dur="short"/> go back to work firstly you've got that readjustment cos you've been off for weeks</u>
<u n="725" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="726" who="S0517">but then <pause dur="short"/> mentally it might <trunc>n</trunc> it might knock you back cos you you're not used to taking time off and you'd be taking time off</u>
<u n="727" who="S0518">well</u>
<u n="728" who="S0517">all the time and then you'd be saying oh what must they think? you know I've just come back after six weeks off</u>
<u n="729" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="730" who="S0517">and now I'm off again for you know this appointment and that appointment and</u>
<u n="731" who="S0518">I mean I've got I'm gonna write the appointments down and when I see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on Tuesday I'm gonna say to her and also I will know when the funeral is by the time I see her <pause dur="short"/> so I want to say to her you know and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be there <pause dur="short"/> obviously we're in the oh and she texts me when I I <pause dur="short"/> she said you know I'm thinking of you and if the tutor meeting's too much let me know and I text her back and said <pause dur="short"/> erm no I'm planning to come to it because whatever happens <pause dur="short"/> I will need to be here for the boys anyway and they'll be at school so it will be fine</u>
<u n="732" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0518">and then obviously she text me on <pause dur="short"/> can't remember what day it was and just said hope the weekend goes okay cos I told her we were going to go down and visit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad <pause dur="short"/> and then I text to her and said oh you know unfortunately <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad erm passed away <pause dur="short"/> late last night <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>s</trunc> and I said I've got <unclear/> you're on holiday today <pause dur="short"/> so I'm sorry if I've disturbed you but she text me back she said I'm really sorry to hear this <pause dur="short"/> I'm here if you need me <pause dur="short"/> because <pause dur="short"/> just before I broke up <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> her husband's mother died so she's been through exactly the same thing as me</u>
<u n="734" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0518"><trunc>in</trunc> and they <trunc>s</trunc> lived in <anon type="place"/> and so she was travelling <pause dur="short"/> and she <pause dur="short"/> basically <pause dur="short"/> just came up me at work one day and said <pause dur="short"/> just to let you know <pause dur="short"/> oh I I'm leaving work now <pause dur="short"/> I can't speak to the rest of the team because I'll be too upset <pause dur="short"/> we're going to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I knew exactly what it was <pause dur="short"/> and she could just go and leave everything with me <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> afterwards she wrote me a really nice <pause dur="short"/> email actually and erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> she just said how supportive we'd been as team leaders and when she'd needed it she different sort of personality from me <pause dur="short"/> so I know <pause dur="short"/> she knows</u>
<u n="736" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she she'll yeah she'll understand</u>
<u n="737" who="S0518" trans="overlap">what exactly what it's like <pause dur="short"/> and she'll be thinking <pause dur="short"/> my gosh she's got all of this on top of everything else <pause dur="short"/> and she just said to me I don't want you to worry about anything in this text</u>
<u n="738" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0518">do not worry about anything <pause dur="short"/> and even tell me on the morning if you're not coming to the meeting <pause dur="short"/> but I want to go to the meeting <pause dur="short"/> I want to go the meeting</u>
<u n="740" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah no no and I think that'll do you good and also you'll find out what's gone on a bit more and you and <pause dur="short"/> and you'll come away as well thinking <pause dur="short"/> oh okay I could probably I could go back <pause dur="short"/> and slot into that or <pause dur="short"/> come away thinking oh my gosh</u>
<u n="741" who="S0518"><unclear>well</unclear></u>
<u n="742" who="S0517">I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="743" who="S0518">before I left <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> we were having a structure change because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanted to change the structure <pause dur="short"/> between September <pause dur="short"/> and Christmas <pause dur="short"/> erm and I was gonna do this quality <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="744" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0518">become a quality manager <pause dur="short"/> and erm <trunc>inst</trunc> er still be team leader <pause dur="short"/> but work with the whole team rather than just my brand team <pause dur="short"/> because the quality of what we were doing she didn't feel was where it should be <pause dur="short"/> and she felt that I was the person to do that and as you know I was a bit mm she's just fobbing me off really</u>
<u n="746" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah but then you <trunc>th</trunc> then you did get on board with that role didn't you?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I did</u>
<u n="748" who="S0517">you did <trunc>i</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but I never started it</u>
<u n="750" who="S0517">no no</u>
<u n="751" who="S0518">now what's happened</u>
<u n="752" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but has anybody done it in your absence?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0518">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="754" who="S0517">do you want another cup of tea <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0518">are you having one?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0517">well I could have a cup of tea</u>
<u n="757" who="S0518">okay</u>
<u n="758" who="S0517">let's have a cup of tea</u>
<u n="759" who="S0518">I haven't given you a single chance to speak</u>
<u n="760" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> on I know and I <trunc>ha</trunc> and I had some sad news too</u>
<u n="761" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0517"><unclear/> oh I know awful</u>
<u n="763" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well shall I be quiet now? <pause dur="short"/> and <vocal desc="laugh"/> you can tell me</u>
<u n="764" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0518"><unclear>should</unclear> just finish this <pause dur="short"/> saga <unclear>later</unclear></u>
<u n="766" who="S0517" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0518">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I know what I think I'm over my tummy</unclear></u>
<u n="768" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh do you?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0518">well</u>
<u n="770" who="S0517"><unclear>shall?</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>shall?</unclear></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
