<text id="SCXU">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:07:32</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics></topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0058">mm yeah I guess it's busy <pause dur="short"/> just nice day <pause dur="short"/>  go out <unclear/> Saturday <pause dur="short"/> still never mind <pause dur="short"/> have a nice drive down</u>
<u n="2" who="S0179">yes indeed <pause dur="short"/> right erm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="4" who="S0179">right do you like to put of your music on?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0058">my music?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0179"><unclear/> iPod <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0058">it's in the in my bag in the back</u>
<u n="8" who="S0179">okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0058">like</u>
<u n="10" who="S0179">I did actually discuss this with you a few days ago that I said</u>
<u n="11" who="S0058" trans="overlap">when?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0179">or we can <pause dur="short"/> like when you got it yesterday <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no but doesn't have any of</u>
<u n="14" who="S0179">that's what your entire music collection right?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0058">yeah okay well I'll</u>
<u n="16" who="S0179">I'm sure there is something in there that's good to listen to in the car</u>
<u n="17" who="S0058">oh there's lots of things that are good to listen to in the car <pause dur="short"/> erm okay well we'll listen to yours on the first bit and then we can grab mine for the second bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I like I'm actually saying you know now we've got it we can listen to it on Saturday <pause dur="short"/> I thought you might like that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0058">yeah yeah well <pause dur="short"/> I just assumed that when I had my big one we didn't listen to my music in the car</u>
<u n="20" who="S0179">well we didn't have a facility to connect an iPod to a car at the time</u>
<u n="21" who="S0058">did we not?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="23" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="24" who="S0179">we only got this connecter after I got this iPod which means that for obvious reasons</u>
<u n="25" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> okay well erm well what would you like to listen to in the meantime then?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="27" who="S0058">er</u>
<u n="28" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I don't know let's er I think it's on the shuffle at the moment <pause dur="short"/> shall we see what's playing?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0058">yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> it's like Bertie Bott's Every Flavour Beans <pause dur="short"/> it could be anything</u>
<u n="30" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> pretty much</u>
<u n="31" who="S0058">it doesn't seem to be picking it up <pause dur="short"/> shall I?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0179">is it meant to be plugged in?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0058">it was but I'll just re un unplug it and reconnect it</u>
<u n="34" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0058">ah it's erm it's frozen <pause dur="short"/> I'll just reset it</u>
<u n="36" who="S0179">your mum's frozen <pause dur="short"/> I'll just reset her</u>
<u n="37" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The</u>
<u n="38" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="39" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0179">oh well the latest M P G was coming at fifty-two <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty good</u>
<u n="41" who="S0058">that's pretty good yeah <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="42" who="S0179">well we're normally on sixty-two so whether that's actually it because I think that's a lot of <pause dur="short"/> that's well mostly commuting driving <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty damn good</u>
<u n="43" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> er so I'll put it on shuffle <pause dur="short"/> excellent <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0179">wait roundabout</u>
<u n="45" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of music"/> Excellent <pause dur="short"/> nice cheery song for a Saturday morning</u>
<u n="46" who="S0179">yes indeed <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> I hadn't <unclear/> enough room to get ahead of that lorry before he got in there so I'll make that <unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0179">strategic</u>
<u n="49" who="S0058">ah ha <pause dur="short"/> very good</u>
<u n="50" who="S0179">I will quite happily undertake on this section because I'm not actually in contact with the road</u>
<u n="51" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort of a separate bit</u>
<u n="52" who="S0179">exactly <pause dur="short"/> so I can now <unclear/> relax <pause dur="long"/> So it's with careful planning I've actually managed to get into four in under twenty seconds</u>
<u n="53" who="S0058">pretty good that</u>
<u n="54" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0058">nice one</u>
<u n="56" who="S0179">maybe I'm bored <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm sorry I now won't car jack you</u>
<u n="57" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I won't ram into the back of you then <pause dur="short"/> never understood those</u>
<u n="58" who="S0179">the thing is though generally used by appalling drivers</u>
<u n="59" who="S0058">yeah no exactly yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to stick stick a sign in so</u>
<u n="60" who="S0179" trans="overlap">people sort of would would tail gate you themselves were it not for</u>
<u n="61" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to stick a sign in the back to yeah so that I don't have to worry about how I'm driving so that you'll just stay away from me <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean? They're just <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0179">no no what I meant was that the people <pause dur="short"/> they're worried that other drivers are like themselves</u>
<u n="63" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean yes <pause dur="short"/> like so there's one that we just drove past on the left there saying grandchildren on board <pause dur="short"/> and that's a bit different because that's kind of more of a joke like</u>
<u n="64" who="S0179">yeah but that's a joke because of the other ones</u>
<u n="65" who="S0058">yeah exactly that's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> so like Dad's taxi in the back is different <pause dur="short"/> whereas yeah just having a baby on board <pause dur="short"/> keep your distance</u>
<u n="66" who="S0179" trans="overlap">the one that really annoys me <pause dur="short"/> little princess on board</u>
<u n="67" who="S0058">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> well is she a princess? Is she actually the <trunc>ki</trunc> you know the daughter of the ruling family? No she's not so shut up</u>
<u n="68" who="S0179">are they <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0058" trans="overlap">is she little? Or is she obese? Be honest</u>
<u n="70" who="S0179"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What I was thinking more along the lines of erm  ones is that so what are you doing about this? So instead of taking advanced driving lessons or you know looking to improve your road safety you put this you put a sticker in the back of a car</u>
<u n="71" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah or picking a very safe vehicle or <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's the er low cost low effort option to keeping your kids safe</u>
<u n="72" who="S0179">well no it's the</u>
<u n="73" who="S0058">giving the responsibility to other people <pause dur="short"/> you can imagine in court can't you? Well I had a sign in the back <pause dur="short"/> isn't it hazy?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> still a nice day</u>
<u n="75" who="S0058">oh no definitely <pause dur="short"/> well it I think it's like that you know if we get up on a morning it's really foggy <pause dur="short"/> it often turns into the nicest day</u>
<u n="76" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hazy <pause dur="short"/> I'd still love to be out running</u>
<u n="77" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I think <pause dur="short"/> well you will be soon</u>
<u n="78" who="S0179">maybe tomorrow we'll see <pause dur="short"/> I'll do some more stretches today</u>
<u n="79" who="S0058">yeah I was going to say if you erm and you can er yeah these stretches will <unclear/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0179">I'm still going to be  of that parallel park</u>
<u n="81" who="S0058">yeah it was good stuff</u>
<u n="82" who="S0179">so it was a tiny space up a hill and a really bad angle</u>
<u n="83" who="S0058">you did it first time</u>
<u n="84" who="S0179"><event desc="sound of music"/> I'll get over this I like a bit of variety</u>
<u n="85" who="S0058"><unclear/> bit of shuffle?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0058">we can do a bit of shuffle on mine and <unclear/> on the last bit if you want</u>
<u n="88" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0058">bit more of a mixed bag</u>
<u n="90" who="S0179" trans="overlap">that's in shuffle of <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mine is more of a mixed bag</u>
<u n="91" who="S0058">no I just mean erm like oh how do you <unclear/> audio? We could have got in trouble <pause dur="short"/> it came with a chapter of Brideshead</u>
<u n="92" who="S0179">oh it shouldn't do <pause dur="short"/> erm there's a section on iTunes for if you go to options you can put exclude from shuffle</u>
<u n="93" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah that's <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I must do that</u>
<u n="94" who="S0179">so I'm doing it on my Christmas music for example</u>
<u n="95" who="S0058">yeah I'll have to do that with er with that</u>
<u n="96" who="S0179">well also unusually for all your  it saves from location <pause dur="short"/> if you just get the</u>
<u n="97" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="98" who="S0179">if you could get all albums to do that</u>
<u n="99" who="S0058">can you?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> cool <pause dur="short"/> I know that it would be quite as relevant because you wouldn't really want to come in half way through a song in the same way</u>
<u n="102" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah exactly that's why it's a default not to</u>
<u n="103" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's interesting <pause dur="short"/> cos that's  Cos that's  quite an old fashioned way of looking at music cos that's how a tape works but not</u>
<u n="104" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0058"><unclear/> have a record or a CD work so it's not that old fashioned just yet <pause dur="short"/> slightly unusual <pause dur="short"/> I used to love my tapes</u>
<u n="106" who="S0179">you see when I first got a DVD I was really disconcerted because it didn't save your place</u>
<u n="107" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> in some ways yeah videos were better for that cos it is a bit of a pain if you watch a film one night and then go back to it</u>
<u n="108" who="S0179" trans="overlap">but then of course you do have to be  to it</u>
<u n="109" who="S0058">yeah the thing is you you were <pause dur="short"/> I think this is the difference between us as children <pause dur="short"/> you rewound it when you were finished with it</u>
<u n="110" who="S0179">yep</u>
<u n="111" who="S0058">we rewound it when we wanted to watch it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0179">yep</u>
<u n="113" who="S0058">but if you watch something and you've got half way through you know and you <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="114" who="S0179">yeah you leave it then obviously</u>
<u n="115" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0179">once you've finished you rewind it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> bless</u>
<u n="118" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> jesus <pause dur="short"/> I thought that car's long</u>
<u n="119" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hang on</u>
<u n="120" who="S0179" trans="overlap">oi</u>
<u n="121" who="S0058">nice</u>
<u n="122" who="S0179">I've never seen a Hummer Range Rover before</u>
<u n="123" who="S0058"><unclear/> a limo really</u>
<u n="124" who="S0179">sorry a limo Range Rover yes</u>
<u n="125" who="S0058">ah it's the same</u>
<u n="126" who="S0179">it is just crazy <pause dur="short"/> I thought in the back that's a Range Rover <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah and then it just carried on</u>
<u n="128" who="S0179">I was like  I was like  well</u>
<u n="129" who="S0058">it was like a weird perspective thing</u>
<u n="130" who="S0179">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="131" who="S0058" trans="overlap">you can see the front and the back but the gap in between was bigger than you thought</u>
<u n="132" who="S0179">that must be a custom job</u>
<u n="133" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> stretch it <pause dur="short"/> car stretcher machine</u>
<u n="134" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="long"/> To be fair what I'd like to be doing now is in an open topped car through Scotland rather than <unclear/> of the M25</u>
<u n="135" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you know</u>
<u n="136" who="S0179" trans="overlap">however <pause dur="short"/> needs must</u>
<u n="137" who="S0058">yeah it's fair to say <pause dur="short"/> and you wouldn't really want an open topped car on the M25 necessarily</u>
<u n="138" who="S0179">erm I wouldn't object to one</u>
<u n="139" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s well enough to be er driving in the open topped car yet</u>
<u n="140" who="S0179">but if not we can borrow it</u>
<u n="141" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> you're always thinking but er yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0179">it's only a two seater though</u>
<u n="143" who="S0058">it is</u>
<u n="144" who="S0179">I think like I can just imagine see seventy <pause dur="short"/> top down <pause dur="short"/> four people in it <pause dur="short"/> imagine how much fun that would be <pause dur="short"/> just cruising</u>
<u n="145" who="S0058" trans="overlap">that's pretty cool <pause dur="short"/> just cruising yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'd all have to tap our fingers and nod our heads on the side of the car</u>
<u n="146" who="S0179">some beers maybe</u>
<u n="147" who="S0058">some beers <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll put music on <pause dur="short"/> some beers I can offer you <pause dur="short"/> shall we book  then?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0179">erm I'm tempted <pause dur="short"/> I just <unclear/> with no cost</u>
<u n="149" who="S0058">yeah and no cost in terms of leave</u>
<u n="150" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0058">which is quite valuable <pause dur="short"/> cos then at the end of the year we could have a couple days off before Christmas or and you know and just have a bit more leeway with it</u>
<u n="152" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm against the idea of saving up lots of leave for the following year purely cos I think you don't</u>
<u n="153" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah just <trunc>tu</trunc> you just roll it over <pause dur="short"/> you would never use it</u>
<u n="154" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0058">but it's nice to have it so that</u>
<u n="156" who="S0179" trans="overlap">that's my instinct <pause dur="short"/> to save it all as long as possible but then you would never take it</u>
<u n="157" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no exactly <pause dur="short"/> I think it's important for us to remember to take leave but <trunc>o</trunc> and maybe more importantly to remember to take holidays which is a key thing <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="158" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think I'd get I'm more keen to not just use up leave as odd days here and there <pause dur="short"/> I'm keen to use it <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="159" who="S0058" trans="overlap">as proper breaks <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0058">but if we do need</u>
<u n="162" who="S0179" trans="overlap">maybe we can go to Alton Towers one day say but</u>
<u n="163" who="S0058">yeah yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> I mean that kind of thing would be fun and I mean it's always I wouldn't mind just having a you know random day off <pause dur="short"/> go to London or something <pause dur="short"/> we could go to a matinee or you know <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah or all the time <pause dur="short"/> I mean don't just use it in dribs and drabs</u>
<u n="164" who="S0179" trans="overlap">but then you don't properly relax <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'd be tempted possibly from a <unclear/> perspective to take a week off and just spend it around home just doing things</u>
<u n="165" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean I think yeah there's definitely advantages just to having a bit of time off <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I think erm if we can have a holiday without using any it would make sense <pause dur="short"/> I mean we could take a day an extra day off but I'm not sure necessarily <pause dur="short"/> and we could have the Thursday off and drive up to my parent's kind of Thursday morning or Wednesday night even erm and have longer there but I'm not sure if it's necessarily worth it</u>
<u n="166" who="S0179">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it might make it seem more relaxing but yeah I agree for the moment I'm tempted not to do that</u>
<u n="167" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think I could probably say that quite short notice at work <pause dur="short"/> erm I don't have anything that week I don't think so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0179">that car looks weird</u>
<u n="169" who="S0058">what the Schirokko?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it does a bit</u>
<u n="172" who="S0179">I thought it was Schirokko</u>
<u n="173" who="S0058">I would say  I would say  say Schirokko <pause dur="short"/> but it might be Schirokko I don't know erm I haven't heard anyone say it apart from me so</u>
<u n="174" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="175" who="S0058">I don't know I haven't been on any car website in a while <pause dur="long"/> But erm yeah we should <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and do you want to ring them tonight or? If you've got the number we could ring them</u>
<u n="176" who="S0179">I'll do it from the car</u>
<u n="177" who="S0058">from the car yeah <pause dur="short"/> or when we get there even</u>
<u n="178" who="S0179">yeah we could</u>
<u n="179" who="S0058">your mum seems determined that we go</u>
<u n="180" who="S0179">I know <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure we've got a lot of choice</u>
<u n="181" who="S0058" trans="overlap">really keen <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean I think that you know sounds like a really nice plan <pause dur="short"/> if we take the erm the recipe book and we take the erm yeah and basically you have the hot tub and the recipe book and just yeah chill out <pause dur="short"/> watch films <pause dur="short"/> read <pause dur="short"/> walk about</u>
<u n="182" who="S0179" trans="overlap">champagne</u>
<u n="183" who="S0058">champagne in the hot tub <pause dur="short"/> bit of that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0179">lies in</u>
<u n="185" who="S0058">pardon?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0179">lies in</u>
<u n="187" who="S0058">lies in yeah <pause dur="short"/> sounds pretty good to me <pause dur="short"/> live TV</u>
<u n="188" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0058">that will be nice</u>
<u n="190" who="S0179">board games</u>
<u n="191" who="S0058">board games</u>
<u n="192" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0058">yeah and erm just yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0179">maybe pop down the gym and do some weights</u>
<u n="195" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just chill out <pause dur="short"/> I think that sounds like quite a nice plan</u>
<u n="196" who="S0179">no that sounds a great plan</u>
<u n="197" who="S0058">cool <pause dur="short"/> let's do that <pause dur="short"/> and we could maybe see our parents which will be nice</u>
<u n="198" who="S0179">or we could consider to have them over</u>
<u n="199" who="S0058">yeah I'll mention that to them</u>
<u n="200" who="S0179">it's not that far <pause dur="short"/> if they can consider to join us for say a day if they wanted to</u>
<u n="201" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah they could come over on the Saturday whatever and just yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah like I said I'll have to see what they're doing with regard to erm when they have to back but yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0179">another thought is <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> oh no we could cos the gym's got weird now isn't it <pause dur="short"/> the old gym <pause dur="short"/> that you can't just go in for like ten quid <pause dur="short"/> per session</u>
<u n="203" who="S0058">what? Yeah it's erm you mean the hotel?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0058">yeah it's fifteen <pause dur="short"/> for it's all day <pause dur="short"/> all the facilities for fifteen quid which makes sense if you're going to be in there all day but it doesn't make sense if you just want to go down and faff about</u>
<u n="206" who="S0179">oh well</u>
<u n="207" who="S0058">yeah it's a shame but never mind <pause dur="short"/> they might change that I mean <pause dur="short"/> or we could make a case to them <pause dur="short"/> we could write to them and say</u>
<u n="208" who="S0179">no that won't do bugger all because they're a national chain <unclear/> hotels do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know but I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I think they do have some kind of autonomous individual deals and things like that <pause dur="short"/> I think they do make their own</u>
<u n="210" who="S0179" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="211" who="S0058">and through the website <pause dur="short"/> that's the impression I get <pause dur="short"/> and they sort of the way they market is very specific to the hotel so they might be able to alter prices <pause dur="short"/> there's no harm in sending them an email saying we will literally never come in <pause dur="short"/> if you make it five pounds to go in just in the pool for a pound an hour we'll come in</u>
<u n="212" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0058">you know <pause dur="short"/> no harm in doing that</u>
<u n="214" who="S0179">bit difficult for them to regulate that</u>
<u n="215" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> true</u>
<u n="216" who="S0179">so Dad likes the new gym</u>
<u n="217" who="S0058">but they can't <unclear/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0058">and and he likes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0058">Good <pause dur="short"/> he seems to be quite into it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0058">what's a wall angel? I I was asking you both of you for like a <trunc>t</trunc> five minutes last night and nobody told me</u>
<u n="224" who="S0179">sorry erm <pause dur="short"/> I didn't hear that</u>
<u n="225" who="S0058">yeah I was going what's the wall angel <pause dur="short"/> and then you carried on talking and I was like what's the wall angel</u>
<u n="226" who="S0179">I'll show you in <anon type="place"/> if you want</u>
<u n="227" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm imagining it involves a wall but that's as far as I've got</u>
<u n="228" who="S0179">who's singing this?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0058">can't remember <pause dur="short"/> is it the cover or is it the original?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0179">oh no it's from the er er <unclear/> CD</u>
<u n="231" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0179">erm what was I saying? Erm yeah I've never seen Dad so happy I don't think <pause dur="short"/> what with him enjoying himself so much</u>
<u n="233" who="S0058" trans="overlap">what last night? He was enjoying himself <pause dur="short"/> he was plastered</u>
<u n="234" who="S0179">not to start with and didn't really change throughout the evening</u>
<u n="235" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> no true</u>
<u n="236" who="S0179">but we I can't believe</u>
<u n="237" who="S0058">so bad</u>
<u n="238" who="S0179">that was ridiculous</u>
<u n="239" who="S0058">oh my word <pause dur="short"/> so bad <pause dur="short"/> your mum was mortified <pause dur="short"/> I left to go to the toilet <pause dur="short"/> did he get a telling off?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0179"><trunc>S</trunc> no</u>
<u n="241" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> oh your poor mother</u>
<u n="242" who="S0179">I think retirement suits him</u>
<u n="243" who="S0058">yes I think he does</u>
<u n="244" who="S0179">I think it's a combination of but he's now retired and very very relaxed</u>
<u n="245" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0179">and the fact that we no longer live together and you two get on very well</u>
<u n="247" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's relaxed and yeah you don't have to get on each other's nerves</u>
<u n="248" who="S0179">exactly</u>
<u n="249" who="S0058">Dearie me <pause dur="short"/> the dog was very pleased to see us I think</u>
<u n="250" who="S0179">I think it's it's nearest to the ideal if we just pop up occasionally</u>
<u n="251" who="S0058">yes I think he's getting better at just going oh they're here <pause dur="short"/> this is exciting <pause dur="short"/> and they're going to go now and that's alright and you know</u>
<u n="252" who="S0179">I'm going to  so there</u>
<u n="253" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean do you think he recognises the name because he was <trunc>b</trunc> it was sort of being said quite a bit and it I do wonder if <trunc>reco</trunc> if he sort of links that or whether he's not quite <pause dur="short"/> or whether he knows he's going away but in he but it's not the words maybe it's more that packing that he understands <pause dur="short"/> the visual</u>
<u n="254" who="S0179" trans="overlap">possibly but he still doesn't want to get into a car</u>
<u n="255" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah he hasn't made that link yet <pause dur="short"/> maybe with dogs it's what's immediately happening that's important and that the kind of expectation of long term</u>
<u n="256" who="S0179" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no but then that but that wouldn't work because so when you're packing boxes like that's what's immediately happening <pause dur="short"/> that's what's happening the next day</u>
<u n="257" who="S0058" trans="overlap">true <pause dur="short"/> yeah so he does know that so <trunc>may</trunc> I mean maybe he just really really hates being in the car so much that it's never worth it</u>
<u n="258" who="S0179">possibly</u>
<u n="259" who="S0058">in his head it's never worth it and then he gets there and goes no it's alright really <pause dur="short"/> he's always a very happy dog when he gets there</u>
<u n="260" who="S0179">next door's baby sounds lovely though</u>
<u n="261" who="S0058">your mum's like obsessed with her baby</u>
<u n="262" who="S0179">yeah it's scary isn't it?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It will go missing and she'll be like shh <pause dur="short"/> but yeah erm it does sound lovely <pause dur="short"/> very nice <pause dur="short"/> you get babies like that though which are just really nice <pause dur="short"/> well you know have a good nature and be quiet</u>
<u n="264" who="S0179">she's right though she doesn't sort of like make a thing about children</u>
<u n="265" who="S0058">well I'm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0179">I think we have a very common attitude to children like some babies I find actually that's quite cute <pause dur="short"/> most of them are like yeah you're just a bit smelly aren't you</u>
<u n="267" who="S0058">but a bit too small really aren't you</u>
<u n="268" who="S0179">the thing that really annoys me is like it's unacceptable to take a dog into a restaurant but acceptable to tale a baby in</u>
<u n="269" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0179">my dog's far more hygienic than a baby</u>
<u n="271" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and better behaved</u>
<u n="272" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0058">it depends on the dog but then if you have sort of</u>
<u n="274" who="S0179">it will lie under the table and be quiet</u>
<u n="275" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sandy does just lie quietly erm whereas a baby is crying or whatever <pause dur="short"/> it will be much much more of a disruption <pause dur="short"/> but I guess it's easier to have a blanket rule and they've just sort of done it that way round <pause dur="short"/> rather than saying you know <pause dur="short"/> but some places do say well behaved dogs welcome though <pause dur="short"/> and I imagine they would <trunc>s</trunc> if your dog was running around barking they would say get out</u>
<u n="276" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think <unclear/> Sandy would very useful in just an exam hall <pause dur="short"/> so many people to go and see</u>
<u n="277" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><trunc>S</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> So useful</u>
<u n="278" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0058">I think he'd really enjoy it <pause dur="short"/> lot's of new people <pause dur="short"/> and they'd be lots of things he could sort of help with because they'd all be stressed so he could and help them out</u>
<u n="280" who="S0179" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah it would literally a question like who's the most stressed here?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you think he'd be able to smell who is the most stressed?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0179">possibly yes</u>
<u n="283" who="S0058">it's interesting isn't it?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0179">he's very good at picking up on that</u>
<u n="285" who="S0058">he's extremely good yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's interesting how a nose can do something that we just really can't <pause dur="short"/> that you know they're just superior <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0179">well he can also sniff out drugs a lot more effectively than you can</u>
<u n="287" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well exactly that's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> there's so many areas where the a dog is just better than a human at doing things <pause dur="short"/> even in top human areas like yeah sort of fear and emotion and things and <trunc>s</trunc> yeah worry and like that kind of thing that in fact a dog is better than a human in knowing how you're feeling I think is just</u>
<u n="288" who="S0179">or better about doing something about it which is always what amuses me</u>
<u n="289" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah he knows what to do <unclear/> <event desc="sound of music"/> Huh <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> Excuse me</u>
<u n="290" who="S0179">er what am I talking about?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0058">but erm talking about Sandy and dogs and how much he understands and going away to <unclear/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0179">oh yes about just about Dad and enjoying last night</u>
<u n="293" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Enjoying last night yeah <pause dur="short"/> I really enjoyed my meal though <pause dur="short"/> I thought  I thought  it was a very pleasant er restaurant experience</u>
<u n="294" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> none of my courses were outstanding</u>
<u n="295" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0179">dessert was the best bit</u>
<u n="297" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0179">like the starter was a bit sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0058">I I was so hungry though that I didn't really <trunc>lo</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you had bruschetta didn't you?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my starter was fine <pause dur="short"/> it was you know wasn't particularly special <pause dur="short"/> I mean cos</u>
<u n="302" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I mean that was my only comment <pause dur="short"/> it was fine <pause dur="short"/> the main course again</u>
<u n="303" who="S0058" trans="overlap">my main course was lovely but I think you maybe yours was maybe more standard</u>
<u n="304" who="S0179">but no it's just a bit <pause dur="short"/> the pizza was just a bit dry</u>
<u n="305" who="S0058">oh it's a shame</u>
<u n="306" who="S0179">it was like a pizza base with the ingredients thrown on top <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't really put together</u>
<u n="307" who="S0058" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0179">like the food in Pizza Express is several notches above that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0058">right okay <pause dur="short"/> an oven yeah I mean it Pizza Express pizza's great but then  if you  if you know like I do like pasta and that was really very good pasta</u>
<u n="310" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="311" who="S0058">erm I've never had anything quite like that <pause dur="short"/> it was really really well put together so</u>
<u n="312" who="S0179">I mean maybe I should think more creatively about what I have next time up there</u>
<u n="313" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0179">Cos I mean that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> you know er <unclear/> if it's <unclear/> you do love it <pause dur="short"/> I think the food is exceptional in there</u>
<u n="315" who="S0058">it's really good yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0058">oh I was thinking actually <pause dur="short"/> erm when we get back tonight do you want to pop into Morrisons on the way back and get some interesting for tea as in there isn't there isn't anything else so?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0179">I was actually thinking of possibly going to the cinema at the <anon type="place"/> on the way home because we're going to be literally underneath it</u>
<u n="319" who="S0058">yeah we could do</u>
<u n="320" who="S0179">er so it might be fun</u>
<u n="321" who="S0058">what and?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0179">Cos the alternative is to go back by the M11 but I think that will be slower</u>
<u n="323" who="S0058">are we going to see a film? Or just getting some food or?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0179">I said go to the cinema</u>
<u n="325" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0179">yeah I originally well just for <anon type="place"/> in general <pause dur="short"/> oh just see a film you said</u>
<u n="327" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0179">right erm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0058">just literally go and see a film or go and have some food or? I mean in some ways it might be nice to get back seeming as we've sort of been out <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="330" who="S0179">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it just seemed like quite a nice sort of chance to round off the day a little bit</u>
<u n="331" who="S0058">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> well well is there anything on?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0179">I'm not sure</u>
<u n="333" who="S0058">I'm not  I'm not  sure what's out at the minute</u>
<u n="334" who="S0179">I was going to check this morning but we didn't really have time</u>
<u n="335" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/>  sure what's out <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I watched the erm the first episode well first half of the first episode of The Apprentice at work at lunchtime</u>
<u n="336" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="337" who="S0058">and erm they used the music from The Artist for one of the tasks and it just really annoyed me <pause dur="short"/> such wonderful music from such an amazing film and they've got it accompanying the</u>
<u n="338" who="S0179" trans="overlap">the what? That rancid shit</u>
<u n="339" who="S0058">what?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0179">the Apprentice</u>
<u n="341" who="S0058">the Apprentice <pause dur="short"/> it's really bad yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you see why I like it? It's really bad <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's embarrassing for them like <pause dur="short"/> but they're meant to be <trunc>s</trunc> you know I am the best at business <pause dur="short"/> and they're saying things and you just think oh my goodness to me <pause dur="short"/> do you are you really this bad? Like genuinely</u>
<u n="342" who="S0179" trans="overlap">like what?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0058">well just the way they approach</u>
<u n="344" who="S0179">problems</u>
<u n="345" who="S0058">yeah like this this the first task there was sixteen people so you didn't really get to know them <trunc>ter</trunc> terribly well as individuals <pause dur="short"/> but erm the erm task was they had to buy sort of <trunc>unbran</trunc> like completely blank items and put a design on them and sell them</u>
<u n="346" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="347" who="S0058">erm and make a <trunc>pro</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> they they <trunc>p</trunc> team that makes the most profit wins <pause dur="short"/> simple as that</u>
<u n="348" who="S0179">well my solution would be I'm going to accept all of us now to work at our regular jobs for this period of time</u>
<u n="349" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0179">and we'll earn far more money</u>
<u n="351" who="S0058">I don't think you'd win The Apprentice that way but yeah good thinking <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah so the guys could they they were sort of worried about the figures</u>
<u n="352" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well it's a pointless task because cos they'll either know nothing about <pause dur="short"/> they don't have to be on the <unclear/> It's just not going to work</u>
<u n="353" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well entirely pointless yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean the the the sort of the there was sort of girls versus boys and the boys erm decided to buy these teddy bears and just stick a Union Jack on the t-shirt and  sell it  sell it to tourists <pause dur="short"/> boring <pause dur="short"/> and the other one they made these</u>
<u n="354" who="S0179">probably quite effective</u>
<u n="355" who="S0058">well they wanted to sell them for fifteen quid for these tiny little teddy bears and it's like oh that's not going to work <pause dur="short"/> erm and the other one they had the words this is a <pause dur="short"/> and they're like a red phone box</u>
<u n="356" who="S0179">right?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0058">I'm sorry no it was a bus <pause dur="short"/> I think it was a bus <pause dur="short"/> yeah a girl and the bus <pause dur="short"/> and this a bus <pause dur="short"/> and it was like well that doesn't mean anything <pause dur="short"/> what does that? What? What?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0179">yeah but many things don't mean anything</u>
<u n="359" who="S0058">yeah I know but it was just a ridiculously bad <pause dur="short"/> and they printed them really badly as well <pause dur="short"/> there was just yeah it's embarrassing</u>
<u n="360" who="S0179">that's a very small door</u>
<u n="361" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a bus for slow people <pause dur="short"/> it's quite bizarre is that just a door that they can?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0179">I think so</u>
<u n="363" who="S0058">how bizarre <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of weird only having one bike <pause dur="short"/> you'd think</u>
<u n="364" who="S0179">the others could be inside</u>
<u n="365" who="S0058">true yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0179">that's obviously quite an expensive bike</u>
<u n="367" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0179">if you have a look at it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the wheels look quite different <pause dur="short"/> I need to get some oil for my bike actually <pause dur="short"/> it's erm it's very the sort of the chain needs er needs some oil on it</u>
<u n="370" who="S0179">it says caution on the back</u>
<u n="371" who="S0058">left hand drive</u>
<u n="372" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="373" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0179"><unclear/> English and</u>
<u n="375" who="S0058">english registration but how bizarre <pause dur="short"/> mind you there is only the one guy in there <pause dur="short"/> maybe he's going away by himself with his fancy bike and his motor home</u>
<u n="376" who="S0179">maybe</u>
<u n="377" who="S0058">you never know <pause dur="long"/> Nice <pause dur="short"/> that Golf that's hanging on the back erm a bit bashed up <pause dur="short"/> and it had you know the Monster Energy Drink symbol</u>
<u n="378" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0058">it had like a sticker of that on the petrol cover thing</u>
<u n="380" who="S0179">how unfortunate</u>
<u n="381" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Don't put Monster Energy in it <pause dur="short"/> that's why it's broken</u>
<u n="382" who="S0179">ha <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0058">oh dearie me <pause dur="short"/> what were we just talking about? Oh The Apprentice <pause dur="short"/> oh embarrassing <pause dur="short"/> really embarrassing <pause dur="short"/> some of the things they say though <pause dur="short"/> some of the things they come out with <pause dur="short"/> like I I was watching this the last series at the same time that I was going to job interviews and I was like if I said that in a job interview they would laugh at me and throw me out for being ridiculous</u>
<u n="384" who="S0179">like what?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0058">well just the some of the cliché they come out with and I'm trying to think of a good example of one</u>
<u n="386" who="S0179"><unclear/> they do select idiots for that</u>
<u n="387" who="S0058">yeah well yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's for entertainment purely <pause dur="short"/> erm none of them are any good</u>
<u n="388" who="S0179">but in effect they don't realise this is the thing</u>
<u n="389" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> they think they're really the best business minds <pause dur="short"/> the best business mind in the country and you're like well blatantly you're not <pause dur="short"/> so I mean yeah so the boys with this Union Jack on the teddy is like yeah I think that's really quite different <pause dur="short"/> that's quite  That's quite  quirky and unusual <pause dur="short"/> I was like since when? Erm and yeah just not thinking about the the girls were adding up the figures once they'd already bought everything <pause dur="short"/> and it's like this couldn't <trunc>proce</trunc> you know really shockingly bad <pause dur="short"/> and I know I'm not exactly business mind but er very good television though</u>
<u n="390" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0058">not as good as MasterChef <pause dur="short"/> because MasterChef they don't bother with sort of <pause dur="short"/> it's not really about the personalities so much <pause dur="short"/> it's about cooking and they do just cook for a long time <pause dur="short"/> in <trunc>dif</trunc> in different situations but they fundamentally spend an hour showing you their cooking <pause dur="short"/> which is quite nice you know <pause dur="short"/> it's interesting <pause dur="short"/> whereas The Apprentice just shows it's an hour of them running around like headless chickens being pathetic</u>
<u n="392" who="S0179">what is it? Hitler's chickens <unclear/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0058">hit list yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0179">no Hitler's</u>
<u n="395" who="S0058">oh Hitler's chickens <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure if Hitler kept chickens but I'm sure if he did they'd be er very regimented <pause dur="short"/> and white <pause dur="short"/> good egg layers</u>
<u n="396" who="S0179">look how we now gained three lanes</u>
<u n="397" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0179">it's weird <unclear/> fundamentally the most dangerous to put low flying aircraft next to a road</u>
<u n="399" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> Yeah very low flying aircraft next to a road</u>
<u n="400" who="S0179">however</u>
<u n="401" who="S0058">they obviously think <unclear/> you know <pause dur="short"/> whenever <pause dur="short"/> it's ages since I've flown</u>
<u n="402" who="S0179">you can always fly dear</u>
<u n="403" who="S0058">ah bless <pause dur="short"/> yeah the last time I flew was I think I went to Dublin in first year <pause dur="short"/> yeah that would have been the last time</u>
<u n="404" who="S0179">I really don't want to go home and work again</u>
<u n="405" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> crazy</u>
<u n="406" who="S0179">that's something I'm gonna bring up in my <pause dur="short"/> cos if I've now got quite a lot of things I actually want to talk about in my er <trunc>assess</trunc> appraisal</u>
<u n="407" who="S0058">well that's great I mean go in with things to to bring up</u>
<u n="408" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="409" who="S0058">like it shows you've thought about it <pause dur="short"/> so are you going to talk about</u>
<u n="410" who="S0179">as in what I'm doing more or less is having a project to work on and having something sort of <trunc>g</trunc> I don't know I feel like I've got little bits of things</u>
<u n="411" who="S0058" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0179">I also think I've possible the last month or so I think I've been quite tired</u>
<u n="413" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="414" who="S0179">and it's difficult therefore to put any enthusiasm into it which makes it worse</u>
<u n="415" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0179">erm it's a little bit self-reinforcing</u>
<u n="417" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0179">but and I've got I love having <unclear/> Cos in my first three months I was there I had quite a few client meetings</u>
<u n="419" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="420" who="S0179">so at least I saw clients and I went to client sites</u>
<u n="421" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0179">and I really enjoyed that and I haven't done that since</u>
<u n="423" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="424" who="S0179">and cos I find like bizarrely bizarrely I find sort of monthly team meeting really interesting and really motivational</u>
<u n="425" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0179">and I can see what I'm doing in the wider context</u>
<u n="427" who="S0058">yes definitely</u>
<u n="428" who="S0179">and I've had less of that which has been de-motivating</u>
<u n="429" who="S0058">okay so so you'd really yeah I mean you could say you'd really like to spend more time in client meetings and meetings and things <pause dur="short"/> and yeah that you'd like more of a project <pause dur="short"/> yeah more more having a project to work on yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm definitely worth bringing up and I think I mean I guess everyone wants to travel for work so</u>
<u n="430" who="S0179">well no not really <pause dur="short"/> erm the more you do the less you like it apparently</u>
<u n="431" who="S0058">true <pause dur="short"/> well I guess you get sick of it</u>
<u n="432" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Well you see I actually love airports for their own sake</u>
<u n="433" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's all nicely neat and self contained and</u>
<u n="434" who="S0179">you see most people hate driving to work and I still love it</u>
<u n="435" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0179">I actively enjoy the process</u>
<u n="437" who="S0058">well yeah maybe worth mentioning then that you like travelling and <pause dur="short"/> okay erm well that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> do you know when it is yet? Have you got a date?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0179">er yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> bizarrely it's the end of April</u>
<u n="439" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="440" who="S0179">which is interesting in fact because I always assumed you call it financial year end but er apparently not</u>
<u n="441" who="S0058" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="442" who="S0179">oh well we'll see</u>
<u n="443" who="S0058">yeah so well it will be a good chance and yeah erm bring up everything I guess</u>
<u n="444" who="S0179">yes I intend to</u>
<u n="445" who="S0058">make a list <pause dur="short"/> yeah I get erm <event desc="sound of music"/> Nice <pause dur="short"/> it never occurred to me before this is five four</u>
<u n="446" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0058">this music <pause dur="short"/> the time signature is really unusual <pause dur="short"/> as in it's five beats in a bar which is very unusual but that's why it sounds so kind of odd <pause dur="short"/> but that bit isn't</u>
<u n="448" who="S0179" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0058">so <trunc>ch</trunc> that's why it sound <pause dur="short"/> it that it kind of <trunc>kee</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's just normal but the erm the other bit is it's got an extra beat <pause dur="short"/> it's got a beat too many</u>
<u n="450" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="451" who="S0058">so which is why it sounds exciting and sort of makes you feel a little bit <pause dur="short"/> it's clever how music works like that <pause dur="short"/> it's very difficult to make a piece work in altering the time signature because people sort of you know what's happening? I I can't clap to this <pause dur="short"/> but you can <pause dur="short"/> this is just so iconic it works</u>
<u n="452" who="S0179">well it wouldn't always have been iconic</u>
<u n="453" who="S0058">hmm?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0179">it wasn't always have been iconic</u>
<u n="455" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I guess it worked first and then it became iconic so people knew it <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0179">I wouldn't mind watching Mission Impossible twoI</u>
<u n="457" who="S0058">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think I've seen that one</u>
<u n="458" who="S0179">I like bits of it <pause dur="short"/> almost in spite of it <trunc>sel</trunc></u>
<u n="459" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> is this the one where I watched it at the end I turned to you I was like I don't understand <pause dur="short"/> and you were like it's fine</u>
<u n="460" who="S0179">no that's Mission Impossible one</u>
<u n="461" who="S0058">that's Mission <trunc>Impo</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that was it <pause dur="short"/> I turned to you and I was like er <pause dur="short"/> story <pause dur="short"/> please explain</u>
<u n="462" who="S0179">er masks and a train</u>
<u n="463" who="S0058">oh god yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0179">and that's <pause dur="short"/> well two things <pause dur="short"/> firstly that's why you should do a shoulder check before starting to move rather than as you're starting to move</u>
<u n="465" who="S0058">hmm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0179">mental note <pause dur="short"/> secondly that's why you don't undertake people fast</u>
<u n="467" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="468" who="S0179">Cos you suddenly put yourself in their blind spot and they're not expecting you <pause dur="short"/> but the second important point is there I did something <trunc>i</trunc> that I could have done better and I want to improve on it next time</u>
<u n="469" who="S0058">hmm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0179">however</u>
<u n="471" who="S0058">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="473" who="S0058">ah busy <pause dur="long"/> Still we're going the right way <pause dur="long"/> as in not carrying on round is I think is er is the way to go isn't it?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="long"/> Oh shit you were just undertaking <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="475" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0179">that's special in that case <pause dur="short"/> that is honestly special</u>
<u n="477" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I see what you mean yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0179" trans="overlap">that wasn't that bad if you were just getting out into lane <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="479" who="S0058" trans="overlap">huh <pause dur="short"/> no he was just yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0179">so interestingly legally <pause dur="short"/> if I hadn't seen him and we had hit him that would have been his responsibility</u>
<u n="481" who="S0058">because he was undertaking right</u>
<u n="482" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah because that would have been driving without due care and attention</u>
<u n="483" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="484" who="S0179">because undertaking is actually illegal</u>
<u n="485" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="486" who="S0179">erm well at least not specifically <pause dur="short"/> it's frowned on in the highway code <pause dur="short"/> it's a you should not do this but it will be prosecuted as driving without due care and attention</u>
<u n="487" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> interesting</u>
<u n="488" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0058">wow</u>
<u n="490" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh God <pause dur="long"/> I love that <pause dur="short"/> national speed limit and then two seconds after it</u>
<u n="491" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I going to have to start thinking about erm what to put on for my iPod <pause dur="short"/> I'm not used to having my music collection with me</u>
<u n="492" who="S0179">well you've now got everything now haven't you?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> literally everything <pause dur="short"/> yeah erm is it alright if I erm yank some audio books?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0179">I have a lot</u>
<u n="495" who="S0058">true I'll stick everything you've got on it cos then we can play it through the dock and all of the audio books</u>
<u n="496" who="S0179">well no I still like mine on the dock thank you very much</u>
<u n="497" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> that's what we said the other day <pause dur="short"/> that's what I I couldn't remember talking about me having it in the car but you did say that we'd just put everything</u>
<u n="498" who="S0179">no we didn't <pause dur="short"/> that was a joke</u>
<u n="499" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="500" who="S0179">I still want my music collection on my iPod <pause dur="short"/> I don't want it on yours</u>
<u n="501" who="S0058">fair enough</u>
<u n="502" who="S0179">otherwise what's the point in mine</u>
<u n="503" who="S0058">fair enough <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of music"/> Who's this?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0179">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> it's good though</u>
<u n="505" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> but erm there was an audio book that we started <pause dur="short"/> I think it was <trunc>Cro</trunc></u>
<u n="506" who="S0179" trans="overlap">those boys don't understand the average speed limit <pause dur="short"/> check</u>
<u n="507" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="508" who="S0179"></u>
<u n="509" who="S0058">but erm yeah what was I going to say erm? Oh I just thought oh yeah that was it Crooked House I think it was <pause dur="short"/> we started and then never actually finished it so I'd quite like to finish that <pause dur="short"/> maybe when I've finished my book on the bus</u>
<u n="510" who="S0179">I like it cos you can watch with your eyes shut <pause dur="short"/> listen to them with your eyes shut</u>
<u n="511" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0179">I still really want to go to Lego Land</u>
<u n="513" who="S0058">let's go some time</u>
<u n="514" who="S0179">I'm not sure that's acceptable <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to find a child</u>
<u n="515" who="S0058">you can just go <pause dur="short"/> you're allowed</u>
<u n="516" who="S0179">are you?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they'll let you in <pause dur="short"/> oh I've got two for one in Lego Land I think and Alton Towers <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> WH Smith gave me a voucher</u>
<u n="518" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="519" who="S0058">so yeah if you want to go to Alton Towers <pause dur="short"/> in all fairness you can generally get two for one for Alton Towers without too much trouble</u>
<u n="520" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> pay for the price of Alton Towers</u>
<u n="521" who="S0058">ah <unclear/> I wonder if they been any more <unclear/> or whether it was another short lived things</u>
<u n="522" who="S0179">I think it was unfortunately it was relatively short lived</u>
<u n="523" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0179">which is possibly as well</u>
<u n="525" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0179">the best one was either the one in the taxi or the land economy one</u>
<u n="527" who="S0058">I think my favourite was still the one  walking to King's with the card <pause dur="short"/> I still like that one I think</u>
<u n="528" who="S0179">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> those were good <pause dur="short"/> there were a whole range of those which were good <pause dur="short"/> that was possibly the best one</u>
<u n="529" who="S0058" trans="overlap">and <pause dur="short"/> yeah I I that was my favourite out of the Boromir ones <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0179">Boromir related humour</u>
<u n="531" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I love it <pause dur="short"/> there's a whole genre <pause dur="short"/> I love the erm the the tourist at John's <pause dur="short"/> there's a picture at the top and then Gandalf <pause dur="short"/> you shall not pass</u>
<u n="532" who="S0179">uh?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> weavey</u>
<u n="534" who="S0179">okay let's get past you <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0058">I presume it's Canned Heat <pause dur="short"/> good song</u>
<u n="538" who="S0179">who by?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0058">jamiroquai</u>
<u n="540" who="S0179">is it?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is</u>
<u n="542" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="543" who="S0058">we can skip it if you don't like it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="545" who="S0058">I quite like Jamiroquai</u>
<u n="546" who="S0179" trans="overlap">this must be one of my running songs <pause dur="short"/> I had no idea I had this</u>
<u n="547" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> it's good <pause dur="short"/> I like it <pause dur="short"/> he he used to wear kind of stupid hats <pause dur="short"/> that was his thing</u>
<u n="548" who="S0179">well as far as things go <pause dur="short"/> that's not too bad</u>
<u n="549" who="S0058">true true <pause dur="long"/> I agree with the sentiment as well <pause dur="short"/> just dance <pause dur="short"/> problems? Er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0179">it's busy</u>
<u n="551" who="S0058">it is</u>
<u n="552" who="S0179">we actually agree on this</u>
<u n="553" who="S0058">I'm glad we both recognise the factual statement is true</u>
<u n="554" who="S0179">I'm glad we both appreciate the traffic density for what it is</u>
<u n="555" who="S0058">dense <pause dur="short"/> yes indeed</u>
<u n="556" who="S0179">dense like your mother</u>
<u n="557" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> dense like your face</u>
<u n="558" who="S0179">just like your mum's face</u>
<u n="559" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0179">see what I did there?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0058">I do yes <pause dur="short"/> I do <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm quite excited about <unclear/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0179">yeah should be fun</u>
<u n="563" who="S0058">yeah it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> it will be really different I think <pause dur="short"/> a different week for us <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/> wanted to kind of be there</u>
<u n="564" who="S0179" trans="overlap">flirt</u>
<u n="565" who="S0058">no not particularly <pause dur="short"/> I think it's because he hasn't seen her since first year <unclear/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="567" who="S0058">I think that will be a very very bad idea</u>
<u n="568" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0058">Heather is there</u>
<u n="570" who="S0179">I think that will be utterly hilarious <pause dur="short"/> they would destroy each other</u>
<u n="571" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would be a mutual black hole I think <pause dur="short"/> in all fairness though she seems much better <pause dur="short"/> like erm well as one of the comments she made when she was upset</u>
<u n="572" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="573" who="S0058">erm she was  she was  like you know I was really upset when we you know we were talking about this in a bus stop and I was like I'm crying in public <pause dur="short"/> I haven't done this since I was mentally unstable last year <pause dur="short"/> which was a you know a nice bit of er</u>
<u n="574" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0058">so she was annoyed for being <trunc>ki</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> for being kind of upset in public and doing stuff that she has doesn't do anymore <pause dur="short"/> so that was quite nice</u>
<u n="576" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="577" who="S0058">but erm yeah I suppose so</u>
<u n="578" who="S0179">right just make sure you take full opportunity with the fact she's living in your house and working underneath you to boss her about</u>
<u n="579" who="S0058">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="580" who="S0179">as in if the opportunity rises you boss</u>
<u n="581" who="S0058">oh yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> well no I I I'll decide</u>
<u n="582" who="S0179">you are actually her boss</u>
<u n="583" who="S0058">no no I am no <pause dur="short"/> entirely <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm her responsible person I believe it's known as <pause dur="short"/> erm cos she can't be manic cos she'll be she's not working</u>
<u n="584" who="S0179" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="585" who="S0058">but erm yeah no what I'm going to do is I'm not I'm going to make her think things through</u>
<u n="586" who="S0179" trans="overlap">give her all the shit jobs</u>
<u n="587" who="S0058">well actually I've got a quite a nice timetable for her but I'm I'm gonna make her think things through for herself <pause dur="short"/> as in if she asks me something I'm going to say okay <pause dur="short"/> if I give you this bit of information I want you to go and think about it and work it out for yourself <pause dur="short"/> have a go <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> just because sometimes you've got to do that at work</u>
<u n="588" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0058">and and just try and get her into that way of thinking <pause dur="short"/> I mean she might do it anyway but if she does <pause dur="short"/> if she's a little bit dependant and a little bit Sarah what do I do now? I'll and I'm what I'm going to do it will be the first half of the week I'm going to give her lots of her tasks and and then say okay so you have a few things at the end of the week sort of you know appointments <pause dur="short"/> but then in the rest of the time I want you to organise your time and complete these tasks by the end of the week</u>
<u n="590" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0058">and keep me updated on your progress and yeah <trunc>t</trunc> do <trunc>ti</trunc> time management basically <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm not going to tell you what when to do what</u>
<u n="592" who="S0179">well to fair I'm never going to start on the first thing finish it and then the next thing <pause dur="short"/> finish it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0058">well no but there there very much ongoing tasks</u>
<u n="594" who="S0179">ah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0058">and so I mean yeah some of them won't be finishable <pause dur="short"/> so I wanted to get what she feels is a reasonable amount done while also completing some tasks and having other tasks as background tasks <pause dur="short"/> same as cos that's how my work very much is <pause dur="short"/> a lot of it isn't finishable but you have to keep doing it as a back as a side task alongside other things that you need to get done for a date you know <pause dur="short"/> so I guess recognising urgency and deadlines and prioritising and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I want her to practise <pause dur="short"/> erm just all that kind of thing that she'll be able to then talk about in interviews <pause dur="short"/> erm and just have a go at doing I think is important <pause dur="short"/> having that freedom</u>
<u n="596" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I have no idea what this song is</u>
<u n="597" who="S0058">erm it's probably from that running CD</u>
<u n="598" who="S0179">yeah I I</u>
<u n="599" who="S0058">I I can't remember what it was called <pause dur="short"/> it's got Spanish in it <pause dur="short"/> is the only thing I know about it</u>
<u n="600" who="S0179">oh good <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad you've narrowed it down there</u>
<u n="601" who="S0058">erm yeah I'm quite looking forward to it</u>
<u n="602" who="S0179">oo</u>
<u n="603" who="S0058">what?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0179">the guy ahead just swerved manically</u>
<u n="605" who="S0058">I missed that <pause dur="short"/> I was watching the er motorbike <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0179">oh dear</u>
<u n="607" who="S0058">oh dear</u>
<u n="608" who="S0179">well at least we now have a washing up monkey</u>
<u n="609" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes <pause dur="short"/> now wash <pause dur="short"/> now dance <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if she's fully accepted the fact that she can't watch iPlayer or 4oD or ITV Player</u>
<u n="610" who="S0179">at least it's unwise to try</u>
<u n="611" who="S0058">hmm?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0179">at least it's unwise to try</u>
<u n="613" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="long"/> People <unclear/> don't get the whole TV thing</u>
<u n="614" who="S0179">that's a fuck ugly car</u>
<u n="615" who="S0058">horrible innit <pause dur="short"/> well it is a van it's not <trunc>e</trunc> I don't think you can even call it a car</u>
<u n="616" who="S0179">well it looks like a if you look at the sides it's actually a huge saloon car which has been added onto a top which is what amuses me</u>
<u n="617" who="S0058">it's not attractive is it</u>
<u n="618" who="S0179" trans="overlap">you see that at the back</u>
<u n="619" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah I see what you mean yeah that big bit at the back <pause dur="short"/> what make is that?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0179">Dodge</u>
<u n="621" who="S0058"><trunc>Y</trunc> okay</u>
<u n="622" who="S0179">it's American</u>
<u n="623" who="S0058">yeah I was going to say it looked kind of American in style <pause dur="short"/> big is basically what I meant by that</u>
<u n="624" who="S0179">swollen</u>
<u n="625" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah I love the fact that like in <unclear/> say even the sort of rubbish cars that all the sort of college cars are driving</u>
<u n="626" who="S0179">are huge</u>
<u n="627" who="S0058">are massive yeah <pause dur="short"/> really huge</u>
<u n="628" who="S0179">yes well super minis just don't sort of exist in the same way</u>
<u n="629" who="S0058" trans="overlap">just haven't caught on <pause dur="short"/> just imagine driving a Yaris around America <pause dur="short"/> it would be like ah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0179">use your Smart Car</u>
<u n="631" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> smart Car looks Smart Cars look weird in England so imagine what they look like in America</u>
<u n="632" who="S0179">indeed</u>
<u n="633" who="S0058">tiny and cute</u>
<u n="634" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="636" who="S0179">feeder?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0058"><trunc>F</trunc> Feeder yeah <pause dur="short"/> sounds like it's <unclear/> doing in the song <pause dur="long"/> Can't believe <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks Word Gets Around is better that Performance Cocktails <pause dur="short"/> just incorrect <pause dur="short"/> I was like I quite their first album <pause dur="short"/> I think that's cos I've cos I sort of listened to it a lot when I was on holiday when I was younger <pause dur="short"/> it was sort of one of the CDs I always had with me <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0179">oh this would be in your CD player?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0058">yeah well I had a diskman and I had a case for it that you could put six CDs in the front and zip</u>
<u n="640" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0058">so erm so yeah you could take seven away with you and so you had to pick carefully <pause dur="short"/> so I generally had Travis <pause dur="short"/> stereophonics and other miscellaneous <pause dur="short"/> pulp <pause dur="short"/> and then other miscellaneous things</u>
<u n="642" who="S0179">oh dear</u>
<u n="643" who="S0058">what?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0179"><unclear/> no rear wipers <unclear/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0058">yeah a bit unfortunate <pause dur="short"/> but then if you can't turn it off</u>
<u n="646" who="S0179">yeah I was thinking that <pause dur="long"/> Oh well <pause dur="short"/> ah TT looks weird</u>
<u n="647" who="S0058">doesn't look weird it's fine it's you know just not terribly exciting <pause dur="short"/> female driver</u>
<u n="648" who="S0179">yeah odd that</u>
<u n="649" who="S0058"><unclear/> in a white Audi TT</u>
<u n="650" who="S0179">I don't understand how men can drive fast cars <pause dur="short"/> they very girly</u>
<u n="651" who="S0058">they're quite feminine yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0179">they look nice but they're sort of <pause dur="short"/> the other thing that possibly amuses me about them <pause dur="short"/> so at work both <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have them</u>
<u n="653" who="S0058">oh right</u>
<u n="654" who="S0179">what? Ubiquitous fairly well earning women's cars then</u>
<u n="655" who="S0058" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> I was like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> and they're both sort of talking about them and it's like well it always annoys me a little bit cos neither of you I imagine can drive at all</u>
<u n="656" who="S0179">yeah they've got these</u>
<u n="657" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yet and yet you're sort of into so of like I would guarantee that I would be able to out drive you in this</u>
<u n="658" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0058">sort of wasted I guess</u>
<u n="660" who="S0179">erm the best driving I've ever seen occurred in a Nissan Micra</u>
<u n="661" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0179">it's not the car it's how it's driven</u>
<u n="663" who="S0058">but who was that?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thought so <pause dur="short"/> no exactly I agree it's entirely how it's driven <pause dur="short"/> and it helps like a good driver in a good car presumably is a thing of beauty</u>
<u n="666" who="S0179">erm to some extent but often it is so often limited by the road and the traffic conditions so yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I guess that's the Top Gear thing isn't it <pause dur="short"/> well on a track yeah it drives like that but you never ever need it to be able to do that cos</u>
<u n="668" who="S0179" trans="overlap">no what you need to be able to do is interact with traffic and read the road conditions</u>
<u n="669" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the the car needs to be suitable I guess to do that and respond quickly enough for</u>
<u n="670" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's actually bizarre I mean probably the best thing is something like er <pause dur="short"/> cos supercars are actually quite big</u>
<u n="671" who="S0058">are they?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0179">which <pause dur="short"/> yeah they're <trunc>hu</trunc> but very wide</u>
<u n="673" who="S0058">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I never really appreciated that</u>
<u n="674" who="S0179">yeah they are huge</u>
<u n="675" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh right okay <pause dur="short"/> fair enough</u>
<u n="676" who="S0179" trans="overlap">erm which makes <unclear/> quite unsuitable for a lot of road use</u>
<u n="677" who="S0058">huh</u>
<u n="678" who="S0179">I E they're not very good for driving around a town centre</u>
<u n="679" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="680" who="S0179" trans="overlap">they've got appalling turning circles there</u>
<u n="681" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> so but if on a very wide empty track <pause dur="short"/> great</u>
<u n="682" who="S0179">well on a motorway or an autobahn yes</u>
<u n="683" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I guess yeah <pause dur="short"/> for getting  For getting  from A to B in Germany <pause dur="short"/> great</u>
<u n="684" who="S0179">that's what I would really like <pause dur="short"/> the C30 Polestar <pause dur="short"/> fuck that's a good car <pause dur="short"/> they are going to produce</u>
<u n="685" who="S0058" trans="overlap">what mental engine in a very small car</u>
<u n="686" who="S0179">they're going to produce it as a rival for the M3</u>
<u n="687" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="688" who="S0179">except it's four wheel drive and more powerful and smaller and bright blue</u>
<u n="689" who="S0058" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="690" who="S0179">it's very Volvo</u>
<u n="691" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0179">it's Volvo do nutty car</u>
<u n="693" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> volvo go mental for a minute <pause dur="short"/> they don't normally do mental</u>
<u n="694" who="S0179">well it's not mental <pause dur="short"/> it's very like it clocked up some ridiculous record on the Nürburgring</u>
<u n="695" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> that's what I mean though like mentally fast and bright blue and sort of look at our stupid car</u>
<u n="696" who="S0179">but they had a feature on the record attempt in <unclear/> magazine on like it was one of Volvo's test drivers went to do it</u>
<u n="697" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="698" who="S0179">and he was basically saying that I mean cos I mean of yeah it was really interesting cos they've got like the reporter went round with him for the first few laps</u>
<u n="699" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="700" who="S0179">and he'd like never done it before but he already got like a time which experienced people doing it a 911 would have been pleased with in the first attempt</u>
<u n="701" who="S0058" trans="overlap">nice <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="702" who="S0179">in an unfamiliar car</u>
<u n="703" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0179">with a reporter on board <pause dur="short"/> and then ditched the reporter to save weight</u>
<u n="705" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> they told the reporter to chop off an appendage of his choice and throw it out of the window to save weight</u>
<u n="706" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0058">told the report to take his clothes off</u>
<u n="708" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0058">oh dear</u>
<u n="710" who="S0179">but yeah that was er</u>
<u n="711" who="S0058">no that's cool</u>
<u n="712" who="S0179">but it was interesting that he apparently just had like <unclear/> didn't have any he didn't have any sort of ego at all <pause dur="short"/> it was just a really sort of a pleasure to watch him drive</u>
<u n="713" who="S0058">what the test driver?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="716" who="S0179">he was very Swedish about the whole thing</u>
<u n="717" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> bless <pause dur="short"/> what kind of a shrug and a yes it is nice car</u>
<u n="718" who="S0179">no no <pause dur="short"/> he was just like nervous about it rather than sort of arrogant</u>
<u n="719" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="720" who="S0179">bless</u>
<u n="721" who="S0058">it is rather unfortunate the erm the CEO of Volvo being German pronounces it Wolwo <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="722" who="S0179">which is quite ironic that they know Volvo's biggest rivals are the German's</u>
<u n="723" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I guess there's maybe too much difference if it's</u>
<u n="724" who="S0179">can you open that <unclear/> do it one handed?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah sure <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0179"><unclear/> supposed to open it or <unclear/> it?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm pleased you went with that option <pause dur="long"/> Yeah er yes</u>
<u n="728" who="S0179" trans="overlap">anyway but er I</u>
<u n="729" who="S0058">I can see you being CEO of Volvo</u>
<u n="730" who="S0179">I can't</u>
<u n="731" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="732" who="S0179">I can see me being chief engineer</u>
<u n="733" who="S0058">ah true yes <pause dur="short"/> I can see you being chief engineer until you get to sort of retirement sort of time <pause dur="short"/> I E about thirty-five and then er thinking oh I'll be CEO for a year or two just you know</u>
<u n="734" who="S0179">they wouldn't pay you very well</u>
<u n="735" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0179">I have seriously considered working for them though</u>
<u n="737" who="S0058"><trunc>Pro</trunc> you mean with engineers they don't pay very well?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0179">well no I am <pause dur="short"/> yeah unfortunately I wouldn't be paid brilliantly unless you get to the <unclear/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0058" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="740" who="S0179">I I have seriously considered working for them but I think you have to be really quite good</u>
<u n="741" who="S0058">yeah oh I'm sure you would really love it <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> but would you need to move to Sweden? Presumably</u>
<u n="742" who="S0179">erm not necessarily although probably <pause dur="short"/> or Germany or China actually</u>
<u n="743" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> have you not?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0179">well I have objections to living in China</u>
<u n="745" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0179">mainly because they actually you know kill people</u>
<u n="747" who="S0058">do they? <unclear/> human rights objections <pause dur="short"/> not just like I don't like the food or you know <pause dur="short"/> with what the climate <pause dur="short"/> a slightly more serious objection <pause dur="short"/> their record on human rights <pause dur="short"/> not so good</u>
<u n="748" who="S0179">no <pause dur="short"/> in fact they are a er still a  one party  one party politically controlled state</u>
<u n="749" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> with a insane death penalty record</u>
<u n="750" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> record being the word</u>
<u n="751" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got some good news and some bad news <pause dur="short"/> the good news is you've got a world record <pause dur="short"/> the bad news is</u>
<u n="752" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="753" who="S0058">everyone hates you for it</u>
<u n="754" who="S0179">well it does raise questions as to what can the state do? Because <unclear/> the concept of war crime which I always thinks interesting right so but you're killing each other anyway <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="755" who="S0058">you mean the idea that that</u>
<u n="756" who="S0179">well the Geneva Convention sets out which a lot of countries signed up to <pause dur="short"/> so even during war there are rules</u>
<u n="757" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="758" who="S0179">which I find a very strange idea</u>
<u n="759" who="S0058">that's bizarre isn't it <pause dur="short"/> so you're allowed to kill each other but not too much <pause dur="short"/> not too effectively</u>
<u n="760" who="S0179">well no so for example when you capture an enemy soldier you're obliged to  you're obliged to  look after him <pause dur="short"/> you have to feed him and house him and look after his well being</u>
<u n="761" who="S0058" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="762" who="S0179">you've but he also wasn't obliged to to reveal anything other than his name rank and serial number</u>
<u n="763" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="764" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="765" who="S0058">and presumably torture is</u>
<u n="766" who="S0179">yeah specifically if if it's torture</u>
<u n="767" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="769" who="S0058">interrogation no though presumably</u>
<u n="770" who="S0179">no in generally <unclear/> interrogate</u>
<u n="771" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0179">er it's a widely ignored now because there aren't any they don't have conventional wars</u>
<u n="773" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0179">but the last time two sides with equivalent two Western armies <pause dur="short"/> well two Western <unclear/> armies with equivalent strength fought each other was Korea</u>
<u n="775" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="776" who="S0179">and that was in the fifties</u>
<u n="777" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="778" who="S0179">it just doesn't happen anymore</u>
<u n="779" who="S0058">yeah it's interesting</u>
<u n="780" who="S0179">it's funny when in this country how the NHS is like the third biggest employer of the world after the Chinese army and the American army</u>
<u n="781" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> huh was the American army second? I I remember reading that</u>
<u n="782" who="S0179">well the American Department of Defense <pause dur="short"/> so all of the American armed services</u>
<u n="783" who="S0058" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> right yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty massive then</u>
<u n="784" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I like I saw something about the Indian army and it just looks so impressive</u>
<u n="785" who="S0058">yeah?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0179">I mean their dress uniforms are lovely</u>
<u n="787" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="788" who="S0179">they're really smart</u>
<u n="789" who="S0058">I don't know anything about it really <pause dur="short"/> cos they're not particularly often kind of out and about <pause dur="short"/> right okay</u>
<u n="790" who="S0179">well you see that's my kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> I'm reading <trunc>g</trunc> no sorry I saw a little advert about India is now sort of emerging gradually as a sort of global superpower</u>
<u n="791" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0179">economically</u>
<u n="793" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0179">er as in it's almost on a route to overtake China</u>
<u n="795" who="S0058">is it?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0179">yeah possibly because it's huge</u>
<u n="797" who="S0058">India yeah yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0179" trans="overlap">and and you you I I  you'd actually much prefer it to China</u>
<u n="799" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I mean I think it's very corrupt in India</u>
<u n="800" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0058">and there are serious problems with erm kind of caste type issues</u>
<u n="802" who="S0179" trans="overlap">massive wealth inequality <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0058">erm but yeah it's probably better than China</u>
<u n="804" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but to be fair it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="805" who="S0058" trans="overlap">er I don't know with India I kind of feel I can talk</u>
<u n="806" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and bearing in mind this is a  state</u>
<u n="807" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="808" who="S0179">but it still seems to be doing quite well for itself as in there's no sort of er er extremist religious groups <pause dur="short"/> well there's a few anyway</u>
<u n="809" who="S0058">yeah I mean I'm sure there are problems but less <trunc>ri</trunc> you know less extreme than so many other countries <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0179">but you look at sort of <unclear/> discrimination <pause dur="short"/> america much</u>
<u n="811" who="S0058">well quite yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean that's the thing I think it from what I've read about it there's still a lot of corruption erm which but I mean it's true of a lot of countries <pause dur="short"/> and yeah <unclear/> but yeah I mean hey <pause dur="short"/> like you said America much</u>
<u n="812" who="S0179">they no longer <pause dur="short"/> you know they don't have a death penalty now which you know in certain countries <unclear/> knocks them up quite a few notches</u>
<u n="813" who="S0058">yeah as far as I'm concerned yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0179">oo he's not going to like that much <pause dur="long"/> And we're coming off soonish <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> comfy in a bed situation</u>
<u n="815" who="S0058">right <pause dur="long"/> I mean it services are twelve miles is out <pause dur="short"/> oh no so we're coming off so that's not ours is it</u>
<u n="816" who="S0179">exactly <pause dur="short"/> I've no idea what that is</u>
<u n="817" who="S0058">what? Oh right <pause dur="short"/> I know it's <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> I've no idea</u>
<u n="818" who="S0179">that BMWs were behaving itself</u>
<u n="819" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Are you surprised?</u>
<u n="820" who="S0179">very <pause dur="short"/> to be fair in my situation I wouldn't be doing that <pause dur="short"/> as in it's determining not overtaking but actually there was a gap and it's not overtaking so I'm going to assume it wants to go slowly for a while</u>
<u n="821" who="S0058" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0179">it might be nearly out of fuel</u>
<u n="823" who="S0058">yeah true <pause dur="short"/> maybe <pause dur="long"/> Ah it still isn't completely it's as though it's quite hazy</u>
<u n="824" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0058">it hasn't gone through completely <pause dur="short"/> it might be a nice view up on <unclear/></u>
<u n="826" who="S0179">to be fair yeah <pause dur="short"/>  but it's just sort of a bit close</u>
<u n="827" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if erm Snow White and the Huntsman's out yet</u>
<u n="828" who="S0179">oh well there's a new trailer out for it so</u>
<u n="829" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> cos there's two come out <pause dur="short"/> there's Snow White and the Huntsman and there's the er Mirror Mirror</u>
<u n="830" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0058">and I wouldn't mind seeing Snow White and the Huntsman now but I'm not sure about the other one</u>
<u n="832" who="S0179">oh dear</u>
<u n="833" who="S0058">why?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0179"><unclear/> just a bit  and it's very busy</u>
<u n="835" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0179">so you see that TT <pause dur="short"/> the spoiler on the back it only comes up at over a certain speed</u>
<u n="837" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh clever <pause dur="short"/> this is The Chemical Brothers yeah?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0179">no idea</u>
<u n="839" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="840" who="S0179">it's a song that was out a rather iconic song from the first Bourne film</u>
<u n="841" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="842" who="S0179">which I don't think you've seen all of</u>
<u n="843" who="S0058">erm <pause dur="short"/> I've seen most of the first one I think <pause dur="short"/> I think I've seen all of it</u>
<u n="844" who="S0179">do you remember <unclear/> driving around Paris at high speed in a mini?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0058">yeah right <pause dur="short"/> I've seen all all that <pause dur="short"/> is there a floppy disk at one point? <unclear/> floppy disk</u>
<u n="846" who="S0179">no that's Mission Impossible</u>
<u n="847" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="848" who="S0179">Doh</u>
<u n="849" who="S0058">Doh <pause dur="short"/> yeah there's a there is some kind of weird room and there's a a disk <pause dur="short"/> oh that's Mission Impossible okay fair enough <pause dur="short"/> in that case Bourne <pause dur="short"/> I've seen</u>
<u n="850" who="S0179" trans="overlap">that's definitely Mission Impossible One</u>
<u n="851" who="S0058">yeah ok <pause dur="short"/> so I've seen</u>
<u n="852" who="S0179">you nitwit</u>
<u n="853" who="S0058">I've seen the bit where they're driving around Paris in the mini yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="855" who="S0058">and for the beginning where he's got the little erm sort of thing in him I've seen</u>
<u n="856" who="S0179">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> are all films just the same to you?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0058">some films are yeah <pause dur="short"/> not all films <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0179">I'm holding position in lane two in anticipation of a lane merging in</u>
<u n="859" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="860" who="S0179"></u>
<u n="861" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0179">better not get over to lane one to take the vehicle in</u>
<u n="863" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="864" who="S0179">beautiful</u>
<u n="865" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Nice timing</u>
<u n="866" who="S0179">well it was so well planned I didn't even need to signal</u>
<u n="867" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="868" who="S0179">oo</u>
<u n="869" who="S0058">oo my God</u>
<u n="870" who="S0179">fuck</u>
<u n="871" who="S0058">fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="872" who="S0179">see if I was that car I'd now be giving him a lot of leeway</u>
<u n="873" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you don't want to be anywhere that <pause dur="short"/> god</u>
<u n="874" who="S0179">pretty much <pause dur="long"/> Oh dear</u>
<u n="875" who="S0058">what? <unclear/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0179"><unclear/> when I'm driving</u>
<u n="877" who="S0058">Good <pause dur="short"/> there we are A303 <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="878" who="S0179">I'm just continuing at this speed to make sure we get past this chap before we drop down</u>
<u n="879" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="880" who="S0179">into the services</u>
<u n="881" who="S0058">but oh alright yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> services two thirds of a mile</u>
<u n="883" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0179">be there in thirty-five seconds</u>
<u n="885" who="S0058">nice</u>
<u n="886" who="S0179">no it's true</u>
<u n="887" who="S0058">true it is</u>
<u n="888" who="S0179">your ad here</u>
<u n="889" who="S0058">hmm</u>
<u n="890" who="S0179">thinking of units in thirty seconds erm circuits Wednesday</u>
<u n="891" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="892" who="S0179">which I'm really looking forward to if they've changed the format</u>
<u n="893" who="S0058">yeah it was good actually erm</u>
<u n="894" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="895" who="S0058">I hope he does do it like that again it was  it was  good</u>
<u n="896" who="S0179">but erm but we still do it so we can do it in groups of three don't we?</u>
<u n="897" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0058">are you thinking all three of us going around together?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0179">well it broadly makes the most sense <unclear/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0058" trans="overlap">in all fairness I mean there wasn't any need to last time <pause dur="short"/> I was by myself and there was another couple of guys by themselves and the rest were in twos <pause dur="short"/> as in there was no need for a three but I guess you could do</u>
<u n="902" who="S0179">but er is there anyway through there we can get into?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="904" who="S0179">not so much is there</u>
<u n="905" who="S0058">he's no <pause dur="short"/> he just parked in the last one</u>
<u n="906" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> oh <unclear/> Shh it's fine</u>
<u n="907" who="S0058">no one will know</u>
<u n="908" who="S0179">we're loyal customers</u>
<u n="909" who="S0058">what of Little Chef?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0058">not so much <pause dur="short"/> ah it's all good <pause dur="short"/> I've been to Little Chef before</u>
<u n="912" who="S0179">exactly</u>
<u n="913" who="S0058">have you been to Little Chef before?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0179">we're just not regular customers</u>
<u n="915" who="S0058">yeah loyal very loyal <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't eat at <trunc>an</trunc> any other motorway</u>
</body>
</text>
