<text id="SCYY">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:50</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Plants, fashion, finance, Donald Trump, politics, pasties</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking in the pub</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<event desc="sound of background"/>
<u n="1" who="S0115">you killed the Jesus plant</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">I can't believe it's come back to life</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's quite kind of just like</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">it's so good like I never thought that it would <pause dur="short"/> but actually like when I um when I got it from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she said that cos she brought loads in to work <pause dur="short"/> oh thank you <pause dur="short"/> she brought loads in to work and um she said oh actually um it had been on my windowsill in my dining room and I'd forgotten about it <pause dur="short"/> and I just looked at it and it was really like like she said but it had loads of little shoots <pause dur="short"/> so I picked off all the little shoots and put them in smaller little tubs <pause dur="short"/> cos you know we got in a tiny tub <pause dur="short"/> and um and she said oh and I just thought oh they might grow <pause dur="short"/> so maybe they just do come back to life <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe the dramatic change though</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah but you so you said that she like the main one was brown but she picked off the shoots</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think her plant came back like I think it just started again</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it must've just been uh thirsty</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dry yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">that that's all um that that's the only</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">but it's but some plants though once they go past that point of no return</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">yeah yeah definitely I mean you you have that one with the</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like I think the chillis one</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">what was it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">which one?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115">yeah the one</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">ah the peace lily</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115">that we overwatered</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> liberal use of we there</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> to be honest I think it was just a really fussy plant</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a peace lily and it's so massive now</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115">ah <pause dur="short"/> why don't we get another one it uh how much was it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037">maybe <pause dur="short"/> they were on offer <pause dur="short"/> I bought two for a fiver in Marxies <pause dur="short"/> I've got one on me desk still <pause dur="short"/> I've like a like like uh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115" trans="overlap">hm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037">like a <trunc>l</trunc> like a sort of just a green one with like leafy things <pause dur="short"/> it's quite nice <pause dur="short"/> doesn't have flowers <pause dur="short"/> although I I kind of didn't water it it's bad cos Sarah kept really good care of it while I was away over Christmas you know before your birthday and that <pause dur="short"/> and it was lovely and then I I dunno where it what happened but I just sort of totally neglected it and like it's like the crispiest plant in town <pause dur="short"/> it's like <event desc="sound of crunching"/> every time I go near it <pause dur="short"/> think it's dead</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">ah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">maybe it'll come back to life</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean there some of some plants I think take a lot of uh effort so um but um</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">as for like you know a lot of the hot ones like oranges that you would need to grow in a greenhouse or something uh</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115">there's <pause dur="short"/> we haven't got much space so we can't really like have a an orange tree or anything</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I fancy getting one of those like you know have you seen those kind of removable one? Like greenhouses I mean like they're sort of it's like a shelf it's like a shelving unit but it's got like plastic over</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">uh yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037" trans="overlap">can get them from B and Q <pause dur="short"/> I fancy getting one of them</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">they're only about twenty quid I think <pause dur="short"/> think me dad was saying</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">how how high is it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037">um I think about as high as you are</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">where do we put it?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">in the back <pause dur="short"/> I dunno like behind the bike in the corner or something</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the back garden?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">dunno</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">ah it's a north facing  north facing  garden</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know it is <pause dur="short"/> it's not as good as it could be</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah d'you know what me leggings like <pause dur="short"/> some of them are</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">what's your <trunc>har</trunc> what's your thoughts on leggings?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">I <pause dur="short"/> d'you I don't  I don't  really <pause dur="short"/> it depends I mean <pause dur="short"/> like in principle uh I don't see why you should hate any type of clothing but uh</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well no <pause dur="short"/> I know what you mean</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but uh <pause dur="short"/> it's a certain just you mean ones that look like the the eighties?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">well they all kinda look a bit eighties I suppose but</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">but I think we used to wear stuff like that you know in Shakespearean sort times?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">well yes the legging I suppose doesn't have its routes directly in the eighties although the advent of Lycra might've</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">Cos you see like you know like like</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">yeah what were they called again then? Like uh knickerbockers and that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115" trans="overlap">men in tights sort of thing</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">or Robin Hood Men <trunc>In</trunc></u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">you know like <trunc>me</trunc> men in tights like</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've never seen that you know</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115" trans="overlap">basically they were knitted like</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've never even seen</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">they knitted them uh they knitted them sorts of</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">uh well I mean they're called</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037">well woolly tights still are the best like <pause dur="short"/> my best</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115" trans="overlap">think I was</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">my best pair of woolly tights were the ones that I had on like them grey ones <pause dur="short"/> they're the nicest warmest ones I had and I just ripped them to shreds when I fell off me bike that time <pause dur="short"/> like the donkey that I am</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so that uh bike thing uh</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">never mind</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">yeah there was <pause dur="short"/> it was a  it was a</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">stupid thing?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">silly silly accident wasn't it?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">well I yo know like the bike man when I told him about it like you know he he screwed my lamp on like so it's fixed like it doesn't move a centimetre</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">yeah?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">and I I never turn it off either <pause dur="short"/> I just cycle in the summer with me <trunc>ligh</trunc> lamp on I'm not bothered <pause dur="short"/> I just think I'll just leave it <pause dur="short"/> it's just working all the time I don't need to bother with it <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a dynamo so</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">I never turn it off</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">no? Oh I I suppose you don't need to do you if it's a dynamo</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> though if you have your lights on <pause dur="short"/> like if you're driving a car with your lights on I mean yes maybe it's flattening your batter but driving your  driving your  bike with your lights on is not doing anything is it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">alright</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">but yeah I'm not a big fan of the <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I think they look nice on some people but for example I would never wear a legging in public</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">well like I weren't those ones that you were talking about then uh worn in conjunction with something else?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037">they were <pause dur="short"/> they were <pause dur="short"/> there's there's a few unusual outfit choices in here tonight</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">not not long ago um people used to wear like uh one piece uh leggings and dress combo</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I was  I was  gonna say d'you ever remember those? Maybe you don't <pause dur="short"/> early nineties trouser skirt combos?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and and a dress looked like uh uh</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">did you ever have you ever see those? They were really weird</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>n</trunc> no I was talking about the ones that are just like</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">maybe like five or six or seven years ago</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">which ones?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">yeah it was a one piece leggings and dress combo</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> really?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like a uh</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like a you mean like a cat suit?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">or a long top</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">that's what that that girl had on like a long top and leggings</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no no no uh <pause dur="short"/> no the the the dress part would have like it was like a lava lamp pattern on it</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115">or a big floral pattern <pause dur="short"/> but it would like uh uh a tight dress but it with leggings like</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">underneath?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">and they'd be like part of the same thing</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">were they attached though or did you just seem them in conjunction with each other? Did you ever explore the attachment issues?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like did we use to? No I think they were I mean</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0115">people just</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">maybe they weren't man <pause dur="short"/> maybe they were just</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh I could explore the attachment issues like how could I have done that? Uh</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you you know</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">well I um <pause dur="short"/> no um they <pause dur="short"/> no some people used to wear them in Lancaster like uh like someone from</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but that doesn't mean they were attached</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">where I used to work in <pause dur="short"/> no I I just thought like well</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">like</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">no but people used to like the sort of seemed like they went together anyway I mean even if they weren't attached so that you you could only wear the two parts with each you couldn't wear them with <trunc>anyth</trunc> anything else</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure if I follow but yes</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you don't  you don't  remember those things then?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">not not <pause dur="short"/> did Curry Girl wear them?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">yeah I think maybe actually uh</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">although</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">I don't think they were attached you know</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">I'm not  I'm not  sure about her like like <pause dur="short"/> but there there were quite a few people who wore them but but they were very  they were very  brief fashion</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've never been a <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">but they they didn't last long</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">I've never been a fan of  a fan of  the legging really <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm mentally scared from when I was like nine years old <pause dur="short"/> and uh me mam bought us some candy stripe leggings <pause dur="short"/> I suppose obviously not not being a girl in the nineties you won't necessarily remember this <pause dur="short"/> equally as much as you won't remember like the head bands with your name like <trunc>gl</trunc> glitter penned on</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">wasn't that eighties?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">well you know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115" trans="overlap">early nineties</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">well I was you know I was only seven in the end of the eighties so</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">nineties really early nineties</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">so you didn't like the visor?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">but me <pause dur="short"/> I like  I like  a visor <pause dur="short"/> and ur um <pause dur="short"/> I've got well you've seen</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you do like visors?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">you've seen like that <trunc>f</trunc> picture of me and our Tom and I've got like a a visor and like a a dayglo like green sort of dress on <pause dur="short"/> and Tom's got like a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles two-piece on <pause dur="short"/> it's like</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah it's awful <pause dur="short"/> I mean just</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">well it's just the styles isn't it? We'll probably look back at pictures our of ourselves now and be like oh my god why did I think X Y and Z looked nice? Like <pause dur="short"/> you'd be like look at that shirt I was wearing <pause dur="short"/> look at my beard and all this</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos I look back  I look back  at now and my pictures of my dad</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I just wear like like ordinary cotton shirts <pause dur="short"/> these have been  these have been  acceptable for like three hundred years or something</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah you do <pause dur="short"/> I know but it'll be like oh my god I can't believe I wore it tucked out or you know? I dunno there'll be something won't there? Or it'll be won't it? It'll be your hair and your beard won't it like?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> I think people should just wear the same stuff like all the time</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037" trans="overlap">forever</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">but it'll be  it'll be  your hair and your beard cos that's what changes when you're a man isn't it like?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it should should there's no reason why you shouldn't just keep to the</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">but you actually you're right like though</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but mind you having having said that I do wear denim trousers not um</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">denim trousers that sounds like not jeans</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">denim based trousers</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">I do wear denim denim trousers</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> you can't have denim trousers that aren't jeans can you?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">yes you can</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">can you?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">you could have like chinos made out of denim like a</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">those would be jeans though wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like a <pause dur="short"/> no but like <pause dur="short"/> jeans means a certain thing</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">why are they called jeans anyway? Is it to do with some French guy?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't know actually I was about it's talk about Nimes but then I remembered that was denim not jeans</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115">un no surely any trouser made of denim is a  is a  jean</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">I don't think that's the case</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115">uh no I I wouldn't think of <pause dur="short"/> anyway but uh that's not like <pause dur="short"/> I mean this isn't</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">yeah but when you think of jeans</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I wasn't that wasn't  that wasn't  my point <pause dur="short"/> my point was uh like <trunc>y</trunc> you know if if if you wanted to keep</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like if you see granddads in jeans they're definitely more of a denim trouser than a jean aren't they?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you were to genuinely have like <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">if you see like a grandda in like a grandda jean that's definitely more a denim trouser than a jean</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">I haven't seen a grandda in denim <pause dur="short"/> I've seen a grandda in <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean like not no no no my grandfathers that are both dead no they would not have worn jeans they would've they they wore like what I  what I  was talking about like uh uh cotton slacks</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't really imagine they were <pause dur="short"/> chinos? Like a chino? Like a chino yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">what is a chino?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">well is is it not like a brand of cotton slack? Oh actually I think it's a cut <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a  it's a  certain cut cut of trouser</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sounds um specific</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037" trans="overlap">um</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">no I just mean like</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">I bet your cousins like a chino</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">does your your um? No no no it's not chino I mean you're using like a silly word to refer to like like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or a corduroy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">used to be like <trunc>trou</trunc> most trousers are supposed to be like that aren't they? Well they were</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like a dress trouser?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115" trans="overlap">until until we all went mental about jeans like <pause dur="short"/> everyone was wore these uh cotton ones</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like a dress trouser yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">but then actually over history obviously trousers have changed and actually used to have those we were talking about the legging type ones you know the like Robin Hood Men In Tights sort of type ones that the uh Shakespearean</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like a pantaloon?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">them sort of Shakespearean tight trousers they used to wear I mean</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like a pantaloon?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">and them ones with like the long johns and like uh big socks</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">like a drop watch?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">you know like Georgian like <pause dur="short"/> so I mean</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">and then you've got like the um the MC Hammer</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think that's that's cool <pause dur="short"/> if they just did</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">I was playing  I was playing  you know Draw Me you know the the app the game Draw Me?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">I was playing Draw Me the other day and I got MC Hammer <pause dur="short"/> and it was for  it was for  Emma and so I draw I drew like this guy with like a hat on and then like these massive trousers and like coloured them in all jazzy colours and wrote Can't touch this <pause dur="short"/> so that was MC Hammer pants I really know that</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well no you can't write words that's cheating</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">yeah you can a bit <pause dur="short"/> a few ones</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">I don't think you can write words um</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">my cousin Ross is really bad at it <pause dur="short"/> he just writes no idea then writes the word and I'm like yeah fine</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">fair enough</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">his spelling's really bad</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">well I I I got I just to be honest like I would write like this game is pointless</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the other day he got um Vikings <pause dur="short"/> ay</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um and then like bye um something</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it is fun <pause dur="short"/> it is funny <pause dur="short"/> like the other day I got Vikings and I drew like um like a helmet like that and then with the you know like the nosepiece</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">uh that wasn't Vikings was it?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">no wait <pause dur="short"/> I drew the helmet like that and then  and then  the nosepiece like that I thought I looked more <pause dur="short"/> that just looks like any hat doesn't it? And then I drew two eyes and then I</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115" trans="overlap">any hat with a nosepiece?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">no but if I just drew a hat like that it could be like a bobble hat I I wanted to make it look like it was a warrior or something</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">so he typed in knight</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">well they but their their hats are distinctive so that that</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037" trans="overlap">wait <pause dur="short"/> so anyway he he typed in knight and then I drew like  and then I drew like  a massive beard and like an angry eyebrows and then started typing in Vikings and then I drew the horns on <pause dur="short"/> and it took him so long to spell it <pause dur="short"/> he was like V I E K <pause dur="short"/> no no no no V <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh my god</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so so some uh someone's learned something then haven't they?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">he's learned how to spell</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037" trans="overlap">spelling was really bad though</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">you've learned how to draw a Viking</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">well I knew how already</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the game has a point</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">it's just an <trunc>in</trunc> it's just like a daft little game like</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I I did a couple of ones yesterday didn't I?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">uh but since they were drawn on top of something else that meant that it wasn't quite the same as as like a computer game</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">so so I was drawing them on the chocolate bar so</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">on the wrapper not on the chocolate bar that sounds wrong</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah no no no <trunc>dire</trunc> not directly on the chocolate bar <unclear/> so yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">anyway sorry I've distracted you from your trouser discussion</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> but well um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah so yeah <trunc>trou</trunc> trousers I mean <pause dur="short"/> people have worn like strange ones over the years and I suppose if you go really back then everyone would sort wear a sort of Jesus outfit wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">yeah like frocks really</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">I don't know if Jesus wore what wore a frock if that's what like</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well the Romans had like the old toga they like they preferred a a bit of blowing in the breeze</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean in in the hotter countries they would wear sort of think sort of toga thing</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so like did um you know like a toga so did they wear like undercrackers under their toga?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh I don't know um <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to go on like you know</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I bet there's a PhD on that</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">well many uh <pause dur="short"/> no I I did did they yeah they probably had like some kind of like long long john thing or</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and women as well I often wonder that like <pause dur="short"/> when did women start wearing bras like?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">oh um yeah well I well I mean whether they <pause dur="short"/> did they not have like a variation of it in um?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">well <trunc>y</trunc> you know  you know  in</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">did uh like?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">well the <trunc>Victori</trunc> um Elizabethans loved all that kind of repressed strap everything in</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115" trans="overlap">elizabethans?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">well yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> well actually they had the wenches didn't they? I mean there was you see those that I mean from the paintings and all</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">well I think they had like <trunc>cor</trunc> corsetry didn't they?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right I mean <pause dur="short"/> didn't they what did they uh the Elizabethans cos that? Oh are they the ones that look like that like pull them themselves into ridiculously tight corsets?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037" trans="overlap">corsetry yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well actually that that that came well the whole corsetry uh thing was was popular for a long time really I mean <pause dur="short"/> in the Elizabethans yes it was all very trussed up like the big the roughs and the uh for the men like the tiny the waist tiny waist but</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah the men  the men  were quite trussed up as well I think weren't they?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">but also but especially like in the Victorians the whole corsetry really came back again <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it <trunc>w</trunc> actually went away <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure of what happened in like the seventeen hundreds <pause dur="short"/> You know in terms of that but <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">so where where are we? In?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">so like the <trunc>si</trunc> you know the sixteen hundreds Elizabethans I mean they were definitely like <pause dur="short"/> certainly the upper classes</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the <trunc>f</trunc> the fifteen hundreds?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">sorry the <trunc>f</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well no actually</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you've skipped out the sixteen hundreds there the uh the the <trunc>s</trunc> sort of Oliver Cromwell period</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">yeah well probably anything goes then <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ri</trunc> probably burning the corsets</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh no no I don't  I don't  think they had much uh that many fashion innovations in England in that in those days like</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well how would we know I mean?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115"><trunc>Fra</trunc> France was having a good time like with uh Louis The Fourteenth but uh</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think <trunc>y</trunc> they always had uh</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but uh we we were having a civil war and and like our country's a real uh in a bit of a mess at that time <pause dur="short"/> the sixteen hundreds</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037">but I think it's a sort of the same now isn't it like people who got money always have</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and that's reflected in their trousers</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">people who've got money always buy themselves nice stuff like</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the best trousers uh available</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the best trousers in town yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to see sort of a survey of the richest people and and like have that sort of like as a function of like trouser type</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what now?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">like</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">yeah well now</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115" trans="overlap">trouser like wealth wealth to trouser type</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they'd go down  they'd go down  Ede And Ravenscroft wouldn't they and get themselves a like Rupert The Bear</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">yeah in Britain maybe but like <trunc>y</trunc> but who's the wealthiest person in the world? Bill Gates?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037">probably some Saudi prince is it not?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think Bill Gates wears cotton slacks <pause dur="short"/> carlos Slim</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I was reading a thing about um <pause dur="short"/> I was reading a thing about</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean Sultan of Brunei well he definitely has some funds like</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">I was reading a thing about British industry and um apparently one of the most uh one of the British one of the companies in Britain that turned the biggest profit last year was this company in I think it was Sheffield or Nottingham one of those kind of <trunc>mi</trunc> midlandsy</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">you mean the biggest export profit?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> was anyway I think it was Nottingham or Sheffield I can't remember which <pause dur="short"/> and um basically they'd you know those uh Airbus Airbus planes?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">yeah they're French aren't they?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">the French Airbus planes so those are planes that have got like two two double decker planes you know? It's like a total like giant like super giant plane</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037">anyway some Saudi prince has bought an Airbus for himself from the French company who make Airbus</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">yeah?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">and had it customized so that it includes for example a Turkish bath double you know queen-size bedrooms</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">so if he needs if he wants a Turkish bath like he might</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037" trans="overlap">A swimming pool conference room</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">if if he if his own Turkish bath was broken then he'd have to get in his plane and fly it just so he could use a Turkish bath?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">well he could just probably use while it wasn't flying</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">he'd have to fly it like round round the block or something</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">aye</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">come back up like on his uh</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I think he could probably use it when he wasn't flying <pause dur="short"/> but basically this kind of basically like you know like they do on cruise ships where it's like just opulence?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah well uh I don't think it would be the same uh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">and it's things like solid marble <pause dur="short"/> this that and the other</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">but anyway this company in</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <trunc>e</trunc> everyone likes opulence</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">this company in Nottingham or Derby or where Sheffield or something has been doing that <pause dur="short"/> and they were saying so anyway I <trunc>w</trunc> this thing I was reading with was on about this like customization of like jumbo planes and stuff and <pause dur="short"/> apparently like Donald Trump obviously has got like a Boeing Seven whatever Seven Five Seven or Seven Three Seven or something <pause dur="short"/> some big plane <pause dur="short"/> and he's had like all of his replaced with like massive luxury seats with the Trump family crest like sown into everything and gold everywhere and</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">well he's got a gold statue of himself hasn't he I mean</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">well I went in</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">that man's achieved a lot but he's he's also made himself look extraordinarily vain and uh greedy</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that hairdo <pause dur="short"/> oh his hair's so bad <pause dur="short"/> but in New York I went in</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> that's funny though isn't it like?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">I went in Trump Towers in New York it's just off Central Park <pause dur="short"/> not very far off Fifth Avenue</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you see the the gold Donald Trump?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's literally just marble and <trunc>g</trunc> I didn't see the golden Donald Trump but it's like gold and marble everywhere like <pause dur="short"/> everything's just <pause dur="short"/> like they have water running everywhere so that everything kind of glitters <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> Trump Trump Towers is like the first three floors I think are like shopping shopping and dining experiences they call it but I just went up the <trunc>e</trunc> like elevator <pause dur="short"/> elevator? Went up the elevator and walked around</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">the?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">the <trunc>l</trunc> the escalator</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the escalator</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">aye <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>wal</trunc> I went up there and walked around and just came down <pause dur="short"/> the security guards were like eyeballing us cos obviously I was like some like scruffpot just tramping around New York on me tod</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">well but he's quite scruffy himself isn't he?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> ugh a fly um</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">maybe just just on the top of his head</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">A what a fly</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">his hair's quite scruffy isn't it?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">oh it's awful</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's like a hair combover</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that sort of like honey coloured <pause dur="short"/> that sort of horrible like beery coloured hair that he's got</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">oh it's really bad</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">it's like partly partly yellow and partly white or?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">Brown yeah like</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">it's like uh a dog weed in the snow</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">aww it's bad it's really bad</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">no uh <pause dur="short"/> he he started The Apprentice sort of didn't he?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">he was the first no I don't know if it was his idea but yes</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so so it's like I watched uh his one before the English one started</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">have you watched any of it this time?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> uh has it started yet? It hasn't started</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">yeah yeah it's like week three now or next time</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115">I've been watching I guess I've been watching the football instead or just not watching</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I was out I I was knitting wasn't I last time?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">yeah and I  and I  was uh working and uh</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037">I just thought that like</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and then before that uh you weren't there and then before that</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wasn't started then</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I dunno but <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">I've just got it in me head like you know when we saw that clip when he was like he says bloody and bleeding so many times <pause dur="short"/> I had it in</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0037">well I had it in <pause dur="short"/> I like all like my favourite thing about The Apprentice like those lines that have so obviously been scripted and he tries to like slot them in</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well well all of them have that</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037">well no <trunc>obvious</trunc></u>
<u n="351" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's a shambles a total bloody shambles</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and he's like you couldn't even organize <pause dur="short"/> You know like those kind of like analogy ones</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">no no some of them are  some of them are  good though like</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037">but actually the um</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115">there are um</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037">actually the um <pause dur="short"/> what are they called? The <trunc>l</trunc> what are them brothers called? The thingybob brothers? On YouTube?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115">the Boleg Boleg Brothers</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what are they called? The Boleg Brothers like <pause dur="short"/> they're really good</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115">I remember them yeah yeah uh</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037">with the Lego animations</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115" trans="overlap">with the and the they used to get banged on the head with a pan</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037">like bong on the frying pan <pause dur="short"/> I I should look them up Boleg Brothers</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah the Lego Boleg Lego stuff yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was uh and they used to take his words and uh reedit them so that like they sort of satirized it</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> and Margaret always had like real Playmobil hair you know? Did you ever have Playmobil?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I um <pause dur="short"/> actually I saw her last night on some show</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">Margaret Mountford?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> well I I watched uh The Daily the This Week with uh Andrew Neil or whatever his name is</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh he's awful</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115">and uh</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037">oh god did you see that thing where <trunc>h</trunc> a picture of himself?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I know  I know  that he's  that he's  got uh he's got like uh he's got a gym and he's got uh yeah like a treadmill  a treadmill  and uh and a <trunc>ph</trunc> and a photo of himself in front of the treadmill</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's bad it's so bad</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so that's what he  that's what he  watches when he when he's in his on his treadmill <pause dur="short"/> he's like this is what I was this is what I will be</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">oh he's horrible</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115">or something and uh <pause dur="short"/> and I mean I I dunno if he actually like he he</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037">I dunno I find him really like oily you know what I mean? Kinda like</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115">his hair's an interesting sort of shade of you know biscuit isn't it like?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037">biscuit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">he's he's biscuit haired like</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">I like that <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>e</trunc> I thought he was more gingery like or is that just my imagination like</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">certainly some kind of biscuit</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037">I imagine him in me mind's eye</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>gin</trunc> ginger biscuit coloured quite like like a orangey</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037" trans="overlap">did you ever you know like this this is a seasonal reference here like</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">did you ever do at school where you had to take a boiled egg in and like decorate it? You know like as something like it could be like Santa Claus or like</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115"><trunc>May</trunc> maybe when I was very young</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the Easter Bunny or like a person</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037">no you must've done that like I did that all through school <pause dur="short"/> like Michael Jackson or something</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well they they really uh they really teach you a lot of stuff don't they?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037" trans="overlap">me dad  me dad  was really good at it <pause dur="short"/> me dad uh made some really good ones but anyway</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sorry I thought school was about like learning and that</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037">no it <trunc>wa</trunc> it is but it's just like an art crafty thing</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037">but anyway um <pause dur="short"/> when I think of Andrew Neil I just think of him as like a massive egg with just like his little face like as a little sticker on the top like</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">well he he's got quite big ears actually</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">I never really thought about that <pause dur="short"/> I just think about him like an egg</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115">well yeah um so uh in in his own Michael Portillo obviously and uh uh Alan Johnson was on uh yesterday</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037">uh from Lancaster?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115">no he's not from Lancaster</u>
<u n="402" who="S0037">he went to uni in Lancaster didn't didn't he? Is he the Health Secretary?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> no he he was</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Alan Milburn I'm thinking of</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">yeah you're <trunc>thin</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> alan Johnson was the one who was nearly the leader like <pause dur="short"/> uh but he had to resign because of an affair or something</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115">uh he's quite old uh but he was like he was pretty like he was quite likable so in fact he he probably would've made a better leader than uh probably the other ones that they've got</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>M</trunc> Miliband just <pause dur="short"/> oh he's just insufferable isn't he like? He's so floppy and like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>whenev</trunc> you know when you see people and they just drain all the life out of you you just think oh like</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115">well I guess it's something about his um <trunc>hi</trunc> his voice and his his his face I suppose are not  are not  perfect enough</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is this like?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115">Cos people people always want like</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037">na na it's not about his face to be honest</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you know someone who's got the right shape face and the right voice you know</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm not bothered about his face <pause dur="short"/> I don't really care</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115">but no you are though people are I mean</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037">but he's got that horrible</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if like if you have if you had the voice that you know if his face looked more like you know Tony Blair or something then people'd be more you know</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037">na I think he's got a really unfortunate lisp</u>
<u n="419" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like imagine Tony Blair's face <trunc>To</trunc> Tony Blair's face and his voice</u>
<u n="420" who="S0037">no I still don't think it would work because if he's got that horrible lisp</u>
<u n="421" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean like you'd be more people'd vote for him wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's got a <pause dur="short"/> and I the one  the one  thing where they're going wrong at the moment is that like like you were saying before the Tories have had a bit of a mare this week really and the best he can do is go down Greggs and like order a pastie and pretend that he's always in there like that's really the best retort they have <pause dur="short"/> that you know the Tories  the Tories  are just cannibalizing the NHS there's so many things they're doing that are really bad</u>
<u n="423" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well him and Ed Balls were went to</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037">and the best  the best  thing Labour can do is just be like I'll go down Greggs</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115">well they I'm sure they  I'm sure they  did other things than go to Greggs like uh</u>
<u n="426" who="S0037">ah well did they? You know it's just</u>
<u n="427" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well that's isn't it you you're just basing it from the news cos obviously they</u>
<u n="428" who="S0037">aye but how else am I supposed to know like <pause dur="short"/> I can't follow their own I can't follow them like</u>
<u n="429" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they tried to do things</u>
<u n="430" who="S0037">I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> the news doesn't show everything but how am I supposed to know like?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0115" trans="overlap">mind you this uh this process with the NHS is probably probably has been going on on a for for ages before I mean like if you're talking about <pause dur="short"/> I mean what specifically are you talking about?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but Labour weren't doing it were they like?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0115">well Sunderland away to Man City</u>
<u n="434" who="S0037">ah they're gonna get hammered aren't they tomorrow?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0115">mind you the they might've thought that uh</u>
<u n="436" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and who are Birmingham playing?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0115">Birmingham is not in the same division so</u>
<u n="438" who="S0037">that's oh of course sorry</u>
<u n="439" who="S0115">they've</u>
<u n="440" who="S0037">totally forgot <pause dur="short"/> sunderland are gonna get knacked tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> or maybe they'll bounce back after the humiliation of uh earlier in the week <pause dur="short"/> na they won't will they?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0115" trans="overlap">maybe they'll <pause dur="short"/> I mean that was pretty bad</u>
<u n="442" who="S0037">man City are way <pause dur="short"/> man City are top of the league aren't they? Aren't they or second?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0115">no they're second uh it looks like um</u>
<u n="444" who="S0037">ah well <pause dur="short"/> that's not much of a difference</u>
<u n="445" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh cos cos <trunc>Ma</trunc> Man United have have uh an easier uh final group of games than than Man City so that's why people think that Man United will will um cos</u>
<u n="446" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah run in <pause dur="short"/> well actually Sunderland have been pretty good away from home albeit let's not mention West Brom but <pause dur="short"/> they beat Liverpool they beat Arsenal like they did do some good stuff but yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="447" who="S0115">well they certainly struggled against Everton anyway</u>
<u n="448" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0115">um d'you wanna pause it or?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0037">I don't mind <pause dur="short"/> d'you want some of this?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0037">then we can get one at the same time maybe</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="453" who="S0115">um so uh saying that um NHS what were you talking about the NHS?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0037">oh no no I was just saying like that I thought it was pathetic that like all the things that are happening Labour are like look I'm buying a pastie like</u>
<u n="455" who="S0115">yeah well I mean</u>
<u n="456" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know what I was saying about Ed Miliband that I thought he was like really unconvincing and I much preferred his brother really if anything</u>
<u n="457" who="S0115">he was more like Tony Blair though</u>
<u n="458" who="S0037">yeah but that's not  that's not  why I liked him</u>
<u n="459" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that that that is a fusion <pause dur="short"/> like I was saying okay so you think that if Tony Blair had his own face but Ed Miliband's voice that that the he he would get the same amount of popularity as um as Ed Miliband or a bit more?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know I appreciate it is about like um you know promotion isn't it?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean it it's it's <trunc>j</trunc> it's not just your face and voice it's obviously also your style and um your your your gestures and your your mannerisms you know and your</u>
<u n="462" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think like a  like a like a  whole man of the people thing could work like I think that's why like Ed Balls could've could've done better really <pause dur="short"/> he's more like a bloke isn't he?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah perhaps he's <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's the sort of guy who looks like he'd actually buy a pastie you know whereas nobody else</u>
<u n="464" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but he is he's along that he's had a few pasties like</u>
<u n="465" who="S0115">I mean Alan Johnson was the  was the  the one that uh that was the most perhaps like ordinary bloke out of all of them</u>
<u n="466" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think Ed Balls I liked <trunc>u</trunc> I liked him because I thought he was more like he just felt less like slimy and like sort of like <pause dur="short"/> the other ones felt like they were just well like they were raised to be politicians you know like <pause dur="short"/> that's <trunc>a</trunc> I suppose I'm just inherently suspicious of these Eton Oxford types who are just</u>
<u n="467" who="S0115">well I mean</u>
<u n="468" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like someone else said like oh okay so he went to Oxford and then he worked as a <trunc>sp</trunc> as a special advisor</u>
<u n="469" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but some of them are Labour and some are you know Conservative</u>
<u n="470" who="S0037">and then he now he's a politician like well wow just you know I'm bowled over by that real-world experience that he's had</u>
<u n="471" who="S0115">so so d'you think that <pause dur="short"/> no yeah I mean uh I suppose I think that politicians should like</u>
<u n="472" who="S0037">least they've done something like</u>
<u n="473" who="S0115">but kind of the the job of politicians is is just like <trunc>s</trunc> it's sort of waffle isn't it?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't wanna do it</u>
</body>
</text>
