<text id="SD2R">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:38:47</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-08</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013 S0152</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>School, wardrobe, deliverymen, jokes, television programs, tweeting, binge drinking, health service, cleaning</topics>
		<activity>ANON ANON and friend discussing schools and other topics.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0152">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Birmingham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>w_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0013">I don't think you're gonna catch anything off me <pause dur="short"/> or don't you know? I reckon it'll be alright</u>
<u n="2" who="S0152">no you're not gonna catch anything off you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0013">I don't want to</u>
<u n="5" who="S0012">I think I oh I've gotta put record now ain't I</u>
<u n="6" who="S0013">give you a bad cold or anything</u>
<u n="7" who="S0012">Cos that's only the chapter two inserted <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> There <pause dur="short"/> off we go</u>
<u n="8" who="S0152">yeah so it's er somebody that I work with basically said this girl could have the two days holiday <pause dur="short"/> so they put the holiday form in <pause dur="short"/> it came to me and I looked at it <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>w</trunc> I said well she's got an exam on the  on the  Monday <pause dur="short"/> I know she might have <trunc>almo</trunc> you know almost a hundred percent attendance <pause dur="short"/> and the woman says well I was told that she could do the exam again <pause dur="short"/> well that's a cost implication of somebody not taking the exam <pause dur="short"/> so it's a cost implication to the <trunc>s</trunc> to the school <pause dur="short"/> so I I spoke to the deputy <pause dur="short"/> mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> sorry? And er he says no mark it down as one day unauthorized and one day holiday</u>
<u n="9" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="10" who="S0152">so the mum so I spoke to the <trunc>w</trunc> lady who had said about that it was okay <pause dur="short"/> so then the mum phoned up and said er I spoke about it three weeks ago and said it was alright <pause dur="short"/> I said I'm sorry but those are the rules <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>sp</trunc> you know I've spoken to somebody <pause dur="short"/> this is what they've said</u>
<u n="11" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0152">and she says well what does it mean? Unauthorized? I said it means that we're not authorizing your daughter's day off from school <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> but what does it mean? It means <vocal desc="laugh"/> we're not <trunc>au</trunc> we're not authorizing it <pause dur="short"/> so it's not having a code in there <pause dur="short"/> it'll have a code in there which will go against her attendance <pause dur="short"/> well why can't it be authorized? I said even if I authorized your day off as holiday it still goes against your daughter's attendance <pause dur="short"/> so it doesn't make <trunc>s</trunc> it doesn't make any difference</u>
<u n="13" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No</u>
<u n="14" who="S0152">it's still  it's still  gonna be <trunc>unauth</trunc> you know it's still gonna be an absence whichever way you do it <pause dur="short"/> so she was a bit oh that's not fair <pause dur="short"/> I'd have done something different <pause dur="short"/> and I thought no you wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> you'd have taken your daughter in any case</u>
<u n="15" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0152">Cos you've got it booked</u>
<u n="18" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> so oh I just left it  I left it  at that <pause dur="short"/> and she was oh in she was alright in the end <pause dur="short"/> and then another girl came to see me about I've got a meeting with er her parents tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> and er she just doesn't wanna come to school</u>
<u n="20" who="S0012">no?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0152">so I  so I  <trunc>s</trunc> I've not met her before and she turned up at my desk on Friday and she went I've come to see you <pause dur="short"/> er okay <pause dur="short"/> tells me who she was and er I put a few facts to her <pause dur="short"/> I you know I just spoke to her normally <pause dur="short"/> I said look I said I don't think you actually realize that you've got ten weeks left <pause dur="short"/> that's all you've got <pause dur="short"/> ten weeks</u>
<u n="22" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> gosh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0152">I says your attendance is running at seventy-nine percent <pause dur="short"/> she says well if I'm here every day until I finish will my attendance be a hundred percent?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh gawd</u>
<u n="25" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="27" who="S0152">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I said it won't actually be a hundred percent I says but it will go up <pause dur="short"/> I said it'll go up probably if you're here for the next ten weeks <pause dur="short"/> here every day <pause dur="short"/> it will go up by five percent <pause dur="short"/> so you'll be at eighty-five percent <pause dur="short"/> which is far better than it being</u>
<u n="28" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0152">at seventy-nine percent <pause dur="short"/> I said you don't understand that do you? And she went not really no <pause dur="short"/> so I said look if you start in September and you're here for the full week I says five days at school equals a hundred percent</u>
<u n="30" who="S0012">A hundred percent <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0152">if you're here for the second week at school ten days of school equals a hundred percent <pause dur="short"/> so you can see her mind going over <pause dur="short"/> I said but if you have a day off in those two weeks it goes down to ninety percent <pause dur="short"/> this is the easiest way I can</u>
<u n="32" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0152">put it to you <pause dur="short"/> I said er if you have <unclear/> if you er if you were here for three weeks but had a day off in those three weeks it would go to something like ninety-five percent <pause dur="short"/> and I worked it all out for her</u>
<u n="34" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0152">so I said that that's the way that it works <pause dur="short"/> so the more days you're here the better your er your attendance <pause dur="short"/> I says but what we can do I said is we can say right you're back in school now and we'll look at your attendance from now through to when you leave <pause dur="short"/> and then we can say you've had a hundred percent attendance from this date</u>
<u n="36" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="37" who="S0152">to this date <pause dur="short"/> yeah we know your attendance was bad</u>
<u n="38" who="S0012">beforehand</u>
<u n="39" who="S0152">before <pause dur="short"/> I said but you have shown an improvement</u>
<u n="40" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds</u>
<u n="41" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0013">good then doesn't it?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0152">and she  and she  looked and she went thank you <pause dur="short"/> and then she came back twice and cos and then she says what about court? And I thought oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I said er where's court come in all this? Well I've been told that if I don't go to school my mum's gonna go to court <pause dur="short"/> I said yeah that's true</u>
<u n="44" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0152">I says but I don't really think that's very fair on your mum when it's you that is <trunc>m</trunc> that is saying as a sixteen-year-old I'm not coming to school</u>
<u n="46" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="47" who="S0152">I says but your mum will get the fine <pause dur="short"/> your mum could have the fine of two and a half thousand pound</u>
<u n="48" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0152">I said or a month in prison if your mum can't pay it <pause dur="short"/> I said that's <trunc>w</trunc> that's what they can do</u>
<u n="50" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0013">that's terrible ain't it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0152">and she looked and she says would they? I said er yeah that's they do <pause dur="short"/> and I just  I just  thought to myself they won't push it <pause dur="short"/> she's year eleven <pause dur="short"/> got ten weeks to go <pause dur="short"/> the time you've got your court dates in <pause dur="short"/> they won't push it</u>
<u n="53" who="S0012">no they won't <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0152">it'll be somebody in year ten they'll push or something <pause dur="short"/> but I weren't gonna say that to her <pause dur="short"/> and she said oh <pause dur="short"/> I said look I says you know I said I wouldn't be happy if it was one of my daughters <pause dur="short"/> I says but from what I gather you give your mum a lot of grief <pause dur="short"/> why? All she's doing is being a a parent telling you you've gotta go to school</u>
<u n="55" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said do you want an easier life or do you want it a hard life where you're arguing all the time? Cos it's cos what I've picked up on two conversations with your mum that's what's happening <pause dur="short"/> and your mum's getting tired of it <pause dur="short"/> and is going to the doctors</u>
<u n="57" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0152">what would you rather have? Would you rather have your mum being happy or do you want your mum to suffer because you're not being very nice? And she thought about it <pause dur="short"/> she went and she got <trunc>ups</trunc> she was upset at this point in time <pause dur="short"/> got some tissues and she went off <pause dur="short"/> then she came back and she says you know what? She says you're the first person that has sat down with me <pause dur="short"/> explained it to me without shouting at me or screaming at me</u>
<u n="60" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="61" who="S0152">and just told me as it's  as it's  straight</u>
<u n="62" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0152">you're the first person</u>
<u n="64" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0152">who's actually taken the time</u>
<u n="66" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0152">to sit down and explain it</u>
<u n="68" who="S0012">well you did it well so she didn't have to retaliate in any way did she?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0152">that's it</u>
<u n="70" who="S0012">Cos if if she gets shouted at she would retaliate</u>
<u n="71" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0012">by shouting back and throwing her arms up in the air and walking out the room</u>
<u n="73" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0012">and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> so er you know it was the best way to do it <pause dur="short"/> brilliant <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0152">so that  so that was that  was it</u>
<u n="76" who="S0012">that's good</u>
<u n="77" who="S0152">and then some year  then some year  nine girls I think they were year nine girls came in <pause dur="short"/> cos they were in trouble <pause dur="short"/> on report <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And this girl goes my sister likes you</u>
<u n="78" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh dear</u>
<u n="79" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0152">she says thinks you're really good <pause dur="short"/> you listen and you help <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="82" who="S0013">oh really?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0152">and that's gone into</u>
<u n="84" who="S0013">him as well</u>
<u n="85" who="S0152">gone into from a year eleven student</u>
<u n="86" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0152">to a year nine student</u>
<u n="88" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0152">in</u>
<u n="90" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0152">three weeks <pause dur="short"/> kids are coming to me and saying</u>
<u n="92" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's no</u>
<u n="93" who="S0013">that's brilliant ain't it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0012">that's brilliant ain't it?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0012">but you wanna take the job as a full-time job?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0152">this there isn't one</u>
<u n="98" who="S0012">there ain't a full-time job? No?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0152">er the <trunc>m</trunc> a er for what? They get paid  they get paid  peanuts</u>
<u n="100" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0152">they <trunc>g</trunc> they don't get paid</u>
<u n="103" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="105" who="S0152">I'd spend most of that in petrol</u>
<u n="106" who="S0012">well I suppose you do</u>
<u n="107" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0012">it's a long way ain't it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0152">sixty miles a day</u>
<u n="110" who="S0012">sixty miles a day</u>
<u n="111" who="S0152">that's a tank of petrol a week</u>
<u n="112" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a lot of petrol</u>
<u n="114" who="S0152">so er if a job <trunc>ca</trunc> I think if a job came up on their management team I think I'd <trunc>g</trunc> I would stand a very good chance of getting it</u>
<u n="115" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0152">well I'd er six years ago I'd have got a job there</u>
<u n="118" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0152">but I decided to go to</u>
<u n="120" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0152">to to</u>
<u n="122" who="S0012">to the other place <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="124" who="S0013">so you wouldn't mind travelling if you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0152">it's it's not I I know er I would I'd be quite happy to travel there</u>
<u n="126" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0152">if I'd got a</u>
<u n="128" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0152">if I could get a senior management role there</u>
<u n="130" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0152">because there's lots of things that I can see needs to happen</u>
<u n="133" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0152">but I'm not there  I'm not there  for that</u>
<u n="135" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="136" who="S0152">I was I mean the exam was set up really well on Friday <pause dur="short"/> the way that it was set up <pause dur="short"/> but I would've done it a little bit differently</u>
<u n="137" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0152">I'd have done it a little bit differently <pause dur="short"/> but that's just knowing how we done things in the past and seen the way that it worked</u>
<u n="139" who="S0012">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's right</u>
<u n="140" who="S0152">so but er no I would  I would  do that</u>
<u n="141" who="S0012">hm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0152">I'm gonna apply for the headship job</u>
<u n="143" who="S0012">you are? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's gonna be a difficult one</u>
<u n="144" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's er it's a tough place</u>
<u n="145" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's a very tough place</u>
<u n="146" who="S0152">it is really tough</u>
<u n="147" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0152">but whatever happens it's er I know it's a no win situation</u>
<u n="149" who="S0012">it's a no win situation</u>
<u n="150" who="S0152">mhm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0012">well it's gonna close down eventually won't it?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0152">it's a no  it's a no  win situation <pause dur="short"/> I think  I think  what'll happen is it'll <trunc>bec</trunc> it'll become an academy</u>
<u n="153" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0152">but two three years there <pause dur="short"/> pay some money get a pay out</u>
<u n="155" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> be nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that would be good</u>
<u n="156" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but I've just gotta get things sorted</u>
<u n="157" who="S0012">huh <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> how did the wardrobe fit?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0152">I haven't started yet</u>
<u n="159" who="S0012">you <trunc>ha</trunc> haven't <trunc>unp</trunc> unpacked it?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0012">no?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0152">I gotta move some stuff out of the room <pause dur="short"/> out of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room</u>
<u n="163" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0152">it's the pits</u>
<u n="165" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0152">I bought a new screwdriver yesterday</u>
<u n="167" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0152">bought a new Black and Decker</u>
<u n="169" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0152">the new one of those</u>
<u n="171" who="S0012">oh yeah? Yeah? That's a Black and Decker one ain't it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0152">hour and a half charge</u>
<u n="173" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0152">three point six lithium battery <pause dur="short"/> and the handle it will do it it rather than just being straight like that one you can actually turn it like a gun</u>
<u n="175" who="S0012">angle round the corner?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0152">and you can get in like that rather than your hand at the top</u>
<u n="177" who="S0012">oh that's brilliant</u>
<u n="178" who="S0152">got it from Homebase</u>
<u n="179" who="S0012">did you? mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0152">it was good</u>
<u n="181" who="S0012">oh <pause dur="short"/> them blokes who delivered that wardrobe he came in it's heavy ain't it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0012">and they put put the heavy one down and then the lighter one down <pause dur="short"/> then he stood up and looked <pause dur="short"/> and he said I'm asleep keep out <pause dur="short"/> that's a teenager's room</u>
<u n="184" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0013">aw</u>
<u n="186" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0152">yep</u>
<u n="188" who="S0012">yep <pause dur="short"/> I says cos they thought I was you</u>
<u n="189" who="S0152">right</u>
<u n="190" who="S0012">because when I got there they'd phoned up <pause dur="short"/> right?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0152">they phoned <unclear/> four times I think</u>
<u n="192" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> way before twelve weren't it?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they'd phoned and and I ran in</u>
<u n="195" who="S0013">you left here about half eleven didn't you</u>
<u n="196" who="S0012">yeah I did <pause dur="short"/> and I just got in just as they hung up <pause dur="short"/> so I phone them back <pause dur="short"/> and they said oh we can't deliver it now <pause dur="short"/> we're on the way to Kings Lynn and we're in Swaffham <pause dur="short"/> well they didn't take long get to Swaffham from from phoning to get to Swaffham</u>
<u n="197" who="S0152">fifteen minutes to Swaffham</u>
<u n="198" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0013">mhm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0012">and I'd phoned them back straight away <pause dur="short"/> anyway they said they'd they'd come back <pause dur="short"/> and I said well I won't be here all day <pause dur="short"/> I'll give you the <trunc>ph</trunc> my phone number er where I'll be <pause dur="short"/> so they phoned here <pause dur="short"/> they said we're we'll arrive about half past three <pause dur="short"/> so I left and I got the doors open and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and played with the cat <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos she's funny ain't she</u>
<u n="201" who="S0152">she's a mad cat she is</u>
<u n="202" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0012">she is a mad cat <pause dur="short"/> and then er they turned up dead on half past three</u>
<u n="204" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0012">so they said they were clever <trunc>w</trunc> we're clever ain't we he said <pause dur="short"/> I said well you got here</u>
<u n="206" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0152">you've already been before</u>
<u n="208" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0152">you've already been once <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0012">so er</u>
<u n="211" who="S0152">I don't think they actually went you know</u>
<u n="212" who="S0012">I don't think they turned up <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="213" who="S0152">I think they phoned up</u>
<u n="214" who="S0013">what at the beginning?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think they phoned up to see whether they you somebody was there</u>
<u n="216" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0152">wasn't</u>
<u n="218" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="219" who="S0152">then went <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="220" who="S0012">straight past</u>
<u n="221" who="S0152">straight straight past</u>
<u n="222" who="S0012">straight along the yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0152">that's why they'd have been in Swaffham</u>
<u n="224" who="S0012">Cos they they could've turned off at <trunc>M</trunc> <trunc>M</trunc></u>
<u n="225" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0012"><trunc>M</trunc> Mattishall couldn't they</u>
<u n="227" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0012">they go er the <trunc>c</trunc> roundabout <pause dur="short"/> but they carried on straight up there didn't they</u>
<u n="229" who="S0152">yes</u>
<u n="230" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0013">and we've even had people delivering things and they say oh we left a note in your box <trunc>t</trunc> and there's nothing there</u>
<u n="232" who="S0012">and there's <trunc>nothi</trunc> not a thing in the box</u>
<u n="233" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0012">you know</u>
<u n="235" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="236" who="S0013">say we called and we've been here all day <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0152">that's right</u>
<u n="238" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> another bloke come and delivered the other day for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and just left it on the doorstep outside here <pause dur="short"/> and we saw him <pause dur="short"/> ran to the door and he by the by then he'd <trunc>driv</trunc> just driven away</u>
<u n="239" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0012">didn't have to sign for them</u>
<u n="241" who="S0152"><unclear/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0012">I signed my name for yours</u>
<u n="243" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's alright</u>
<u n="244" who="S0012">but I</u>
<u n="245" who="S0152">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> that's no problem</u>
<u n="246" who="S0012">no wonder <pause dur="short"/> they didn't even look to see <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> the they've got the address and everything don't they</u>
<u n="248" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="250" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0152">they've got the address</u>
<u n="253" who="S0012">but er mm I took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <trunc>hospita</trunc> er to the doctors that morning <pause dur="short"/> and as we were coming back it was about eleven o'clock we were coming back</u>
<u n="254" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="255" who="S0012">no it was before then <pause dur="short"/> cos we had a cup of tea when we got back didn't we <pause dur="short"/> eleven o'clock we come back <pause dur="short"/> and there was a little van called</u>
<u n="256" who="S0013">we thought it might've been that</u>
<u n="257" who="S0012">home deliveries</u>
<u n="258" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0012">went past</u>
<u n="260" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0012">and we said oh I hope that weren't them <pause dur="short"/> but that weren't them <pause dur="short"/> they came in a great big Luton</u>
<u n="262" who="S0152">mhm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah they I'm quite impressed with Hovells really</u>
<u n="263" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0152">I'm quite impressed with Hovells</u>
<u n="265" who="S0012">I see it come from Denmark</u>
<u n="266" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0013">so are you pleased with them?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0152">I haven't <trunc>d</trunc> put them together yet</u>
<u n="269" who="S0013">oh er you haven't? Oh right</u>
<u n="270" who="S0152">no I haven't put them together <pause dur="short"/> I've got</u>
<u n="271" who="S0012">gotta clean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room out first</u>
<u n="272" who="S0152">gotta clean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s oh well I'm huh I've gotta decorate it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0152">I've gotta decorate the room</u>
<u n="276" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0152">and I've got some filling to do</u>
<u n="278" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0152">some <unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0013">just got some more paint in as well <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you've got some painting to do</u>
<u n="282" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0012">but she she's been really bad</u>
<u n="284" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0012">ain't you?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0013">it's only since Monday</u>
<u n="287" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a week</u>
<u n="288" who="S0013">Monday</u>
<u n="289" who="S0012">that's that's a week tomorrow</u>
<u n="290" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0012">then you went down</u>
<u n="292" who="S0013"><unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0152">no it's the change in weather temperatures</u>
<u n="294" who="S0012">well she couldn't even</u>
<u n="295" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0012">she couldn't even breathe <pause dur="short"/> her asthma was so bad</u>
<u n="297" who="S0152"><unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0012">she got got to the doctors and and blew er blew in that thing</u>
<u n="299" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0012">and she couldn't even blow in it</u>
<u n="301" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0152">well it didn't go positive did it for drink?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No</u>
<u n="304" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0012">mind you that could er could've done <pause dur="short"/> cos that that stuff you take has got alcohol in it ain't it</u>
<u n="307" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's got er eight <trunc>m</trunc> eight milligram or something <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a an inhaler and that's got alcohol in it</u>
<u n="309" who="S0152">so it absorbs in your body quicker</u>
<u n="310" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I expect it is ain't it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0013">and she said while I was there you'll take six puff now <pause dur="short"/> got it with you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And come back</u>
<u n="312" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0012">well we walked into the  into the  doctors right <pause dur="short"/> and we sat er</u>
<u n="314" who="S0013">and it said something about mm don't take more than ten</u>
<u n="315" who="S0012">oh yes it does <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0013">doses a day doesn't it</u>
<u n="317" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0012">we got into the doctors and we sat there <pause dur="short"/> and everyone was sitting there</u>
<u n="320" who="S0152">oh it's awful in the <trunc>doc</trunc></u>
<u n="321" who="S0012">ain't it</u>
<u n="322" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's just so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0012">so I just said huh the silence here is deafening ain't it <pause dur="short"/> and this bloke up the corner he <trunc>la</trunc> or</u>
<u n="325" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0012">right opposite us he he laughed didn't he</u>
<u n="327" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0012">and then he started oh he started talking er</u>
<u n="329" who="S0013">started on about his cockerels first didn't he</u>
<u n="330" who="S0012">started talking about the cockerels <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And he says <vocal desc="laugh"/> tell you this he says yeah <pause dur="short"/> starting when the cockerels are going off in the morning <pause dur="short"/> and he said they'll drive you up the wall he said <pause dur="short"/> they start and he said they're going cock-a-doodle-doo cock-a-doodle-doo <pause dur="short"/> and my missus got up opened the window and shouted out you got it wrong <pause dur="short"/> any cock'll do</u>
<u n="331" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0012">this was in the surgery</u>
<u n="333" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0152">did that get a response?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0012">nobody</u>
<u n="337" who="S0152">I bet every</u>
<u n="338" who="S0013">not not for that one</u>
<u n="339" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="340" who="S0013">but er</u>
<u n="341" who="S0012">and then he <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="342" who="S0013">then he started telling jokes</u>
<u n="343" who="S0012">he started telling jokes <pause dur="short"/> and I said</u>
<u n="344" who="S0013">and he did have to say to this young girl who was sitting quite near us</u>
<u n="345" who="S0012">do you mind if I tell them?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0013">you don't mind? And she she was on the phone</u>
<u n="347" who="S0012">she was on she was just texting <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="348" who="S0013">she said no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="349" who="S0012">we had a good laugh in there <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="350" who="S0013">I'm sure she was taking it all in</u>
<u n="351" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0152">ah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0012">but er I said  I said  to him do you know the pheasant pluckers rhyme? Oh he said I've got a better one than that <pause dur="short"/> and he reeled off this rhyme</u>
<u n="354" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0012">and it was  it was  so fast and so tongue twisty and it was er very very rude</u>
<u n="356" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0013">but we don't really know what it  what it  was</u>
<u n="358" who="S0012">but we couldn't catch it all</u>
<u n="359" who="S0152">oh</u>
<u n="360" who="S0012">we couldn't catch it all <pause dur="short"/> but er that was he was <vocal desc="laugh"/> quite brilliant</u>
<u n="361" who="S0013">then he got called in unfortunately <pause dur="short"/> just at the end</u>
<u n="362" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he got called in just at the end so we didn't catch it all <pause dur="short"/> and he <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="363" who="S0013">when we saw him again we said we didn't catch <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0012">so we're in the <trunc>s</trunc> we're in the pharmacy then <pause dur="short"/> waiting for  waiting for  the prescription right <pause dur="short"/> and he <trunc>c</trunc> he come in and he's he come in with Dr <unclear/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0012">and he said oh thank you  thank you  And he's one of these blokes that we think there was something seriously with him</u>
<u n="367" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0012">Cos they can't get the medicine for him</u>
<u n="369" who="S0152">right</u>
<u n="370" who="S0013">and he'd been to see him</u>
<u n="371" who="S0012">and and they and er they'd got got to find out whether they could get it</u>
<u n="372" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0012">and he had to phone them back in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> but he was a very jolly fella <pause dur="short"/> proper old Norfolk boy <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You know <pause dur="short"/> they just say it as they er</u>
<u n="374" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0012">as it is don't they <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> and er he turned round and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to him we didn't catch the the last one <pause dur="short"/> so he said it again right in the middle of the</u>
<u n="376" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0013">still didn't get it</u>
<u n="378" who="S0012">but we we still didn't</u>
<u n="379" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You didn't get it?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0012">get it <pause dur="short"/> cos he did it so fast <pause dur="short"/> he's very very clever <vocal desc="laugh"/> bloke</u>
<u n="381" who="S0013">it's just  it's just  a tongue twister <pause dur="short"/> but we we couldn't get it</u>
<u n="382" who="S0012">A very good tongue twister</u>
<u n="383" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0012">which was very rude <pause dur="short"/> if you said the</u>
<u n="385" who="S0152">the right <trunc>w</trunc> you got the tongue twister</u>
<u n="386" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="387" who="S0152">the wrong words</u>
<u n="388" who="S0013">what what what he says was right</u>
<u n="389" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0013">but you know you could twist it</u>
<u n="391" who="S0012">but you know it</u>
<u n="392" who="S0152">you know you could twist it</u>
<u n="393" who="S0012">that took the the the the bits like pheasant plucker</u>
<u n="394" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0012">could be turned round</u>
<u n="396" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0012">to er to be er</u>
<u n="398" who="S0013">he'd been practising this one</u>
<u n="399" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0013">to death <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="401" who="S0012">and er forty years he says that took me to get this right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Forty years <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0152">forty years? Blimey</u>
<u n="403" who="S0012">oh that was funny</u>
<u n="404" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0012">that was good</u>
<u n="406" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we spent quite a long time waiting for your stuff didn't we</u>
<u n="408" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0013">and then I forgot I had to go back in</u>
<u n="411" who="S0012">and the doctor come out after her</u>
<u n="412" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0012">she said er have you had <trunc>t</trunc> chance to er do your six inhalers yet? And</u>
<u n="415" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had forgotten <pause dur="short"/> oh just just take them now</u>
<u n="417" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0012">so she had to take them all now didn't you</u>
<u n="419" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0012">and then we went back into the surgery not er into the waiting room</u>
<u n="421" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0012">but into the surgery part</u>
<u n="423" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0012">we er where there's a seat <pause dur="short"/> we went back in there and she has someone in then didn't she</u>
<u n="425" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> never mind <pause dur="short"/> it was all alright anyway</u>
<u n="426" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but when she blew into the thing again what was it?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0013">well I blew into it</u>
<u n="428" who="S0012">two hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="429" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No it wasn't</u>
<u n="430" who="S0012">oh a hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="431" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> A hundred and twenty</u>
<u n="432" who="S0012">A hundred and twenty</u>
<u n="433" who="S0152">A hundred and twenty</u>
<u n="434" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> This was er</u>
<u n="435" who="S0012">I'm six thirty <pause dur="short"/> she's a hundred and twenty</u>
<u n="436" who="S0013">but mine um that's my usual <pause dur="short"/> she knows it's well a hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="437" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0013">is my usual</u>
<u n="439" who="S0012">A hundred and fifty's your usual <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0013">I don't breathe very well</u>
<u n="441" who="S0012">that's just the best she can do</u>
<u n="442" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so fail</u>
<u n="443" who="S0012">her lung capacity is useless ain't it</u>
<u n="444" who="S0013">but I'm okay</u>
<u n="445" who="S0012">yeah you're okay <pause dur="short"/> you can manage it</u>
<u n="446" who="S0013">fit and healthy</u>
<u n="447" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0152">that's what it's about</u>
<u n="450" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0012">well when when you're normal you're fit and healthy</u>
<u n="452" who="S0152">yeah but your lung capacity <trunc>i</trunc> improves with what you do doesn't it</u>
<u n="453" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0012">how's your leg anyway?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0152">sore</u>
<u n="457" who="S0012">sore still?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0012">you're losing the is it in the hip?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0152">I don't know where I don't think it is in the hip</u>
<u n="461" who="S0012">is it in the groin?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0152">mm no <pause dur="short"/> I think it's  I think it's  muscle tear</u>
<u n="463" who="S0012">do you?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0152">I really think it's muscle tear <pause dur="short"/> there's lots of knots just in that bit of <trunc>mu</trunc> muscle just there</u>
<u n="465" who="S0013">so it needs to be</u>
<u n="466" who="S0152">compared to the other side <pause dur="short"/> and it's swollen</u>
<u n="467" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0152">you can <trunc>f</trunc> you can actually feel there's a difference between my one leg in the same place and the other side</u>
<u n="469" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0152">and I</u>
<u n="471" who="S0013">you should go to physiotherapy again shouldn't you</u>
<u n="472" who="S0152">I well they er er all they did was stretch my leg and er they didn't put any hands-on <trunc>pr</trunc> you know she kept saying about oh well let's</u>
<u n="473" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0152">put some hands-on pressure and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> nothing <pause dur="short"/> nothing at all <pause dur="short"/> if I wrap I think if I got a huh one of those bandage</u>
<u n="475" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0152">not a crepe bandage <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>c</trunc> you're supposed to put</u>
<u n="477" who="S0013">no?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0152">cold on not heat</u>
<u n="479" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0012">oh are you?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you should</u>
<u n="482" who="S0012">A cold compress?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you shouldn't put anything hot on it any more <pause dur="short"/> it's er  it's er</u>
<u n="484" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> which is</u>
<u n="486" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="487" who="S0152">interesting concept <pause dur="short"/> because if you think of <trunc>y</trunc> years ago if you injured yourself you put the Deep Heat on or you</u>
<u n="488" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0152">pulled something <pause dur="short"/> the idea is</u>
<u n="490" who="S0013"><trunc>T</trunc> loosens the muscles then</u>
<u n="491" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="493" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was told not to put Deep Heat on his um foot</u>
<u n="494" who="S0152">you put ice on</u>
<u n="495" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0152">that's why footballers have an ice bath</u>
<u n="497" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="498" who="S0152">because all the blood circulation gets going a lot quicker</u>
<u n="499" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0152">um but if I <trunc>p</trunc> put I think er not a crepe bandage you can get like those support stocking type thing</u>
<u n="501" who="S0012">you can</u>
<u n="502" who="S0152">bandages</u>
<u n="503" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0152">I reckon if I put a really tight one of those on my leg the pain would disappear</u>
<u n="505" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0152">Cos if I push it in</u>
<u n="507" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0152">it doesn't hurt</u>
<u n="509" who="S0012">doesn't it?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="511" who="S0012">and the quack ain't done anything else about it?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0152">I haven't been back since the last <unclear/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0012">well there you go <pause dur="short"/> you should go back <pause dur="short"/> you're as bad as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0152">yeah but</u>
<u n="515" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0152">mm <pause dur="short"/> I've got I haven't got the time at the moment to go back <pause dur="short"/> in two weeks' time I will have the time</u>
<u n="517" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="518" who="S0012">mhm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0152">within a few weeks</u>
<u n="520" who="S0012">in the meantime you're walking about like a</u>
<u n="521" who="S0152">it's all yeah it just</u>
<u n="522" who="S0012">three-legged donkey</u>
<u n="523" who="S0152">no it just sometimes it just gets gets on my nerves</u>
<u n="524" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="526" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0152">did you see the did you catch up with the Dales programme last week?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="529" who="S0152"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0012"><trunc>W</trunc> we recorded them</u>
<u n="531" who="S0152">oh</u>
<u n="532" who="S0013">we've missed that one haven't we <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0012">no er we missed that one <pause dur="short"/> yeah we missed one</u>
<u n="534" who="S0152">the first one?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0152">I've got the first one recorded twice</u>
<u n="537" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0152">I er</u>
<u n="540" who="S0013">we've got the other one recorded <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> recorded</u>
<u n="541" who="S0152">which one? The Great Britain one?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0013">that's about the railway ain't it tomorrow</u>
<u n="543" who="S0152">tomorrow is about the railway</u>
<u n="544" who="S0013">mhm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0152">tomorrow night's one is</u>
<u n="547" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0152">when he goes on the Settle to Carlisle railway</u>
<u n="549" who="S0012">that's right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0152">um</u>
<u n="551" who="S0012">made in Britain</u>
<u n="552" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0013">oh in the Dales</u>
<u n="555" who="S0152">in the Dales <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0012">in the Dales <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0152">in the Dales</u>
<u n="558" who="S0012">it was Made in Britain before weren't it</u>
<u n="559" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos you had the great country <trunc>w</trunc> Great British Countryside on</u>
<u n="560" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0152">BBC with Julia Bradbury <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she was and they were in the last one we saw they were on the Downs</u>
<u n="563" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't  that wasn't  very good that one</u>
<u n="564" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="565" who="S0012">I didn't think that was very good either <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="566" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="567" who="S0152">there isn't hm I don't think that that it's a nice area but it isn't the same</u>
<u n="568" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0152">as er like Cornwall or</u>
<u n="570" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="571" who="S0152">Devon</u>
<u n="572" who="S0012">no well it is er</u>
<u n="573" who="S0013">well I suppose it's neglected isn't it</u>
<u n="574" who="S0012">totally different</u>
<u n="575" who="S0152">because you haven't got</u>
<u n="576" who="S0013">so maybe it's a good job someone's</u>
<u n="577" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and of course</u>
<u n="579" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0152">they're not they haven't they're not doing the Lakes one <pause dur="short"/> up there <pause dur="short"/> cos they've done Cornwall and Devon</u>
<u n="581" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0152">they've done North Yorkshire</u>
<u n="583" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0152">they've done the South Downs</u>
<u n="586" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0152">and they're going up to Scotland</u>
<u n="588" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0152">that's the four programmes in this series</u>
<u n="590" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="591" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> you could er you could have three programmes just in the Dales <pause dur="short"/> in in in North Yorkshire</u>
<u n="592" who="S0012">you could <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0152">Cos you could have the</u>
<u n="594" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="595" who="S0152">dales <pause dur="short"/> a bit more of the Dales</u>
<u n="596" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0152">more of the Moors</u>
<u n="598" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0152">and then you could do the coast-line</u>
<u n="601" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0152">that's what they need</u>
<u n="603" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0012">well they got</u>
<u n="605" who="S0013">it's a big area isn't it <pause dur="short"/> Yorkshire</u>
<u n="606" who="S0012">well I suppose they've still gotta do Northumberland and and Cumberland haven't they</u>
<u n="607" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0012">I mean that's</u>
<u n="609" who="S0152">there's two big areas <pause dur="short"/> er the the Lakes <pause dur="short"/> and Northumberland</u>
<u n="610" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="612" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> good programmes <pause dur="short"/> I like them</u>
<u n="614" who="S0152">they are  they are  really good</u>
<u n="615" who="S0013">Cos they're different <pause dur="short"/> they're</u>
<u n="616" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0013">geological and</u>
<u n="619" who="S0152">yep <pause dur="short"/> they are good</u>
<u n="620" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> how it <trunc>dev</trunc> developed</u>
<u n="622" who="S0152">I watched on <trunc>y</trunc> I recorded the last two walks of the Coast to Coast Walk</u>
<u n="623" who="S0012">did you? Yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0152">Cos that was on Yesterday channel last week</u>
<u n="625" who="S0012">oh <pause dur="short"/> was it? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I didn't see that <pause dur="short"/> we got we can get Yesterday</u>
<u n="626" who="S0152">and they did the one from Swaledale to Richmond</u>
<u n="627" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0152">and then the next one is like Richmond to</u>
<u n="629" who="S0012">to <trunc>R</trunc></u>
<u n="630" who="S0152">to Robin Hood's Bay</u>
<u n="631" who="S0012">to Robin Hood's Bay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0012">er Julia Bradbury did</u>
<u n="634" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0012">that walk as well</u>
<u n="636" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0012">didn't she</u>
<u n="638" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that those are the ones that</u>
<u n="639" who="S0012">that was the one</u>
<u n="640" who="S0152">they repeated er they repeated them</u>
<u n="641" who="S0012">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> that was the repeat <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I was  I was  tweeting on that</u>
<u n="643" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You're tweeting again are you?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0152">I was tweeting <pause dur="short"/> I've had er quite a few retweets</u>
<u n="646" who="S0012">have you?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0012">you got some followers now have you?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0152">I've got forty-two followers</u>
<u n="650" who="S0013">I'll just go and check the pie</u>
<u n="651" who="S0012">oh wow</u>
<u n="652" who="S0152">some of them I don't know why they're following me</u>
<u n="653" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0152">and I've got a hundred</u>
<u n="655" who="S0012">they're called stalkers <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0152">and I've got a hundred and and I'm following a hundred and twenty-two</u>
<u n="657" who="S0012">yeah? Brilliant</u>
<u n="658" who="S0152">and last night this astro one um mm there was lots of tweets about this meteorite which was up in that they'd seen up in the northern part of the country</u>
<u n="659" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="660" who="S0152"><trunc>Ri</trunc> and it got down to the Midlands as well and Wales <pause dur="short"/> and there was some video footage of this meteorite</u>
<u n="661" who="S0012">was there?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0012">oh brilliant <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0152">and you could see that on the er on the tweet as well <pause dur="short"/> cos you can attach things</u>
<u n="665" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0152">so you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fish? The trout that she caught?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0152">well I got a picture of that in a bucket</u>
<u n="669" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0152">so I tweeted that picture about really good place to go in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> is is the trout <anon type="place"/> trout</u>
<u n="671" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0152">daughter's face was a picture when she reeled this in <pause dur="short"/> priceless <pause dur="short"/> so you put a hashtag <pause dur="short"/> that got  that got  retweeted to four thousand four hundred people</u>
<u n="673" who="S0012">what?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0152">from Yorkshire Life</u>
<u n="675" who="S0012">did it?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that got a retweet</u>
<u n="677" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="678" who="S0152">and my you know my um Sir Nigel Gresley picture?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0152">the Photoshop one?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0152">that got retweeted by North York Moors National Railway</u>
<u n="683" who="S0012">did it?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0012">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="686" who="S0152">to all their followers</u>
<u n="687" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0152">so you have you checked on how many people have looked at the website?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0012">no I haven't</u>
<u n="690" who="S0152">have a look</u>
<u n="691" who="S0012">well I I did look the other day a couple of days ago <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0152">had it gone up had it er?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0012">I I don't know now <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I looked at the looked at how many there is <pause dur="short"/> cos you've gotta scroll down a bit and look at er Concept Effects co dot UK</u>
<u n="694" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I went in er there'd been a fair there'd have been a fair bit of traffic over the last fortnight of people looking at that</u>
<u n="697" who="S0012">yeah? Brilliant <pause dur="short"/> you might have some oh we'll have to see if we can get to your</u>
<u n="698" who="S0152">get to e-mail <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="699" who="S0012">to your e-mail bit <pause dur="short"/> otherwise otherwise you'll not know anything about it</u>
<u n="700" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="701" who="S0012">will you</u>
<u n="702" who="S0152">but they'll have gone to yours as well</u>
<u n="703" who="S0012">hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah er yeah well <trunc>w</trunc> all we keep getting is a load of spam <pause dur="short"/> you know the pharmacy bits and</u>
<u n="704" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="705" who="S0012">all that <pause dur="short"/> um we had to empty our empty the box out the other day didn't we</u>
<u n="706" who="S0013">what for</u>
<u n="707" who="S0012">yours and mine</u>
<u n="708" who="S0013">concept?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0012">from Concept</u>
<u n="710" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0012">effects</u>
<u n="712" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0152">well you can set the password back up on that again <pause dur="short"/> cos you've got control of it</u>
<u n="714" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I should do shouldn't I <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0152">I was just saying to Carl that</u>
<u n="716" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0152">um I tweeted my Sir Nigel Gresley picture <pause dur="short"/> my Photoshop one</u>
<u n="718" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="719" who="S0152">I tweeted that to North York Moors Railway</u>
<u n="720" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="721" who="S0152">and put my take on a classic</u>
<u n="722" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="723" who="S0152">as the <trunc>ti</trunc> as the title</u>
<u n="724" who="S0013">can you?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0152">and they retweeted it out to all their followers</u>
<u n="726" who="S0013">do they?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0152">if it's good <pause dur="short"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s picture of her fish <pause dur="short"/> that big trout that she caught</u>
<u n="728" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0152">I tweeted that</u>
<u n="730" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="731" who="S0152">just to people that who follow me</u>
<u n="732" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0152">but a couple of other people <pause dur="short"/> and Yorkshire Life retweeted that to four thousand <trunc>th</trunc> five hundred people</u>
<u n="734" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="735" who="S0013">goodness</u>
<u n="736" who="S0012">that's good ain't it</u>
<u n="737" who="S0013">so they might want it in their magazine some time?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0152">so things like  so things like things like  that</u>
<u n="739" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0152">so that got</u>
<u n="741" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0152">that got retweeted <pause dur="short"/> and er there are at least eight photographers following us</u>
<u n="743" who="S0012">are there?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0013"></u>
<u n="745" who="S0152">from from Yorkshire</u>
<u n="746" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0152">and the  and the</u>
<u n="748" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0152">lake District</u>
<u n="750" who="S0012">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="751" who="S0013">so you put Concept on all of them?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="753" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="754" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="755" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0152">so so the web address that I've put in for me</u>
<u n="757" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0152">well from from my tweet <pause dur="short"/> cos my I'm <anon type="socialMediaName"/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> but the web address is Concept Effects</u>
<u n="761" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="762" who="S0152">so people</u>
<u n="763" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="764" who="S0152">look at it and they make comments</u>
<u n="765" who="S0013">Great <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="766" who="S0152">so I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er cos there is a a chart on the statistics to say how many people have looked at</u>
<u n="767" who="S0013">yeah I see</u>
<u n="768" who="S0152">the website</u>
<u n="769" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0152">and whereabout</u>
<u n="771" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh good</u>
<u n="774" who="S0152">so you need to check that out</u>
<u n="775" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to have a look <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="777" who="S0013">well I've had a few letters sent me in the past</u>
<u n="778" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had got a few letters</u>
<u n="779" who="S0013">A few I haven't replied to <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0012">asking</u>
<u n="781" who="S0013">schools and things asking</u>
<u n="782" who="S0012">if they can use things</u>
<u n="783" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0012">and er other bits and pieces</u>
<u n="785" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="786" who="S0012">didn't they</u>
<u n="787" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0012">somebody wanting to know the prices of er although</u>
<u n="789" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0012">the prices of</u>
<u n="791" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s stuff is on</u>
<u n="793" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0012">A lot of money but</u>
<u n="795" who="S0152">no but</u>
<u n="796" who="S0152">yeah well they're not <pause dur="short"/> I showed somebody at work <pause dur="short"/> rose at work <pause dur="short"/> cos she likes embroidery and stuff like that</u>
<u n="797" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0152">and she was amazed by er your stuff</u>
<u n="799" who="S0013">huh</u>
<u n="800" who="S0152">absolutely amazed</u>
<u n="801" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0152">didn't believe that they were sewn and whatever</u>
<u n="803" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0013">Good</u>
<u n="805" who="S0012">that's good</u>
<u n="806" who="S0013">have to do some more <pause dur="short"/> I haven't done anything for a</u>
<u n="807" who="S0012">Cos she's still on you're <trunc>st</trunc></u>
<u n="808" who="S0013">a year now</u>
<u n="809" who="S0012">still on the artists one aren't you? The</u>
<u n="810" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er yeah <pause dur="short"/> someone phoned it up the other day didn't they</u>
<u n="811" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="812" who="S0013">still under textile artist <vocal desc="laugh"/> as well</u>
<u n="813" who="S0012"><trunc>Te</trunc> textile artist <pause dur="short"/> and she's under that</u>
<u n="814" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0152">oh that's good <pause dur="short"/> and a <trunc>coup</trunc> and a couple of students that I've been working with all doing GCSE photography as a course</u>
<u n="817" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0152">so when so for some of them breaking down that barrier</u>
<u n="819" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0152"><trunc>T</trunc> I said oh have a look at this <pause dur="short"/> so I pulled that website up</u>
<u n="821" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0152">and showed them what and they were just amazed with what we've done</u>
<u n="823" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0152">all the bits and pieces</u>
<u n="825" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0152">so that</u>
<u n="828" who="S0012">well that's very good ain't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0013">get inspiration to do a bit more</u>
<u n="830" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0152">but er</u>
<u n="832" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="833" who="S0152">well I think I've got the girls Whitsun</u>
<u n="834" who="S0012">whitsun have you?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="836" who="S0012">oh that's</u>
<u n="837" who="S0152">for the whole week</u>
<u n="838" who="S0012">well <pause dur="short"/> they'll enjoy that won't they <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0152">think I've got the girls for the whole week of Whitsun <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0012">aw</u>
<u n="841" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="842" who="S0152">Cos they're going away</u>
<u n="843" who="S0012">where are they oh are they going away are they? What?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0152">they're going away on the thirtieth of May</u>
<u n="845" who="S0013">so when's Whitsun?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0152">thirty-first of May</u>
<u n="847" who="S0013">thirty-first of May</u>
<u n="848" who="S0012">we're away then</u>
<u n="849" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0012">no er no we're not</u>
<u n="851" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="852" who="S0152">no we're not away then are we?</u>
<u n="853" who="S0012">we're er away again</u>
<u n="854" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="855" who="S0012">March ain't it?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0152">you're away at at Easter</u>
<u n="857" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0013">end of March we go</u>
<u n="859" who="S0012">the end of March</u>
<u n="860" who="S0152">you're away  you're away  the the first week</u>
<u n="861" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="862" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="S0152">of the holidays</u>
<u n="864" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="866" who="S0152">Cos we go away the second week</u>
<u n="867" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="868" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0152">and then you're away the last week</u>
<u n="870" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0152">thirty-first of August aren't you</u>
<u n="872" who="S0012">mhm</u>
<u n="873" who="S0152">for that week</u>
<u n="874" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0012">yep <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="876" who="S0013">so apart from a couple of days we don't clash this time do we</u>
<u n="877" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="878" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="879" who="S0013">which is good</u>
<u n="880" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="881" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0013">we didn't mess up last year</u>
<u n="883" who="S0012">we did mess up last year didn't we?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0013">huh</u>
<u n="885" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="886" who="S0013">oh yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0152">just one of those things <pause dur="short"/> I am thinking if I've got the girls for the whole of that week I might see if I can go up to the Dales for a couple of days with them</u>
<u n="888" who="S0012">yeah? That'll be nice</u>
<u n="889" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="890" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0152">just go up to the Dales</u>
<u n="892" who="S0012">what anywhere?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's <trunc>c</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they like it up there don't they</u>
<u n="895" who="S0152">well they've never been to the well they like it up there <pause dur="short"/> they've never been to the Dales <pause dur="short"/> and I think it'd be good to take them there</u>
<u n="896" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I I thought you'd been to the Dales with them</u>
<u n="897" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="898" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="899" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually said <trunc>s</trunc> something the other day <pause dur="short"/> she says I can remember a place where we stopped and there was ducks</u>
<u n="900" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0013">oh really?</u>
<u n="902" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0152">Cos</u>
<u n="904" who="S0013">could be lots of places couldn't it</u>
<u n="905" who="S0152">so I said er she says we we used to come out the door she says <pause dur="short"/> and we would walk round the corner and there were ducks <pause dur="short"/> and the picture used to be on the side</u>
<u n="906" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="907" who="S0152">and that was in two thousand</u>
<u n="908" who="S0012">what?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0152">that was October two thousand</u>
<u n="910" who="S0012">well she weren't very old then was she</u>
<u n="911" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="912" who="S0152">she was two and a half</u>
<u n="913" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Two and a half?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0152">well she was cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was born in two <trunc>th</trunc> July two thousand</u>
<u n="916" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="918" who="S0152">and we went up to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="919" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0152">but we didn't stay at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> we stayed at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and there was a canal that runs er the there was a no it wasn't a canal it was a stream at the back of where we stayed</u>
<u n="921" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0152">and that's where the ducks were</u>
<u n="923" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh right</u>
<u n="924" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="925" who="S0152">but she knew the picture <pause dur="short"/> and she says and I remember <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> slept in a drawer</u>
<u n="926" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I remember you telling us that</u>
<u n="927" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="928" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> slept in a drawer</u>
<u n="930" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0152"><trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="933" who="S0012">she was very small <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="934" who="S0152">she was</u>
<u n="935" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0152">but that's</u>
<u n="937" who="S0013">would be the first party she came to um as well</u>
<u n="938" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="941" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0013">she's <trunc>te</trunc> ten days old weren't she</u>
<u n="944" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0012">ten days old <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="947" who="S0012">we had a party outside</u>
<u n="948" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0012">didn't we</u>
<u n="950" who="S0013">tiny weren't she</u>
<u n="951" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0012">remember them coming</u>
<u n="953" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="954" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="955" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> where does time go?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0012">I don't know where it goes <pause dur="short"/> that's amazing <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's twelve years</u>
<u n="958" who="S0152">mm <pause dur="short"/> twelve years since she</u>
<u n="959" who="S0013">we've got all the pictures of him in a big thing</u>
<u n="960" who="S0152">twelve years this year</u>
<u n="961" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="962" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="963" who="S0152">and what has happened in those twelve years eh?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0012">well quite a lot has happened to you in that twelve years</u>
<u n="966" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="967" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="968" who="S0152">yep</u>
<u n="969" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="970" who="S0152">so</u>
<u n="971" who="S0012">yes <pause dur="short"/> quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> would you go through it all again?</u>
<u n="972" who="S0152">I don't think you have a choice do you <pause dur="short"/> if it's gonna happen it's gonna happen</u>
<u n="973" who="S0012">that is ain't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0013">yep</u>
<u n="975" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing you can do about it you see</u>
<u n="976" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="977" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0013">choose the path you want to take <pause dur="short"/> and er that's the way it goes isn't it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="979" who="S0012">well sometimes you don't get a chance to choose the path</u>
<u n="980" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="981" who="S0012">the path is</u>
<u n="982" who="S0013">not always</u>
<u n="983" who="S0012">chosen for you <pause dur="short"/> and you can't help but stumble down the hill <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0152">true <pause dur="short"/> you can't  you can't  No matter what path you think you wanna take</u>
<u n="985" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="986" who="S0152">you can't</u>
<u n="987" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="988" who="S0013">and you'll never know the other bit</u>
<u n="989" who="S0012">no you'll never know the other bit</u>
<u n="990" who="S0013">what would've happened if um</u>
<u n="991" who="S0012">what would've happened if you'd have taken the left-hand path instead of the right-hand path</u>
<u n="992" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="993" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="994" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0152">could've been far worse couldn't it</u>
<u n="996" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="998" who="S0012">I wonder if you <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="999" who="S0013">sliding Doors</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0012">if you  if you  have a a life elsewhere where you er took that path</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0152">took the other path</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort of parallel parallel universe</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0152">parallel <pause dur="short"/> well you might do mightn't you?</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0152">can you just imagine? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0013">it is that film Sliding Doors</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0012">that is Sliding Doors <pause dur="short"/> yeah sorry</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0013">where she shows both sides of it</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you've gotta have that <trunc>ima</trunc> you've gotta have that imagination haven't you <pause dur="short"/> to be able to</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0152">say that's the way it's gonna go</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0012">yes <pause dur="short"/> you have <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean some people are really lucky and take take the path that lead them to fame and fortune <pause dur="short"/> others are not quite so lucky but it'll lead them to satisfaction in life</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0152">yeah that's what you need really is satisfaction isn't it</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0012">course it is</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0152">I think er if you've got satisfaction that's that's the best bit <pause dur="short"/> but it's when you haven't got the satisfaction that it's</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0012">and others decide not to take the path at all and just sit round eating and getting fat <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0013">yep</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0012">Don't they?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0012">when you watch them <pause dur="short"/> when you see them</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0013">A lot do with your character though isn't it? Whether you've got ambition or not</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0012">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's a lot to do with your parents too</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0013">well mostly to do with parents</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0012">I think it's a lot to do with parents <pause dur="short"/> I mean your parents were self-employed and my</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0012">our parents were both self-employed</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0012">you know <pause dur="short"/> and they guide you on the right path on a path that they think's good for you</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0152">I think it also depends how strong you are as a character</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0152">because some people just give up</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0152">it gets to a point where you can you just wanna give up</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was watching um Norwich <trunc>Cit</trunc> did you see Norwich City?</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> well anyway they got  they got  this er community service going <pause dur="short"/> and they got er like prisoners <pause dur="short"/> borstal people <pause dur="short"/> er people that er don't do much <pause dur="short"/> and they joined <pause dur="short"/> and they you know they go round asking them to join this <pause dur="short"/> and they play football</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0012">t the weekend <pause dur="short"/> and these blokes I mean they're fairly old I mean er you're you're talking about thirty and forty year er <trunc>o</trunc> old blokes <pause dur="short"/> saying that they'd wished they'd known that this was going on before <pause dur="short"/> and they're people that are sleeping rough <pause dur="short"/> but what I can't understand is they smoke like troopers <pause dur="short"/> they sleep rough <pause dur="short"/> they reckon they got no money <pause dur="short"/> and they're tattooed from top to bottom</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0012">well they've got money to do all the tattoos and all stuff</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0152">but is it the case the people are doing the tattoos are using them as experiments to do the tattoos on?</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Could well be</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0152">so therefore these people wanna tattoo so therefore they'll be like the guinea-pig</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0152">or they're trying their tattoos out</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0012">mm <pause dur="short"/> the nice bit about it was</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0012">with the kids I mean the fifteen-year-old kids that</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0012">you know like <trunc>y</trunc> you deal with</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0012">they're <trunc>tha</trunc> that <trunc>ty</trunc> <trunc>t</trunc> type of kids <pause dur="short"/> they were really enjoying the girls and the boys they were really enjoying it all <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0012">but as for the older people I don't know what happened to them <pause dur="short"/> do you? I don't know why they get into that</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0012">position <pause dur="short"/> they seem to  they seem to  relish in the position they're in <pause dur="short"/> and then they well I dunno</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0152">I think you're right when er huh you said about parents <pause dur="short"/> er hm  er hm  it is very much about what or where people live</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0012">where people live come into it quite a bit don't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0152">because if they see it happening around them</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0152">then it becomes the norm</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0152">so therefore that's what you do</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0012">that's what you do <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0152">but it's also like hm er <trunc>c</trunc> it's a  it's a  culture thing isn't it <pause dur="short"/> a culture</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0012">it is a culture thing <pause dur="short"/> trouble is <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0013">I mean you you said from going to school that you were never given the the even thought that you could go on to further education</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0012">never</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0013">or anything <unclear/></u>
<u n="1085" who="S0012">never given the chance</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0013">left school early</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0012">didn't even know there was a further education <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1088" who="S0013">whereas it was pushed my school you went <vocal desc="laugh"/> on to do <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0152">but was that because again back to that area</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0013">well mm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0012">I don't know but we were expected as a secondary school to take up not the academics</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0152">the the apprenticeship route</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0012">but the apprenticeship route <pause dur="short"/> and when <trunc>y</trunc> when you were fifteen you left school and worked a year before you got your apprenticeship <pause dur="short"/> so we had to work a year to see if you were any good</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0012">and if you were any good you er you got an apprenticeship</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0152">got offered an apprenticeship</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0012">I mean it didn't cost anything</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0013">but you weren't given loads of options were you?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0012">we were given no options <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0152">I don't think you I</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0152">but going back I don't think the options were there as such</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0012">well <pause dur="short"/> the point is I don't think the people who had er like the you had the these people come round and interview you not interview you talk to you about your future and your jobs</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0152">careers people</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0012">the careers people <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they had any idea <pause dur="short"/> because they had their careers they didn't give two monkeys about other people</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0012">especially what they looked at as second class citizens</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0152">yeah but at your <trunc>t</trunc> but at that point in time all the people with certain level qualifications ended up working at Norwich Union</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0152">and on the  on the  other side you had people going either into work at Carters or Laurence and Scott</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0012">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0152">or Autowrappers was Autowrappers?</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0012">yeah <trunc>Au</trunc> Autowrappers</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0152">autowrappers</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0012">heatrae</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0152">heatrae <pause dur="short"/> there was jobs that</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or Matthews Turkeys</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0012">british tin box company the</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> you had er you had those people filling those jobs there <pause dur="short"/> so there was never that issue</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0152">of you had what you had <trunc>f</trunc> Smiths Crackers didn't you?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0152">Cos that was people</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0013">on rotation</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0012"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0152">um <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sta</trunc></u>
<u n="1132" who="S0012">you worked there didn't you?</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0152">start-rite</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I did part-time</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0152">start-rite shoes</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there was I tell you the shoe factories in Norwich were enormous <pause dur="short"/> there was Norfolk Start-rite er Clarks <pause dur="short"/> there was loads <pause dur="short"/> absolutely loads of shoe factories in Norwich <pause dur="short"/> plus there was that great big um Courtaulds factory as well</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0152">mhm</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0012">A huge Courtaulds factory <pause dur="short"/> then all of a sudden they're gone <pause dur="short"/> well what happened to all these people? Just like the steel works up in <trunc>Cor</trunc> Corby and all that <pause dur="short"/> they're just chucked out aren't they? Shame <pause dur="short"/> but then we had the chance <pause dur="short"/> I mean when when we were young when I was young when I'd done my apprenticeship I could walk into any job and demand well not demand but ask er the pay I wanted</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0012">and either they give it to you or they didn't <pause dur="short"/> and there was so much work about</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0012">loads of work about</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0152">but if you look at what work is available now</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0152">it's all shop work</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0012">well it's all service <trunc>indus</trunc> industry</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0152">it's all it's service industries</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0152">I mean</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0152">that's all that is er is around <pause dur="short"/> unless you <trunc>l</trunc> go into these little industrial villages type thing</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0152">where people take some more people on</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0012">but I mean this is  this is  half the reason half the people er leave the countryside and go to huge cities <pause dur="short"/> because they think they'll be able to get jobs better <pause dur="short"/> I mean you think about the countryside and how many people worked on farms in the sixties and seventies even</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0012">which isn't that long ago <pause dur="short"/> and now you got one farmer and a boy to a couple of hundred acres of land</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0152">machinery has</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0152">taken over hasn't it</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0152">and the way you farm things make er makes it easier</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0012">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0152"><unclear/> make it easier <unclear/></u>
<u n="1167" who="S0012">but that used to be good  that used to be good  but now uh I I feel so sorry for the kids nowadays</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0152">well they <trunc>d</trunc> huh they don't take on board what you tell them <pause dur="short"/> some of them</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0152">you know I I don't need this qualification</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0012">well that's true <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0152">but you do need the qualification</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0152">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> you don't know me <pause dur="short"/> um <vocal desc="laugh"/> I might not know you but I know full well that you need the piece of paper that opens a door</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0152">otherwise you're just gonna end up doing nothing</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0152">which is why which is what I've witnessed</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0012">well er</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0152">recently</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0012">well you have <trunc>w</trunc> you've had quite a lot of experience in kids haven't you all them years working?</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0012">but as you say they don't they don't take on in <trunc>boar</trunc> on board the advice any more</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> and when you say to them look you know you're not the first person that has has turned round and said you don't care <pause dur="short"/> I says but you're not won't be the first person that in five years time or ten years time or fifteen years time will turn round and say I wish I'd have tried at school</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0152">I says because the majority of people that at your stage five ten fifteen it will happen <pause dur="short"/> you'll say you wish you'd have tried when you realize you're not getting everything that you want</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0152">what I felt like saying is but in some cases you'll nick what you want so</u>
<u n="1191" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1192" who="S0012">well that's true</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0013">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0012">that is true</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0013">huh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1196" who="S0012">in some cases that that's what they do <pause dur="short"/> and last resorts let's face it they go onto drugs</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0152">mm <pause dur="short"/> you know  you know if  if <trunc>par</trunc> I'm sorry but if parents know that their child is taking drugs shouldn't something be done about it? Huh</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I should've thought so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0152">but it's okay for him to do it at weekends as long as he doesn't during the week</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0152">that's the attitude of one family</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0012">hm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0152">that I've heard of recently</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0013">huh <pause dur="short"/> gosh</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0152">because it's er because again it's in this area</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0152">that's where it all happens from</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0152">and you're thinking to yourself this is not</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0012">it's not good is it</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0152">it's not good</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0013">they just they don't care do they</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0152">you know</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0013">parents just don't care</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0152">it's like  it's like  drinking</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0012">well yeah</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0152">I mean you know I'm not  I'm not  knocking it or anything <pause dur="short"/> because when you're sixteen or fifteen you do try <pause dur="short"/> you try it on</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0012">course you do</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0012">that's what teenagers are about</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0152">and you know and <trunc>cer</trunc> certainly when you're sixteen <pause dur="short"/> when you're just about to leave school <pause dur="short"/> you are trying it on <pause dur="short"/> in parties or whatever</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0012">yeah it's</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0152">you you you do <pause dur="short"/> but it's when it's not it's when it's the it's happening on a regular basis <pause dur="short"/> cos it's that's what you do when you're sixteen <pause dur="short"/> is the bit that</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0152">is not it's not right</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0012">that's not right <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> when I was sixteen my mum and dad went out to see my gran in hospital <pause dur="short"/> um my grandad in hospital rather <pause dur="short"/> and there was the cocktail cabinet <pause dur="short"/> you know they had the</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0012">cocktail cabinets then didn't they <pause dur="short"/> and they had some rum in there <pause dur="short"/> and the next thing I knew they'd come home and woke me up <pause dur="short"/> and there was the rum <pause dur="short"/> and I I've never drop never tasted a drop of rum since <pause dur="short"/> even them little stupid rum and butters</u>
<u n="1233" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0012">rum and butter sweets</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0013">sweet <unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0012">oh <pause dur="short"/> that put me off rum forever <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But I was ill <pause dur="short"/> really ill</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0012">sixteen years old <pause dur="short"/> dear oh dear <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what they did <pause dur="short"/> whether whether they were angry or not <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1240" who="S0152">but you  but you</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0013">didn't need to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0152">no but you <trunc>lear</trunc> but you learn from it</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0012">you do</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0152">but unfortunately youngsters at the moment don't learn from that experience</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>b</trunc> because they dare each other to do some more</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0152">you know</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0012">that's the trouble <trunc>w</trunc> where you got peer pressure</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0012">oh I can have I can drink this and I can drink that</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it <trunc>al</trunc> but it also but it's also when you get older I I lose what what looked at somebody else's Twitter account <pause dur="short"/> quite a person quite high up within a within an organization <pause dur="short"/> and it was oh I'm just gonna have a few shots getting ready before the family come round</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0152">and you're thinking er why are you</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0013">why?</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0152">why do you need to do?</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0013">it's er it's wrong it's</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0152">why do you need to do it?</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0012">Strange</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0013">they haven't got enough confidence in themselves <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> something's gone wrong hasn't it</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> and it and it's that</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0152">you know to have a good time you've gotta get absolutely blottoed</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0152">mm <pause dur="short"/> I must be missing out somewhere <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Maybe that's where I've gone wrong all these years</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1267" who="S0013"><unclear/> we never had enough money anyway to</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> that is  that is  another point ain't it</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0012">where do they get their money nowadays? When there's hardly any work <pause dur="short"/> yet they can go out and get absolutely legless <pause dur="short"/> most well at least three times a week <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>l</trunc> look down</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0012">Norwich</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0152">I think a lot of them drink before they go</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0152">so once they're there they just top it up</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0012">they do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0012">we had a</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0012">when we were doing this um what was it? The the first aid stuff</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0012">we had that old boy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't we</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0013">we did</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0012">he worked on a voluntary bus <pause dur="short"/> and he said oh the stuff I see <pause dur="short"/> cos he used to go out</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0012">um collecting these</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0012">young girls</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0152">what the SOS bus?</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0013">he used to stress all the time <pause dur="short"/> make sure they're covered up</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0013">you know</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0012">make sure they're covered up</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0012">and keep their dignity <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0012">but these</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0013">Cos they looked so awful</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0012">but they wear next to nothing</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0012">pff <pause dur="short"/> dear oh dear <pause dur="short"/> my mum wouldn't let me go on out without my vest on <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1303" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0012">clean vest and pants in case you had an accident</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That was great weren't it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1307" who="S0152">I <trunc>d</trunc> er pff</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know what it is</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0012">no I <trunc>s</trunc> that that seem to have seem to go on over over the top don't it <pause dur="short"/> in these recent years <pause dur="short"/> but then you gotta <trunc>ha</trunc> blame half of the stuff on on er the powers that be</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0012">for allowing it to happen in the first place <pause dur="short"/> I mean the police can't do anything <pause dur="short"/> when I was a kid if you were drunk in the street they'd have you for drunk and disorderly</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just think how many people would be done on a Saturday night now</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but if they'd have carried that on there wouldn't have been so many now would there <pause dur="short"/> if they just instead of letting them  letting them  walk the streets</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0012">absolutely blotto and pissed <pause dur="short"/> breaking windows and peeing up walls and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0013">you see the pubs used to close early</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they used to close at eleven o'clock</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0013">you know perhaps</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0152">half past five half past ten wasn't it</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0013">different before</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0012">half past ten on a Sunday weren't it</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0012">and eleven o'clock the rest of the week</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0013">open it later anyway</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's was cos last orders was half ten</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ten minute drinking up time used to have</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0152">and you were  and you were  out by</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0152">eleven o'clock</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0013">so it made a huge difference didn't it <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0012">well they wanted to go Continental didn't they</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0012">but I mean that's only recently that the they've had pubs open all the time <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1338" who="S0152">but it's made no difference</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0012">that's made no difference at all <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0152">I think in some respects that side of it apart from the number of pubs closing down because there isn't the money around that bit's alright <pause dur="short"/> it's this  it's this  binge drinking on a <trunc>Th</trunc></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0012">the binge drinking <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0152">Thursday Friday</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0152">Saturday night <pause dur="short"/> the likes of <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="1345" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0152">where you've got all those bars</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0152">and you're in and out  and you're in and out</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0013">and the happy hours and</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0013">tut</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0012">mind you they're supposed to have stopped the happy hours haven't they?</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0012">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> er I mean there was a time when you could go down these places and and walk feeling safe <pause dur="short"/> but now you got all these drunkards about</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0152">you're on your guard <pause dur="short"/> and when I went into the city I <trunc>d</trunc> in all the years that I've lived in <anon type="place"/> I've only been down the <anon type="place"/> twice <pause dur="short"/> and never really fancied it <pause dur="short"/> never done</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0152">never done that <pause dur="short"/> but I felt quite intimidated</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0152">walking back to the car park</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0152">maybe it's cos I was by myself <pause dur="short"/> at least if er there's the two of you you're</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0012">well that's right <pause dur="short"/> I'm always huh worrying about people walking behind you now <pause dur="short"/> if you're  if you're  down them sort of places <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> ain't it weird <pause dur="short"/> not maybe you</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0012">get like that as you get older</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0152">get older</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0012">cos when we were kids I remember when we were kids we used to go and stand outside the fish shop under the light <pause dur="short"/> cos that was the only light in the village <pause dur="short"/> and we used to just talk</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0012">and at eight o'clock every single evening night the copper used to come along on his bike and go come on lads move along  move along  We're getting complaints about you <pause dur="short"/> complaints? We're not doing anything <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> we were just <trunc>stand</trunc> and this is where the resentment come in <pause dur="short"/> cos you start to think well where else have we got to go? Where do we go?</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> was silly weren't it</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0152">you've never they've never put anything in for youngsters <pause dur="short"/> teenagers <pause dur="short"/> you have the youth club but not everybody wants to go to a youth club</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0012">well the youth</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0012">club we used to go to you used to get the vicar come in and say come along we gotta say prayers <pause dur="short"/> well what kid want to do that?</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it's not see er <trunc>w</trunc> huh I feel a lot easier walking around Paris of a night-time than down the <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="1378" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0152">and that's quite and that's</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0012">well I suppose Paris have got their own little roads that are no go areas as well</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0152">oh there will be <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0012">you know</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0152">at the same time it's er it  er it  feels a lot</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0012">well I er I've I've walked up up the walk you know in in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think that's the <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc> middle of <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="1388" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0012">and you think mm <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> mm <pause dur="short"/> and we were walking that was ages ago we were walking down past um the guildhall</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0012">walking down the hill past the guildhall</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0012">and just behind the guildhall there's a water trough ain't there <pause dur="short"/> there's an old</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the old where the taxi rank is</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and there was all these people <pause dur="short"/> they just shouted at us didn't they <pause dur="short"/> what</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0013">they</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0012">you looking at? And all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0013">Don't remember</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0012">we were with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="1400" who="S0013">no we</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0012">and we just looked over there at that was one Christmas time <pause dur="short"/> we were walking around it</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0012">and we were with you know <unclear/> me you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> walking down</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0013">must've been all of us then <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0012">huh?</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0013">must've been all of us then</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0012"> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was very small then</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0013">oh I see</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I just happened to look over toward the guildhall <pause dur="short"/> and there was these all these people</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0012"><trunc>Sh</trunc> they were drinking</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0012">and drugs and what have you <pause dur="short"/> and this was a long while ago now <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1414" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0012">over thirty years ago <pause dur="short"/> and then I went in</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0012">the loo at the  at the  er marketplace</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0012">walked in there <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="1420" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0012">and there was this bloke just been bottled <pause dur="short"/> face was pouring with blood</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0012">and I walked out again <pause dur="short"/> just as I walked out there was two coppers walking along the top of the um er up the  up the  steps</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0012">and I went and said you you should go in there <pause dur="short"/> and they just said no we shouldn't <pause dur="short"/> they didn't bother did they</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0012">but they know the where the cos all along that nice little bit where the where them little gardens were above the <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="1428" who="S0152">what at the war memorial park?</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0013">they've changed it now</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0152">they've changed it all <unclear/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0012">but there used to be loads of drunks lying there</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> laying on the benches <unclear/></u>
<u n="1437" who="S0012">laying on the benches down there <pause dur="short"/> but they've cleaned that up now <pause dur="short"/> you daren't walk through there at one and that was a beautiful little walk <trunc>w</trunc> where the gardens were and</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0012">weren't it</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0152">they've <trunc>ju</trunc> they've er redone it all now so</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> remember when they did the the fountain outside C and As <pause dur="short"/> there used to be all lawns up there <pause dur="short"/> and they put a fountain in didn't they</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> do you remember that that statue is?</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0013">I think that statue is still there</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0012">there's a statue still there <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0013">the the writer or something isn't it</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0012">and that used to be lawns where all the students</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0013"></u>
<u n="1450" who="S0012">used to sit and and</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0012">have a really nice time <pause dur="short"/> and then they concreted it and put this big</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0013">that was lovely there</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0012">that was lovely <pause dur="short"/> and they stuck this big</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0012">fountain er pond with a fountain <pause dur="short"/> and what did <vocal desc="laugh"/> what did they do? Stuck Fairy Liquid in it didn't they</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0012">and it just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1459" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1461" who="S0013">now it's all shut down anyway</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0012">now that's shut down</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0012">total waste of money <pause dur="short"/> total waste of time <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0152">it's not there any more is it?</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0012">waste er</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0013"><unclear/> fountain</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0012">waste of a  of a  beautiful spot where people used</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0013">it was a nice everyone used to go picnic there</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0012">have a picnic area didn't they <pause dur="short"/> and just sit around</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0013">round this statue <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it takes maintenance doesn't it</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0012">well only a lawn</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0013">what with grass?</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0152">yeah you <trunc>g</trunc> you gotta get the mower in there <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta get</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0012">think of the  think of the  maintenance that it took with this water fountain <pause dur="short"/> well that's why they shut down</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0152">well you think of how how many times they've changed the footpaths around</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0152">right</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0152">so years ago it was we'll get rid of all the flagstones</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0012">yep</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0152">and we'll tarmac it</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0152">few years later all the tarmac comes up</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0152">and they start putting Brickweave down</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0012">brickweave down</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0152">few years later Brickweave doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> they then start putting flagstones back down <unclear/></u>
<u n="1498" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0013">cobbles so that</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0152"><unclear/> cobble</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0013">cars can</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1504" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0152">and if you take you know then if you take about what they've done round the Forum <pause dur="short"/> they had to replace all the <trunc>s</trunc> flagstones which were there</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0012">they did didn't they <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0152">because they were too soft</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0013">oh really?</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0152">and they were all <vocal desc="laugh"/> wearing they were wearing out</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know about that one</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0012">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> well they certainly know how to spend money</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0012">well they used used to be a time where they used to have to get rid of their money pot before the end of April didn't they</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0012">otherwise they wouldn't get it allocated again</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0012">the next year <pause dur="short"/> so they used to just waste it</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pathetic <pause dur="short"/> rather than carry it over and do something better</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0152">Cos you can't do that in schools</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0152">where I am at the moment I still think I was telling you where I am at the moment they have kept their budget in credit</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0152">right <pause dur="short"/> they can't get they get how they want to get rid of some staff <pause dur="short"/> these staff</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0152">want to retire</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0152">alright? But they want to go maybe a year early or two years earlier</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0152">but because the school keeps its budget on line they can't make them retire <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Because they can't pay them to retire</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0152">if the school was in a deficit budget and they needed to get rid of these members of staff then they would get help on</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0013">they'd get help</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0012">getting rid of</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0152">getting rid of</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0013">they could <trunc>cre</trunc> they couldn't use the <vocal desc="laugh"/> use the credit then?</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0013">no?</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0012">that's pathetic ain't it</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0013">how weird</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> totally weird</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0012">well that's the situation <trunc>ev</trunc> that's er in all over the place <pause dur="short"/> the councils are the same</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not good for you to save money either um if you're</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0013">on any sort of benefits <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just think it's silly</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0152">er</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0013">anyone who's got any savings then er</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0152">he was at <unclear/></u>
<u n="1558" who="S0013">lose out</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's I'm I retweeted an article about academies</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0152">now I don't know how far it will go <pause dur="short"/> but it came from somebody who had had done some work at OBA Academy</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0152">and it was saying that <trunc>Worcestersh</trunc> Worcestershire County Council was questioning the role of academies <pause dur="short"/> because when you have an authority who looks after the schools</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0152">you've got some accountability</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0152">who are the academies accountable to?</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0012">well that's true <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> who are they?</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0152">are are they accountable to the government?</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0152">because the government have allowed them to become academies</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0012">academies <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0152">or are they accountable to their sponsors?</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0152">which isn't the government <pause dur="short"/> it's their sponsors <pause dur="short"/> are their sponsors then accountable to the government? So who's in charge? So where do you get the accountability?</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hm</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0012">Cos the council has got nothing to do with them any more</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0152">nothing to do with them</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0012">nothing at all to do with them</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0152">nothing to do</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0012">that is  that is  a thought that is ain't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1585" who="S0152">and you you kind of think that you know here's a person that is working for an academy <pause dur="short"/> has been an adviser in one of the academies <pause dur="short"/> who is <trunc>re</trunc> who is tweeting that out</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the trouble is you see the people that are working within the <trunc>c</trunc> the academies are getting so much money they just don't care</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0152">they don't care <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> I had a  I had a  text this week from somebody from OBA Academy <vocal desc="laugh"/> saying that they cannot buy anything  they cannot buy anything  They can't do any er they've got no money</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1589" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> How do you work that one out?</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0152">and what they're saying is it's all because the er predecessor school had a deficit budget <pause dur="short"/> predecessor school had a deficit budget but it had nothing to do with the OBA budget</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0152">because it was wiped clean on the thirty-first of August</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0152">when it became an academy <pause dur="short"/> that deficit budget was <trunc>s</trunc> shared amongst all the other schools within the</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0152">county</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0152">so they all got a little bit less to cover that budget</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1601" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> and when you take all the schools though <pause dur="short"/> it well it didn't work out to be that much <pause dur="short"/> but some heads are saying it did <pause dur="short"/> but but this OBA are saying they have no money so they can't do things</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1605" who="S0013">tut</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0152">which</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0152">you know where that's gonna lead to? That's gonna lead to saying</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0152">we've gotta cut some more staff</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0012">well yeah</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and even more good teachers'll go <pause dur="short"/> down to the</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0012">er the great teacher pit <pause dur="short"/> and what'll happen? They'll have teachers that can't teach</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0152">oh well er <trunc>w</trunc> what will will happen is they'll have teachers in there for two years three years then they'll be burnt out because of the pressure they've been put under or the way they've been treated</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0152">and some will end up with nervous breakdowns <pause dur="short"/> some will end up not carrying um on in teaching where that's where they need to be</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0152">and some people will will move on to doing something else</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0152">and they'll keep the costs down by having lots of NQT teachers in for three or four years where they don't have to</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0152">pay them a certain amount of money</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's that's what I mean</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0013">or parents doing some bit of voluntary work to help out</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> tut</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0012">do they still use parents in academies? Or not?</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> they try and <trunc>k</trunc></u>
<u n="1635" who="S0012">they only use them in <trunc>pri</trunc> private schools?</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0013"><unclear/> just the little schools</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0152">in the little schools <pause dur="short"/> they try and keep parents out</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> you don't want parents do you <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0152">they try and keep parents out</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0152">or they mm</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0152">try and tell them things which are not going on</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's wicked</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0013">Don't need parents in schools</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> they interfere too much</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1649" who="S0152">you don't want  you don't want  people who care in schools in academies</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0012">well that's right <pause dur="short"/> er it er it's like the <trunc>n</trunc> the nursing <pause dur="short"/> nurses and <trunc>w</trunc> they they used to have a vocation <pause dur="short"/> now they've just got a job <pause dur="short"/> and they've only just got that job <pause dur="short"/> so they that's not a vocational job any more <pause dur="short"/> it's just a job that they have to do day in and day out <pause dur="short"/> cos they don't get any appreciation for it</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0152">everybody's</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0152">quick to moan</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0152"><trunc>W</trunc> certainly when it comes</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0152">to</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0013">well</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0012">I mean <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc> you get these like with Norfolk and Norwich Hospital <pause dur="short"/> it isn't it's a <trunc>p</trunc> privatized hospital almost <pause dur="short"/> because it's run by sponsors</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0012">and people that</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0152">it's a trust isn't it</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0012">it's a trust <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> our doctors is a trust <pause dur="short"/> and they have they get paid and then they have er money taken out <pause dur="short"/> they have to pay the Norfolk and Norwich Hospital for everybody they send there <pause dur="short"/> it's weird ain't it</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> strange</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0152">it's one <trunc>po</trunc> one pot of money <pause dur="short"/> why can't you just share it?</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0012">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> because they're supposed to be the National Health Service</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0152">but isn't but that's what the doctors are arguing about <pause dur="short"/> they don't want that responsibility</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0012">well that's er right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0152">that shouldn't it shouldn't be they shouldn't have that responsibility</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0152">but if you put people that are managers in all they do is want to cut back things and</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0152">save the money</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0012">of course they do</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0012">but I mean the matrons in hospital used to keep keep the wards running didn't they <pause dur="short"/> then you had the <trunc>s</trunc>  the <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> sisters  sisters <pause dur="short"/> and then you had the staff nurse <pause dur="short"/> well the staff nurse and then the sisters whatever happened <pause dur="short"/> and then just the ordinary <trunc>n</trunc> nurses <pause dur="short"/> and then the porters and everyone <pause dur="short"/> they all had their job to do <pause dur="short"/> and they enjoyed doing the job <pause dur="short"/> now the all they got to do is turn over  turn over turn over  I mean people used to go into hospital and occupy a bed for a couple of days or more <pause dur="short"/> because they were ill <pause dur="short"/> now they're kicked out</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0152">if we can get you home then that's the best isn't it</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0012">I mean you used to go to the maternity hospital and have the baby and stay in for er until they were thought they were okay to go home <pause dur="short"/> now they're kicked out</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0152">twenty-four hours isn't it <unclear/></u>
<u n="1683" who="S0012">twenty-four hour turn-over</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0012">and they still reckon they haven't got any money <pause dur="short"/> when they got all this turn-over going on <pause dur="short"/> that's the administrators</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0012">you know <pause dur="short"/> they don't care about people's health <pause dur="short"/> they don't care about people's education any more <pause dur="short"/> well that's what it seem like anyway <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0152">they they wanna cut back on all the good things</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0152">that's what they that's what they're doing in education <pause dur="short"/> they're cutting back <pause dur="short"/> some of the things needed to be come back cut back <pause dur="short"/> some of the courses which were on offer for making league tables look good <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> did need to get chopped back</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0152">but it's gonna have a knock-on effect on what pupils choose <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has picked her options</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0012">has she's picked her</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0012">options has she?</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0152">she knows what she's gonna do</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0013">doing art?</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0152"><trunc>D</trunc> doing art and history</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0013">and history</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0012">brilliant</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0152">she's gone away from the catering and the textiles</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0012">Don't she wanna do that any more? No?</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0013">oh I thought it was gonna be art textile no?</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0013">just er plain art</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0152">just art</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0152">just art and history <pause dur="short"/> because of what she wants to do</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0013">what does she want to do?</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0152">she wants to be</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0013"><trunc>D</trunc></u>
<u n="1715" who="S0152">psychiatric person</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0152">something like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0152">so she checked out the er university qualifications and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0013">gosh</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0152">and the first thing she said to me was the two places that do the course that I'm thinking about if I go to university is Cumbria University</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0152">and the UEA</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0012">oh right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1725" who="S0013">oh so</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1727" who="S0013">let's hope she goes to Cumbria <pause dur="short"/> that'd be lovely wouldn't it</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1729" who="S0152">that's the first thing that she said</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0012">so she's either looking for the</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0013">gosh</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0012">she's got the torch and the</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0013"><unclear/> that now <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1736" who="S0013"><unclear/> yet</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0152">she had a good report this week <pause dur="short"/> I didn't go to the  I didn't go to the  parents' evening cos on Tuesday <unclear/> for this one <pause dur="short"/> but got a really good report <pause dur="short"/> big change in attitude in maths <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> working really well in</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0152">lots of things</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0152">science is good <pause dur="short"/> english is good <pause dur="short"/> she's come <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="1742" who="S0013">mhm</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0152">coming round in English <pause dur="short"/> er which is  which is  good to see <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1746" who="S0152">which is nice</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0013">ah</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0012">Will you took a photo of her door?</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0152"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1750" who="S0012">you ought to take a photo of her door <pause dur="short"/> and a photo of her room <pause dur="short"/> and then I can tell her she's a little older</u>
<u n="1751" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1752" who="S0013">but don't show her <unclear/></u>
<u n="1753" who="S0012">Don't show her</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1755" who="S0012">wait until she's older <pause dur="short"/> and this is how you used to live <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1756" who="S0013">aw</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0012">that's why we took a photo of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room <pause dur="short"/> I mean you could not see the floor for all her paperwork and clothes <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't see the floor could you</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0013">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s they're still like that really</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0012">well that's</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0013">but they they make a huge mess <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then they do a real <trunc>r</trunc> brilliant blitz</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0012">then they</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0013">they clean it all up</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0012">they clean it all up <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0013">um when they can't stand it any more <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1766" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's er</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0012">but the photograph we got went missing didn't it <pause dur="short"/> she pinched it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos we weren't allowed to show it to anybody</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That was a lovely picture</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0012">that was a great picture</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dirty hovel</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <unclear/></u>
<u n="1773" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1774" who="S0013">it wasn't dirty <pause dur="short"/> it was just</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> it was just</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0013">it was her working space</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0012">her working space <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> She didn't didn't work in there</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Papers papers papers <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1780" who="S0152">that's what it's about <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit like the study really</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0013">it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0152">bit like my study <pause dur="short"/> although that's quite tidy at the moment</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0013">well I I've got nothing to say just</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0152">Cos I've done nothing in</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0012">well our study is useless</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0013">I I'm terrible</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0012">well you are <pause dur="short"/> but I mean I</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1789" who="S0012">I'm very clean</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1791" who="S0012">very clean</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1793" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0152">I think we hoard too much</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0012">Gawd yeah</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0013">I know we do</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0012">oh <pause dur="short"/> I went and helped a friend of ours</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0013">I know we do</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because er her <trunc>m</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum has now had to go into a home <pause dur="short"/> but she wanted a a chair and a few other bits and pieces to take with her <pause dur="short"/> and her house well her little bungalow is full of everything <pause dur="short"/> and I thought huh you know <pause dur="short"/> and I remember sorting my mum's house out <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0012">you think oh gawd look at it all <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0012">they'll never be able to sort ours out will they <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1806" who="S0152">I I keep <trunc>j</trunc> I keep I you know cos if I'm gonna sell I keep thinking of what I need to do <pause dur="short"/> even just like the shed</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0013">it's</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you start sorting things out and think oh I'll keep that <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1812" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0013">that may come in useful <pause dur="short"/> I'll use that soon</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0013">but you don't er</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0013">another few years</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0013">you've still not used it <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0152">all the books that I got</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0152">do I look at them any more?</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0013">I've still got all the children's books haven't we</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we got</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0013">whole bookcase full of them</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0013">we've still got <trunc>s</trunc> loads of toys really <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0013">games</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0012">games</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0012">we got jigsaws galore</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0013">I've got to keep loads really for</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0012">for <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0013">when people do come <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0012">but the point is when they are the trouble is they're so old</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0013">some are <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0012">I mean the jigsaws are useless <pause dur="short"/> most jigsaws have have got bits missing</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0012">so what do you do with them? You can't give them to jumble-sale <pause dur="short"/> you can't do anything with them <pause dur="short"/> all the all they're fit for is recycle bin <pause dur="short"/> and then we've got all this plastic toys</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0012">mm I mean that over there is full of toys</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0013">I did go to a car boot and get rid of loads</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0012">the shed is full of toys</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0013">the toys went really well</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0012">they did didn't they</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0013">I obviously sold those too cheap</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0012">but how much did you make profit that day?</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0013">no nothing <pause dur="short"/> I sold them too cheap</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0012">one pound something profit <pause dur="short"/> and then they had to go</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1854" who="S0012">by car there and back</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1856" who="S0012">so really</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0013">huh</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0012">you might just as well have stuck them outside the gate</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0012">and said please help yourself</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0152">no I gotta have a big clear-up</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1866" who="S0152">oh</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0012">that'll do you good <pause dur="short"/> once you once you've done it all and looked you'll think guh how did I not do this before?</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0152">how much can I sell? How much can I get for what I've got? mm</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0012">we gotta do that too <pause dur="short"/> we bought a an extractor fan for the shower <pause dur="short"/> and we were told by the electrician that we <trunc>ca</trunc> they can't put it in because it's not for the inside the shower <pause dur="short"/> we we got in touch with the people that made it and they said yes it is</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0012">but the electrician said still said no</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0012">it's not <pause dur="short"/> so we had to get another shower another extractor fan in there</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0013">now we've got this really expensive one <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0012">now we've got this really expensive one we've gotta get rid of</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0012">so it's gotta go on eBay <pause dur="short"/> we paid two hundred quid for it <pause dur="short"/> we won't get fifty quid for it</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0012">it's never been used</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0013">you know when you buy you <trunc>w</trunc> you think it's probably the best at the time <pause dur="short"/> and we shouldn't have bothered</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0012">we shouldn't have bothered <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> should've just bought a cheaper one</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0012">this one's is a inline one you see <pause dur="short"/> and this one <trunc>w</trunc> the <trunc>oth</trunc> that one was in the inside the shower unit itself</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0013">but that one was gonna be inside the <trunc>u</trunc></u>
<u n="1886" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0013">shower unit</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but this one er is outside the shower unit <pause dur="short"/> the new one</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0013">no he said that's the only place I can put it <pause dur="short"/> outside <pause dur="short"/> I can't put it inside</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0152">why? That's what they're designed for</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0012">which one are you talking about? Now I'm talking about mm the new one what we got in now</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0013">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0012">it's an inline one <pause dur="short"/> and it's</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0013">okay <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0012">in the <trunc>p</trunc> pipework outside the shower unit <pause dur="short"/> it works from outside the shower unit <pause dur="short"/> up in the loft</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you have  so you have  a hole in the ceiling</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0152">then you have a tube that goes up and then halfway <trunc>alo</trunc></u>
<u n="1901" who="S0012">and then the motor inside</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0152">then halfway along that tube you have a motor</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0152">that sucks the air through</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0152">then goes out</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0012">then goes out <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what we got <pause dur="short"/> but the other one we were supposed to that one's supposed to fit inside the shower</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0152">right</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0012">but they said it's too dangerous didn't they</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0012">and when you think logically that is really</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0013">that is a bit weird one <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they said yeah <pause dur="short"/> fine for a shower</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0013"><unclear/> inside showers</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0012">and we even wrote to Xpelair <pause dur="short"/> and they said yes fine <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> got a condenser in it as well hasn't it?</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0012">it's got a condenser in it</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0012">as well you see</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0013">anyway <pause dur="short"/> we've got to get rid of that somehow</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0012">yep</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0013">take whatever we get offered really</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0013">Cos it'll only <trunc>st</trunc> I mean it's been here nearly a year now</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0012">that'll be nearly a year</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0013">so</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0012">since we <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0013">it'll just lay around the house deteriorating</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0013">well not deteriorating</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0152">not deteriorate just not using it</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0013">that's</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0152">you know Bennetts in Dereham's closing?</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0012">what little Bennetts?</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0152">no Bennetts next to Homebase</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0013">that's been on the plans for a long time</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0012">I thought that was Hughes <pause dur="short"/> owned by Hughes weren't it?</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0012">they gotta close it down?</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0152">it closes today</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0013">today</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0012">does it? Wow</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0013">that's been they've been talking about it for a long time</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0152">but yeah</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0012">that's gone has it? Oh gawd <pause dur="short"/> are they having a sale?</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0152">well there was reduction there's price reductions on in there <pause dur="short"/> er and then I mean I don't know what they're gonna do with the <trunc>s</trunc> they'll take all the stuff to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos that's where the big Bennetts place is now</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0013">oh they're still keeping some open?</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're still keeping some open</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0152">er <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> lowestoft</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0152">the Hall Road</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0012">well I don't suppose Bennetts of Dereham was that er</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0012">when they've got Hughes as well haven't they</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0152">oh Hughes in the precinct's doubled</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0152">which I thought was a bit silly <pause dur="short"/> you've got all that <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1967" who="S0013">I thought they were gonna close <unclear/></u>
<u n="1968" who="S0152">you've got all that space</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0012">up up the top</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0152">and the car parking</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0152">at Homebase</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0152">and then you keep the one in the centre of Dereham open</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0152">and doubled the <trunc>sp</trunc> shop space in there</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0152">where parking is a pain</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0012">terrible pain there ain't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0152">you know <pause dur="short"/> you're thinking what's what's um er it must be down to the the cost <pause dur="short"/> and I reckon the cost would be in the precinct they got a deal for five years where the rent will be of a certain</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0152">where that big place</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0152">by Homebase will be</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0152">the the Homebase should buy that and put other stuff into it</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they might do <pause dur="short"/> have they still got the bed stuff next door to?</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0152">carpetright</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0012">carpet <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0152">Cos Carpetright are doing beds now</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so there's er there's that'll just be Carpetright and</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0152">um <pause dur="short"/> homebase</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0012">Homebase now won't it</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and behind Homebase dunno what used to be behind Homebase <pause dur="short"/> is it er ah Gentiques used to be <trunc>behi</trunc></u>
<u n="2000" who="S0012">gentiques yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it was <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0152">well that's gone</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0012">that's gone has it?</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0152">that's flattened <pause dur="short"/> and I reckon they're gonna build houses there</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0012">they've opened up the new er recycle plant haven't they</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0012">I haven't been along to it yet <pause dur="short"/> but you can rid of all your televisions and your computers up there <pause dur="short"/> can't you</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to go sometime</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0012">we'll have to go sometime <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we ain't got any left</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> dehumidifier</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0152">you've got a <trunc>dehu</trunc> you got a <vocal desc="laugh"/> microwave that you</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0013">we hope not</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0012">no that'll work <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to get that working again</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0013">that was an expensive one wasn't it</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0012">I'm quite surprised how easy that is to take to pieces</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> in the  in the  end <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2020" who="S0012">in the end</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0152">well you gotta have somebody to put it together haven't you so</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0013">we went on their help site and they're and people the number of people that er</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0012">that have complained about</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0013">all the doors have broken</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0152">what on those ones?</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0012">Panasonic</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0013">and complaining cos the silly plastic bit er fell off</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0012">you pay what did they say? Er pay two hundred pound for a really good microwave and it's held together by little</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0152">plastic</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0012">tiny plastic joint</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0152">it's throw away society <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing though</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it make you sick</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0013">yeah but for er just that</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0152"><trunc>W</trunc></u>
<u n="2037" who="S0013">when the whole thing is brilliant</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0152">why not have you tried huh the household place on the Dereham Road? Cos I reckon you might mm if there is a fault on that you might be able to buy a new component for it</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0012">you can buy new components for it <pause dur="short"/> but it's getting it getting to it</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0152">oh</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0012">you've gotta take half the stuff off to get to it <pause dur="short"/> well working with a microwave that's a bit dodgy ain't it</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0152">as long as you don't go anywhere near the</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0012">yeah but</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0152">radiation part</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0012">well that's right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I don't  I don't  <trunc>fan</trunc> mm that <pause dur="short"/> or where I've gotta get to it look I've gotta take all this front bit off here <pause dur="short"/> well all this stuff is all</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0013">no we don't want to do that</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> don't wanna do that</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0012">can't do that</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0152">Don't do it</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0012">so I just gotta bodge it up <pause dur="short"/> no I'll I'll do it in the end</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0152">you'll do it <pause dur="short"/> you'll sort it</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0152">I saw a nice cooker yesterday in Bennetts</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0012">you've been to Bennetts have you?</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0152">I went to Bennetts yesterday <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2062" who="S0152">Cos I had a letter come through telling me about it</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0152">and then it says because I've been a customer for so long and bought so many things from there that if I go to Hall Road or somewhere else</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0013">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0152">they'll give me ten percent off</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0152">after tomorrow</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0152">but I don't need anything</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0012">but ten percent <pause dur="short"/> what's that? I mean ten quid on a hundred</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0152">it's not much is it</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0012">that's ain't a lot is it <pause dur="short"/> when you think about how much they make anyway</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0152">yeah</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0012">and in most of these places and if you go on the online you can get them for a lot cheaper anyway</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0152">so <pause dur="short"/> but no I saw a half a one of those</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0013">did you?</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0012">did you? Yeah?</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0013">mhm</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0152">which was like that side</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0012">they do a smaller one <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0152">so it hasn't got that one</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0152">but it's just half a one</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2097" who="S0152">free-standing</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know the one</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0013">hm</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0152">but when I move I'm gonna have one</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0012">you're gonna have one are you? Gas or electric?</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0152">depends on where I move to doesn't it</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0012">or you can get an oil-fired one</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0152">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="2107" who="S0012">or you can get an Aga</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> it all depends on where I move to</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0012">Cumbria? Dales?</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0152">I had</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0152">didn't I tell you this?</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2114" who="S0152">I had a tweet</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0012">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2116" who="S0152">from the estate agents in the Dales</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0152">the one that is on the telly</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh right</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0152">in the Dales programme</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0152">personally tweeted me</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0012">er why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2125" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0152">Cos I'd put a tweet on there <pause dur="short"/> makes me want to move there <pause dur="short"/> been saying that for the last twenty years <pause dur="short"/> looks like I've got another ten to wait</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2128" who="S0152">always checking out <trunc>p</trunc> house prices <pause dur="short"/> and I tweeted that</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2130" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0152">and the <trunc>es</trunc> the estate agent that was on the telly tweeted back to me you know where to come</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2133" who="S0152">and we'll be happy to help you out</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0012">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="2135" who="S0152">and they were in Leyburn</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0012">are they in Leyburn</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0012">are they? Oh brilliant</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0152"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So I tweeted back yeah I know you're in Leyburn <pause dur="short"/> looked in your shop looked in your window many a times</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0152">and follow you on the web <pause dur="short"/> fantastic you know where to come</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2143" who="S0152">do you want us do you want me to put you on our mailing list?</u>
<u n="2144" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2145" who="S0152">and I found a nice cottage <pause dur="short"/> a three-bedroom cottage in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2146" who="S0012">in <anon type="place"/>? Did you? Right <unclear/> away</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0152">right</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2150" who="S0152">for a hundred and eighty thousand pound</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0012">what? Has it got any parking space?</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0152">mm <pause dur="short"/> I didn't go that far <pause dur="short"/> cos I just thought a hundred and eighty thousand pounds</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0013">it's a cottage? mm</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0152">three floor cottage</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0152">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2158" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2159" who="S0152">so the creamery</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The rope factory <pause dur="short"/> oh that's is that closing down?</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0152">yeah the rope factory's still there</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0012">is it still there?</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0152">it's at the back there <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0152">you got the steam trains</u>
<u n="2166" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2167" who="S0013">is that where you'd like to be <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0012">oh you can dream  you can dream <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2169" who="S0152">I would like to be up there</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0012">hm</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0013">I know you'd like to be in Yorkshire <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="place"/> in particular?</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0152">I anywhere round there</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0152">anywhere round there</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2179" who="S0152">or the Lakes <pause dur="short"/> dales er I think the Dales would probably be the better</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0012">I think the Dales is the best bet <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> They don't get as much rain as the Lakes</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0152">I've been  I've been  to the Dales</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0152">or the North York Moors</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0012">or the North Yorks <pause dur="short"/> but it's cold up there</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0152">I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't think the <trunc>th</trunc> the cold  the cold  doesn't bother me <pause dur="short"/> cos you can have a nice wood-burner <pause dur="short"/> cos it that's the other thing it's gotta be able to have a wood-burner in the house</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0012">but you can't leave the door open all the time letting the cat in</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0152">no</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2192" who="S0152">I could do with putting another cat flap in that kitchen door</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You could</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0152">so I don't have to <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="2195" who="S0012">have to leave the door open</u>
<u n="2196" who="S0152">have to leave the door open <pause dur="short"/> that'd be useful <unclear/></u>
<u n="2197" who="S0012">that'd be better wouldn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0152">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think another cat flap <pause dur="short"/> I'll see <pause dur="short"/> but you never know what's gonna happen <pause dur="short"/> you never know what's round the corner do you</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0152">you never know</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0012">mind you you've got until well you start this other job in September don't you?</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0152">no start it in May</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0012">in May? Well it ain't far along</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0152">no true</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0012">then you work until September or?</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0152">I work until July and then if I haven't got a full-time job by then it continues after</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2211" who="S0152">until Christmas</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0013">oh not in September?</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> September September through to Christmas</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2218" who="S0012">coo</u>
<u n="2219" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2221" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0012">it's all that tea you keep feeding me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="2223" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> would you like to stay for some lunch?</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0152">I'm gonna say  I'm gonna say  no <pause dur="short"/> cos I gotta go and do the housework</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0013">oh right <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0152">my house is a tip <pause dur="short"/> and I'm not eating at the moment</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0013">aren't you? Oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2228" who="S0152">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm not eating um very much at the moment</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0152">hm <pause dur="short"/> can't</u>
<u n="2231" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0152">I've got I'm behind at home <pause dur="short"/> the house is a tip at the <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="2233" who="S0013">so are we <pause dur="short"/> terribly <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0152">I need to give everywhere a good vacuum and I need to start painting</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I got a whisper of sunrise I think last time</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="2237" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2238" who="S0152">no I do need to strip the kitchen</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0013">mm?</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0152">I need to strip the kitchen <pause dur="short"/> get rid of those cracks in the wall and</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0152">things like that</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0013">so which one's first? The kitchen or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room?</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0152"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room will be first in the sense that I need to <trunc>g</trunc> get it tidy</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0013">and the wardrobe up</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0152">and the wardrobe <pause dur="short"/> I need to I need er I'm going home to do <trunc>s</trunc> to change some plugs <pause dur="short"/> I need to do some electrics because my central heating stopped the hot water on my central heating stopped again</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0152">um but I could have heating</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2250" who="S0152">so my radiators will get hot but I'm not getting any hot water</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0152">and yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came back from riding and I hadn't checked <pause dur="short"/> jess had had her shower and whatever</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0152">which was fine <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came back and I checked and it was cold <pause dur="short"/> so I had to put the immersion heater on</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0152">well the immersion heater is not plugged in at at the moment <pause dur="short"/> so I had to get an extension cable</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0152">so I need to change the plug on the wall for the immersion heater <pause dur="short"/> um so that I can just switch it on and off rather than having to put all the</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0152">and then I need to change a plug <pause dur="short"/> but I need to do that in daylight so <pause dur="short"/> I went and got the plugs yesterday to change so <pause dur="short"/> and I'd got things recording on the telly this morning <pause dur="short"/> and I'd got washing in as well</u>
<u n="2261" who="S0013">right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2262" who="S0152">so I couldn't turn the <trunc>elec</trunc></u>
<u n="2263" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2264" who="S0152">couldn't turn the electrics off while all that is on so</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2267" who="S0152">I'm gonna go and change some electric socket</u>
<u n="2268" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2269" who="S0012">oh yeah? Yeah</u>
<u n="2270" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="2271" who="S0012">we gotta get a new booster for our television so you know plugs for the aerial</u>
<u n="2272" who="S0152">oh you're gonna get a booster?</u>
<u n="2273" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2274" who="S0152">well you can get it from Argos</u>
<u n="2275" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2276" who="S0013">is that what you're getting?</u>
<u n="2277" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2278" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="2279" who="S0012">I think <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> try that first <pause dur="short"/> they're not very expensive <pause dur="short"/> you might as well try that first instead of</u>
<u n="2280" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2281" who="S0012">getting an aerial <pause dur="short"/> but we've still gotta get another</u>
<u n="2282" who="S0013">oh that's the one in the loft?</u>
<u n="2283" who="S0012">that's the one in the loft</u>
<u n="2284" who="S0013">okay</u>
<u n="2285" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2286" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2287" who="S0012">we've still gotta get another recorder</u>
<u n="2288" who="S0013"><unclear/> think</u>
<u n="2289" who="S0012">they don't do <trunc>f</trunc> er Freesat recorders much <pause dur="short"/> they do free Freeview recorders <pause dur="short"/> they don't seem to do Freesat</u>
<u n="2290" who="S0013">it keeps coming up with no service at the moment</u>
<u n="2291" who="S0012">no service it keep saying</u>
<u n="2292" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="2293" who="S0013">but we'll try that first</u>
<u n="2294" who="S0012">yeah we will try that first <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2295" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2296" who="S0152">but</u>
<u n="2297" who="S0012">Cos that there was</u>
<u n="2298" who="S0152"><unclear/> but <trunc>w</trunc> er so you're gonna take it off your other sat then?</u>
<u n="2299" who="S0012">well we <trunc>w</trunc> I was going to do a Freesat one but if I get this this er booster I'll that'll probably work off the Freeview again <pause dur="short"/> cos we got a <trunc>Frees</trunc> Freeview recorder you see</u>
<u n="2300" who="S0152">yeah you said Freesat</u>
<u n="2301" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="2302" who="S0152">why do you need a Freesat recorder?</u>
<u n="2303" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="2304" who="S0152">when you've already got one</u>
<u n="2305" who="S0012">we <trunc>w</trunc> we got <trunc>f</trunc> we haven't got freesat recorder at all <pause dur="short"/> we got a freeview recorder</u>
<u n="2306" who="S0152">so why don't you put get a freesat recorder then?</u>
<u n="2307" who="S0012">can't get</u>
<u n="2308" who="S0152">and then put that in there <pause dur="short"/> then put that recorder over there</u>
<u n="2309" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2310" who="S0152">onto that telly?</u>
<u n="2311" who="S0012">but that recorder's</u>
<u n="2312" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2313" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2314" who="S0013">we were thinking of that</u>
<u n="2315" who="S0012">that <trunc>rec</trunc> yeah we are thinking of that <pause dur="short"/> but that recorder's twenty years old <pause dur="short"/> no it ain't that old</u>
<u n="2316" who="S0152"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2317" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="2318" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="2319" who="S0013">it's not</u>
<u n="2320" who="S0012">no it ain't <pause dur="short"/> it's er that's</u>
<u n="2321" who="S0013">not er</u>
<u n="2322" who="S0012">that crack that keep going kr kr</u>
<u n="2323" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="2324" who="S0012">Don't it</u>
<u n="2325" who="S0013">but at the moment we don't know why</u>
<u n="2326" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> cos we can watch free freeview and that's fine <pause dur="short"/> but as soon as it come to recording it</u>
<u n="2327" who="S0152">sounds like the <trunc>har</trunc> hard drive's going down</u>
<u n="2328" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2329" who="S0013">it's <trunc>B</trunc> no but it's just BBC mainly isn't it</u>
<u n="2330" who="S0012">it's BBC mainly yeah</u>
<u n="2331" who="S0013">the others seem to record alright</u>
<u n="2332" who="S0152">have you <trunc>r</trunc> have you retuned it?</u>
<u n="2333" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's all been done properly <pause dur="short"/> it's all been retuned all the time</u>
<u n="2334" who="S0152">if it's cracking it sounds like what you're recording on to which is the hard drive is</u>
<u n="2335" who="S0012">yeah it was giving up</u>
<u n="2336" who="S0152">it was giving up</u>
<u n="2337" who="S0012">but that was the first Panasonic one weren't it</u>
<u n="2338" who="S0013">it's only occasionally isn't it</u>
<u n="2339" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2340" who="S0013">and we haven't worked out why</u>
<u n="2341" who="S0012">that did <unclear/> in the kitchen okay yesterday didn't it</u>
<u n="2342" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2343" who="S0012">and that's BBC</u>
<u n="2344" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2345" who="S0012">but I think  I think  what we'll have to do is just get this this new er plug thing <pause dur="short"/> whatever it's called</u>
<u n="2346" who="S0013">booster</u>
<u n="2347" who="S0152">booster</u>
<u n="2348" who="S0012">booster</u>
<u n="2349" who="S0013">right <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="2350" who="S0012">Cos I mean they're only  they're only  twenty quid a time up  up to up  to about thirty quid I <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="2351" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="2352" who="S0012">I think they go <pause dur="short"/> but we only need a two-socket one</u>
<u n="2353" who="S0013">we do really <pause dur="short"/> we've got one for loads of</u>
<u n="2354" who="S0012">there's no point in having them er all</u>
<u n="2355" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos we've got a</u>
<u n="2356" who="S0012">all over the house any more</u>
<u n="2357" who="S0013">there's a socket in our bedroom</u>
<u n="2358" who="S0012">we got that room and that room</u>
<u n="2359" who="S0013">and a socket in another bedroom haven't we</u>
<u n="2360" who="S0012">well we got socket in all the bedrooms</u>
<u n="2361" who="S0013">which we never use</u>
<u n="2362" who="S0012">which we never use</u>
<u n="2363" who="S0152">and you've taken the one out of here haven't you?</u>
<u n="2364" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2365" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2366" who="S0012">yeah we don't use this one <pause dur="short"/> that used to be there in there</u>
<u n="2367" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2368" who="S0152">Argos is a good place to get them from</u>
<u n="2369" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2370" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2371" who="S0012">well I been looking on the net for them</u>
<u n="2372" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2373" who="S0012">and er they're almost all the same</u>
<u n="2374" who="S0152">mm</u>
<u n="2375" who="S0012">everything you can buy is almost all the same <pause dur="short"/> but there are a couple that are er what do they call it? <trunc>F</trunc> ten to fifteen <unclear/> hertz or something <pause dur="short"/> and there are others that are fifteen to twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> so that you can get a more powerful one you see</u>
<u n="2376" who="S0152">that's the one to go for</u>
<u n="2377" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they're a bit more expensive</u>
<u n="2378" who="S0152"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2379" who="S0012">I think that's the one to go for <pause dur="short"/> the powerful one</u>
<u n="2380" who="S0013">okay</u>
<u n="2381" who="S0012">well look we'll save</u>
<u n="2382" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'll do that first then</u>
<u n="2383" who="S0012">you know buying a new aerial</u>
<u n="2384" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="2385" who="S0012">and we'll see how it go</u>
<u n="2386" who="S0152">right <pause dur="short"/> time to go and change plugs</u>
<u n="2387" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2388" who="S0013">alright</u>
<u n="2389" who="S0012">okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2390" who="S0152">go and turn my electric off</u>
<u n="2391" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2392" who="S0152">wuh</u>
<u n="2393" who="S0013">sign a piece of paper?</u>
<u n="2394" who="S0012">oh we haven't got it yet</u>
<u n="2395" who="S0013">haven't we?</u>
<u n="2396" who="S0012">no <pause dur="short"/> we'll give it him</u>
<u n="2397" who="S0152">you could</u>
<u n="2398" who="S0012">later</u>
<u n="2399" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="2400" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2401" who="S0152">not a problem</u>
<u n="2402" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="2403" who="S0152">thank you for the tea</u>
<u n="2404" who="S0012">that's okay</u>
<u n="2405" who="S0152">I may have to go zz vacuum</u>
<u n="2406" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> the vacuum <unclear/></u>
<u n="2407" who="S0152">oh the house is a tip</u>
<u n="2408" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2409" who="S0152">the house is a tip</u>
<u n="2410" who="S0012">is it?</u>
<u n="2411" who="S0152">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've not ironed for ages</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
</body>
</text>
