<text id="SD68">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:34</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Music, Morecambe, cycling </topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking while listening to the radio</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">so we're still on uh Asian Network then?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">I've enjoyed it more than I thought I would like <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I I didn't listen to that much sort of um Asian inspired music <pause dur="short"/> you know current music</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> it it's something that I <trunc>w</trunc> I hadn't listened to a lot before but uh obviously uh now um there's</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">it's better than like the pop like <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather listen to this than like One Direction or something</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it yeah <pause dur="short"/> it felt that there was um some of the ones uh were getting too sad at at the  at the  far end of the um</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">which ones?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">at the far end of the <trunc>s</trunc> of the list of um uh of uh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">of the radio stations you mean?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115" trans="overlap">stations <pause dur="short"/> yeah like uh that it was getting too  it was getting too  sad yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I suppose it's the night time like <pause dur="short"/> it's not got it like and it's like not like a Friday or Saturday</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but these ones that that some of them are um putting like this one's probably more sort of</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">yeah more upbeat</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then well probably I suppose</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I'd much rather listen to this than like um you know like some of those bands like the Saturdays or like One Direction or what that other one you know</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I mean I wouldn't have recognized uh <trunc>l</trunc> One Direction if if if it had come on so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">no but Justin Byber or whatever he's called <pause dur="short"/> he's no he's not called that is he?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115">bieber</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">Justin Bieber</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0037">I was in um uh Primark the other day and they had T-shirts with Justin Bieber's face on that said I love Justin Bieber on the front</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0037">like what <vocal desc="laugh"/> So obviously like just for the thirteen year-olds</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115">he's uh he's a great performer uh</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is he? He's a great something</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Why why does no one like him I mean?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">Cos if you just listen to him for like five seconds you realize he's like the most insanely annoying person in the universe</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know I mean</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">he's very annoying</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">no I don't think it's his his voice I think</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037">no it's not his voice <pause dur="short"/> it's not his voice at all</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no like if if it was like The Voice or something like and you knew uh you know</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no he is a good singer</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">no I  no I  mean if you couldn't see his face then I think like you'd you'd probably like have a different you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037">I suppose it's not just about like the song is it? Or him singing in fact because really if we're honest there's loads of people who who are good singers <pause dur="short"/> like the thing with like being like a pop star if you like is about more much more than that it's about image and looks and all that stuff isn't it? I mean I i'm not interested in any of that anyway but <pause dur="short"/> he's very very annoying <pause dur="short"/> and I don't like his music anyway</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well d'you think it's it's more just sort of his <trunc>appearan</trunc> you know his his his his hair?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">well he's just a pop <pause dur="short"/> he's like a teen fluff pop star <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't offend us massively <pause dur="short"/> I think he's annoying but not angry at him</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean yeah he <trunc>w</trunc> he was quite annoying uh on uh Graham Norton's show uh which I don't really like I wouldn't <trunc>w</trunc> wanna watch that <trunc>h</trunc> very often but uh</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> I dunno it can be quite funny <pause dur="short"/> I like that thing where they tip people over the back of the chair</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> no I I don't like that actually</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">it's quite funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">some bits are <pause dur="short"/> because you know what you're going into like you must expect to be like just flipped over the chair</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115">well yeah but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">you know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">fair enough</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">it's not like it's like tortuous for them <pause dur="short"/> people aren't forced into it they're going into that fully expecting to be like you know</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037">think if you know what you're letting yourself into it's not like they're just like <trunc>s</trunc> gunging people at random or something <pause dur="short"/> gunge <pause dur="short"/> every time I hear that word it <trunc>r</trunc> just reminds me of like Noel's House Party</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah right yeah yeah he was annoying wasn't he?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I used to watch that</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">Noel Noel Edmonds</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">crinkley Bottom <pause dur="short"/> and that reminds me of <anon type="place"/> like you know they opened like a</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">yeah yeah the the uh dilapidated uh</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">blobby World</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">uh theme park did that theme park with the Polo Tower <pause dur="short"/> it's a big Polo Tower</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">ah poor old <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">ah no one still not enough people go there <pause dur="short"/> well it had a bit of you know there was a bit of economy going on like</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well they're trying to I mean</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there was like during the you know in the during the sort of conveyancing boom um</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">the <trunc>con</trunc> the construction boom or whatever like when I was working there um <pause dur="short"/> I mean the office  the office  space has gotta be quite cheap like but there was  there was  quite a few little little companies um working there <trunc>th</trunc> there was a bit of an economy you know and they had a bit of the like <trunc>i</trunc> you know the sort of shops and things that you'd associate with uh with with people like people commuting to <anon type="place"/> you know uh rather than simply uh yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037" trans="overlap">God yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I <trunc>l</trunc> I know what mean <pause dur="short"/> I think maybe they've done a lot since they like did the Midland up</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>S</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> yeah I mean not not that there's anything wrong with um having it as a place that you commute from to <anon type="place"/> but but I suppose it didn't look like that it looked kind of like <pause dur="short"/> like it didn't look like a wealthy  didn't look like a wealthy  commuter suburb I <trunc>th</trunc> you know it it was like a <trunc>de</trunc> a declining</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> just a bit sad wasn't it like? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> we sort of got lost there d'you remember? I just remember like walking around like looking for the the bus stop like <pause dur="short"/> in some of the back streets <pause dur="short"/> d'you remember?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> That shouldn't have uh shouldn't have been so hard</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037" trans="overlap">sort of got lost <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">it shouldn't have been that hard should it?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037">no it shouldn't have been that hard <pause dur="short"/> but we did get back in the end <pause dur="short"/> we were just a bit lost</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">think we got on the bus eventually yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">we did yeah yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115">no it it's actually <trunc>m</trunc> an <trunc>i</trunc> uh uh uh a nice I thought it was quite a nice place an interesting place and uh hadn't</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think  I think  was because they'd moved the bus stops hadn't they like there was like they're doing loads of road works and they were like move to such and such a street but obviously we didn't know where that was</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I I I quite um quite liked it and uh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I got to know it quite well I mean I passed me driving test in <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Remember? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> right <pause dur="short"/> did you? That's an easy place to  easy place to  do it</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well it is and it isn't <pause dur="short"/> I didn't drive in my driving test in <anon type="place"/> at all I I passed it in <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> So I know the roads quite well</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> did all of me manoeuvres and <pause dur="short"/> they've got some like really um some of those you know if the States where they have like those big sweeping corners and those kind of Victorian terraces where you have like those right angles to reverse round you know? So</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">it was good but there's a lot of roundabouts <pause dur="short"/> I'm good at roundabouts <pause dur="short"/> well some of the times <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">yeah I guess uh <pause dur="short"/> ah it's ages since I've driven I can hardly remember like</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it feels different like I drive so rarely now</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115" trans="overlap">getting in  getting in  this guessing that lane and uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah it seems <pause dur="short"/> things that are that seem very easy when when you're used to it</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">it seems  it seems  really easy</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">you don't even think about it like</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037">when like it's funny cos when you</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's sort of <trunc>y</trunc> you say like <trunc>y</trunc> you know go round this go round that like</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">like <trunc>w</trunc> as a if you if you're starting from scratch or or something then you wouldn't know <pause dur="short"/> when you say go round it like you <trunc>d</trunc> have no idea how how to sort of um get the the curve right so that you're going round like a fat roundabout or a thin roundabout</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">uh but but if you experience it of course you you would just know how the curve how how to draw the curve out of the shape that you turned in the steering wheel so</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know it's a funny one like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> you know when <trunc>peo</trunc> you know when you're learning to drive people always say to you Yeah once you've learned like <trunc>y</trunc> you just do it without thinking it and you can drive any car you can drive anywhere and <pause dur="short"/> and it</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you never forget? Yeah well yeah I think I I <trunc>d</trunc> I learned you know for and uh and I could've could drive at the time but uh I just have to refresh myself and it's a lot of uh  a lot of time  since I last did it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think so <pause dur="short"/> I think it comes back to you <pause dur="short"/> it is stressful though like <pause dur="short"/> like when we hired that car for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding like I hadn't driven for two years <pause dur="short"/> it's quite a long time and I did make some mistakes</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but but you did <trunc>dr</trunc> yeah you did drive like for for quite a long time uh like two years um</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037" trans="overlap">did you? Yeah but that's still not a long time really not compared to some people</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I mean I I probably only like like a few months really uh that I had like of good decent driving um</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I I suppose it's like anything I mean <pause dur="short"/> like when we moved here and I bought a bike I hadn't probably ridden a bike <trunc>un</trunc> since I was eleven like</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh right yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">you know like</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">that's yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">fifteen years or whatever <pause dur="short"/> more than fifteen</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean stuff should come back that I think like uh yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">as Gok Wan would say it's all about the confidence</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Obviously it's easier to be confident on a bike than in a car <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">essentially on a bike turn your legs round <pause dur="short"/> go forward</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115">yeah I think it is partly about confidence but um drinking and driving don't go together</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> definitely not</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">so it's also  it's also  about the coordination</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I can see why they don't like I mean even like drinking and cycling don't really go like <pause dur="short"/> I I would cycle after two beers</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think no I I think that you can after after a couple uh</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> after two beers yes but I I've done it after more but like you lose all your inhibitions like I think <trunc>y</trunc> like I suppose you don't really realize it when you're just pootling around or you're just walking you know you're walking to <trunc>pla</trunc> from place to place and mooching about you don't really notice but like <pause dur="short"/> if you have to like I'm <trunc>de</trunc> like so sometimes on a Friday I go for a drink after work <pause dur="short"/> and like I have two beers and I fly home <pause dur="short"/> I just like I just cycle so much faster and I'm so much more like daring and like</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">oh really? Yeah you see I I don't think I'd be um I don't I'd be like that if I was</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you just think I wanna get home <pause dur="short"/> I wanna get home <pause dur="short"/> I wanna get home <pause dur="short"/> like your sort of mentality changes <pause dur="short"/> even after just like a couple of beers</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">uh I don't think I'd be like that if I was um uh drunk or uh I don't think</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I dunno I think it's <pause dur="short"/> I think  I think  it's the exercise though as well</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't think drink drink would make  would make  make me go really fast unless of course like there was no one in sight</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">but I think it's like the exercise of it like I think it's sort of it must drive it round your body faster</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> possibly yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like you know <trunc>sit</trunc> sitting still and drinking a glass of beer <pause dur="short"/> versus drinking a glass of beer and then like giving it some on your <trunc>ex</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I mean it must pump your blood round your body dead fast if I think</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I I think it yeah <trunc>dr</trunc> it drives it  drives it  through um</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">so it must like hit you faster</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">although</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'm just a lightweight now</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">I think it would</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">I'm always a bit cautious thought I don't think I would ever <trunc>dri</trunc> I would don't think I would ever cycle after two beers after I fell off that time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I I remember a <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> um I no I think that's cos that's not cos of drinking that's cos of you were talking to someone else</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">I know but I think uh</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">so it's I think  I think  when you're talking to somebody you sort of focus you really put a lot of focus in the the other person like um that they they yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know but I still get pain off that <pause dur="short"/> well it was <pause dur="short"/> there was just too <pause dur="short"/> I mean there was too many stupid things I did then <pause dur="short"/> yes I'd had some beer and yes we were chatting away like two old ladies and like you know I try to do something ridiculous like I try to sort of move me bike light with me foot and then just got tangled in me bike and</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">um it was just like a <trunc>m</trunc> series of misfortunes but I think it's made us realize that like if I hadn't had them beers I don't know if I would've attempted that like <pause dur="short"/> while talking while doing you know <pause dur="short"/> I probably wouldn't have <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">it was so painful <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's still sore <pause dur="short"/> like it doesn't hurt it's not hurting us now but sometimes like it's painful</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah well uh it's a  it's a  bad one I no but uh when when we  when we  went um</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">it's not that bad really considering we've been here for cycling every single day for two and a half years</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">that was a yeah it was a really quite <trunc>unnec</trunc> unnecessary but you just you got  yo got  it from simply from playing like from trying to like you know stupidly kick a thing like it was  it was  absolutely not really even an an accident in that I mean not not an accident as in a a crash or</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> no nothing bad happened no no no</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">uh it wasn't a crash or a slip yeah it didn't have any external cause it was  it was  entirely your own</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037" trans="overlap">not caused by anyone else <pause dur="short"/> no it was entirely my own fault <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no I agree <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115">and and as such wasn't so much an accident</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but look I've still got scars like <pause dur="short"/> I'm like like a seven year-old with like scabs on me</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">uh you have to scrub them though don't you when you're uh? To stop them</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's just like the scar tissue <pause dur="short"/> you can't scrub your knee before you fall off</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I mean like before the <pause dur="short"/> like I mean when the when it's um <pause dur="short"/> the you know like <trunc>w</trunc> if you got a graze proper graze you've gotta like scrub it haven't you and?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I did <pause dur="short"/> I did <pause dur="short"/> I did everyday and I've put like I'm I rubbed like Vaseline in it and</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">I guess they they'll go down eventually <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">ah yeah it's just a scar now I mean it course it'll go</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">but um</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">I've got plenty <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">uh yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">I had one on me face d'you remember when I <trunc>s</trunc> like scraped all me face that's that totally went</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">that's gone hasn't it yeah so uh but but no I mean uh I think it is it can be dangerous like with a lot of cars but I think if if I was uh like uh riding myself I would try and avoid um a lot of cars uh</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">I don't know I mean cars are like in most of <anon type="place"/> it they're pretty good like <pause dur="short"/> because people who drive in <anon type="place"/> all the time are really I suppose really used to like loads of cyclists</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">you've told me about loads of things like like like near near um yeah things have nearly happened to you and you've had to sort of shelter people and stuff uh or like</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037" trans="overlap">some people are bad yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">you've seen accidents you've seen like bumps and stuff um</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I have yeah <pause dur="short"/> I have yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw someone get their front wheel bent like that was really bad <vocal desc="laugh"/> They were alright it was quite a sort of slow and in the end it was quite a slow impact</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's it's terrible when uh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but like the car just went into the wheel and the wheel was like you know bent sort of that way and uh na they weren't happy</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um how uh how did that how d'that happen?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">so um I was  I was  waiting at <pause dur="short"/> it was a it they're always tend to be at this one junction <pause dur="short"/> um and I was at this so I was coming up to this junction and then um it's kind of a one where it's got three sort of um roads that feed into this roundabout and quite often it comes to the point for some reason where there's because the the road so I'm coming up I'm I'm sort of coming towards the junction and there's a road coming in from the right and there's a one sort of well both coming in and going out to the right and also to the left <pause dur="short"/> and on the left that road's the road to the motorway so that's always jammed it's always busy</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037">so even though like so I'm coming up to the roundabout even though you should give way to the person on the right <pause dur="short"/> the person on the right you can't give way to them if there's nowhere for them to go</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so it's like a so you can go then <pause dur="short"/> cos if they can't  if they can't  go then you should go</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">D'you know what I mean if you if they're not gonna move then you should move but sometimes this ends in like a weird stalemate like</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah I can imagine uh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037" trans="overlap">where everyone's everyone's just stopped at the roundabout and so then everyone goes at the same time</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">but even</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">so it can be really dangerous but</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">but even so you can <trunc>st</trunc> you've still got some sight of the person coming at you haven't you?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> but what happened this time was it was exactly that so on the left like it was  it was  blocked um the road going out to the left was blocked and the road coming in from the right they would just stop because there was nowhere for them to go</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">so the cyclist ahead of me just went round <pause dur="short"/> then the road coming in from the left they just thought no there's no one coming <pause dur="short"/> just went out and then just just they saw each other too late</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037">and like they just <trunc>w</trunc> just went into the cyclist <pause dur="short"/> the cyclist had their brakes on and the car had their brakes on but they just sort of clashed <pause dur="short"/> no one fell off or anything but literally just bent the wheel like in half</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">and the cyclist was like you look what you've done to my bike rah rah rah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um and uh what what do you do if uh if that happens to your bike</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037" trans="overlap">sorry I'll just close that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's never happened to me <pause dur="short"/> actually I went into the</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">like you can't it you're not  you're not  insured you don't  you don't  pay road tax so you you you have</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037">you can get bike insurance yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I I <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I suppose like <pause dur="short"/> but you don't have all this like the same kind of uh</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">I don't know I mean you can though you can specifically claim I mean I've seen I've seen it advertised for like claiming for that sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> depends</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sort of thing is <pause dur="short"/> which which bike you drive I see yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's not like car insurance where you can sort of you you you have to pay uh car insurance don't you?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the other person's liable? No you don't have to have bike insurance no</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">but um</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">but but if you didn't then but even if it was caused by someone else like what would you do if I mean cos I imagine if even if you don't have insurance of a bike not if it's someone else's fault they they would have to pay anyway wouldn't they so?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I suppose you would have to like get the police involved like you usually need to have like some proof that there's been an accident like</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">um but I don't know it's never happened to me thankfully <pause dur="short"/> I mean I went into the back of another cyclist once and they snapped off a bit of my um front um when I had my old bike my front sort of mud guard and I was really annoyed</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> they went into the back cos they stopped and?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> they slammed the we were in a cycle lane a really narrow cycle lane and they had their</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's it's difficult there must be loads of uh these kinds of you know like just like with cars</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> well they had their they had like a um a chip like a bike their bike lock um was on the back of the or or on the back <trunc>s</trunc> or on the bike somewhere and it just fell off <pause dur="short"/> and so she just slammed her brakes on like didn't think <pause dur="short"/> so literally just like went from cycling quite fast to stop <pause dur="short"/> and so I just couldn't stop in time and my bike and I couldn't pull her like out of the way cos there was parked cars on one side and traffic on the other so I just went into like just crunched into the back of her <pause dur="short"/> and I was like What what are you thinking? like you just can't do that and she was like ah I'm really sorry <pause dur="short"/> and I was like you just snapped off half the front of my thing and she's like yeah d'you want it back cos she'd picked it up and I was like grrr</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">but just one of those things but</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">yeah I guess you it's a much more because <trunc>i</trunc> there's a lack of compulsory insurance uh <pause dur="short"/> uh and and also um well I guess that's how the compulsory insurance for cars started um but the the difficulty of uh proving um like like uh</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think so maybe <pause dur="short"/> I suppose the damage you can do <pause dur="short"/> liability</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">yeah I mean there's there's always like it's it's always gonna be you know hard to prove liability um but but I suppose we if you're looking at car versus car then of course you've got the  you've got the  the evidence on both cars but whereas if it's car versus bike it may  it may  not have any evidence on the car</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">whereas the bike could be just be totally mangled or something like for <pause dur="short"/> but I mean uh <pause dur="short"/> if that's how like car insurance then</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">but you can get  you can get  bike insurance though</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115" trans="overlap">compulsory car <trunc>ins</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> cos you might've thought well um we would we wouldn't  we wouldn't  have compulsory insurance instead we would just uh instead we would just find out you'd have a method of finding out who's liable and then uh um simply make them pay you know when they  when they  have to pay you know</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">and no <trunc>insura</trunc> uh or or like <pause dur="short"/> yeah they they could have insurance if they wanted but they'd but you know but it's not compulsory so</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">uh but they'd they'd just take their chances and pay when they had to pay <pause dur="short"/> but I guess the difficulty is that you can't decide who who's caused it but then I suppose well they do decide who caused it so <pause dur="short"/> I mean perhaps that that's why they have it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well it's there's usually witnesses like if you have a crash like that where someone just <trunc>go</trunc> like crashes into your bike there's always gonna be people there</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">yeah I mean well it's it's it is it's different isn't it? Cos like</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I mean I've seen like that that that one roundabout that I was talking about at <anon type="place"/> Road like it's really treacherous like there's um <pause dur="short"/> I once saw a Chinese student I imagine student riding the wrong way around the roundabout <vocal desc="laugh"/> And I was just like oh my god you're dicing with death like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Mind you though if you go the wrong  if you go the wrong  though it's like walking against cars you know <pause dur="short"/> they can see you really clearly so</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's true but they're genuinely surprised</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you're you're you're probably probably a lot less uh likely to get into an accident if you if you're riding the wrong way cos they they can just see you and like</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">it was pretty bad though</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean <pause dur="short"/> unless unless you ride directly into them but then that's like <trunc>s</trunc> that's like riding directly into any inanimate objects and then like</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no they didn't do that but <pause dur="short"/> but there's a funny bit after that like just as like if you're coming from here to work like after you get over the roundabout there's a bit where it like filters down to so it really is only one lane like only one car <pause dur="short"/> and sometimes like most most cars and stuff like back right off and so they let you go through and then overtake you whence the <trunc>ro</trunc> once the road like broadens out again <pause dur="short"/> it's like a funnel sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> it really narrows and then it really <trunc>wi</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> and then there's a <trunc>cro</trunc> pedestrian crossing <pause dur="short"/> and then it  then it  opens and like</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just like a  like a  funnel like a egg timer</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">so if people back off I normally give them like a big thumbs up like <pause dur="short"/> to say like thanks sort of thing but sometimes people hassle you or try to like edge through at the same time</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's impossible <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">and I've seen so many people like just like tipped off the bike there probably not really hurt but like just pushed <pause dur="short"/> you know like cars and vans and stuff just squeeze through and they lose their nerve and like <pause dur="short"/> just tip over onto the side and <pause dur="short"/> it's not very nice</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">I'm lucky not to have had a big thing <pause dur="short"/> accident or anything <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna um get me washing out</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">alright shall  shall I  pause this uh?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">I don't mind I mean <pause dur="short"/> I just I've only got a few things that I wanted to get out but <pause dur="short"/> it's up to you</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">depends how it's going</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">uh well I'll I'll pause it and then do like an extra bit</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">what's it on?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">I don't actually know how to turn it off though <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's on twenty-two so I can do another another you know eight or something</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">okay</u>
</body>
</text>
