<text id="SDAJ">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:48:36</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>The military, magazines, films, computers</topics>
		<activity>Friends eating, chatting.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0084">the curry sauce is good</u>
<u n="2" who="S0041">yeah it is</u>
<u n="3" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0041"><unclear/> it more <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> I've never had <unclear/> before</u>
<u n="5" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0041">yeah and I've had that belt since I was seventeen</u>
<u n="7" who="S0084">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> that's awesome</u>
<u n="8" who="S0041" trans="overlap">seventeen <pause dur="short"/> you know it's like my favouritist belt <pause dur="short"/> it's really not very fashionable now but it just fitted perfectly on that hook <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> on the tighter hook</u>
<u n="9" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh nice <pause dur="short"/> mm winner <pause dur="short"/> eat more chips that's clearly the answer</u>
<u n="10" who="S0041">yeah clearly the answer <pause dur="short"/> not to think yes this is going really well <pause dur="short"/> keep it up <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> eat chips and curry that is the answer</u>
<u n="11" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> that is always the answer <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0041">my next step which obviously won't probably be this year but you know it's alright</u>
<u n="13" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0041">is my aim is to wear a bikini <pause dur="short"/> I've never worn one in my life before <pause dur="short"/> like in my whole life <pause dur="short"/> never</u>
<u n="15" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="16" who="S0041">never <pause dur="short"/> never never never</u>
<u n="17" who="S0084">but you wear a trikini</u>
<u n="18" who="S0041">well yeah there isn't much to that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0041">but that is the most naked thing I've ever owned</u>
<u n="21" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0041">swimwear wise</u>
<u n="23" who="S0084">yeah I mean absolutely hate it but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why I don't own a swimming costume <pause dur="short"/> I suppose cos I don't go swimming</u>
<u n="24" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0084">if I'm  if I'm  in beach wear it's because I'm on the beach and in which case I want to get a brown tummy</u>
<u n="26" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0084">but only because I want to lie somewhere <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to go walking around so I always sarongs etcetera</u>
<u n="28" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> parading <pause dur="short"/> yes so that's my aim before I die and I figure over the next couple of years he's probably going to be the closest I'm going to get to that</u>
<u n="29" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> army training <pause dur="short"/> army boot camp</u>
<u n="30" who="S0041">army boot camp <pause dur="short"/> do you think after the army boot camp takes like twelve weeks or whatever it is you get a holiday or do you just have to go straight into it?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think they give you a holiday to like kiss your family goodbye <pause dur="short"/> I mean you will come back presumably <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="32" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos maybe that would be perfect time for eighteen thirties crazy holiday</u>
<u n="33" who="S0084">ooh <pause dur="short"/> naked holiday</u>
<u n="34" who="S0041">naked holiday basically yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I really want to do this as well <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think I'm too old already so what's going to happen is</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084">you're going to do an eighteen to thirties holiday?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0041">and it all sounds very good in my head and hilarious fun with loads of teenage boys <pause dur="short"/> however I think in actual practice after five days I'm going to want rip my own eyes out</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">you're going to want to kill everybody <pause dur="short"/> you know the staff <pause dur="short"/> all the younger kids because it's they're all going to be tiny and young</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041" trans="overlap">all the screaming girls <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they will actually just be eighteen <pause dur="short"/> that's the problem</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0041">but erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that I work with which you wouldn't think of this if you met him <pause dur="short"/> he used to rep</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0041">in Greece and he said well you can still do those types of holidays at those resorts but not with eighteen thirties</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084" trans="overlap">eighteen year olds <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="46" who="S0041">so there are places that are set up for that holiday but they don't specify themselves under the eighteen thirties bracket so they don't</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0041">they get young people but most young people will go to the brochure club travel agent place and ask for eighteen thirties <pause dur="short"/> he said but there's quite loads of other companies that do it <pause dur="short"/> they just don't advertise as that <pause dur="short"/> so I could do that</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> that's an idea <pause dur="short"/> that was always mine and my sisters backup plan was to be holiday reps <pause dur="short"/> I think there was some sort of TV show at the time that all looked very glamorous and everyone was having a lovely time</u>
<u n="50" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">but I think in reality you would probably kill everybody</u>
<u n="52" who="S0041">yes and you'd be knackered</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0041" trans="overlap">absolutely whacked all the time</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0041">all the time</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">it's like my friend became an air steward <pause dur="short"/> she loved it and had a brilliant time though <pause dur="short"/> like flying <pause dur="short"/> still drunk the next day <pause dur="short"/> sobering up on a plane</u>
<u n="58" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> that's bad times</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">it's really bad like going to the toilets to be sick on a plane and then having to serve food and drink to people <pause dur="short"/> you've got to though because if you don't you'll never make it through <pause dur="short"/> like we've got to go out and do all those things with everybody because otherwise you don't like be part of the team because that's what everyone's doing <pause dur="short"/> I can't stand flying at the best of times</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041">well no I couldn't be arsed with that</u>
<u n="63" who="S0084">no no no</u>
<u n="64" who="S0041">just the thought of being trapped in a plane for that long <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind flying at all <pause dur="short"/> but it just it makes your skin feel all funny <pause dur="short"/> it makes your hair go static</u>
<u n="65" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0041">it makes me get snotty because I'm allergic to the air con</u>
<u n="67" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0041">like no</u>
<u n="69" who="S0084">I get a really bad <trunc>hat</trunc> headache every time it must be the <trunc>ai</trunc> cabin pressure</u>
<u n="70" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0084">but I get a banging banging headache</u>
<u n="72" who="S0041">sinus capsules sometimes help that</u>
<u n="73" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0041">but no I just couldn't imagine <pause dur="short"/> I could just couldn't imagine anything worse <pause dur="short"/> waitressing but doing all those things</u>
<u n="75" who="S0084">but being up in the air</u>
<u n="76" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="78" who="S0041">mm mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">the risk of death</u>
<u n="80" who="S0041">I couldn't couldn't do that</u>
<u n="81" who="S0084">no no no</u>
<u n="82" who="S0041">ah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I saw on his Facebook today put erm oh the girl I'm seeing wants to join the navy</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0041">not me <pause dur="short"/> another girl</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0041">erm something about making her a a cum bucket or a</u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0041">yeah I think I need to get Lazza</u>
<u n="89" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0041">yeah I have to read it to you it's shocking<pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came in earlier and I was stripping my bed but he couldn't see that bit and he just saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like precariously balanced on a few like er cushions on my settee <pause dur="short"/> and he went <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>why are you treating <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that way?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0084">ah cos it's got a little personality</u>
<u n="93" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0084">ah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she's horrible to you <pause dur="short"/> calls you names and everything <pause dur="short"/> is this going to make me say to you why are you joining the navy again?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> well no because I think it's because <trunc>sh</trunc> oh I don't well <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to not comment for now</u>
<u n="96" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="97" who="S0041">er</u>
<u n="98" who="S0084">does it make you feel sick?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0041">it is it's very gross <pause dur="short"/> it's very gross <pause dur="short"/> the stark realisation that we're sharing a ship with boys</u>
<u n="100" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0041"><unclear/> my browser</u>
<u n="102" who="S0084">huh<pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0041">oh I'm just going to have to <unclear/> this is pissing me off <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0084">nom nom nom</u>
<event desc="sound of washing machine"/>
<u n="105" who="S0041"><trunc>Thi</trunc> this girl I'm seeing wants to join the Navy and become a spunk bucket right and then there's loads of different comments on it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> one says dipped <pause dur="short"/> exclamation mark <pause dur="short"/> exclamation mark</u>
<u n="106" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says chuck it up her wrongun <pause dur="short"/> ditch her and when she joins your steps ahead of everyone else as in everyone else gets a go on her</u>
<u n="108" who="S0084">oh gross <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0041">see mate <pause dur="short"/> problem solved</u>
<u n="110" who="S0084">oh god</u>
<u n="111" who="S0041">and then someone says  what's the  what's the wrongun? And he goes tradesman's entrance</u>
<u n="112" who="S0084">as if you couldn't work that out</u>
<u n="113" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm one of them says a dirty home wrecking cum receptacle lol <pause dur="short"/> give her up <pause dur="short"/> give her one up the ranger's end <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0084">home wrecker? That's a bit weird</u>
<u n="115" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it must be because they're with boys all the time that anybody whose got a wife or a girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> katie used to say she got a lot of shit when she was in the RAF <pause dur="short"/> when they used to have like balls and things <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0084">Jesus Christ</u>
<u n="117" who="S0041">so we all have a high opinion of wrens then lol <pause dur="short"/> that's what they call girls in the navy <pause dur="short"/> wrens</u>
<u n="118" who="S0084">erm why join the navy?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0041">someone wrote they make me sick and then you are such a nob</u>
<u n="120" who="S0084">he is such a nob <pause dur="short"/> why do you like this boy?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0041">I mean he never wrote they make me sick <pause dur="short"/> oh no he hasn't wrote all these <pause dur="short"/> these are all what different people have written on it</u>
<u n="122" who="S0084">no but he wrote the spunk bucket</u>
<u n="123" who="S0041">yeah he did <pause dur="short"/> shocker isn't it</u>
<u n="124" who="S0084" trans="overlap">so this isn't the girl that's got all the kids is it?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0041">no no no <pause dur="short"/> no this is another girl <pause dur="short"/> not serious with her <pause dur="short"/> well obviously not to write this shit about her</u>
<u n="126" who="S0084">if that was me I would go fucking ape shit</u>
<u n="127" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0084">what the hell is the matter with him? Well that's probably what you're going to have to get used to</u>
<u n="129" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="long"/> Jesus wept</u>
<u n="130" who="S0084">Mate <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean really it's like you know that you're walking into that environment where it's all men all the time</u>
<u n="132" who="S0084">yeah but it's not until it's confronted <pause dur="short"/> you're confronted with it that it's real</u>
<u n="133" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like holy fuckers as if they actually say that <pause dur="short"/> but then I suppose at least when I'm on the ship none of them will be able to speak like that to me</u>
<u n="134" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="135" who="S0041" trans="overlap">like getting them fired <pause dur="short"/> they would be in really big trouble</u>
<u n="136" who="S0084">well in theory <pause dur="short"/> it's whether it depends how far you take it</u>
<u n="137" who="S0041">yeah I think  from what  from what my Michael's saying which is why he didn't want me to go in as an officer is so you know I don't think you'll have so much fun cos you know people won't be able to have a laugh and banter with you like they can with each other cos they're really not allowed <pause dur="short"/> it's really really strict</u>
<u n="138" who="S0084" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> that's a good thing</u>
<u n="139" who="S0041">yeah and I'm thinking yeah that's a good thing thanks</u>
<u n="140" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0041">which I can see where he's coming from <pause dur="short"/> like if you wanted to go and have a piss up and a laugh</u>
<u n="142" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0041">yeah but I'm thinking twenty-five erm that I would have probably found that amusing for about three weeks and then want to die</u>
<u n="144" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah and then you've got four years</u>
<u n="145" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0041">I suppose that's one good thing at least they won't actually be able to say it to my face</u>
<u n="148" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0084">it's going to be like school though isn't it</u>
<u n="151" who="S0041">yeah it's definitely going to be like school</u>
<u n="152" who="S0084">I literally couldn't imagine anything worse</u>
<u n="153" who="S0041">it's going to be like  it's going to be like  school</u>
<u n="154" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0041">I think</u>
<u n="156" who="S0084">and I wouldn't go back to school</u>
<u n="157" who="S0041">I thought school was great</u>
<u n="158" who="S0084">hmm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0041">well then maybe you'll get on fantastically <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> getting quite sore now <pause dur="short"/> it has to be said <pause dur="short"/> you should stop eating</u>
<u n="160" who="S0084" trans="overlap">do you need a second sitting?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0041">yeah I need to have a rest</u>
<u n="162" who="S0084">to be honest I'm more concerned about cos my friends at school were all boys so I was used to be around that type of yak language</u>
<u n="163" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0084">but they all knew not not to go there with me erm but I'd I'd join in and I'd give it as good as I got but they would never they'd never cross the line seeming as they called me Miss Manners they knew that there was certain things like say bad as that wouldn't get that bad</u>
<u n="165" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0084">erm my problem my my worry is that maybe when I'm there I might get carried away in joining in and taking the piss out of them and then I'll get in trouble</u>
<u n="167" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0084">for being too familiar with them which is a bit of a</u>
<u n="169" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you can't let your guard down really can you</u>
<u n="170" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> not at all</u>
<u n="171" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0084">but I suppose when you're there and there's other people that are officers to learn from that have already done that position for ages you'll know what type of behaviour to adopt won't you</u>
<u n="173" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and you've been a manager before so it's not totally alien</u>
<u n="174" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> the only thing is when you're a manager you go home and then you're silly all the time</u>
<u n="175" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0084">whereas I won't be able to go home and be silly <pause dur="short"/> I'll just be silly there and then people might see</u>
<u n="177" who="S0041">you might have an officers' mess on the boat where you can just be <trunc>m</trunc> where you can be silly together</u>
<u n="178" who="S0084">yeah that's alright <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I could <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="179" who="S0041" trans="overlap">because you'd have to have some sort of outlet wouldn't you</u>
<u n="180" who="S0084">yeah I couldn't keep me silly contained for all that time</u>
<u n="181" who="S0041">you'd just be like guy <pause dur="short"/> you know that American guy that's gone around shooting people in erm Afghanistan</u>
<u n="182" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what? What?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0041">an American was it off an army base? An American soldier walked off an army base and shot sixteen civilians</u>
<u n="184" who="S0084">shut up</u>
<u n="185" who="S0041">yeah they said oh he's had a breakdown <pause dur="short"/> oh he's had a nervous breakdown <pause dur="short"/> oh sorry about that</u>
<u n="186" who="S0084" trans="overlap">when was that?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0041">over the weekend <pause dur="short"/> walked off the base</u>
<u n="188" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I haven't seen the news <pause dur="short"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="189" who="S0041">fucking awful <pause dur="short"/> really really bad <pause dur="short"/> really bad <pause dur="short"/> and that that because that's what happens because you go fucking mental because it's not <pause dur="short"/> like your brain can't really cope with that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how many tours he'd been on <pause dur="short"/> like it might have been his first tour but and we don't know what else he'd seen while he was out there <pause dur="short"/> like one of his mates might have been killed <pause dur="short"/> you don't know but <event desc="recording skips"/> into the nearest village and started shooting</u>
<u n="190" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh <event desc="recording skips"/> Oh my god <pause dur="short"/> that is really bad <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna say it's nearly dinner time and you're gonna say but I've just eaten chips</u>
<u n="191" who="S0041">dad <pause dur="short"/> hi Dad <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> what on the internet? mm <pause dur="short"/> erm can you press F five that might work <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> cos that often works on my Mac <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/> If not and it's in a web browser you should be able to refresh on at the end of the web address it will have a little circular arrow and you just click that <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay well yeah if you go to the <trunc>we</trunc> on your browser where it's got the <trunc>in</trunc> erm ISP address you just click the circular arrow at the end <pause dur="short"/> does that make sense? Yeah? Perfect <pause dur="short"/> alright <pause dur="short"/> that's alright dad <pause dur="short"/> see you soon <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
<u n="192" who="S0084">argh</u>
<u n="193" who="S0041">he's got a Mac <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="recording skips"/> <unclear/> and he's not getting to grips with it</u>
<u n="194" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="195" who="S0041">I know he's so cute</u>
<u n="196" who="S0084">how sweet</u>
<u n="197" who="S0041"><unclear/> so cute man</u>
<u n="198" who="S0084">how sweet <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Mum used to call us up <pause dur="short"/> I've just got this <pause dur="short"/> shall I pop in in the bin in the trash can <pause dur="short"/> she nearly deleted him in <trunc>tr</trunc> by dragging it <pause dur="short"/> no stop <pause dur="short"/> stop touching <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh cute <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0084">Cos I couldn't really help him very much because I'd only just using <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s Mac cos it was a few years ago</u>
<u n="201" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh bless her <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0084">I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> please just stop touching <pause dur="short"/> I'll get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to ring you</u>
<u n="203" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'll see you later ladies</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">have fun</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084" trans="overlap">bye</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">erm this young girl that used to sit next to me was dappy as pig shit and erm use the FTP site to transfer big files and erm normally what you would do is you would locate your files <pause dur="short"/> press upload</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0041">load it up into the FTP site and then go away and whoever wanted to can go <unclear/> get it</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084" trans="overlap">can get it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041">she tried to upload an entire server</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041">so funny <pause dur="short"/> she was like this it's really taking a long time and it's got this error message and I said oh you're such a dick <pause dur="short"/> what are you <trunc>tr</trunc>? What? What are you trying to do? And she said oh it's erm silence <pause dur="short"/> then she realised what she'd done <pause dur="short"/> absolutely hilarious <pause dur="short"/> and she had to call the <trunc>he</trunc> the help desk and she was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> the thing is</u>
<u n="213" who="S0041">that's exactly like something I would do</u>
<u n="214" who="S0084">I've upload the entire <unclear/> server onto the FTP site and I've  and I've  crashed it <pause dur="short"/> erm sorry <pause dur="short"/> what a dip shit <pause dur="short"/> honestly</u>
<u n="215" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> I erm I tried to I wasn't concentrating and thought I was just making a a short cut to my desk top for our conference folder which by the way has built up and built up over nine years or something <pause dur="short"/> I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I'd copied <pause dur="short"/> I've moved the folder <pause dur="short"/> didn't know <pause dur="short"/> went away <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has a heart attack <pause dur="short"/> goes into the server <pause dur="short"/> no conference folder <pause dur="short"/> she's like holy fuck <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> where's the conference folder? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> where's it gone? They had to ring up IT <pause dur="short"/> I'd got it on my desktop <pause dur="short"/> I'd stolen it</u>
<u n="216" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0041">I was like I'm so sorry <pause dur="short"/> she was like it's fine as long as you have it <pause dur="short"/> everything we have is in there <pause dur="short"/> erm er <pause dur="short"/>  I thought I'd  I thought I'd hit short cut</u>
<u n="218" who="S0084">hilarious</u>
<u n="219" who="S0041">no I'd just stolen the whole folder</u>
<u n="220" who="S0084">fine fine <pause dur="short"/> mine mine</u>
<u n="221" who="S0041">mine mine</u>
<u n="222" who="S0084">I'm not really tech savvy really</u>
<u n="223" who="S0041">no I'm really not at all <pause dur="short"/> it's cos I've got no patience <pause dur="short"/> I get bored with it</u>
<u n="224" who="S0084">oh yeah I learn up a <trunc>cer</trunc> I learn a certain amount <pause dur="short"/> I could learn the shortcuts on the keyboard or I learn a few things to get me around and I I get bored <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah then that's it yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> I very rarely save things in the proper file cos I have to click through all the files the place to save it <pause dur="short"/> no desktop</u>
<u n="226" who="S0084">everything's on my desktop it's a complete mess</u>
<u n="227" who="S0041">yeah mine too</u>
<u n="228" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0041">when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to try and fine something the other day and she was like holy crap <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what happened to your desktop? And I was like it's a dumping ground</u>
<u n="230" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it vomited</u>
<u n="231" who="S0041">it's basically a dumping ground <pause dur="short"/> I got really exited when you were on the phone because I thought it was Gypsy Wedding day</u>
<u n="232" who="S0084">is it not?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0041">it's Wednesday isn't it Gypsy Wedding day</u>
<u n="234" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> is it Love in the Wild? I really want to watch Love in the Wild <pause dur="short"/> when is that on?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0041">I don't know</u>
<u n="236" who="S0084">that's never on <trunc>we</trunc> I think I've just dreamt that</u>
<u n="237" who="S0041">no I watched it <pause dur="short"/> where did I watch it? I saw the last tiny tiny smidgen of it</u>
<u n="238" who="S0084">I need it</u>
<u n="239" who="S0041">it might have been this weekend <pause dur="short"/> this whole weekend's like rolled away from me so</u>
<u n="240" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's gone bye bye</u>
<u n="241" who="S0041">yeah I don't really know what happened with that</u>
<u n="242" who="S0084">mm bye bye</u>
<u n="243" who="S0041">do you watch One Tree Hill?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="245" who="S0041">ah you are a wrong'un <pause dur="short"/> you are wrong</u>
<u n="246" who="S0084" trans="overlap">is that on tonight? My sister would very much agree with you <pause dur="short"/> she likes  all your all your  all your programmes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> you're wrong in the head <pause dur="short"/> that's because I I like basically teenage crap</u>
<u n="248" who="S0084">essentially yep</u>
<u n="249" who="S0041">Don't have to too much watching <pause dur="short"/> quite simple</u>
<u n="250" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> thinking</u>
<u n="251" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="252" who="S0084">in fact the less thinking you do the better really cos you're if you try and think about it you'll realise it doesn't make any sense</u>
<u n="253" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah it definitely doesn't make any sense</u>
<u n="254" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0041">that's why I get along with er crap teen films too</u>
<u n="256" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> I like crap TV as well</u>
<u n="257" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that's on at nine</u>
<u n="258" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> what time is it now?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0041">six <pause dur="short"/> even though it feels like it's eight</u>
<u n="260" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> does feel like bed time</u>
<u n="261" who="S0041"><event desc="recording skips"/> movie</u>
<u n="262" who="S0084"><event desc="recording skips"/> you don't have any movies here do you? Apart from Harry Potter <pause dur="short"/> one to three</u>
<u n="263" who="S0041">oh no they've been stolen now</u>
<u n="264" who="S0084">oh<anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0041">we could go and raid <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room though</u>
<u n="266" who="S0084">we should take <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh oh that hurt me more than I thought it would <pause dur="short"/> more than I hate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> hate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> </u>
<u n="268" who="S0084" trans="overlap">my sister's little bedroom</u>
<u n="269" who="S0041">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0084">go on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> don't be naughty for mummy <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0041">you <pause dur="short"/> you <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> and you <pause dur="short"/> and you <pause dur="short"/> and oops and you <pause dur="short"/> knives <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> no no no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0084">come on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0041">mm yum yum <pause dur="long"/> And you in there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0084">oh did it fall down?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0041">no it wasn't up</u>
<u n="276" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0041">but I just saw it and wanted it up <pause dur="short"/> I keep not putting it up because it needs framing but it's just going to get boshed around so I just thought I'd put it up for now</u>
<u n="278" who="S0084">put it up <pause dur="short"/> I went <pause dur="short"/> oh look what I've got in here</u>
<u n="279" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0084">erm I've got my frame from The Framing Shop in Sussex <trunc>r</trunc> Sussex Park thingy <pause dur="short"/> you know where brother's mum is?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that place <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="282" who="S0084">that secret place</u>
<u n="283" who="S0041">was it not expensive?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0084">erm I don't know because I don't know how much frames cost</u>
<u n="285" who="S0041">well we can get one for about a tenner</u>
<u n="286" who="S0084">oh yeah then yes <pause dur="short"/> it was maybe twenty-five</u>
<u n="287" who="S0041">oh that's not too bad</u>
<u n="288" who="S0084">I thought it was fine and she fitted it all for me which was quite nice because I would never have been able to do that</u>
<u n="289" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh that's good</u>
<u n="290" who="S0084">she did a really good job because it was the poster was a really weird fit</u>
<u n="291" who="S0041">erm <pause dur="short"/> what do we need? We need this</u>
<u n="292" who="S0084">I just need this secret thing here</u>
<u n="293" who="S0041">the secret little  thing here</u>
<u n="294" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just need this</u>
<u n="295" who="S0041">yeah  bought it as a moving in present when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I moved into the barn</u>
<u n="296" who="S0084">oh nice</u>
<u n="297" who="S0041">erm because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> calls me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0084">oh yeah you said <pause dur="short"/> oh that's cute</u>
<u n="299" who="S0041">yeah so she got it from Camden Market I think</u>
<u n="300" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0041">I just like touching it because of the oil <pause dur="short"/> touch touch</u>
<u n="302" who="S0084">it proves you're not supposed to do that</u>
<u n="303" who="S0041">yeah pretty sure that's not part of it but it was too late had to do it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0084">fine</u>
<u n="305" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> there's no film on there</u>
<u n="306" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0041">what are you? Judge Judy <pause dur="short"/> Gossip Girl <pause dur="short"/> none of those</u>
<u n="308" who="S0084">so you're going to be a godmother then?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah apparently</u>
<u n="310" who="S0084">it turned out</u>
<u n="311" who="S0041">er it turns out I'm going to need some pretty good excuses when that comes around</u>
<u n="312" who="S0084">erm you hate children <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty god excuse</u>
<u n="313" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I hate children <pause dur="short"/> I am not religious <pause dur="short"/> I'm going in the navy</u>
<u n="314" who="S0084">you're a really bad influence</u>
<u n="315" who="S0041">I'm an awful influence <pause dur="short"/> completely unreliable <pause dur="short"/> you've seen how much I loose my phone <pause dur="short"/> you might just loose <trunc>c</trunc> touch with me just like that</u>
<u n="316" who="S0084">imagine you had a baby <pause dur="short"/> imagine if you had a baby <pause dur="short"/> you might just loose the baby</u>
<u n="317" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I might just <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> might just loose your baby</u>
<u n="318" who="S0084">would you risk it? I don't think so</u>
<u n="319" who="S0041">no I don't think you should risk it <unclear/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="321" who="S0041">yes that's a bit concerning</u>
<u n="322" who="S0084">well I don't think she is pregnant otherwise they would have done another test</u>
<u n="323" who="S0041">yeah I I think she's not</u>
<u n="324" who="S0084">I think she's probably milking it for some reason <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure why</u>
<u n="325" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><trunc>S</trunc> Si was stupid gone with the wild <pause dur="short"/> live in the wild one</u>
<u n="326" who="S0084">gone in the wild <pause dur="short"/> gone wild <pause dur="short"/> where is it? ITV something</u>
<u n="327" who="S0041">oh you're hurting me leg <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="328" who="S0084">oh that's quite a good er little rest isn't it</u>
<u n="329" who="S0041">oh I just happened to be there</u>
<u n="330" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="331" who="S0041">just happened to find it</u>
<u n="332" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos that's what it's there for</u>
<u n="333" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> resting on <pause dur="short"/> not exercising on</u>
<u n="334" who="S0084">no no no no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> it's not that <pause dur="short"/> I thought it might have been BBC two but it's not that either</u>
<u n="336" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I hope <trunc>lo</trunc></u>
<u n="337" who="S0041">Don't Tell The Bride is on at eight</u>
<u n="338" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="339" who="S0041">I hate you such much</u>
<u n="340" who="S0084">I <unclear/> it now</u>
<u n="341" who="S0041">there is nothing good on here I'm afraid</u>
<u n="342" who="S0084">oh no <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> we need <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s movies</u>
<u n="343" who="S0041">I know I'll text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and ask him to see if we can get them <pause dur="short"/> get a film <pause dur="short"/> I can make it</u>
<u n="344" who="S0084">go go gadget arms</u>
<u n="345" who="S0041">yes go go <trunc>ga</trunc> ah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> Inspector Gadget <pause dur="short"/> I used to love that programme</u>
<u n="346" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> It was amazing <pause dur="short"/> it reminds me of school holidays because I think that's when they used to put it on <pause dur="short"/> in the summer</u>
<u n="347" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh did they?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0084">it reminds me of the school holidays <pause dur="short"/> I'll get you Gadget<vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0041">that was always one of my favourites is Gadget actually</u>
<u n="350" who="S0084">gadget was pretty good <pause dur="short"/> danger Mouse <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> DM</u>
<u n="351" who="S0041">why don't I remember Danger Mouse?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0084">probably a little bit too young</u>
<u n="353" who="S0041" trans="overlap">was I?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it wasn't on for very long <pause dur="short"/> early eighties <pause dur="short"/> only like eighty-one eighty-two <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Like Button Moon would have been too early for you</u>
<u n="355" who="S0041" trans="overlap">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't born till eighty-seven</u>
<u n="356" who="S0084">crumbs DM</u>
<u n="357" who="S0041">Cos like I know what it is but I don't remember watching it</u>
<u n="358" who="S0084">you don't remember it?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="360" who="S0084">dogtanian?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I know  I know  who Danger Mouse is</u>
<u n="362" who="S0084">dogtanian and the Muskehounds?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I go <unclear/> movies <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0041">you're such a criminal <pause dur="short"/> do you know remember when I spilt something wet on my bed over there?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="366" who="S0041">when I was tidying up <pause dur="short"/> do you remember?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0041">well so I stripped my bed earlier and it had gone through the mattress protector to over here and I sponged it and I've got it up whatever it was</u>
<u n="369" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="370" who="S0041">it smells really funky</u>
<u n="371" who="S0084" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="372" who="S0041">right I need to fabreze this shit</u>
<u n="373" who="S0084">oh what could it be? Maybe it was a milk product</u>
<u n="374" who="S0041">I don't  I don't  know but it's bad times <pause dur="short"/> it's really bad times</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084">oh man <pause dur="short"/> it's fungus in your bed</u>
<u n="376" who="S0041">yeah it smells awful <pause dur="short"/> but it smells quite chemically which is strange</u>
<u n="377" who="S0084">oh maybe it was the cleaning product <pause dur="short"/> I mean you were cleaning <pause dur="short"/> that's why I remember it</u>
<u n="378" who="S0041">the one and only time</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084">the one and only time you tidied your room</u>
<u n="380" who="S0041">one and only time <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know what to do about that <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to get some Fabreze</u>
<u n="381" who="S0084" trans="overlap">erm fabreze it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I can smell it now <pause dur="short"/> it's driving me mad</u>
<u n="383" who="S0084">so what is it now on the top or on the bottom?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">and it's on the top because you can't flip it over?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084">why?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0041">because it's like this on the other side</u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">ah maybe I put mine upside down <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>p</trunc></u>
<u n="388" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so I've just switched it round and if that doesn't work I'll actually flip it <pause dur="short"/> I'm just going to spray it with this for now <pause dur="short"/> I don't suppose that's normal putting deodorant on your mattress but</u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> probably not</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041">do you think I can just go up there even if he doesn't reply? Do you think that's allowed?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> we've we've we've messaged him</u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">yeah that counts let's go</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> oh man <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm full of</u>
<u n="394" who="S0041"></u>
<u n="395" who="S0084">I'm cold</u>
<u n="396" who="S0041">are you cold?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0084">I'm freezing <pause dur="short"/> are you not cold?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="399" who="S0084">I need to get my jumper <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0084">I knew he wouldn't mind <pause dur="short"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> oh it's <trunc>co</trunc> it's it's down here that it's cold <pause dur="short"/> upstairs is warm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0041">is there a window open?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0084"><unclear/> I think</u>
<u n="403" who="S0041">I need to choose some juice</u>
<u n="404" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0041">choose some apple juice <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/>Little boxes on the hillside <pause dur="short"/> little boxes made of ticky tacky <pause dur="short"/> little boxes on the hillside <pause dur="short"/> little boxes on the hillside<shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah why have I got that in my head?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0084">what are you singing?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0041">it's from an advert</u>
<u n="408" who="S0084">what is it?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>Little boxes on the hillside <pause dur="short"/> little boxes made of ticky tacky <pause dur="short"/> little boxes on the hillside<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> I think it probably is from an advert <pause dur="short"/> although I can't tell you what it is</u>
<u n="411" who="S0041">and obviously you have to sing it with the craziest <unclear/> accent</u>
<u n="412" who="S0084">crazy scary accent of murderers</u>
<u n="413" who="S0041">of murderers <pause dur="short"/> it does sound like a murderers song doesn't it</u>
<u n="414" who="S0084">Cos it sounds like a murderers was singing it as they were chopping someone up to put in the little boxes</u>
<u n="415" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> have you seen chocolate orange?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0084">have I seen the chocolate orange advert?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0041">no the film the chocolate orange <pause dur="short"/> clockwork Orange</u>
<u n="418" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't realise <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>  had entered  had entered the room</u>
<u n="419" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> comment <pause dur="short"/> that was brilliant</u>
<u n="420" who="S0084">Cos I was like does she mean it's a film <pause dur="short"/> I'm <trunc>s</trunc> I've never heard of this <pause dur="short"/> erm I have seen A Clockwork Orange <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="421" who="S0041">with the pig</u>
<u n="422" who="S0084">with the pig <pause dur="short"/> I don't like the pig <pause dur="short"/> he freaks me out</u>
<u n="423" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> which are we doing</u>
<u n="424" who="S0084">er flesh eating zombies</u>
<u n="425" who="S0041">flesh eating zombies</u>
<u n="426" who="S0084">if there are zombies <pause dur="short"/> zombies</u>
<u n="427" who="S0041">I don't think it's zombies <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a virus</u>
<u n="428" who="S0084">oh that will do <pause dur="short"/> I'll try not to get too scared <pause dur="short"/> it's not too dark yet <pause dur="short"/> although we might have to turn the lights off because it is a <trunc>sp</trunc> a scary film</u>
<u n="429" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> it's only fair <pause dur="short"/> have you been put back in there</u>
<u n="430" who="S0084">you</u>
<u n="431" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> I pressed the wrong button again</u>
<u n="432" who="S0084">you</u>
<u n="433" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>Little boxes on the hillside<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0084">so Vodaphone is supposed to be picking up my phone tomorrow</u>
<u n="435" who="S0041">okay</u>
<u n="436" who="S0084">what do you reckon the chances are? Slim to none?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0041">probably slim to none <pause dur="short"/> erm the killer of course being the orange is really really good</u>
<u n="438" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0041">like they're brilliant <pause dur="short"/> they'll <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lost her phone <pause dur="short"/> three times <pause dur="short"/> in a month</u>
<u n="440" who="S0084" trans="overlap">are they? Right</u>
<u n="441" who="S0041">and they <pause dur="short"/> they like they brought the <trunc>sh</trunc> the <unclear/> They brought a new one <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't working properly <pause dur="short"/> they collected it <pause dur="short"/> picked it up the next day <pause dur="short"/> they were in and out of the house about seven times a month <pause dur="short"/> they were brilliant</u>
<u n="442" who="S0084">bloody hell</u>
<u n="443" who="S0041">on time every time <pause dur="short"/> like she wasn't without her phone for more than twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="444" who="S0084">oh I'm so jealous</u>
<u n="445" who="S0041">yeah they were really good</u>
<u n="446" who="S0084">because I'm going to take this phone away and I don't <pause dur="short"/> well A I don't know if they are actually come or do it at the right address</u>
<u n="447" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0084">I mean this is <pause dur="short"/> oh that was the eighth yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0041">er that seems a bit tight in there at the moment <pause dur="short"/> how is that?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0084">have you got  have you got  other secret things in there?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="452" who="S0084">berties not hanging out in there is he?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ber</trunc> Berties just rocking it in there</u>
<u n="454" who="S0084">he's running away from you <pause dur="short"/> that's that's what this is <pause dur="short"/> you know when you can't find him <pause dur="short"/> he's actually just running running away from you</u>
<u n="455" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh do you think <pause dur="short"/> oh don't say that</u>
<u n="456" who="S0084">well I just want to tell it like it is really <pause dur="short"/> really <pause dur="short"/> that really made me piss my pants yesterday when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> slammed that door</u>
<u n="457" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0084">you know when we were in here last night and watched a movie and he slammed the door <pause dur="short"/> and I jumped out of my skin</u>
<u n="459" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0084">oh man</u>
<u n="461" who="S0041">that was some scary times</u>
<u n="462" who="S0084">I thought the zombies were going to come in <pause dur="short"/> you've seen The Hills Have Eyes <pause dur="short"/> you know what's possible</u>
<u n="463" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> I know what's a possibility <pause dur="short"/> let's put these little lights off <pause dur="short"/> erm yes so</u>
<u n="464" who="S0084" trans="overlap">they probably do all kind of testing around here <pause dur="short"/> military testing</u>
<u n="465" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="466" who="S0084">on people's brains <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0041">yes I looked out of the kitchen window this morning</u>
<u n="468" who="S0084">the kitchen window <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="469" who="S0041">to notice that just outside my on my window frame at the top is a peg</u>
<u n="470" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="471" who="S0041">A blue peg <pause dur="short"/> and I was like what is that?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0084">normal</u>
<u n="473" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and it was like oh yeah you've been pegged <pause dur="short"/> I was like <pause dur="short"/> should I <unclear/> what that means <pause dur="short"/> what is that?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0084">erm <pause dur="short"/> don't know <pause dur="short"/> what is that?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0041">erm <pause dur="short"/> apparently <pause dur="short"/> what's his name? Crazy horse</u>
<u n="476" who="S0084">crazy horse <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="477" who="S0041">did it <pause dur="short"/> why did he do that? He said well you know some people you know pull on the weekend <pause dur="short"/> well he's taking to carrying around pegs and pegging people</u>
<u n="478" who="S0084">rank <pause dur="short"/> rank as hell <pause dur="short"/> so what he actually puts pegs on girls?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> without them knowing</u>
<u n="480" who="S0084">and <trunc>sa</trunc> and says you've been pegged</u>
<u n="481" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> ha ha ha ha <pause dur="short"/> yeah just as a joke</u>
<u n="482" who="S0084">is he twelve years old?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0041">yes in short</u>
<u n="484" who="S0084">what the hell? I mean who does that? So you've been pegged <pause dur="short"/> so you have to marry him now</u>
<u n="485" who="S0041">I forgot my bloody mattress protectors in there <pause dur="short"/> I erm ought to put it on really to cover that smell because it's been driving me mad <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> least until I can <pause dur="short"/> strange thing to have to sort out but there we go</u>
<u n="486" who="S0084">there's that boy who was in Boy Meets World</u>
<u n="487" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0084">I know <pause dur="short"/> his mate <pause dur="short"/> the quite hot one who was naughty <pause dur="short"/> his name's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> possibly <pause dur="short"/> oh I need to find you the charger</u>
<u n="489" who="S0041" trans="overlap">boy Meets World <pause dur="short"/> oh is he really famous now?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0084">erm he's really famous now <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0041">if this is who I think it is he's actually really famous now and you'll be kicking</u>
<u n="492" who="S0084">well I probably do need kicking <pause dur="short"/> I haven't heard of Emeli Sande to be fair</u>
<u n="493" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="494" who="S0084">so I probably do need some sort of erm lesson in modern modern culture</u>
<u n="495" who="S0041" trans="overlap">you've probably got issues <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="496" who="S0084">I might need to start reading you know <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>he</trunc> Heat</u>
<u n="497" who="S0041">I hate that type of stuff</u>
<u n="498" who="S0084">well that's my problem <pause dur="short"/> I actually detest it <pause dur="short"/> it's so negative <pause dur="short"/> you know the circle of shame <pause dur="short"/> you know laughing at everyone all the time if they've just got a little bit of <trunc>l</trunc> if they've got a spot or a bit of bloody cellulite and you think no wonder girls have got eating disorders</u>
<u n="499" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0084">that <pause dur="short"/> and I went in Mango recently <pause dur="short"/> bought a a yellow jumper and a medium is a ten</u>
<u n="501" who="S0041">I'm so glad you said that cos I went into Mango and tried on a a dress in a large and there was no way I was getting in it</u>
<u n="502" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's disgusting <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but that's like <pause dur="short"/> that's a twelve</u>
<u n="503" who="S0041">ah right <pause dur="short"/> well that probably makes some sense then</u>
<u n="504" who="S0084" trans="overlap">in in mental Mango world a large is twelve</u>
<u n="505" who="S0041" trans="overlap">Cos I usually think a large is a fourteen and an extra large is a sixteen</u>
<u n="506" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0041">that's what I would go for</u>
<u n="508" who="S0084">well in European sizes I suppose it is cos they're all quite petite <pause dur="short"/> but even by their standards that's disgusting <pause dur="short"/> because you're saying to girls who are twelve which is an average size <pause dur="short"/> you're large</u>
<u n="509" who="S0041" trans="overlap">you're large</u>
<u n="510" who="S0084">so no wonder girls have got eating disorders</u>
<u n="511" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0041">it's it's so responsible isn't it</u>
<u n="513" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I can't believe that</u>
<u n="514" who="S0041">A twelve is a large <pause dur="short"/> shitting hell <pause dur="short"/> there's no hope for anybody</u>
<u n="515" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I mean you can fuck off <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you might as well just kill yourself now</u>
<u n="516" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0084" trans="overlap">if Mango have got anything to do with it <pause dur="short"/> oh so yes that's why I don't read gossip magazines <pause dur="short"/> I like to read a bit of er Love It</u>
<u n="518" who="S0041">what's that?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0084">hmm?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0041">what's Love It?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0084">you know what Love It is <pause dur="short"/> it's the one of those awful magazines where it's like my dog mauled my babies head but I still love it and I might marry it</u>
<u n="522" who="S0041"><unclear/> Really <pause dur="short"/> love It</u>
<u n="523" who="S0084" trans="overlap">hmm <pause dur="short"/> it's fine <pause dur="short"/> love It <pause dur="short"/> it's like Bella <pause dur="short"/> chat <pause dur="short"/> take A Break</u>
<u n="524" who="S0041">I like Take A Break</u>
<u n="525" who="S0084">you've put that on the wrong way</u>
<u n="526" who="S0041">oh piss <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="527" who="S0084">your life is so hard isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I mean other people might say they would hold up the er cover before they put it on just to check</u>
<u n="528" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="529" who="S0084">not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>knows best</u>
<u n="530" who="S0041">and I'm such a bad bed maker <pause dur="short"/> that's another thing that concerns me about this navy thing <pause dur="short"/> when they start checking and find all your shit and and I'm going no I'm focused</u>
<u n="531" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's not  that's not  worked has it</u>
<u n="532" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no it hasn't has it <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="533" who="S0084">why don't you just spread it out and do it later when you can actually be able to</u>
<u n="534" who="S0041">yeah I think that's the plan</u>
<u n="535" who="S0084">erm the thing is though <pause dur="short"/> they'll actually you know train you in this <pause dur="short"/> that's their job <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose lots of people go in the army and navy and whatever and have you when you are young</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">I suppose they don't really know what they've got their work cut out for with me do they</u>
<u n="537" who="S0084">well no</u>
<u n="538" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0084">Dearie me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> the noise</u>
<u n="540" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> that will just do now <pause dur="short"/> all of you over there <pause dur="short"/> that's all done now</u>
<u n="541" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="542" who="S0041">all done now <pause dur="short"/> over now <pause dur="short"/> oh thank god for that <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="543" who="S0084">do you know what? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was telling me about being in the mess there when you do your training <pause dur="short"/> he was saying that his drill sergeant was such an arse and wanted things so precise <pause dur="short"/> like he'd really punished <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the week before for not having his bed exactly like at a right angle <pause dur="short"/> all this carry on <pause dur="short"/> so they spent the whole <pause dur="short"/> him and his bunk mate spent the whole day getting their stuff like washed <pause dur="short"/> ironed <pause dur="short"/> they scrubbed the place <pause dur="short"/> on the floor <pause dur="short"/> they slept on the floor <pause dur="short"/> naked <pause dur="short"/> so that they didn't mess up the bed <pause dur="short"/> and so when the guy came in at six O'clock in the morning he came in and he threw everything around <pause dur="short"/> like he'd pulled everything out of the cupboards <pause dur="short"/> throwing stuff on the floor <pause dur="short"/> he went mental <pause dur="short"/> and he was like you two <pause dur="short"/> you live in shit <pause dur="short"/> and he made them run around outside for like an hour</u>
<u n="544" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0084">run around in their pants <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0041">see I have</u>
<u n="547" who="S0084">Cos it's a mind fuck <pause dur="short"/> that's what annoys me</u>
<u n="548" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0084">there's no need to do that</u>
<u n="550" who="S0041">I have talked this through with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually because if someone did that to me I wouldn't be having it</u>
<u n="551" who="S0084">it would be game over <pause dur="short"/> he would <trunc>nev</trunc> <trunc>wh</trunc> why would you take <trunc>o</trunc> orders from someone like that?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0041">no you wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> and I said that to him <pause dur="short"/> and he was like no no they're not like that <pause dur="short"/> I said no but if they actually did that</u>
<u n="553" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0041">I'm not talking oh shit and get on with it <pause dur="short"/> I would plain blank refuse to move</u>
<u n="555" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0041">I would just fuck tell them to fuck off</u>
<u n="557" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there's just no justification for that</u>
<u n="558" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> They can't pick me up and physically move me</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">they can do what they want <pause dur="short"/> I will just sit there and not move cos that's just out of control</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">there's no need for it</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041">he said that they do that in the army <pause dur="short"/> they don't do it in the navy</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">well it's like breaking your spirit isn't it <pause dur="short"/> that's what really upsets me <pause dur="short"/> like there just doesn't seem to be a need for it</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041" trans="overlap">they don't even do it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think they must do with them because they have to prepare for not thinking and just going over the top</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">yeah but still</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? Yeah I just</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084" trans="overlap">horrific</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">how are you supposed to respect someone like that?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041" trans="overlap">horrible</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084">it's mad but they do cos they break them</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">they break them and remould them don't they</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0041">that's the whole  that's the whole  plan</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> all of the plan</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041">right are you ready for this shit?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084">I'm scared already <pause dur="short"/> that all looks a bit terrifying <pause dur="short"/> are we going to get the virus?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0041">maybe <pause dur="short"/> I've probably already got it</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084">you probably have <pause dur="short"/> I've been incubating it all day <pause dur="short"/> and then I <trunc>w</trunc> getting ready to spread it around everybody at work tomorrow</u>
<u n="582" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">I'm so nice like that</u>
<u n="584" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm really getting a cold <pause dur="short"/> he was like she's going to love me going around there with a cold <pause dur="short"/> he's like I would call her and tell but then she'd say not to go around so I'm just going to go</u>
<u n="587" who="S0084">urgh <pause dur="short"/> so you're going to infect her and the kids</u>
<u n="588" who="S0041">on purpose <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084">urgh <pause dur="short"/> he's such a weirdo</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">isn't he</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">I'm scared <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">see these type ones scare me more than The Grudge type ones because these ones could happen <pause dur="short"/> there's one called Cabin Fever</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084">that's</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">no  is that  is that this? Okay <pause dur="short"/> that's not the one I mean <pause dur="short"/> there's one called lake cabin or cabin lake or?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> that does sound a bit familiar</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">that don't ever watch that <pause dur="short"/> that could really happen <pause dur="short"/> that's about gypos <pause dur="short"/> killer <pause dur="short"/> gypo killer <pause dur="short"/> killer gypos</u>
<u n="597" who="S0084">killer gypos <pause dur="short"/> shit man</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> and their rottweiler dogs <pause dur="short"/> it could actually happen</u>
<u n="599" who="S0084" trans="overlap">shit <pause dur="short"/> they're going to actually eat your face</u>
<u n="600" who="S0041">yeah they they do eat faces yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0084">mm I bit <trunc>s</trunc> a bit concerned</u>
<u n="602" who="S0041">and it's like you know those slap videos?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0041">like that but got extreme <pause dur="short"/> it's gone too far and the kids are egging each other on and it goes to far and they're killing people</u>
<u n="605" who="S0084" trans="overlap">shit <pause dur="short"/> happy slapping</u>
<u n="606" who="S0041">yeah that's what I mean</u>
<u n="607" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="608" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah it's really realistic <pause dur="short"/> it could actually happen</u>
<u n="609" who="S0084">oh I don't want to <pause dur="short"/> er can you hear the flies?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0084">are they on your face?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> hear flies <pause dur="short"/> where's the good stuff? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you want some <trunc>s</trunc> sour Skittles in your life?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0084">erm?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0041">taste good</u>
<u n="615" who="S0084">Don't I don't know who if <pause dur="short"/> will it turn my face inside out?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0041">erm a little bit inside out</u>
<u n="617" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> just so long as I know what I'm getting myself into</u>
<u n="618" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> I'm dropping them on the floor <pause dur="short"/> you need a good handful to make sure it gets them</u>
<u n="619" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh you nutter <pause dur="short"/> ta</u>
<u n="620" who="S0041">gets the face turning</u>
<u n="621" who="S0084">thank you <pause dur="short"/> we've got a Skittle escape <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="623" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="625" who="S0084">it's gone wrong <pause dur="short"/> it's gone wrong <pause dur="short"/> oh Gromit it's the wrong trousers <pause dur="short"/> it's gone wrong</u>
<u n="626" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> There's one there</u>
<u n="627" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> no oh stop <pause dur="short"/> off they go again <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> well you behave yourself <pause dur="short"/> thanks <pause dur="short"/> I was just saving them for later</u>
<u n="628" who="S0041">that sound was perfect <pause dur="short"/> I think they're just the right amount of face turning</u>
<u n="629" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> they're not too bad are they <pause dur="short"/> these are the ones that make your face sweat though</u>
<u n="630" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0084">do you get the face sweats?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">it doesn't sweat but I get the tingle</u>
<u n="633" who="S0084">I get the face <pause dur="short"/> oh shit man <pause dur="short"/> what is that?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0041">Don't know</u>
<u n="635" who="S0084">scared</u>
</body>
</text>
