<text id="SDHU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:52:48</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0238 S0242</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>My dining room, Bradford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>scruffy clothes, breakfast, fruit farms, deserted medieval villages, roadworks, jam, coffee, growing herbs, old people, junk mail, phones, selling ANON's old house</topics>
		<activity>Conversation over breakfast</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, anecdote telling </conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0238">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Shipley, West Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>senior lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified; Chinese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0242">
				<exactage>69</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Windsor</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>Germany</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- advanced; Italian -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0238">to get the strimmer working erm then obviously I'm not I'm gonna be wanting to wear my real scruffy clothes</u>
<u n="2" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0238">because you can get oil on you and all sorts of things</u>
<u n="4" who="S0242">yes <unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="5" who="S0238">I've already <trunc>real</trunc> I've got a mark on those white trousers which I'm thinking could be oil I mean I haven't used them in the garden but you sometimes get oil on you even from things like a car door</u>
<u n="6" who="S0242">yeah it can happen</u>
<u n="7" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> but I've put them through the washing machine and it didn't shift so erm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0242">oh</u>
<u n="9" who="S0238">things like oil are difficult</u>
<u n="10" who="S0242">yes</u>
<u n="11" who="S0238">erm so <pause dur="short"/> cereals cutlery no <unclear/> got both <vocal desc="laugh"/> bread things to put on bread</u>
<u n="12" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="13" who="S0238">the milk erm is still in the fridge er there is some juice as well if you want it but otherwise I wouldn't I've held my coffee I haven't had coffee yet</u>
<u n="14" who="S0242">okay alright I'll start off with some</u>
<u n="15" who="S0238">erm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0242">cereal of some sort</u>
<u n="17" who="S0238">and oh yes what I didn't say was there's a little bowl with a few strawberries left in it in the fridge if you want to put those on your cereal they could do with using</u>
<u n="18" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh oh well</u>
<u n="19" who="S0238">I sort of <pause dur="short"/> I've been tending to do that I sort of start it in the strawberry season and then carry on <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm if if something doesn't seem to have a lot in I've got that maple and pecan one there's another packet in here so that would be fine <pause dur="long"/> I could have been doing this knitting when we were talking last night I've never taken so flipping long to knit a sleeve <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0242">to what sorry?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0238">to knit a sleeve</u>
<u n="22" who="S0242">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="23" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> I start cos I started it before I went away and then of course I didn't take it with me because I always worry if I'm travelling if I take knitting with me either the needles might break in the suitcase or I might have something stolen and lose that wool or you know so erm but I have been back a week <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I still haven't finished the damn thing</u>
<u n="24" who="S0242">you still haven't finished the sleeve? right</u>
<u n="25" who="S0238" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0238">no once you've got what you want I'll go in there and and make the coffee but</u>
<u n="27" who="S0242">wait wait sorry go again</u>
<u n="28" who="S0238" trans="overlap">I said once you've got what you want I'll go in there and make the coffee but there isn't really room for both of us at the same time</u>
<u n="29" who="S0242">yeah right <pause dur="long"/> this looks like a new milk is that it?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0238">yes erm because I've been using that almond milk</u>
<u n="31" who="S0242">oh right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0238">which is actually quite nice on cereal I don't know how it cooks though so I would have needed to buy some normal milk anyway because I wanted to use some in cooking</u>
<u n="33" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0238">erm and I don't really want to present you with a failed experiment <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0238">so finish those strawberries I said</u>
<u n="36" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> alright</u>
<u n="37" who="S0238">no I'll start doing that putting a few strawberries on cereal in the strawberry season and then I sort of gradually realise that it's not <vocal desc="laugh"/> really the strawberry season anymore and I'm still doing it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="39" who="S0238">but er <pause dur="long"/> well they can't be that expensive cos I would have noticed I mean there comes a point with a lot of fruit where it's still available but it's suddenly become ridiculously expensive</u>
<u n="40" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0238">at which point I normally stop buying it</u>
<u n="42" who="S0242">yep</u>
<u n="43" who="S0238">erm so I don't know where they get their strawberries from at this time of year</u>
<u n="44" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0238">I know actually that the fruit from <vocal desc="cough"/> where I go fruit picking</u>
<u n="46" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0238">which is just beyond <anon type="place"/> erm I know that seems like a long way to go but it's really good quality stuff and so on</u>
<u n="48" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0238">whereas anything more local I've gone and it if you plough your way through nettles and thistles to get at the strawberries I just think</u>
<u n="50" who="S0242" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="51" who="S0238">and they've got a lot of places just have strawberries and this place has got a whole range of things</u>
<u n="52" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0238">including you know peas and stuff as well erm and I particularly like raspberries they're my favourite fruit erm but their notice said <pause dur="short"/> up to the end of August for both strawberries and raspberries</u>
<u n="54" who="S0242">really?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0238">which surprised me</u>
<u n="56" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0238">so they obviously just have a whole range of varieties</u>
<u n="58" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0238">and plant them at <trunc>diff</trunc> at slightly different times and</u>
<u n="60" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0238">just manage it because it's in their interest</u>
<u n="62" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0238">to have it going as long as possible</u>
<u n="64" who="S0242">if you can keep it the season going great</u>
<u n="65" who="S0238">mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0242">great of course for them</u>
<u n="67" who="S0238">true <pause dur="short"/> no I I the only reason why I didn't try raspberries this year was I was just it was just there would have been too many things you know my mum grows them but they're a bit pathetic</u>
<u n="68" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0238">erm but I've actually been over <pause dur="short"/> three times to their <trunc>frui</trunc> I normally just go once you know but I went once on my own and then I took my mother cos it's a farm shop with <pause dur="short"/> er a café a <trunc>mu</trunc> er</u>
<u n="70" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0238">in the café I realised why this year that they've expanded the café since last year <pause dur="short"/> erm so I took her for lunch one day erm <pause dur="short"/> and I just went and did a very little quick pick whilst she was walking between the <vocal desc="laugh"/> car and the café more or less I mean</u>
<u n="72" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0238">slight exaggeration there but you know</u>
<u n="74" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0238">erm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0242"><unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0238">she she's very slow these days <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><unclear>well</unclear></u>
<u n="79" who="S0238">erm and and then bought some some things from the shop cos they have stuff that they've picked in the shop as well you know</u>
<u n="80" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> and then I was oh I know where I went I went to erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> deserted medieval village does that mean anything to you?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0242">no</u>
<u n="83" who="S0238">erm there are quite a lot of <pause dur="short"/> deserted medieval villages around I think</u>
<u n="84" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="85" who="S0238">but this one's in <anon type="place"/> er it's English Heritage <pause dur="short"/> er and obviously a lot of of such places may have been deserted in medieval times but then they were built on later so this is</u>
<u n="86" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0238">just in a in a field kinda thing so I mean it's mostly lumps in the grass</u>
<u n="88" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0238">erm but the church is still</u>
<u n="90" who="S0242" trans="overlap">you need a vivid imagination</u>
<u n="91" who="S0238">yeah erm the church is still a building albeit roofless it was used for quite a long time as a parish church</u>
<u n="92" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0238">after people had gone from the village itself <pause dur="short"/> erm but it was excavated for quite a long something like between nineteen fifty-nine and nineteen ninety-nine you know I mean a really long period of time</u>
<u n="94" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="95" who="S0238">and presumably not continuously but but every year they'd go and do a season erm so I presume that the grass that you're seeing there now has grown over since they excavated</u>
<u n="96" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0238">erm and it's a nice day out so</u>
<u n="98" who="S0242">and is the history a bit known? you know was it</u>
<u n="99" who="S0238">well</u>
<u n="100" who="S0242">was it the plague or or did</u>
<u n="101" who="S0238">no</u>
<u n="102" who="S0242">or was it just economic <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0238" trans="overlap">it was just it it yes er</u>
<u n="104" who="S0242" trans="overlap">was it a?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0238">enclosure the initially the the you know the it was taken over by a new landlord who <trunc>en</trunc>enclosed the land</u>
<u n="106" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0238">for erm sheep farming and and</u>
<u n="108" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="109" who="S0238">therefore they didn't need the tenant farmers so much</u>
<u n="110" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0238">and that sort of started the decline? and then just the long slow decline I think</u>
<u n="112" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm m</u>
<u n="113" who="S0238">and it wasn't a sort of <pause dur="short"/> but it was later than the plague</u>
<u n="114" who="S0242">mm mm okay</u>
<u n="115" who="S0238">erm but because it's a free site there isn't a <pause dur="short"/> little kiosk with a little man in it you know</u>
<u n="116" who="S0242">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0238">but when I went to er <anon type="place"/> Priory which is probably last year now <pause dur="short"/> which is the nearest manned site in their in their shop they had guidebooks to <anon type="place"/> and thought that would be a good idea because I've been before but I mean obviously yes there are notices up on the site but you get more information from the guidebooks that they do so I thought right okay I'll do that I'll go and erm I'll buy the guidebook now and at some point I'll go over there and and just hadn't got round to it and hadn't got round to it and it was a beautiful day so I did that and and it's actually really near the fruit farm so it just made sense to go there on the way back</u>
<u n="118" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="119" who="S0238">and oh yeah that was one I had this really weird experience with my car that I'd come through <anon type="place"/> it's that sort of area</u>
<u n="120" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0238">and <pause dur="short"/> there was a bit of a mess because there's a bridge <pause dur="short"/> that has got a traffic lights on it cos it's too narrow for two way traffic</u>
<u n="122" who="S0242">okay yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0238">and then just beyond that was some really serious roadworks with a one way traffic light and the traffic was coming through and blocking everything so that</u>
<u n="124" who="S0242">yep yep yep</u>
<u n="125" who="S0238">erm and I realised also when I finally got beyond the lorry that was in front of me and could see what was happening it was it wasn't a it wasn't a traffic light it was a convoy <pause dur="short"/> which is always slower so you're waiting for this thing to come and lead you through you know?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yep right yep yep yep</u>
<u n="127" who="S0238">erm but I was stuck behind something big that I and so I couldn't see past this you always are in those situations</u>
<u n="128" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah right</u>
<u n="129" who="S0238">and we were sitting for ages so I switched my engine off <pause dur="short"/> finally we started moving I switched my engine on and started moving and there's this horrendous noise as of <pause dur="short"/> engine knocking</u>
<u n="130" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0238">you know and I thought something was gonna fall you know I thought the engine was gonna fall on the floor through through the it was just awful <pause dur="short"/> I only had to go a couple of hundred yards before the end of the roadworks was actually the entrance into the fruit farm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="133" who="S0238">so I went in there and parked when I set off again nothing at all and the only thing I can think of is I had my windows open cos it was hot but actually it wasn't my engine at all it was somebody else's I was hearing</u>
<u n="134" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0238">but it was so alarming</u>
<u n="136" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe it was?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0238">and I'm driving on thinking well I can't break down here because I'm in the middle of all this one way whatsit and</u>
<u n="138" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0238">it would hold everybody up for hours <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0242">yeah right</u>
<u n="141" who="S0238"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but er <trunc>d</trunc>do you want your coffee with your breakfast? shall shall I make the coffee now or do you want it?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yep yeah that'd be fine <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0238">and are you a milk in coffee person?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0242">no</u>
<u n="145" who="S0238">no so you're like me black no sugar</u>
<u n="146" who="S0242">absolutely</u>
<u n="147" who="S0238">right jolly good I'll clear that</u>
<u n="148" who="S0242">oh okay <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0238">well they suggested doing it while you're cooking or something cos it gives you something to do which is all very well but you do move around and you do bang things on the table when you <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0242">so what what bread is this?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0238">er that is wheat <unclear/> and rye that's not one I've made that's Morrison's</u>
<u n="152" who="S0242">oh I see</u>
<u n="153" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm waiting until I get this stuff <pause dur="short"/> before I do any <pause dur="short"/> more bread making which as I said should be arriving soon so <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> you've got a homemade raspberry from the place I stayed last week</u>
<u n="154" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="155" who="S0238">and unhomemade blackcurrant and honey and that is quince jelly that my mum gave me that somebody that she knows makes if you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0242">what <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="157" who="S0238">oh and the other <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="158" who="S0242">which is quince jelly? this</u>
<u n="159" who="S0238">that one that's says quince jelly on the side</u>
<u n="160" who="S0242" trans="overlap">that one oh sorry</u>
<u n="161" who="S0238">and that is my marmalade</u>
<u n="162" who="S0242">oh <unclear/> rye</u>
<u n="163" who="S0238">which I can recommend</u>
<u n="164" who="S0242">I'm sure you can <pause dur="long"/> I will take these straight off to the table</u>
<u n="165" who="S0238">right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0242">ah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0238">yes I stopped bothering to make raspberry jam because it's very easy</u>
<u n="168" who="S0242">yep</u>
<u n="169" who="S0238">erm but I was <pause dur="short"/> using raspberries from this fruit farm which were fairly pricey and though when I knew I was making jam I sort of they've got quite big <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>containe</trunc> punnets that you pack into and I found because it's quite a long way by the time I've driven home if you fill the punnets fairly full the thing that's in the bottom has already started to got</u>
<u n="170" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="171" who="S0238"><unclear/> it's really squashed you know?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0238">so that was actually quite good for making jam</u>
<u n="174" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right yes yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0238">and as I say</u>
<u n="176" who="S0242">pre squashed <unclear>drinks</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0238">pre squashed raspberries yes erm but <pause dur="short"/> although it's very straightforward actually you can buy perfectly nice raspberry jam whereas the marmalade</u>
<u n="178" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0238">you cannot buy even in a farm shop marmalade as nice as that I don't think</u>
<u n="180" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="181" who="S0238">I mean see what you think maybe you don't agree it depends what kind of marmalade you like but <pause dur="long"/> so even though marmalade is very faffy I make some every year</u>
<u n="182" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0242">mm that's nice marmalade</u>
<u n="185" who="S0238">mm that's just Delia</u>
<u n="186" who="S0242">mm yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> but I've never had the recipe not work erm <pause dur="short"/> and it's a bit you know you you're boiling it well no you're simmering it for two hours so that the er pulp softens and everything</u>
<u n="188" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0238">well that's a bit difficult to gauge because one person's simmer is another person's boil if you see what I mean</u>
<u n="190" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0238">for for when it's as long as two hours that could make quite a bit of difference</u>
<u n="192" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0238">to how much water has actually evaporated and therefore to the whole consistency so I would have thought it would vary enormously from year to year but actually doesn't that much</u>
<u n="194" who="S0242">it doesn't right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0238">there we go so now <pause dur="short"/> check that that is the right sort of strength for you</u>
<u n="196" who="S0242">okay</u>
<u n="197" who="S0238">cos I've done it at the right strength for me</u>
<u n="198" who="S0242">they are nice mugs aren't they?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0238">and yeah and if it isn't I'll put a little bit more water in</u>
<u n="200" who="S0242">mm that's fine</u>
<u n="201" who="S0238">that's fine? good you're about the only person I know who doesn't go yar when they drink my coffee <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0242">it's a good solid brew I mean definitely yes but that's fine with me</u>
<u n="203" who="S0238">mm <pause dur="long"/> and that is that quince thing is so weird because if you flip the top you realise <pause dur="short"/> it obviously was something holding cinnamon or something it's <trunc>ob</trunc> it's not meant for jam at all</u>
<u n="204" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="205" who="S0238"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's <trunc>mean</trunc>meant for slices</u>
<u n="206" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right yeah yeah it's a pepper pot or whatever isn't it?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0238" trans="overlap">and it's actually it's yes and it's too narrow to put a spoon into</u>
<u n="208" who="S0242">ah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0238">you can put a knife in but you couldn't put I erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> you could not fit a spoon in <vocal desc="laugh"/> very weird</u>
<u n="210" who="S0242">and did did you say your mother made this?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0238">no no</u>
<u n="212" who="S0242">no</u>
<u n="213" who="S0238">somebody that she knows made it and gave it to her</u>
<u n="214" who="S0242" trans="overlap">somebody she knows yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0238">I'm always getting she's well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gone now the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the woman who lived next door to her</u>
<u n="216" who="S0242">mm right</u>
<u n="217" who="S0238" trans="overlap">erm you know when we were kids the the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lived next door and he was <pause dur="short"/> something like Latvian and I'm not actually very sure</u>
<u n="218" who="S0242">ah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0238">and she was Italian</u>
<u n="220" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="221" who="S0238">so they both spoke fairly broken English <pause dur="short"/> erm I mean obviously they used English to communicate with each other and</u>
<u n="222" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0238">managed to have a perfectly good relationship for all those years but erm but she he died quite a long time ago and she'd been continually living next to <pause dur="short"/> my mum</u>
<u n="224" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0238">and she after what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s three years older than me and obviously she was born here cos they must have met here you know?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0238">so she must have been in this country for about fifty-seven years or something like that and she still sounds as if she just arrived off the boat from Naples</u>
<u n="228" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0238">I mean just so difficult to follow</u>
<u n="230" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0238">really really heavy accent really peculiar grammar and and erm even I found it difficult so and erm you know my mum would sort of sit there smiling and nodding sometimes <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know</u>
<u n="232" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0238">erm but er she grew oregano in her garden</u>
<u n="234" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0238">erm as possibly Italians will you know I don't know</u>
<u n="236" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0238">erm but obviously far more than she needed so she'd give my mother an enormous polythene bagful of oregano well <pause dur="short"/> however much you like herbs you don't really need huge great bags of them one normally buy them in little sachets from the <unclear>supermarket</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah right right</u>
<u n="239" who="S0238">so my mother passes things like that onto me and <pause dur="short"/> then as I say she's got these apple trees erm <pause dur="short"/> which are cooking apples <pause dur="short"/> so I get those</u>
<u n="240" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="241" who="S0238">erm and tomatoes which I don't mind at all</u>
<u n="242" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0238">which I have tried to grow but because I tend to go away in June</u>
<u n="244" who="S0242">yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0238" trans="overlap">that's then they <trunc>nee</trunc> I'm away when they need watering erm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="247" who="S0238">one year I took my tomato plants around and left them in my mother's greenhouse when I was away <vocal desc="laugh"/> but then in what sense are they my tomatoes? they're really hers</u>
<u n="248" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0238">erm so I've stopped bothering but again <pause dur="short"/> actually home grown tomatoes particularly if you do not put them in the fridge if she just when she brings <trunc>the</trunc> she'll give me a little handful and I'll try and keep most of them out on the work surface and and use them fairly quickly</u>
<u n="250" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0238">they just have so much more flavour than anything from the supermarket</u>
<u n="252" who="S0242">yes yeah very good <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0238">but that's why really why I guess why I want to get my orchard up and running</u>
<u n="254" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0238">because she's not gonna be around forever and I suspect you know she's got two blackcurrant bushes and I love blackcurrants and I've been going and harvesting from her</u>
<u n="256" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0238">previously er and I did a bit this year but of course I did have a few of my own next year I'm sure I'll have more but I suspect if one of hers dies or something she probably just won't bother to replace it</u>
<u n="258" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="259" who="S0238">erm and then of course we don't know how long she's gonna go on for</u>
<u n="260" who="S0242">no well well how old is she?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0238">eighty-three</u>
<u n="262" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0238">erm and I think her mother was something like eighty-seven <pause dur="short"/> erm and my grandma <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was ninety-two or ninety-three? that sort of age</u>
<u n="264" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="265" who="S0238">but she was in a home you know she could really couldn't manage on her own</u>
<u n="266" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0238">erm she had she had shingles and was taken into hospital and <pause dur="short"/> because of her age before they let her go back into her council house they sort of ran her through various tests in the hospital you know I think they put take them into a kitchen and see whether they can make themselves a cup of tea sort of thing</u>
<u n="268" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0238">and decided that she wasn't fit to live on her own and we were going oh my god because my mother's mother was really really adamant she was not going into anywhere and she had <pause dur="short"/> stroke after stroke at intervals you know and every time she she lost a little bit of mobility and</u>
<u n="270" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0238">and she was mentally she was absolutely fine but but <pause dur="short"/> she could just about move around her own house with a Zimmer frame and luckily it was a bungalow <pause dur="short"/> and she had meals on wheels</u>
<u n="272" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0238">for lunchtime five days a week</u>
<u n="274" who="S0242">right right</u>
<u n="275" who="S0238">er and a home help who came in I don't know how frequently? and a very nice next door neighbour who was just as old as she was but used to</u>
<u n="276" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0238">go and knock on her door every day <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>w</trunc> on at least one occasion he he basically saved her life because she what she didn't he realised that I don't know whether he'd actually knocked on the door but her bedroom curtains were still drawn and she was always up</u>
<u n="278" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0238">so he called an ambulance and she'd actually had a stroke while she was getting undressed the night before and spent the whole night sitting in a chair in her underwear unable to move</u>
<u n="280" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="281" who="S0238">and was sort of ended up being rushed to hospital wrapped in foil cos she had hypothermia</u>
<u n="282" who="S0242">yeah right right yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0238">a non central heated bungalow of course</u>
<u n="284" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0242">of course</u>
<u n="286" who="S0238">erm and that was weird as well because it was when I was at school <pause dur="short"/> and I used to be taken to school but a neighbour whose daughter went to the same school <pause dur="short"/> and I <pause dur="short"/> was standing by his car on his drive waiting for them to come out of the house</u>
<u n="287" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="288" who="S0238">cos they were faffing about and I heard an ambulance go by along the main road and you can be it's quite a long distance away but it comes up <pause dur="short"/> cos my parents house is higher than</u>
<u n="289" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0238">the <unclear/> road and I remember thinking I hope that's not my grandma</u>
<u n="291" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0238">and it probably had been cos she had been taken in at about that time</u>
<u n="293" who="S0242" trans="overlap">that time oh really? mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0238">but well she had her wish in the end <pause dur="short"/> she did die in her own home</u>
<u n="295" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0238">but you know if she'd lived in a country without all those social services she obviously wouldn't have been able to carry on</u>
<u n="297" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> but no my dad's mum <pause dur="short"/> we were as I say we were sort of going oh dear because we knew what my grandma <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> had been like and thinking <pause dur="short"/> she's not gonna like this</u>
<u n="299" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0238">erm so my dad and his sisters sussed out a few places and took her to look at them and she like oh yeah this is really nice and she</u>
<u n="301" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0238">settled in and she used to gossip about the <pause dur="short"/> erm what do I mean? I don't mean inmates I mean I actually</u>
<u n="303" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0238">and I don't even mean I don't mean the patients I mean the staff</u>
<u n="305" who="S0242">the staff right</u>
<u n="306" who="S0238" trans="overlap">you know and she found a a gentleman friend</u>
<u n="307" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0238">who used to have a very mild flirtation with over a cup of tea I that <vocal desc="laugh"/> was really was all that happened</u>
<u n="309" who="S0242" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="310" who="S0238">erm and was perfectly happy so people just are so different</u>
<u n="311" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0238">but I I know my mother wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> she's more docile than her mother but she wouldn't be happy</u>
<u n="313" who="S0242">no no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> one of the people I visited on this trip where I was <pause dur="short"/> er er da da da round <trunc>Eng</trunc> round Britain as it were</u>
<u n="314" who="S0238">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0242">was erm <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is <pause dur="short"/> ninety-four</u>
<u n="316" who="S0238">right</u>
<u n="317" who="S0242">and <pause dur="short"/> she's lived in the same house for about <pause dur="short"/> forty years or so but it is a bungalow</u>
<u n="318" who="S0238">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0242">and she can erm <pause dur="short"/> er she can just about look after herself <pause dur="short"/> she's she's bright as a button but her her legs weren't always doing</u>
<u n="320" who="S0238" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0242">what she wants them to but she <pause dur="short"/> she's got a <pause dur="short"/> a a sort of trolley on wheels</u>
<u n="322" who="S0238">yes</u>
<u n="323" who="S0242">things and she <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> makes a point of going down to round to a village shop at least once a week</u>
<u n="324" who="S0238">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0242">which is a big well it's only I could sort of walk it in well <pause dur="short"/> five minutes probably but</u>
<u n="326" who="S0238" trans="overlap">mm but it's a big trip for her <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0242">but for her like that's that's a big trip what I really like about her is that she is determined she is gonna do it and I mean she's not bloody minded when it's been snowing or something</u>
<u n="328" who="S0238">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0242">she she says <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I won't go today but but she is determined that she is gonna keep on going and she's got lots of friends who say oh you know we'll run you down there in the car</u>
<u n="330" who="S0238" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0242">or we can get things for you no no no</u>
<u n="332" who="S0238" trans="overlap">no oh it's much I if you don't keep doing it <pause dur="short"/> you see I I think my mother is has been saying lately erm <pause dur="short"/> things that she's finding it she's actually finding that her legs aren't very happy just going from the car to the supermarket and I think it's cos she doesn't do enough walking</u>
<u n="333" who="S0242">yep</u>
<u n="334" who="S0238">whereas my auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> which was my dad's sister is much more like your <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0238">she's older than my mum and she had she definitely wouldn't go out in snow because she had a bad fall a few years ago <pause dur="short"/> just going she lives in sheltered housing</u>
<u n="337" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0238">and she was just going from the community centre to back to her little bungalow</u>
<u n="339" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh right yeah?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0238">erm and went down and broke her wrist and her ankle and it was her right wrist and she's right handed and</u>
<u n="341" who="S0242" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0238">and was in and it has got and when I say broke I mean smithereen kind of broke they had to really pin the ankle <unclear>up</unclear> and so on</u>
<u n="343" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah right</u>
<u n="344" who="S0238">erm and therefore she still although she can now use her hand things like cutting up steak are a little bit tricky</u>
<u n="345" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0238">she hasn't got the full strength back in it and so</u>
<u n="347" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="348" who="S0238">erm but she's got one of those like a Zimmer but on wheels</u>
<u n="349" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0238">so she can yeah I think it what you were talking about and she insists on going into into Skipton from where she lives which is <pause dur="short"/> she used to walk it <pause dur="short"/> quite comfortably and I think she's still doing it with this trolley</u>
<u n="351" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0238">and then getting the bus back cos it's up it's slightly uphill from the <unclear/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0242" trans="overlap">okay right fair enough yeah good compromise</u>
<u n="354" who="S0238" trans="overlap">but again the bus that they had which was one with the that was designed for old people</u>
<u n="355" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0238">and had a really good driver who you know they bloody cancelled</u>
<u n="357" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0238">so now the bus is coming round at a less convenient time for shopping and it's it doesn't have the the step at the right height</u>
<u n="359" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="360" who="S0238">so luckily there's a really nice driver who gets off</u>
<u n="361" who="S0242">who jumps out</u>
<u n="362" who="S0238">and helps her on with her <unclear>trolley</unclear></u>
<u n="363" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0238">but otherwise she wouldn't be able to get into the er shop how's and it's</u>
<u n="365" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0238">that that bus was full of old people a lot of people just stopped going into town because they can't</u>
<u n="367" who="S0242">yes yeah yeah yeah that that's that's <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="368" who="S0238">but she's got a tame taxi driver</u>
<u n="369" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="370" who="S0238">er whenever she's going a little bit further afield she just rings him up and says right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0238">erm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0238">you know and and she's got various allowances and so on because she and and I don't think she's got a lot in the way of savings or anything they ran a shop you know I wouldn't have thought they managed to put a lot away erm and she just thinks it makes sense to use that money on things like like paying for a taxi from time to time to make her life a bit more interesting</u>
<u n="375" who="S0242">absolutely absolutely</u>
<u n="376" who="S0238">and I just contrast that with my mum who just who just <vocal desc="sigh"/> er has let her life get narrower and narrower and I know it kind of had to happen when my dad was ill <pause dur="short"/> cos she couldn't leave him</u>
<u n="377" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0238">and even when she could leave him she felt guilty about doing so you know and er but <pause dur="short"/> most <pause dur="short"/> of the widows that I know <pause dur="short"/> sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0238">have sort of blossomed after their husbands died</u>
<u n="381" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0238">and my mother was the opposite</u>
<u n="383" who="S0242">right right mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0238">I mean even someone like someone called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that she worked with that they sort of shared a class as it were that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did three days a week and my mum did two and a half and they so they overlapped by half a day <pause dur="short"/> for quite a few years and and her husband I think it was a heart attack but he died <pause dur="short"/> really young you you know?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0238">forties perhaps <trunc>cer</trunc></u>
<u n="387" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0238">certainly not more than fifties so a long time ago she's now found somebody else I mean she's spent a long time mourning</u>
<u n="389" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0238">you know and I think being quite lonely</u>
<u n="391" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0238">er but er <pause dur="short"/> she's now with somebody else so</u>
<u n="393" who="S0242">ah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0238">which is really nice</u>
<u n="395" who="S0242">right great</u>
<u n="396" who="S0238">not that I would have expected my mother to go and find somebody else but it would have been nice if she'd taken advantage of things like the theatre</u>
<u n="397" who="S0242">yes</u>
<u n="398" who="S0238">has a whole lot of women of a certain age involved</u>
<u n="399" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0238">some of them are widows some of them are not but they just they like doing things</u>
<u n="401" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="402" who="S0238">without their husbands from time to <trunc>ti</trunc></u>
<u n="403" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="404" who="S0238">and so there is a kind of little social group there that she could do things with and they kept inviting her and and she just oh no I don't feel like it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh I don't yeah yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0238">erm and and now it's oh well I don't think I can leave <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well you know yes you can</u>
<u n="407" who="S0242">yes you can yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0238">but there are times when she'll only come out for coffee not lunch because she doesn't want to leave him <event desc="sound of doorbell"/> well I'm sorry that's my doorbell could be a parcel <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="409" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hi</u>
<u n="410" who="S0238">hello hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thank you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you go thanks very much <unclear>goodbye</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0238">yes</u>
<u n="413" who="S0242">is this flour?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0238">sorry?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0242">is this flour?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0238">no no no it's a it's a I've got I've ordered two different things online from Amazon</u>
<u n="417" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="418" who="S0238">and both of them are potentially small enough to go through the letterbox but it depends how they're packed and I didn't know how they were gonna be packed <pause dur="short"/> erm one is this erm <unclear>zantham</unclear> gum that I need for for the gluten free</u>
<u n="419" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="420" who="S0238">erm so <pause dur="short"/> I I don't know if you'd seen I left a little note on the door saying erm if I'm not in and it won't go through the letterbox can you leave it in the storage bin round behind the dustbins</u>
<u n="421" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="422" who="S0238">cos it's totally out of sight there</u>
<u n="423" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="424" who="S0238">it's waterproof</u>
<u n="425" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="426" who="S0238">and I don't want to have to go right into <pause dur="short"/> there used to be a parcels office in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0242">ah but now</u>
<u n="428" who="S0238">and now there isn't</u>
<u n="429" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="430" who="S0238">erm and it's just such a nuisance and it's a good job that I did that I was in actually because it wouldn't it should have been able to go through the letterbox but they'd packed it square rather than flat if you see what I mean</u>
<u n="431" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0238">so it would you know Barclaycard why do we get? <pause dur="short"/> look at that weight of paper</u>
<u n="433" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0238">what a waste and that ditto but at least that is I mean why Barclaycard think I want a Barclaycard I've no idea I've never you know it's not my bank</u>
<u n="435" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0238">erm at least this is from a company that I have ordered things from but it's the second thing I've had from them in a week</u>
<u n="437" who="S0242">yeah yes</u>
<u n="438" who="S0238">erm and every time I it's the plant company so it's like I ordered a lot of those plants from them erm but every time you do an order with them you get a free gift that you don't want erm <pause dur="short"/> last time it was er it's down it's by the shoe cupboard in the hall a little backpack well I've got a backpack and if I want another one I want one that has all those compartments like</u>
<u n="439" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0238" trans="overlap">the current one because I take it to work and I need to be able to put different things in different places and and it's actually quite difficult to find one with all those compartments</u>
<u n="441" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah uhu</u>
<u n="442" who="S0238">so I'm not just going to accept any random backpack that's just got one compartment</u>
<u n="443" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="444" who="S0238">it's of no use whatsoever</u>
<u n="445" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right right</u>
<u n="446" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0238">I think having said that my kitchen scissors were from them</u>
<u n="448" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="449" who="S0238">one time I some kitchen scissors and a set of knives</u>
<u n="450" who="S0242">ah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0238">er which <event desc="sound of phone"/> <pause dur="short"/> is that my phone?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0242">was a peep</u>
<u n="453" who="S0238">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh the answerphone'll pick up <pause dur="short"/> that is the loudest I can put it on and it's really not</u>
<u n="454" who="S0242">no</u>
<u n="455" who="S0238">very loud I don't think</u>
<u n="456" who="S0242">no</u>
<u n="457" who="S0238">erm I mean <pause dur="short"/> this</u>
<u n="458" who="S0242" trans="overlap">that was that was it ringing?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0238">and it's only there</u>
<u n="460" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0238">yes</u>
<u n="462" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="463" who="S0238">erm and with with this new phone there's a base unit and a handset so I can and I do I mean <unclear/> it's not very useful in there because we're not in there at the moment but <unclear>obviously</unclear> I did that yesterday <trunc>inc</trunc> when I was in there before you arrived</u>
<u n="464" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0238">thinking if your were <trunc>c</trunc> held up you would ring and I would need to be able to hear it</u>
<u n="466" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="467" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> but there's no way before that it or if I just if I if I leave the handset with the base unit they're in the office <pause dur="short"/> I can probably hear it in the living room with the door shut but I don't think I would hear it in any other room of the house</u>
<u n="468" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0238">erm I mean obviously that's why you have a detachable handset so you can put it in whatever room you're in but then you've got to remember to do it</u>
<u n="470" who="S0242">yes</u>
<u n="471" who="S0238">erm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0238">that's not <pause dur="short"/> and I find with that that sometimes it's a bit like a mobile phone that sometimes there's a bit of a sort of echo on it it's not as</u>
<u n="474" who="S0242">oh</u>
<u n="475" who="S0238">as brilliant as</u>
<u n="476" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="477" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's not as good as the old phone except that the old phone didn't detach you know cos it was a</u>
<u n="478" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0238">erm I can't remember what actually went wrong with the old phone something did <pause dur="long"/> plus I mean in a way I wasn't too bothered about having a to replace it because it was actually a fax <pause dur="short"/> machine</u>
<u n="480" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="481" who="S0238">I bought it when I first came back to this country cos I'd had a fax machine in Japan which was really quite good for keeping in touch with mum</u>
<u n="482" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0238">cos they had one at that point</u>
<u n="484" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="485" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> and then I got that job er with the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> where I was actually involved with it all year round but that it was only running in the summer so I needed to be able to communicate and this must just it must just have been <pause dur="short"/> before everybody was doing emails so I mean obviously emails existed</u>
<u n="486" who="S0242">yes</u>
<u n="487" who="S0238">but it wasn't as widespread</u>
<u n="488" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="489" who="S0238">and a lot of offices were still using faxes</u>
<u n="490" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0238">and they actually offered to buy me a fax machine erm and <pause dur="short"/> I don't <trunc>th</trunc> I don't think they did I mean I think I paid for it in fact cos I it was it was my main phone</u>
<u n="492" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0238">you know <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but obviously that meant it took up quite a bit of space on the desk and periodically I would still get unsolicited faxes from people who offering to collect my debts for me and things like that because they assume anyone with a fax machine is a business</u>
<u n="494" who="S0242">a business yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0238"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm and at the other house <pause dur="short"/> because the <trunc>per</trunc> people that I bought the house from had been running a business he built kitchens</u>
<u n="496" who="S0242">okay</u>
<u n="497" who="S0238">and <pause dur="short"/> that number was the company number they had a different line for personal things</u>
<u n="498" who="S0242">ah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0238">I when I first moved in and I just had a phone with no answerphone and no nothing I was getting faxes coming through in the middle of the night you know which obviously couldn't come through</u>
<u n="500" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0238">but you've picked the phone the phone would ring and I have no means of switching of doing anything with it because it I didn't have an answerphone yet</u>
<u n="502" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0238">and I pick it up and all I was getting was this bloody beeping noise</u>
<u n="504" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0238">and I ended up having to unplug the phone every night and it was so annoying</u>
<u n="506" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0238">erm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0242">yes yes</u>
<u n="509" who="S0238">so it was actually quite useful to to get a fax machine so it could actually cope with the faxes that were still coming for somebody else <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0238">but er I don't I think that's kind of tailed off now <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0242">and have you had any contact with the old house? with people in <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0238" trans="overlap">no not at all no er I left the new address <pause dur="short"/> erm and but I but with a note well I mean I sort of left a <pause dur="short"/> something telling them a few things about how to use things in the house</u>
<u n="514" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0238">because I wasn't doing a I wasn't there when they moved in</u>
<u n="516" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0238">erm they were just getting the key from the agent and I was at work so we weren't actually talking and I've never actually met them because the agent showed them round the house</u>
<u n="518" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you've never met them?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0238"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="520" who="S0242">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> no they they cos the agent that I moved to they did viewings themselves on Tuesdays Thursdays and Saturdays or something like that and so the only I showed a couple of people round who could only do Sunday</u>
<u n="522" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0238">but anybody who could do those days the agents did it was much I it was so much less stress with the second agent</u>
<u n="524" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0238">erm and that's partly why you know that I just</u>
<u n="526" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0238">so they didn't even tell me that someone had been viewing until <pause dur="short"/> afterwards erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I'd never met these people</u>
<u n="528" who="S0242">oh</u>
<u n="529" who="S0238">erm so as I said I left them a sort of a piece of paper that was saying this key's for that one this key's for that one</u>
<u n="530" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0238">and erm you know you need to do X Y and Z with a thermostat that sort of you know little things like that</u>
<u n="532" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="533" who="S0238">that I would have said if we'd have been able to do a handover <pause dur="short"/> left my address but said as far as I know I've given the new address to everybody who needs it so any mail that comes for me is probably junk</u>
<u n="534" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0238">but use your judgement about that <pause dur="short"/> nothing has been forwarded at all so</u>
<u n="536" who="S0242" trans="overlap">nothing mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0238">I didn't bother to ask the post office to forward stuff because most of the mail I get is junk</u>
<u n="538" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0238">erm and what's the point?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0238">in forwarding that?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0238">as I say I thought I told everyone as it turned out I'd forgotten the doctor</u>
<u n="544" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="545" who="S0238">as I realised when I went to the doctor's</u>
<u n="546" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0238">but I have I mean banks and and utility bills</u>
<u n="548" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0238">and all of those well I don't get those in the post anyway but erm I I had told everybody so <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but I used to even after ten years very very occasionally I would get mailing for the people who lived in my old house it is ridiculous that people don't just get things off their databases</u>
<u n="550" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> you know things that were obviously junk <pause dur="short"/> and you just think this is mad</u>
<u n="552" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0238">but I think I think it's wasteful enough to send stuff like this out in the first place but</u>
<u n="554" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0238">erm to keep on sending it after ten years <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="557" who="S0238">without just checking that people are still there <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> er I mean the house could have been pulled down in that time couldn't it? anything could happen</u>
<u n="558" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sure yeah indeed <pause dur="short"/> indeed</u>
<u n="559" who="S0238" trans="overlap">yeah so my my spy <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> who lives in the house behind</u>
<u n="560" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh right right</u>
<u n="561" who="S0238"><unclear>my old</unclear> house you know tells me that they've <pause dur="short"/> changed the kitchen you know the the you remember my kitchen had that bar down</u>
<u n="562" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0238">that counter in the middle</u>
<u n="564" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0238">that they've pulled that up and and made it all into one big room</u>
<u n="566" who="S0242">okay</u>
<u n="567" who="S0238">well I can understand that actually because I loved that whole layout and everything and it was great if you were cooking</u>
<u n="568" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0238">people could be sitting at the table and you could be sitting at the table and you could put the food on the counter</u>
<u n="570" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yep yep yep yep</u>
<u n="571" who="S0238">and everything but the dining area was a bit small</u>
<u n="572" who="S0242">yeah a bit yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0238">erm so that's fine if you had two people there and you can manage with four but but the person who went round the far side couldn't get up and go to the loo in the middle of a meal very easily</u>
<u n="574" who="S0242" trans="overlap">mm well okay yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0238">erm but if you had any more people than that there it wouldn't have been possible</u>
<u n="576" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> and you know this is a young couple who possibly are entertaining and I've no idea what their families are like and so on so</u>
<u n="578" who="S0242" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="579" who="S0238">I can understand why they would decide to do that</u>
<u n="580" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0238">erm but I think she's been a from her kitchen she can see into their kitchen which is a bit naughty really she shouldn't be doing that but</u>
<u n="582" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0238">erm she's seen workmen coming and going and sort of <pause dur="short"/> what's gone on and I gather they want to turn the garden into a more of a vegetable garden</u>
<u n="584" who="S0242">oh <pause dur="short"/> well fair enough</u>
<u n="585" who="S0238">yeah I think it's a I kept that square of lawn because I think it's quite nice to have a bit of lawn</u>
<u n="586" who="S0242">oh I would agree I I think a bit of lawn <trunc>i</trunc>is a good idea but I <pause dur="short"/> if they're really into growing as much of their own as they can then</u>
<u n="587" who="S0238">well I presume that's one reason why they bought the house a lot of houses have have houses at that sort of price probably didn't have much in the way of garden</u>
<u n="588" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="589" who="S0238">and there was enough there to do something with it it's one of the reasons I bought it</u>
<u n="590" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0238">erm but when I moved in there were three lawns that the front bit where the roses are</u>
<u n="592" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0238">was a lawn and I dug that up</u>
<u n="594" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="595" who="S0238">and the side bed was a lawn</u>
<u n="596" who="S0242">oh okay</u>
<u n="597" who="S0238">and <pause dur="short"/> that was a real really difficult to to mow because it was slightly below the level of the concrete path and so when you got to the edge <pause dur="short"/> you you couldn't really do the edge of the lawn like you know</u>
<u n="598" who="S0242" trans="overlap">understood <pause dur="short"/> understood yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0238">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't see any point in having just lawn there because you weren't ever <trunc>go</trunc>going to sit on it or anything</u>
<u n="600" who="S0242">no</u>
<u n="601" who="S0238">it was in shade all day</u>
<u n="602" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0238">so I just er dug that up as well and and found some shade loving bushes which were relatively little trouble <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0238">but er no I wouldn't have wanted to have none</u>
<u n="606" who="S0242">no no I well as I say I I agree with you but I can see if they really wanted to maximise for growing your own then fair enough</u>
<u n="607" who="S0238" trans="overlap">mm yeah yes cos you couldn't really do that in the front cos with those terrace well I suppose you could if you had it reterraced some a bit more manageably</u>
<u n="608" who="S0242">you probably could but yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0238">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0242">tricky</u>
<u n="611" who="S0238">but so it'll be interesting to see how they're getting on with the people who moved into not the other half of my house but next door and over the fence</u>
<u n="612" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="613" who="S0238">were a young couple who'd only been in about a year and they'd done a lot</u>
<u n="614" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="615" who="S0238">to the house really a lot you know I mean erm not just new kitchen all new windows and doors and then then they were doing all sorts of things with the garden because <pause dur="short"/> where my front garden was terraced that one was just a slope</u>
<u n="616" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0238">which was quite dodgy to work on I would have thought</u>
<u n="618" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0238">I don't know why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had left it like that because she was <trunc>qu</trunc> was well into her sixties by the time she moved she came to this area and she was up here for <pause dur="short"/> five or six years I would say before she died</u>
<u n="620" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0238">which is just before I moved here you know</u>
<u n="622" who="S0242">mm yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0238">erm and she was pottering about weeding she really kept up with the garden god did she keep up with the garden</u>
<u n="624" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0238">she was never out of it you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="627" who="S0238">erm and I would just have thought it was she she would have felt unsafe on a slope like that</u>
<u n="628" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0238">but obviously not erm but they'd actually had it terraced</u>
<u n="630" who="S0242">they have okay</u>
<u n="631" who="S0238">well had it done it with help because they were young and fit you know?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0242">mm mm mm hm <pause dur="short"/> and the dog is still next is it as far as you know?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0238" trans="overlap">I <trunc>th</trunc> no I don't well their house had finally sold it was also for sale</u>
<u n="634" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh it had? <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0238">it had been for sale longer than mine</u>
<u n="636" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0238">erm so whether they'd moved out or not I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> now you'd have thought I'd have that conversation with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the last time I saw her but that is a while ago I need to call on her again</u>
<u n="638" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm get the latest gossip</u>
<u n="639" who="S0238">well partly <pause dur="short"/> she was one of those people we'd chat over the wall and sometimes it would go on a bit long and you'd think I want to go back in the house now</u>
<u n="640" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0238">but she was very kind and she was a good neighbour to have</u>
<u n="642" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="643" who="S0238">she watched out</u>
<u n="644" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="645" who="S0238">you know and if she'd seen something going on that shouldn't be going on she'd have called the police you know?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0238">erm and indeed the guy in the other half of her <trunc>hou</trunc> what is a couple I didn't I knew the bloke better</u>
<u n="648" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="649" who="S0238">and sort of one time when I was cutting my apple tree down I was making a bit of a meal of it cos I had rather an old saw and he called over do you want me to come and do it for you? and I said no <trunc>thank</trunc> well do you want me to lend you a saw? <vocal desc="laugh"/> yes I well I wouldn't mind that actually</u>
<u n="650" who="S0242" trans="overlap">well <vocal desc="laugh"/> yes you're right</u>
<u n="651" who="S0238">this one's a bit ancient</u>
<u n="652" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0238">erm which he did <vocal desc="laugh"/> er and things like that you know</u>
<u n="654" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0238">and and and he there was one day when I'd been you know I was going back to check the house <pause dur="short"/> I'd been in and I must have opened a window and and left it open and</u>
<u n="656" who="S0242">uhu</u>
<u n="657" who="S0238">then we're off of course for a few days and and he'd rung the estate agent to tell them that there was a window open</u>
<u n="658" who="S0242">oh right good</u>
<u n="659" who="S0238">erm so you know they were really</u>
<u n="660" who="S0242">that's nice</u>
<u n="661" who="S0238">they were good people</u>
<u n="662" who="S0242">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0238">erm but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s husband died of Parkinson's <pause dur="short"/> oh three or four years ago now</u>
<u n="664" who="S0242">mm mm</u>
<u n="665" who="S0238">erm and they'd been married for fifty-seven years</u>
<u n="666" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0238">er and don't have kids so</u>
<u n="668" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0238">you know I think she's a little bit lonely</u>
<u n="670" who="S0242">yes yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0238">so I do feel I should keep in touch and I've I've called round a couple of times and I brought her up here to see the house</u>
<u n="672" who="S0242">oh that's nice yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0238">er you know obviously she didn't have transport so I went and fetched her</u>
<u n="674" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0238">but that's quite a while ago now and you know it's it's just time just goes</u>
<u n="676" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0238">and and probably for her it's not just going you know she I I doubt if she has enough to do</u>
<u n="678" who="S0242">dragging around the yes</u>
<u n="679" who="S0238" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> trying to don't know I see my my auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not like that at all she's got a million things that she does and you ring her up and say how are you fixed next week? can I come over for lunch one day? and it's well I'm doing so I've got Monday club on Monday and I'm doing so and so on Tuesday and I might just be able to squeeze you in on Thursday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0238">and actually last time I was supposed to go over <pause dur="short"/> ah it was bank holiday Monday so it's not actually that long ago</u>
<u n="681" who="S0242">right</u>
<u n="682" who="S0238">I'd rung her up the week before and said I suddenly realised that it was a bank holiday Monday I'd completely forgotten about it <pause dur="short"/> do you happen to be free? well if we did something in the morning yes cos it's <trunc>some</trunc> she does something on a Monday afternoon right so I was gonna go out for coffee and then she rang me up on the Sunday to say could we make it lunch rather than coffee because she was taking some antibiotics that have to be taken an hour before a meal and <pause dur="short"/> it just fitted in better with the way she did things</u>
<u n="683" who="S0242">right okay okay</u>
<u n="684" who="S0238">which <pause dur="short"/> I said yes and then after I'd come off the phone I thought oh because that means it's the whole day rather than the morning</u>
<u n="685" who="S0242">mm</u>
<u n="686" who="S0238">kind of thing if you go in as far as <anon type="place"/> from here and she was wanting to have lunch at twelve o'clock which is way early for me <pause dur="short"/> and in any case I'm just having so many problems eating that I really didn't put particularly want to do it</u>
<u n="687" who="S0242"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0238">er the coffee had been much a better suggestion and in the end I rang her up on the Monday morning to say look <pause dur="short"/> I've had a bad night with my indigestion which I had erm and I just think it's not a good idea sorry and she said right well I've ordered a taxi I'm going to go anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's my auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for you I I <unclear/> for my lunch on my own because</u>
<u n="689" who="S0242" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> nice to hell with it yes</u>
<u n="690" who="S0238">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm so you and so I don't feel even though I don't see her that often and and well I mean she's got two sons anyway you know</u>
<u n="691" who="S0242">yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0238">erm but I don't feel guilty about that I go and see her because I like to talk to her</u>
<u n="693" who="S0242" trans="overlap">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="694" who="S0238">she's you know <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but er <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="695" who="S0242">so</u>
<u n="696" who="S0238">have you finished? or have you</u>
<u n="697" who="S0242">I have definitely</u>
<u n="698" who="S0238">you don't want another thing of coffee or anything?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0242">no I'm fine I don't <trunc>th</trunc> nothing more</u>
<u n="700" who="S0238">oh right erm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0242">so the jobs I know about are <pause dur="short"/> tall man in bathroom</u>
<u n="702" who="S0238"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0242">er <pause dur="short"/> the <unclear>hut</unclear> floor and the strimmer</u>
<u n="704" who="S0238">yes</u>
<u n="705" who="S0242">and the compost area</u>
<u n="706" who="S0238">yes I think that's probably enough don't you? erm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0242">a good opening bid as you may say</u>
<u n="708" who="S0238" trans="overlap">mm yes <pause dur="short"/> something else that I'd forgotten about until we were sitting in there last night</u>
<u n="709" who="S0242" trans="overlap">oh sorry and possibly go and buy or carrying some</u>
<u n="710" who="S0238" trans="overlap">well yes but that's kind of to do with the compost isn't it?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0242" trans="overlap">some concrete yep yep</u>
<u n="712" who="S0238">erm is I know this sounds really the the living room window sill has got a sort of nasty plastic veneer on it <pause dur="short"/> which I think looks horrible and I'm assuming that you can't because it's shiny that you can't just paint it white because it wouldn't take the paint</u>
<u n="713" who="S0242">okay</u>
<u n="714" who="S0238">so I started removing it and I got part of it off and then the rest of it is so bloody well glued that I can't get it off so I could actually do with some help with that but that's not exactly it's been sitting like that for a year literally so <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not <unclear>urgent</unclear> erm so if we've got time we can</u>
<u n="715" who="S0242">we can certainly <unclear/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0238">that was on my list but</u>
<u n="717" who="S0242">put that on the erm <pause dur="short"/> er provisional list</u>
<u n="718" who="S0238" trans="overlap">so erm so I think it would make sense to look at that er bathroom thing first</u>
<u n="719" who="S0242">I would say</u>
<u n="720" who="S0238">and then</u>
<u n="721" who="S0242">one two three four</u>
<u n="722" who="S0238">yes I would say that</u>
<u n="723" who="S0242">okay</u>
<u n="724" who="S0238">erm so</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
