<text id="SDJ9">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:58:03</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-12-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0015 S0281</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Recent news, personal situation</topics>
		<activity>Chatting with sister</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0015">
				<exactage>68</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Scotland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Brighton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>67 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">so tell me what happened with your er your car?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0015">well I I left erm the supermarket and went to try and get some bits that I'd er couldn't couldn't buy at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0015">chestnuts and things so I drove down to a little supermarket down in</u>
<u n="5" who="S0281" trans="overlap">can I make some tea?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0015">mm in the old village</u>
<u n="7" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0015">and <vocal desc="laugh"/> I parked the car and I saw an old student of mine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who well she's just an amazing girl anyway she runs erm <anon type="place"/> and she's in a big choir and she's been running it for about ten years and I I was first to go just before Christmas and take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to see it anyway <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was ill but she was telling me about it but she's now been invited to er or asked to to take her gospel choir to <anon type="place"/> for a big charity show and she was really excited about it someone very famous has asked her but yeah so she was telling me all about that we sat in my car <vocal desc="laugh"/> and and I obviously run the battery down somehow and of course when we left I went and got my shopping came back and my car wouldn't start</u>
<u n="9" who="S0281">oh has that happened before?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0015">and it has happened once before yeah but it was when the battery needed replacing anyway I</u>
<u n="11" who="S0281">maybe it well when was the last time you had it replaced?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0015">about a year ago so it's not not old no no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh it shouldn't shouldn't really</u>
<u n="14" who="S0015">anyway erm I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and left a desperate message I don't know if you're there but on the answerphone you know? left a desperate message saying oh you know my car's not starting anyway I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he came over bless his little heart in his car</u>
<u n="15" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0015">and tried it and he didn't have any luck and then I happened to see a garage the door slightly open and they're <trunc>cl</trunc> they're closed for until January but anyway I went running over and he came over and jump started it for me they got the car going drove home parked outside and then got well got my bag and we went off to <anon type="place"/> because that's where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works so he was able to in <anon type="place"/> he was able to put the machine on and check that it was the alternator battery erm and something else but anyway he said the battery was good so it had just run down low and erm wouldn't start</u>
<u n="17" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but have you used it the last few days?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0015">I have yeah I use it all the time but it had drained it obviously it was only a small battery I presume a small car but anyway yeah <trunc>f</trunc> but so we went hurtling down there with his his erm pass and he went in and got the machine and put it on and sorted it out for me and do you want to put some more water in that?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0281">no I'm alright</u>
<u n="20" who="S0015">are you sure?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0281">yeah sure</u>
<u n="22" who="S0015">a bit short yeah so I I got that going he got it going for me and erm I you know drove around a bit and came back by which time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was home</u>
<u n="23" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0015">and erm I said to him well this is where cos I then I thought if he hears that answerphone message come back and hears it he'll go and look for me down in <anon type="place"/> old village which is where I where I was initially but no fortunately he had only just come in <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he said well you don't need me then and I said no it's alright <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come to my rescue bless his heart and he was really good he went in got his machine out and just dislodged the battery and er and checked it all and put the machine on and that's it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0015">yeah so I got it going and I just said to him you've just saved me sixty pounds cos if it had been us we'd have gone to get a new battery</u>
<u n="27" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0015">and put it straight in but because he'd checked it and said the battery's good just run down but you know what? I had my phone charger plugged in not charging my phone but whether that sort of takes the battery? hi are you off darling?</u>
<u n="29" who="UNKMALE">yes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0015">I'm just telling <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about how wonderful you were and how you helped me out oh look oh is that for me?</u>
<u n="31" who="UNKMALE">well use them</u>
<u n="32" who="S0015">they're clean oh I'm allowed to use them but I can't keep them cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works at <anon type="place"/> he's got some windscreen cleaners because my windscreen is smeary isn't it?</u>
<u n="33" who="UNKMALE">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0015">he said to me he said you're so fussy in the house why don't you clean your car? he cleans his car all the time don't you?</u>
<u n="35" who="UNKMALE">when it needs it</u>
<u n="36" who="S0015">well no no even when it doesn't need it you clean it</u>
<u n="37" who="UNKMALE"><unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0015">yeah you do he's just off to work now</u>
<u n="39" who="UNKMALE">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0015">nearly ready freezing he is gonna be down there cos they're outside all the time</u>
<u n="41" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0015">fitting</u>
<u n="43" who="S0281">yeah it was zero last night wasn't it?</u>
<u n="44" who="UNKMALE">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0281">minus seven in some parts of the country</u>
<u n="46" who="S0015">in Scotland it was certainly in</u>
<u n="47" who="S0281"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0015">yeah in er <anon type="place"/> where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0281">yeah I do</u>
<u n="50" who="S0015">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still lives there in <anon type="place"/> and it's always the coldest spot in the country I think they're really really cold all the time there even on a good day it's cold but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> reckons that it's about ten degrees nearly always throughout the year ten degrees colder there than it is here</u>
<u n="51" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0015">yeah cos he watches the temperatures</u>
<u n="53" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0015">in <anon type="place"/> to see what we're basking in while he's free of him but no it's always quite cold up there in comparison several degrees difference at least but they erm get by he erm I don't know how they survive one winter a couple of winters ago he he's got quite a big driveway <unclear/></u>
<u n="55" who="UNKMALE">hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0281">hi</u>
<u n="57" who="UNKMALE">watch out for ice gathering on your car when erm</u>
<u n="58" who="UNKMALE">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="UNKMALE">I think it's alright</u>
<u n="60" who="UNKMALE">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="UNKMALE">get some petrol as well</u>
<u n="62" who="UNKMALE">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0281">so er yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0015">but he was out there trying to clear the snow from his parking area and erm he's got a snow clearing machine anyway he lost control of it and it turn it flew off and hit him and broke his ribs broke some ribs on this</u>
<u n="65" who="UNKMALE">I'll see you later on</u>
<u n="66" who="S0015">bye darling</u>
<u n="67" who="UNKMALE"><unclear/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0015">bye don't get cold see you later</u>
<u n="69" who="UNKMALE">see you later <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0281">see you</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMALE">I'll be back later I need to get petrol</u>
<u n="72" who="S0015">er?</u>
<u n="73" who="UNKMALE">I'll be back a bit later cos I'm getting petrol</u>
<u n="74" who="S0015">alright well I'll come with you to get some petrol I said I would buy you some I'll come with you I'll buy some on my card</u>
<u n="75" who="UNKMALE">well you go with him</u>
<u n="76" who="S0015">come back and I'll get you some or <trunc>gran</trunc>grandad might go with you he's obviously needs petrol before he goes to work sorry I forgot what we were saying? what were we saying about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0015">and he broke his ribs and he was really ill for ages he couldn't work erm but his girls how they get about I don't know it's really they get really thick snow up there</u>
<u n="79" who="S0281">it's supposed to be fine like this again tomorrow</u>
<u n="80" who="S0015">sunny?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0015">sunny but cold</u>
<u n="83" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well I suppose I suppose <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got two erm er barometers in his er living room and er it was very high high pressure but they're starting to fall now so</u>
<u n="84" who="S0015">mm yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0281">I think we're gonna get some rain <unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well out there it's always cold we we've got a barometer out there</u>
<u n="87" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh have you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0015">yeah just to see what it is but that that's almost like a fridge so I keep my you know food food like potatoes and stuff and vegetables out there like having it in a fridge <vocal desc="laugh"/> almost good enough to keep your wine in but not quite</u>
<u n="89" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0015">alright has he gone? I said I would buy him petrol help to buy him some next time erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0281">yeah I've been trying to get er some information about er</u>
<u n="92" who="S0015">pensions?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0281">topping up my pensions and it's crazy er I I got er this number from this form er this letter they sent me which is and then then they said no you need to phone the national number so I phoned the national number and they said no you need to phone the local number</u>
<u n="94" who="S0015">oh</u>
<u n="95" who="S0281">so I get the local number and then they say you need to phone er the HMRC Her Majesty's er</u>
<u n="96" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah whatever</u>
<u n="97" who="S0281">Records and Customs <unclear/> or something like that</u>
<u n="98" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0281">and that's when I phoned them and then they said no you've got to phone the advice centre which is the <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="100" who="S0015">where you'd been</u>
<u n="101" who="S0281">where I'd been and they they sent me said oh you've got to go and phone this <trunc>nu</trunc> I said I phoned it already and I'm just going round in circles</u>
<u n="102" who="S0015">mm so what was the outcome?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0281">well nothing I couldn't get any information so</u>
<u n="104" who="S0015">your best bet</u>
<u n="105" who="S0281">she she said try your local pension centre and that must be in <anon type="place"/> I should think</u>
<u n="106" who="S0015">probably mm your best bet is to send a letter to them all the same letter to them all with with you know a a reference on it</u>
<u n="107" who="S0281">yeah well it's useless doing this I mean it takes so long</u>
<u n="108" who="S0015">mm and what do you do you think you can do it then? did you ask them that?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well yeah yeah if I haven't contributed for the last six years</u>
<u n="110" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0281">which I haven't then you can</u>
<u n="112" who="S0015">you can buy it?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0015">buy back in?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0281">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says it's worth it because</u>
<u n="116" who="S0015" trans="overlap">definitely</u>
<u n="117" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0015">well yeah because it's long term isn't it?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0015">definitely I did I told you that when you were home that I bought in some for my teacher's pension I bought in four years that I'd missed paying to to erm and from from point of view my college had to pay as well so it was a really worthwhile</u>
<u n="121" who="S0281">are there any pies left?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0015">what?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0281">mince pies left?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0015">mm over there they're in the thing at the back</u>
<u n="125" who="S0281">so er yeah I've I'll I'll do that tomorrow but tomorrow I've got to go to the er Citizens Advice Bureau</u>
<u n="126" who="S0015">you didn't go there today?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0281">yeah I did they open at quarter past nine I got there at half past nine and they said erm oh I'm sorry we're full up today you'll have to come back tomorrow</u>
<u n="128" who="S0015" trans="overlap">that's when people queue outside</u>
<u n="129" who="S0281">you you start queuing at half past eight</u>
<u n="130" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah you do if you wanna be seen you have to be in there in the queue at least by half past eight I think it's crazy</u>
<u n="131" who="S0281">mm and I've got to get up about seven o'clock tomorrow</u>
<u n="132" who="S0015"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god crazy</u>
<u n="133" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0015">yeah so are they open every day then?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0281">every week day yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0015">yeah well I imagine at this time of year it's particularly busy is it? oh they're queuing because as you go in you get a number do you or something?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0281">I've got no idea</u>
<u n="138" who="S0015">no</u>
<u n="139" who="S0281">may be maybe they you have to come back and they give you an appointment for that day</u>
<u n="140" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well I I I think you get erm a consultation or something</u>
<u n="141" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0015">you queue up you go in and obviously they give you some sort of numbering system</u>
<u n="143" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0015">erm so you <trunc>g</trunc> you get seen in turn but it doesn't hold many in there erm and then you get a consultation and they'll find out what your problem is and then probably erm send you off for help you know that's more specialised help I imagine that's how it all works</u>
<u n="145" who="S0281">so if I do that in the morning and then if and when I get that sorted and I need to go down to erm <anon type="place"/> I suppose</u>
<u n="146" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0281">the pension place</u>
<u n="148" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0281"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0015">well well look it up on the internet and find out exactly where it is but I imagine it is because that's er I think that's where the kind of job centre is isn't it in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0281">unbelievable the way they just pass you oh so you have to phone so and so</u>
<u n="152" who="S0015">mm I know I know these these erm government offices are always the same aren't they? they have erm I don't know different areas I suppose that deal with different things</u>
<u n="153" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0015">so where was your tax office then when you were here?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0281">I've got no idea</u>
<u n="156" who="S0015">mm no paperwork dating back you can actually ask well you've got you've had a prediction for your pension</u>
<u n="157" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0015">but you can ask for erm a printout of all the stamps you've paid</u>
<u n="159" who="S0281">I have</u>
<u n="160" who="S0015">while you were here and you've got that have you?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0015">oh right okay</u>
<u n="163" who="S0281">yeah I did that erm last year</u>
<u n="164" who="S0015">mm so then could you then? not that very office that that came from you've got a headed notepaper</u>
<u n="165" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah but it's not in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0015">no but that's what I mean send a letter</u>
<u n="167" who="S0281">well I could do</u>
<u n="168" who="S0015">or you might even be able to email if you get into the right erm you know the right area you know the right address and the right thing you could try emailing them</u>
<u n="169" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0015">and that way it goes direct</u>
<u n="171" who="S0281">right and you can't <unclear/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0015">yes often you can't <unclear/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0015">is that the letter not the letter connected to it no?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no this is just a a letter they sent me about a <trunc>qu</trunc>query a query they had</u>
<u n="176" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0281">but erm there's no email address</u>
<u n="178" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0281">no they don't do</u>
<u n="180" who="S0015">no you won't deal with the same person</u>
<u n="181" who="S0281" trans="overlap">they don't do emails</u>
<u n="182" who="S0015">mm?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0281">they don't do emails</u>
<u n="184" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah sometimes they do a kind of general info one don't they? <unclear/> no not in there and when was this? November two thousand and nine so you you might you might find something on a later thing that's for info</u>
<u n="185" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0015">you know an information email they don't like the phone calls because they have to answer <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0281">I was on the phone or one phone I persisted and actually I came off the phone and went on rephoned them on Skype cos it was taking so long it took me thirty minutes to get through and then they just said oh you've got to phone this number again</u>
<u n="188" who="S0015">is that on that phone?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0015">oh my god cos that'll use up a lot of your money</u>
<u n="191" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well that's what I say after fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="192" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0281">I thought well this is getting silly so I Skyped I</u>
<u n="194" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah I mean had you got five hundred minutes have you?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah and so I I came off that and went back onto Skype but then she said oh you keep breaking up are you on Skype? and I said yes</u>
<u n="196" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0015">oh oh oh dear</u>
<u n="198" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="199" who="S0015">and you'd say yes because you don't answer and wait so long for your calls to answer</u>
<u n="200" who="S0281">yeah well that's not their fault the staff are <unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no I know it's not their fault you can't shoot the messenger <vocal desc="yawn"/> can you really? they do their best it's a horrible job and no one would like erm I think their job</u>
<u n="202" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0015">you know tax the inspector of taxes and things not good <pause dur="short"/> so is that all you've managed to get <trunc>do</trunc>done today then your?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0281">erm yeah basically</u>
<u n="205" who="S0015">you didn't get to er?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0281">I went out for a walk</u>
<u n="207" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0015">a bit cold</u>
<u n="210" who="S0281">yeah it was lovely sunshine</u>
<u n="211" who="S0015">yeah the weather was nice but it's erm still very cold</u>
<u n="212" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0015">walking around I was frozen <vocal desc="laugh"/> frozen sitting in the car trying to get this car sorted out really annoying I mean that's such a reliable little car but I think it was I've had the erm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0281">so do they do they know what the problem was?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0015">it had just run the battery down something had run <unclear/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it should it shouldn't do that</u>
<u n="217" who="S0015">well I <trunc>ha</trunc> I've had this phone charger in the car <pause dur="short"/> it plugged in for two or three days but not it's not charging anything but while it's <trunc>dr</trunc> it's taking it out I think it's not you know it's I don't know that's the only thing I could think of <pause dur="short"/> the man and the man at the garage that came over and jump started the car for me said it was erm bad weather is playing havoc with cars and I don't wouldn't have thought it would cause it not to start</u>
<u n="218" who="S0281">no <pause dur="short"/> that shouldn't</u>
<u n="219" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I don't know but it was really flat and I could hear it as soon as I turned it and it went <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0281">how's it go?</u>
<u n="221" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0015"><vocal desc="misc"/> tried but it didn't it just wouldn't start there wasn't enough to get the thing going and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was gonna push me and I thought no if I get stuck somewhere cos I was on a bit of a hill but I thought I don't want to you know be trying trying to get it jump started and find I'm stuck and a bus comes or something so I was very grateful this little man you won't believe he's closed until the fifth of December and <trunc>ori</trunc>originally I went over because there was a light on and it said closed until the fifth of December and I thought oh no anyway I went back and phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and a little while later I saw part of the garage door</u>
<u n="223" who="S0281">fifth of December?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0015">sorry fifth of January part of the door open so I went over and started started shouting hello <vocal desc="laugh"/> anyway he wasn't there but I went around the back and he was around the back checking something part of his you know roof had come off or in the wind so I says oh I said is that your garage? and he said well he said yes he said but we're closed I said yes I saw that I said but I was hoping someone could jump start my car have you got jump leads? he said no he said but I've got a battery pack I'll come over with that and he jump started it so he just saved my life really cos</u>
<u n="225" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0015"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was out for quite a while he went off to pay some bills and do some running around so he didn't get back and I was stuck over in the thing and with a boot full of shopping it should have been in the fridge but mind you the boot was freezing it was freezing out so but I'd got all this food that I should be cooking and I wanted to come back and do the cooking but I spent ages chatting to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is lovely she's a lovely girl she really is she was one of the funniest students that I've ever taught I used to go into the room to try and teach them theory and she just would I don't know cause an uproar with laughter was always one of the and I used to say you know I'll never get you through your exams stop talking stop laughing you know joking and stop making me laugh and she said I promise we'll all get through our exams and they did but they were just a bundle of fun a bundle of fun and interestingly she ran this thing on erm in December that I was going to see this gospel she she runs a erm a what they call a performance choir and then a workshop choir and they have like a hundred and fifty people join well in all and they joined the performance choir and they trained for six weeks and put on a show every twice a year she does it and erm she is just the most amazing she's got always has these incredible ideas of new new things to introduce in her show but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she was young when she was at college sixteen seventeen she used to sing in the <anon type="place"/> do you know the did you know the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="228" who="S0015">no in the do you remember <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0015">in the in the <anon type="place"/> anyway it was on on there it was a really popular bar I mean she wasn't old enough to drink or anything but she used to go and sing there and she was really</u>
<u n="231" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0015">really popular people used to go oh come on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> please sing tonight play the guitar she was really a very talented girl very talented and her mother became very ill she had erm some form of <trunc>de</trunc><trunc>de</trunc>dementia I'm not sure what quite sort not Alzheimer's it wasn't straightforward some form of dementia and she looked after her for gave up everything and looked after her for about eight or nine years devoted her whole life to her she really sort of did everything for her and she always looked immaculate this lady she had her hair done her nails done lovely clothes on you know no matter what was wrong she <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made her she said just cos she's not well why should she you know be neglect her just leave her</u>
<u n="233" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0015">she was really really good she looked after her but when her dad who didn't wanna know I think he was just in denial of it all she gave up her whole life really and and did everything everything for her mum and her dad he's eighty-something now but her mum when she died it was about two years ago was younger than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she'd been ill for about eight or nine years I think prior to that so tragic really cos she's get well had no life and she's got so many talents so many and it seems very sad but she's lovely a lovely girl what she does now is because she she fought the social services and won</u>
<u n="235" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0015">which is almost unheard of erm because someone from the social services I think looking to cut down on costs that was what it was about said that her mother should not come out of bed it wasn't safe for them to get her out of bed and erm lift her up</u>
<u n="237" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0015">well the result of that is that eventually she would die from lack of you know moving around and you know the with the organs I suppose go anyway <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said and and then the carers were forbidden to take her out of bed so consequently <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said right if you erm if this happened and she went above anyway to her bosses and said I'll sue if my mother dies I will sue and you you know it will be really serious erm publicity for you</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0015">you know you know I'll do it nationally it won't be just local anyway eventually they changed their mind and gave back the package for looking after her and erm but when she <trunc>even</trunc> you know she kept going and even after her mother died and they all thought she'd give up then erm and she didn't she just fought them and she won and she got an apology and they said to her what do you want then? she said I want it never to happen to anyone else</u>
<u n="241" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0015">and erm anyway she did win and and did very well out of it but she now erm is an advocate for people who you know have got problems with their <trunc>o</trunc> elderly parents or family in hospital she she'll turn up and help them fight for what they want for that parent or or relative and she's such a worker so you know?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0281"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a woman he goes to visit who's in hospital she's ninety</u>
<u n="244" who="S0015">really?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0281">yeah and she is a <trunc>m</trunc> do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0015"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? I don't</u>
<u n="247" who="S0281"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0015">no not really</u>
<u n="249" who="S0281">erm do you know up <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0281">and next door erm there was a years ago there was a coffee shop a very small coffee shop</u>
<u n="252" who="S0015" trans="overlap">where?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0281">and erm it was run by this woman and her husband and it was their son <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who was a friend of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0281">and mine</u>
<u n="256" who="S0015">I do remember the name</u>
<u n="257" who="S0281">yeah not his daughter's <trunc>f</trunc>famous she's in EastEnders</u>
<u n="258" who="S0015">really?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0281">yeah and erm anyway erm she er she had an operation just before Christmas er have her pacemaker you know removed</u>
<u n="260" who="S0015" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0281">or replaced</u>
<u n="262" who="S0015" trans="overlap">removed?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0281">removed or replaced</u>
<u n="264" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh I was gonna say</u>
<u n="265" who="S0281">because apparently the skin the skin was growing over it erm it was the the flesh was forming around it or something so they</u>
<u n="266" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was convinced she she wasn't gonna survive</u>
<u n="268" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0281">and he thought he'd he went up to see her and he what he thought for the was for the last time but she's she's still there</u>
<u n="270" who="S0015">mm where is she in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0281">I don't know I don't know where it is</u>
<u n="272" who="S0015"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a pacemaker</u>
<u n="273" who="S0281">yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="274" who="S0015">and they I I'd from what I can gather they can't ever take them out</u>
<u n="275" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0015">because the heart or the muscles will grow around it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0281">mm that's right</u>
<u n="278" who="S0015">and so you know you'd rip <vocal desc="laugh"/> holes into the heart wouldn't you? so er</u>
<u n="279" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah but she's still there</u>
<u n="280" who="S0015">oh bless her heart ninety</u>
<u n="281" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0015">that's going some isn't it?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0015">really great yeah well what about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281">he committed suicide</u>
<u n="286" who="S0015">no</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0015">why?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0281">er well his personal situation wasn't great you know he was living in a council house somewhere and er I think you know it's just making ends meet and he <unclear/> from what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tells me he wasn't doing anymore music but erm I think that the the thing that really got to him well there are two things er the first thing was that erm was his daughter's wedding and they had it in I don't know a really posh <anon type="place"/> hotel</u>
<u n="290" who="S0015">oh right</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281">erm the <anon type="place"/> the <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> or something something like that and er she took him to buy some clothes and he wanted this suit and she said no that's er it's too much money you know you know get this</u>
<u n="292" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281">and he wanted to try and you know look the part and she was scrimp trying to scrimp and scrape and begrudge him this and that and but the greatest er insult was that erm he wasn't allowed to walk her up the aisle</u>
<u n="294" who="S0015">oh what?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281">or or at the if it I don't know if it's a church or a civil reception anyway he wasn't allowed to give his daughter away</u>
<u n="296" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281">and er then another snub came at the reception there was basically er two er groups there was the group where the the love is you know from the the sitcom</u>
<u n="298" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281">and friends and family er from the other two families and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was er not asked to sit at the head table</u>
<u n="300" who="S0015">oh that's stupid <unclear/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah I know I know yeah yeah and it really got to him and he he apparently he wrote to the <anon type="place"/> er complaining about it and it was on the front page</u>
<u n="302" who="S0015">really?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281">yeah was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying and he really</u>
<u n="304" who="S0015" trans="overlap">it's sad isn't it?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281">made a stink about it well it is yeah so</u>
<u n="306" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well it was embarrassing for him obviously</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I mean er it is in direct contrast to you know the the daughter you said had <trunc>sac</trunc>sacrificed a life to look after her mother</u>
<u n="308" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0281">and you've got the the <unclear/> complete opposite of you know she how she</u>
<u n="310" who="S0015" trans="overlap">gone to her head <unclear/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0281">treated her father</u>
<u n="312" who="S0015">yeah lost to the groups</u>
<u n="313" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and erm he really got uptight and about this and erm when I came over for my sixtieth</u>
<u n="314" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0281">erm the er I I saw him it was in the summer of course and er he we met him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I met him at <anon type="place"/> and we went into the teahouse there</u>
<u n="316" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh I vaguely remember you going off to yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0281">and er I think that's the very last time we saw him and erm yeah and he at that time he was er said he'd got a young Belgian girlfriend and was very happy with that but that fell through and I think that might have precipitated</u>
<u n="318" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0281">the last thing and he hung himself</u>
<u n="320" who="S0015">oh god that's dreadful</u>
<u n="321" who="S0281">and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was very cut up about it he'd had had a very er love incredible love hate relationship with him I mean they'd had each other's women and wives and</u>
<u n="322" who="S0015" trans="overlap">what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0015">oh my god</u>
<u n="325" who="S0281">you know he was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for years and years and years and years?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0015">I don't remember</u>
<u n="327" who="S0281">er oh anyway he was and erm he split up from her and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came in and said he came into to live in the house and actually took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s place in the bed <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to sleep in the on the couch or something</u>
<u n="328" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="329" who="S0281">and this was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house ah oh it's</u>
<u n="330" who="S0015" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0281">I know but he'd done the same to he'd had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s one of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ex-girlfriends or</u>
<u n="332" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="333" who="S0281">but it's a very complicated relationship</u>
<u n="334" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="335" who="S0281">and erm they've both er been good friends and good enemies as well sometimes</u>
<u n="336" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0281">but when he did do that he he felt very bad about it</u>
<u n="338" who="S0015">oh my goodness me</u>
<u n="339" who="S0281">I know</u>
<u n="340" who="S0015">dodgy dodgy life that isn't it? but I suppose the worse thing is you can't ever get over being rejected by your daughter though can you really?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0281">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0015" trans="overlap">it must have gone to her head I mean</u>
<u n="343" who="S0281">well I mean especially if you've got nobody else</u>
<u n="344" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0281">and it's erm well I suppose he had his parents although his father is dead now</u>
<u n="346" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0281">but his his mother's still there</u>
<u n="348" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm but it's not it's you know that your child you want them to be you know?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0281">I know I know it's but it's not uncommon is it? you often hear about family feuds and you know somebody's not speaking to somebody else for years</u>
<u n="350" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah you do I mean everybody has yeah everybody has family problems but usually in that situation if he wasn't gonna be accepted as as <unclear>her father</unclear> he wouldn't have been invited to the wedding you know I mean would he? I mean it's like it's almost worse to go to the wedding and not have your</u>
<u n="351" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0015">positionbe accepted and not to go to the wedding you know?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0015">very sad you know if you don't go you don't know what you're missing and what you yeah it's kind of like not you haven't got to face it but to have <trunc>th</trunc>that many snubs in one go you know the wrong suit and erm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0015">you know? poor man what did he do <trunc>mu</trunc>musician?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0281" trans="overlap">he was a musician</u>
<u n="358" who="S0015">really?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> told me a story about erm when he was er living up in <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="360" who="S0015" trans="overlap">what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was living in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0281">yeah and and er he was er had a room in some house or something and erm another room was er being used by David Bowie and</u>
<u n="362" who="S0015" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0281">yeah and he used to come in and say hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm what do you think about this? and</u>
<u n="364" who="S0015" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0281">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0015">so he was a good musician was he then?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0281">er yeah he was yeah and er I think he told me another story about he had the chance to go off to where was it? to Sweden to play with Abba or something</u>
<u n="368" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0281">yeah something like that and er</u>
<u n="370" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0281">he didn't go for some reason some silly reason but</u>
<u n="372" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0281">but er</u>
<u n="374" who="S0015">it sounds like he had chances and missed the chance</u>
<u n="375" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0015">opportunities there</u>
<u n="377" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0015">to be</u>
<u n="379" who="S0281">he showed me once one of his albums that he'd made</u>
<u n="380" who="S0015">was he good?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0281">well I mean he was he's a good musician but the thing is there are so many good musicians</u>
<u n="382" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0281">and</u>
<u n="384" who="S0015">the luck of the draw isn't it being in the right place at the right time?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it is it is because <trunc>w</trunc>when I had the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> erm and we we had some not very good musicians but there were from time to time excellent musicians you know?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0281">and erm I came to the conclusion over the years and then buskers as well a lot of them</u>
<u n="388" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0281">were buskers you know? and it's it's not just talent a huge part of it is luck</u>
<u n="390" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0281">just being in the right place at the right time</u>
<u n="392" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah yeah mm mm and contacts</u>
<u n="393" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh that yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0015">and you know contacts and contacts that you know put you in the right place at the right time and it is it's it's er it's erm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0281">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> introduced me to a guy who was in his car the other day and he says this guy's a neighbour and he was doing some work for him actually erm doing some plastering and erm he said oh he's a musician he said he's a good musician he said he's he's making another album at the moment he said he's he was on the er he's been on this and been on that and he he showed me erm er a TV programme and he he was on the Jules Holland show</u>
<u n="396" who="S0015">really?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0281">yeah his his group there and he writes er background music</u>
<u n="398" who="S0015" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="399" who="S0281">and scores and all this kind of thing</u>
<u n="400" who="S0015">nice</u>
<u n="401" who="S0281">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always like that erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah I think there's like areas and a lot of lot of</u>
<u n="403" who="S0281">when I was staying for my you know</u>
<u n="404" who="S0015" trans="overlap">last visit</u>
<u n="405" who="S0281">I stayed with him when I came over for when I was sixty erm and this guy he was a real character walked up the stairs with this sort of cowboy hat thing and leather jacket on and big bushy beard and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had one had one as well at the same time and er his name was Patrick Bergin and he was an actor</u>
<u n="406" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0281">who'd made films you know big films and it was well not you know the B not in the A stream is it?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="409" who="S0281">but I mean if you if you Skyped his name and and Skyped it</u>
<u n="410" who="S0015" trans="overlap">what was his name Patrick Bergin?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0281">Bergin yeah and er you can see all the films he's been in the only one I remember is Robin Hood so</u>
<u n="412" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0281">yeah so he he does have you know these people he mixes with</u>
<u n="414" who="S0015">in that area where he lives though there's quite a lot of you know erm arty people and</u>
<u n="415" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0015">and you know people in TV and film and it's quite a sort of around the <anon type="place"/> area there's a lot of people like that I mean erm and further just further along erm just as you get to <anon type="place"/> there there's a lot of very famous people <unclear/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0281" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0015">yeah er Fatboy Slim</u>
<u n="419" who="S0281">oh yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0015">lives there and Zoe Ball and yeah they live all around that and quite a <unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it used to be like that for <anon type="place"/> wasn't it?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0015">yeah yeah it did</u>
<u n="423" who="S0281">Laurence</u>
<u n="424" who="S0015" trans="overlap">Dora Bryan and</u>
<u n="425" who="S0281">Dora Bryan and Laurence Olivier</u>
<u n="426" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah that's right yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0281">and erm er Dame erm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0281">what's her name?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0281">erm oh</u>
<u n="432" who="S0015">I can't remember but</u>
<u n="433" who="S0281">yeah but all all around that</u>
<u n="434" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0281">area they used</u>
<u n="436" who="S0015"><anon type="place"/> is still full of very theatrical people</u>
<u n="437" who="S0281">yeah <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0015">mm yeah but it's erm <anon type="place"/> I mean erm Paul McCartney <unclear/> lived in erm <anon type="place"/> and Paul McCartney lived had a place not far away</u>
<u n="439" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0015">and they used to see him flitting around he doesn't come to <anon type="place"/> now but that's how erm his ex wife Heather whatever her name was I can't remember Heather something</u>
<u n="441" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0015">she she lives in <anon type="place"/> still somewhere</u>
<u n="443" who="S0281">I thought she was dead</u>
<u n="444" who="S0015">mm?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0281">she's dead</u>
<u n="446" who="S0015">no no that that's not not his first wife that was erm what was her name? Linda McCartney</u>
<u n="447" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0015">no she died but he met he <trunc>m</trunc>married Heather with the</u>
<u n="449" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh yeah the one that had the one leg?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0015">yeah mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0015">well she's still got the erm erm café at erm <anon type="place"/> in the <anon type="place"/> she owns that</u>
<u n="453" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0015">mm she's there sometimes yeah <unclear/> but erm yeah so she lives somewhere in and around <anon type="place"/> and I'm not sure where but not far away I wouldn't be surprised if she lived along where Zoe Ball and and er Fatboy Slim live somewhere because it's close to that but yeah no <anon type="place"/> is full of people people like that and always has been I suppose where since old erm prince what's his name? the prince Regent days there's always been famous people in and around <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0015">and that's why the price of houses here</u>
<u n="457" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0015">are well have crept up close on to what they are in <anon type="place"/> a lot of people come down from <anon type="place"/> cos they're a bit cheaper but it's not much cheaper now hence people</u>
<u n="459" who="S0281" trans="overlap">crazy</u>
<u n="460" who="S0015">are spreading out towards <anon type="place"/> and erm <anon type="place"/> area and that's</u>
<u n="461" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well we we went to <anon type="place"/> yesterday</u>
<u n="462" who="S0015">mm it's a lovely little village</u>
<u n="463" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and oh it is a little village and the prices out there oh dear</u>
<u n="464" who="S0015" trans="overlap">sky high</u>
<u n="465" who="S0281">oh my god well you know a lot of them around the million pound mark or</u>
<u n="466" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well you know</u>
<u n="467" who="S0281">between one and two million</u>
<u n="468" who="S0015">mm you I'm I don't know if you er ever remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on Christmas day about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> no? no his family owned quite a lot of land in in erm <anon type="place"/> and when he when the children were born he's got two brothers the three of them were born his father bought a plot of land for each of them as they were born they're very very wealthy I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there were I think three brothers two brothers stayed together and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> split away and does his own thing with property but they've got a lot of factories and erm houses and</u>
<u n="469" who="S0281" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="470" who="S0015">you know builder developer and er so he's very good I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had properties with him but I don't think they've got anything together now he has a lot of erm shops and factories here here and but you know the houses the other houses in er <anon type="place"/> where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> live</u>
<u n="471" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0015">the houses that are sixties seventies style?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0015">seventies style his father built those those houses but his you know he's <unclear/> now but loads of money <trunc>multi</trunc>multimillionaire but not happy it doesn't make you happy you can't buy happiness can you?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0281">what it gives you is choice</u>
<u n="476" who="S0015">yeah it gives you a bit more choice but then quite often you make bad choices I think when you when money's no object you make some very bad choices I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she you know lost her husband you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s husband died in <unclear/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm yeah the Falklands</u>
<u n="478" who="S0015">well she had lots of money I hope this never gets printed anywhere where she would hear had lots of money afterwards she sued the <trunc>F</trunc> the Falkland Island government which of course is ours and you know they admitted liability cos the oxygen flask er erm cylinder wasn't filled</u>
<u n="479" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="480" who="S0015">to the you know enough it wasn't full it was obviously not being checked someone had not done their job erm but I think it never made her happy she just she bought houses and put rooms in the roof or put extensions on and loads spent loads of money and then moved on to the next one she never settled never settled erm until basically the money had gone and then she got back down to normal to to reality and you know had to work and but she had a lot of money when she was young but it just couldn't buy her happiness and it couldn't what she was trying to do always was holiday and trying to compensate for what she'd lost really and it you know you can't and er yeah it was very very sad and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now twenty-six the same age as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just moved in on the twenty-third moved in to his first flat on his own well with his girlfriend you know left home but but he's been living with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for a number of years</u>
<u n="481" who="S0281" trans="overlap">twenty-six <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0015">mm?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0281"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is twenty-six?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0015" trans="overlap">twenty-six yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0281">good grief</u>
<u n="486" who="S0015"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> twenty-five</u>
<u n="487" who="S0281">what?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0015"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> twenty-six mm yeah yep you know time flies actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> all look young for their age that's gonna be one day it's gonna be a big advantage I mean we always say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> looks twelve when she erm when she was about twenty-one it was soon after she'd learnt to drive she had a a little prang in the car in <anon type="place"/> and she erm got out of the car and the people got out of the car and it was only just like a knock of the bumper the people got out of the car shouting and screaming at her and swearing at her saying what are you doing in that car you're not old enough to drive? and she went I am I'm twenty-one and she went to come off marched off to get all her documents cos they were cos she looked like a twelve year old she's you know small and she just looks twelve and she looks a little bit older now but not a lot and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's the same and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was DJing sometimes he wouldn't be allowed in they wouldn't let him in you know if he hadn't got his passport or his erm driving licence with him then there's been times he's had to go home and get them when he was in <anon type="place"/> but when he's been in different towns then he's not had that problem but yeah he had to go sent him home to get his passport once</u>
<u n="489" who="S0281">wow</u>
<u n="490" who="S0015">ridiculous isn't it? cos he's just looked you know bouncers and security people that don't know him yeah he had to go home and get them but that'll be an advantage one day soon when he's you know</u>
<u n="491" who="S0281">I mean yesterday when after we we erm when we went to <anon type="place"/> we we went into the church there</u>
<u n="492" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0281">it's called <anon type="place"/> it dates back to over a thousand years</u>
<u n="494" who="S0015">good grief</u>
<u n="495" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0015">a thousand years <unclear/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah and it was erm because it was built on the site er of the original Saxon church</u>
<u n="498" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="499" who="S0281">and which was mentioned in the Doomsday Book</u>
<u n="500" who="S0015">good grief</u>
<u n="501" who="S0281">yeah and it's a lovely charismatic er church</u>
<u n="502" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0281">very very small and but there was some erm commemorative stones well gravestones I suppose cos they</u>
<u n="504" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0281">were for the person who was laid to rest here</u>
<u n="506" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="507" who="S0281">you know dating back hundreds of years</u>
<u n="508" who="S0015">mm <unclear/> when I've been here now we've been to a few churches haven't we?</u>
<u n="509" who="UNKMALE">mm?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0015">we've been to a few churches</u>
<u n="511" who="UNKMALE">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0015">and cathedrals</u>
<u n="513" who="UNKMALE">yep</u>
<u n="514" who="S0015">we always had this plan is to spend time on our retirement going off for the day to places like that but we never never found the time <vocal desc="laugh"/> grandchildren or other things or distractions work well I plus I didn't really retire so it's only now that I and I have to say I woke up this morning and I was thinking I haven't got it hanging over me worrying about you know the next lesson that I've got to prepare or the next group I've got to deal with or the next observation I'm gonna be and it's the first time ever I haven't had it hanging over me I should be doing my lesson preparation or</u>
<u n="515" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="516" who="S0015">you know thinking about the next test or the tracking of something of students is a really strange feeling did it feel like that to you though when you'd finished?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0281">er well yes erm it wasn't</u>
<u n="518" who="S0015" trans="overlap">did you have a lot of tracking or?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0281">no no I didn't do that erm but er it was er very strange and you know when I finished leaving leaving the campus for the last time</u>
<u n="520" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0281">but I still went back to see a few people but it was er I'd been there seven years you know a bit of a wrench</u>
<u n="522" who="S0015">well you imagine how I felt when I had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> twenty-five years I'd been there</u>
<u n="523" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="524" who="S0015">but actually I didn't feel anything as I walked away</u>
<u n="525" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0015">no not at all I think it had run its course you know I'd been there long enough and things were changing erm erm and I wasn't the last one of because there were four of us that worked together for not for the full twenty-five years but two of us that worked for twenty-five years there and one of them was one of my first groups of students and then another one that I'd been at college with she didn't work there that long but there were four of us that knew each other and had came through roughly the same sort of background training and and work experience and erm so we worked together for twenty-five years but one erm my friend that I worked the longest with she erm went she took a year out and went to work in <anon type="place"/> and came back and took early retirement so she was the first one out and another one that I'd been at college with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she left to go and live in <anon type="place"/> erm and then that left myself and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that was my ex-student and erm I had the opportunity if I didn't take early retirement then I'd have to have committed to another five years and I couldn't face five more more years so I thought right I'll get out now to get my early retirement money</u>
<u n="527" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0015">and then I can do less hours and still take home the same and that's what I did and I erm I took the opportunity was literally just on they were <trunc>cha</trunc> just about to change it to say twenty-five year you know to fifty-five so I I managed to get it and my birthday was in the July and they were gonna start it in the September and I so I went yes I'll have it panicked a bit but I didn't as I walked away I felt nothing it was really strange I mean I'd spent well if you think I was fifty I'd spent twenty-five years more time at work than at home don't you? when you're five days a week you're home two days so I I was I couldn't understand why I felt that when I went to <anon type="place"/> erm and it was very much more a relaxed regime and erm and I didn't work many hours to begin with and I just got ended up getting dragged in more and more but I felt more when I left there erm because I left for a year and went to work at <anon type="place"/> and that was the weirdest experience working in <anon type="place"/> it was a strange and bizarre year and they my head of department erm got to know that I wasn't very settled it was I found it yeah I I met some of the staff at a competition and someone said to me how is it going how are you enjoying working at <anon type="place"/>? and I went don't ask and she said why isn't it good? I said well it's weird it's not right it's you know different and she went back and told my boss from <anon type="place"/> and she sent a message I want to poach you back come back</u>
<u n="529" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0015">so I did I went back so I actually worked for <anon type="place"/> for seventeen years but I felt more leaving there than I did at <anon type="place"/> because the people that I worked with were still there very strange I don't know why it should be like that yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> left <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> died <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so all four of us went within a space of eighteen months to two years from <anon type="place"/> and that was a really weird thing and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> died soon after I was working at <anon type="place"/> she lived nearby near er near <anon type="place"/> she lived in <anon type="place"/> so I used to go to work have a class in the morning and afternoon off and an evening class and go and see her and er and I saw her just a a day or so before she died</u>
<u n="531" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0015">she had cancer she was forty-something</u>
<u n="533" who="S0281">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0015">just just over forty forty-one or forty-two something like that beautiful girl she was too <unclear>lovely</unclear> but yeah so <anon type="place"/> I felt more leaving there than I did erm <anon type="place"/> for some reason erm and I think it's people the people that you know were there I really I mean I went up for lunch with er well I'm saying lunch dinner just before Christmas just <trunc>be</trunc> well the day you came home no no what day did you come home on? you came home on the ninth</u>
<u n="535" who="S0281" trans="overlap">ninth yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0015">it was the week after sixteenth</u>
<u n="537" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0015">I went on the <trunc>Tue</trunc> that Tuesday yeah I worked on there no I worked on the ninth and the sixteenth and so it was the Friday I went up for to have dinner with them which was really nice to be invited still but I get called every now and again</u>
<u n="539" who="S0281">for what?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0015">for what? for to cover</u>
<u n="541" who="S0281">oh yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah so I mean I I gave up last Easter was my last officially you know my class <unclear/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well it's handy for them isn't it?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0015">well yeah and I've had two phone calls one saying erm could you come and take a class tonight?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0281">wow</u>
<u n="546" who="S0015">I went er yes <trunc>wh</trunc>what what is it? and it was theory so I went and then she said well actually could you do two weeks someone's off sick for two weeks would you do two? so I said okay and I took the class for two weeks got the register in order everything sorted and then erm I took all the paperwork to the register and all the stuff that I'd been doing while I'd been covering and she said well she said that I'm really stuck I'm trying to recruit new staff erm she said can you hang on while I recruit that staff maybe until Christmas? so this was in October time and I went okay erm so I I stayed until Christmas and we got close to Christmas and I said well who's gonna take over cos they want to know the group want to know? and they finished at Easter so she said well I've got you permanently pencilled in until Easter</u>
<u n="547" who="S0281">oh wow</u>
<u n="548" who="S0015">to go with when the group go and I <trunc>s</trunc> cos they were a lovely group so I said yeah okay I will I will do that so I did that and then I got a call again erm just before erm someone had an operation one of the other staff had an operation well they've lost two more staff since then but they hope got two new ones in and one of them's had an operation and erm so I've covered two weeks of her classes the ninth and the day you came home and the sixteenth but she's just had her gallstones removed or something yeah so but I'd I quite like <anon type="place"/> because I like the atmosphere there and it's changing now because they've got no money and it's you know there's no paper for printing there's no materials for teaching with and you know it's cut back cut back cut back whereas well <anon type="place"/> you always had like endless amounts of everything you needed there was no question whether you could do this or do that or colour print or you know there was no <trunc>i</trunc>in fact just prior to the <trunc>Of</trunc> last Ofsted people were taking in their own printer paper</u>
<u n="549" who="S0281" trans="overlap">were they really?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0015">so they could do their lessons yeah and flipcharts and things and they were buying their own stuff cos they couldn't guarantee they'd have it for their lessons</u>
<u n="551" who="S0281" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="552" who="S0015">but erm the college what happened was the college erm when the new principal took over she announced that they were erm I think she said four million in debt or two million in debt two million in debt and there would be redundancies some redundancies so she took over in the January and February and she announced this erm and then a few months later she she said erm actually we're not four million er two million in debt we're in four and it's much more serious than I initially thought and she immediately erm had the finance officer marched off the building and investigated</u>
<u n="553" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0015">yeah and the principal was called in and the finance officer and they were interrogated and the finance officer got sacked with no pension</u>
<u n="555" who="S0281">woah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0015">and the principal well he'd gone with his money so but I know what happened they they had a massive new state-of-the-art building of one of the erm satellite centres in <anon type="place"/> and I watched it being built cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was at college there erm and it you know oh I'm having this place just two little extensions you know whatever your budget you start with you can double it and that's closer on what it would be but theirs probably was more cost it went over a long time and erm like you know you get your buildings are in a <unclear/> they'll get them sorted but once you've done that you've got all the furnishings and the</u>
<u n="557" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0015">equipment and the materials that you need to set it all up and I think that's and it turned out to be ten million ten million in debt which means it triggers an immediate Ofsted</u>
<u n="559" who="S0281" trans="overlap">woah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0015">erm and that's what <event desc="sound of doorbell"/> that's what all of that was about so I'm just going to the door <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="561" who="UNKFEMALE">hello</u>
<u n="562" who="S0281">hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="563" who="UNKFEMALE">how are you?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0281">fine how are you?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0015"><unclear/></u>
<u n="566" who="UNKFEMALE">hello how are you?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0015">I'm alright thank you oh you're cold do you want a quick cup of tea?</u>
<u n="568" who="UNKFEMALE">no I've got to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up</u>
<u n="569" who="S0015">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> why? oh my god why? you've got <unclear/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="570" who="UNKFEMALE">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0015">oh no darling you'll never recover you've got <unclear/> off tomorrow?</u>
<u n="572" who="UNKFEMALE">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0015">oh right I should think so</u>
<u n="574" who="UNKFEMALE">yeah look I've to collect cheese as well</u>
<u n="575" who="S0015">come and collect cheese oh <unclear/> cheese</u>
<u n="576" who="UNKFEMALE">I've been sent over for some cheese by my sister</u>
<u n="577" who="UNKMALE">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think mum's eaten it</u>
<u n="578" who="UNKFEMALE">really?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0015">we've not we've got <unclear/> packet <unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="UNKFEMALE">have you?</u>
<u n="581" who="UNKMALE">no we haven't you haven't touched that there's</u>
<u n="582" who="S0015">what am I looking at? oh I can't find it now oh where's it gone? oh it arrived today <unclear/> but I've lost it already <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="583" who="UNKFEMALE">have you finished <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0281">yeah yeah that's fine that's fine thanks</u>
<u n="585" who="S0015">oh goodie <unclear/> oh your son rescued me today</u>
<u n="586" who="UNKFEMALE">why?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0015">why?</u>
<u n="588" who="UNKMALE">oh yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0015">I broke down</u>
<u n="590" who="UNKMALE">it was payback time</u>
<u n="591" who="UNKFEMALE">did you?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="UNKFEMALE">what do you mean payback time?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0015">I broke down</u>
<u n="595" who="UNKMALE"><unclear/> wasn't it <unclear/>?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
