<text id="SDJL">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:36:45</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-02</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0198 S0229 S0230</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Café, Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Bumping into other English people abroad, package tours, Christmas markets, city traffic, Antwerp, Language learning, Herne Bay shopping, Christmas shopping, puppies, losing family, children’s birthdays, Brighton Seafront, Dorset caravanning, university cohort, retirement, raising boys, relationships, English rhyming. </topics>
		<activity>Family discussing friends and family over ice-cream</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0198">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Gillingham, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Easten</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>27</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0229">
				<exactage>69</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>69</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0230">
				<exactage>57</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harlow, Essex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>care assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0198">funny mum was just telling me about when you saw some English people I got two flakes in mine by the way do you want another one?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="3" who="S0198">when you saw some English people in er in somewhere in Belgium where were you?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0230">erm Antwerp</u>
<u n="5" who="S0198">and you said you were from Mars <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0229">no I said I'm from Mars and mother's from Venus <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0230">no the woman said that</u>
<u n="8" who="S0229">oh was it <unclear/> where did I say you was from?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0230">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> you said I'm from Mars and she looked at me and and said I suppose you're from Venus?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0198">it was her that had that bit yeah at least she knew what to come back with</u>
<u n="11" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0198">I hate it when people it's always Americans come up to us abroad and go oh I'll have to say something or give you some advice about something I'm like no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0198">just cos I'm white too <pause dur="short"/> although they're all probably around dad's age</u>
<u n="15" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> compelled to talk to people</u>
<u n="17" who="S0230">that was that weren't far from those sex shops either</u>
<u n="18" who="S0198">oh wasn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0230">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0198">finding their way down there too</u>
<u n="21" who="S0230">I think it was a mother and daughter cos she was sort of my age and she was with an older woman</u>
<u n="22" who="S0198">oh right I thought you'd say was gonna say her daughter was sort of my age</u>
<u n="23" who="S0230">no and they'd come in on a erm cruise ship</u>
<u n="24" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0230">they were doing a <unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0198">probably then you do see like a few like package tours as well for Belgium come up on online and stuff like that</u>
<u n="27" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0198">I saw one the other day cos on Trainline you see it a lot and then you can go over on the Eurostar or whatever but erm there was one for the Christmas markets cos that's an expensive time of the year to go there and it it was really like five days or something was like eight hundred pounds or something</u>
<u n="29" who="S0230">really?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0230">but that being everything I should imagine that'd be your meals as well I would have thought</u>
<u n="32" who="S0198">I don't know maybe maybe the accommodation</u>
<u n="33" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0198">I thought it's just five nights and accommodation erm maybe some meals time of the year though those Christmas markets in Europe are really popular all fairytale like there are some more napkins here dad if you need them</u>
<u n="35" who="S0229">no</u>
<u n="36" who="S0198">well do you want a bit more Flake mum? no? ah I got the special one did I? finally had our Mr Whippy and a Flake at the beach</u>
<u n="37" who="S0229" trans="overlap">how did you how did you how did you end up with two flakes?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0198">cos they gave us one</u>
<u n="39" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0198">wasn't paying attention maybe</u>
<u n="41" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="42" who="S0198">stuck one in stuck another in</u>
<u n="43" who="S0230">and that it it was her that said they were supposed to have stopped at Brussels</u>
<u n="44" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0230">but because the traffic was so bad that they didn't cos it would have took too long to have got into Brussels and they wouldn't have had had enough time then</u>
<u n="46" who="S0229">that that that helped me make my mind up anyway</u>
<u n="47" who="S0230" trans="overlap">so they they erm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0198">oh did it?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0230">yeah so they spent two days at Antwerp instead but she said we're not at all worried she says it's lovely here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean people people want to go to the capitals but I dunno why I think I'd rather potter around somewhere like nice in England than London</u>
<u n="51" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0198">if you only had a couple of days <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta know where you're going in a city more I think than the big city</u>
<u n="53" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0198">how big was Bruges? it was smaller than Antwerp was it?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0230">I thought so</u>
<u n="56" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0229">it was still big though weren't it?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0230">but it was big yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0229">huge</u>
<u n="60" who="S0230">well it was smaller than Antwerp</u>
<u n="61" who="S0198">mm <pause dur="short"/> different style was it? was there still like European architecture in Antwerp as well?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0229">but Antwerp you could walk up the main road <unclear/> do a left if we'd have know we could have done a left up some steps and been there</u>
<u n="64" who="S0198">oh right</u>
<u n="65" who="S0229">that's how the difference is if you know your way about do you remember that bit dear? along the front when we come down the steps we could have gone up then to start with</u>
<u n="66" who="S0230">yeah but that was that was still a lovely long way along there</u>
<u n="67" who="S0229">I know but it was still quicker than going right round like we did</u>
<u n="68" who="S0198"><unclear/> you're too far away what are you sitting out there for? you're getting your ice cream everywhere</u>
<u n="69" who="S0229">stretch my leg out <pause dur="short"/> and the cars'd be driving along and then you see them do a left across a footpath but they were allowed to</u>
<u n="70" who="S0198">oh really?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear/> all road yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0230">yeah they've got like footpath the instead of the road going up there it's made into a footpath and they drive over the footpath</u>
<u n="73" who="S0229">over the footpath</u>
<u n="74" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0230">to go up the side roads</u>
<u n="76" who="S0198">to cut to cut up the side road</u>
<u n="77" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0229">if you know where you're going it's so quick and easy but like me and mum we never had a bloody clue</u>
<u n="79" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="80" who="S0229">there's nothing in English <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0198">erm I didn't know they cycled so much there</u>
<u n="82" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0198">makes sense</u>
<u n="84" who="S0230">in Antwerp</u>
<u n="85" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0230">a lot a lot of cycles</u>
<u n="87" who="S0229" trans="overlap">thousands of bikes</u>
<u n="88" who="S0198">mm I feel like there's a load here but that's cos you just don't see them that often in England</u>
<u n="89" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0229">yeah that'd be nothing to what's over there</u>
<u n="91" who="S0198">no yeah I bet not</u>
<u n="92" who="S0229">you could walk you could walk from here to that pier and there's rows of bikes on most everywhere you go</u>
<u n="93" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you'd probably quite like going to Holland actually</u>
<u n="94" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0198">it's even smaller they'll have flea markets and stuff as well</u>
<u n="96" who="S0229">we do a left and a right</u>
<u n="97" who="S0198">and they're basically bilingual</u>
<u n="98" who="S0229">come out and have our own <unclear/> with rows of bikes</u>
<u n="99" who="S0230">yeah I do think a lot of erm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0198">a lot of European countries are French Italy Spain not so much they're not quite so good at it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0230" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="102" who="S0198">but erm Germany Holland Scandinavia in general they're all really good at English</u>
<u n="103" who="S0230">our television in erm the room as well had a <unclear/> picked up BBC One</u>
<u n="104" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0198">I think that's why they get really good at it I think I I assumed they just you know had a really good education system for it which I think it's not bad but the girl the Dutch girl on my course is doing it she didn't start learning at school until she was eleven and they have English television</u>
<u n="107" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0198">with no subtitles</u>
<u n="109" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0198">and it's a part of their culture almost now like but you'll hear young people talking Dutch but then talking English and stuff like that like they they see <unclear>it's</unclear> constant in their own culture</u>
<u n="111" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0198">and they have done for a long time apparently <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying actually he's doing creoles and pidgins which is you know what creoles is? it's like the English they talk in the Caribbean it's what <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> probably speaks it's English but not quite English</u>
<u n="113" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0198">it's <trunc>bas</trunc> it's come from English erm masters</u>
<u n="115" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0198">when they had like the slaves and stuff like that erm and he said interestingly cos the Dutch are really good at it he said that they typically have always <trunc>tri</trunc> they had their own empire didn't they? and they always made a point of trying to talk in the in the lingua franca and whatever language was necessary to communicate in rather than tell talking in Dutch so he said there's less Dutch pidgins around the world because creoles around the world because they never spoke to their slaves in Dutch anyway</u>
<u n="117" who="S0230">ah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0198">they would have tried talking to them in English or something else so it seems like it's just been a part of their culture for centuries so talking in other languages and whatnot and we never did that in English basically</u>
<u n="119" who="S0230">yeah we're lazy with the languages</u>
<u n="120" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0230">terribly lazy</u>
<u n="122" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> shockingly so <pause dur="short"/> but there's not as much of a requirement for us to learn it to learn another language cos it takes a lot of hard work and you've gotta have a real reason to put in that much work to get that good at a language</u>
<u n="123" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0198">and er if our jobs or whatever depended on it then maybe more people would be motivated but they don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0230">well if you go and</u>
<u n="126" who="S0198" trans="overlap">live somewhere else yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0230">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0198">mm <pause dur="long"/> never mind eh see how well my French how good my French gets</u>
<u n="129" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0229">bloody hard them old cornets aren't they?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0229">they ain't like those original ones are they?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="134" who="S0229">where did we buy that one and we dropped it straightaway? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0230">you did</u>
<u n="136" who="S0229">great big double one it was where was it? Hastings or Eastbourne?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="138" who="S0229">somewhere down the coast huge one and it stood there like that for two seconds and whop it went on the floor</u>
<u n="139" who="S0230">no it went flop</u>
<u n="140" who="S0229"><vocal desc="laugh"/> left it there</u>
<u n="141" who="S0198">saw a woman do that really recently where was I?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0229">Herne Bay weren't it? I think it was Herne Bay</u>
<u n="143" who="S0230">no it wasn't Herne Bay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0229">where we seen B Q</u>
<u n="145" who="S0230" trans="overlap">no no it wasn't Herne Bay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0198">where did we watch a lady do that? we <trunc>tho</trunc> oh it was here with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we came off we came off the pier here a couple of weeks ago a bird had swapped swooped past and a lady dropped hers fresh ice cream you're like ah that's two pound fifty gone on the floor there</u>
<u n="147" who="S0229">there's some old antique shops down here closed weren't it do you remember where we went that time to see B Q? it was Herne Bay weren't it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0230">where we saw B Q that time was Herne Bay I don't remember any antique</u>
<u n="149" who="S0229" trans="overlap">we went round the shops but they was all closed weren't they?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0230">I don't remember</u>
<u n="151" who="S0198">don't remember</u>
<u n="152" who="S0230">mm I don't remember antique shops in Herne Bay</u>
<u n="153" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0198">when did you go to Herne Bay?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0229">oh</u>
<u n="156" who="S0198">where's Herne Bay again?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0229">not far from <unclear/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0198">oh yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> go back to Whitstable again sometime suppose you'll have a trip free couple of months after this will you?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0230">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="160" who="S0198">save some money</u>
<u n="161" who="S0230">and the weather'll be changing as well won't it?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0229">see how it is might do one more out before Christmas somewhere local</u>
<u n="163" who="S0230"><unclear/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0229">and see what happens after that after Christmas</u>
<u n="165" who="S0198">got a few weeks yet</u>
<u n="166" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0230">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was doing yesterday Christmas shopping</u>
<u n="168" who="S0198">oh yeah dad said it's a bit early isn't it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0230">well we had erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been acting manager he's had extra money</u>
<u n="170" who="S0198">yeah so what they're spending it while they've got it?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0198">before it disappears on something else</u>
<u n="173" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0198">what were they buying?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0230">well they they've done all the kids</u>
<u n="176" who="S0198">oh have they?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0198">what <trunc>cr</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0230">yeah oh and no not erm well they've done some of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s they've done like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and</u>
<u n="180" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0230"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and er</u>
<u n="182" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0230"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she done her mum and dad</u>
<u n="184" who="S0198">what did they get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? what sort of things do they buy them?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0230">erm they got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like an erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like a er erm spy tech watch</u>
<u n="186" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0230">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a I don't know if it was Meccano or Lego I think it was Meccano</u>
<u n="188" who="S0198">oh little building set things</u>
<u n="189" who="S0230">yeah they can make a like a racing car or something</u>
<u n="190" who="S0198">yeah that'll be alright won't it?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0198">whatever really innit? it's the thought that counts</u>
<u n="193" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0198">oh so we'll have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there Christmas morning</u>
<u n="195" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0198">he'll be getting well excited</u>
<u n="197" who="S0229">there'll be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there tonight</u>
<u n="198" who="S0198">got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there for the next week <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she's coming back Saturday she's not gonna want him Saturday is she?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0230">no I wouldn't have thought so</u>
<u n="200" who="S0198">I mean she might if she comes back early enough</u>
<u n="201" who="S0230">no I doubt it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0198">I bet she'll be home too late</u>
<u n="203" who="S0229"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0230">unless she's got a really early flight</u>
<u n="205" who="S0229"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0198">pardon me</u>
<u n="207" who="S0230">they got a puppy off of erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh yeah is that theirs to keep? actually the</u>
<u n="209" who="S0230">but it's gonna stop at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="210" who="S0198">oh okay he just gets the name <unclear/> have one that's his</u>
<u n="211" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0198">fair enough bet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is pleased about that gets to have a puppy but</u>
<u n="213" who="S0229" trans="overlap">can't leave one shut up indoors <unclear>though</unclear> can you?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0198">no no yeah she's not home enough to look after a dog is she?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0229" trans="overlap">have it to look after it I'll stop that straightaway</u>
<u n="216" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0230">it's when she said at the party last week oh did did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tell you we got a puppy? I said no she said yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got him you know one of his <trunc>pup</trunc> I said is it gonna stop at yours? cos it cos <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos if it comes to yours it'll end up at ours <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0229">no it won't</u>
<u n="220" who="S0230">she said no no no it's gonna stop at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="221" who="S0198">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll bring it down won't he?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0229" trans="overlap">I won't have it for a day not starting that cos then it'll be like day after day taking care of it and taking it out for walks</u>
<u n="223" who="S0198">ah it'd be lovely though</u>
<u n="224" who="S0229">I can think of better things to do than walk along that road and picking dog <unclear>shit</unclear> up behind me thank you very much</u>
<u n="225" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well you have to do that these days don't you?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0229">and whoever's got them let them have them but at this moment I don't want one</u>
<u n="227" who="S0198">no fine</u>
<u n="228" who="S0230">it's a a <unclear/> erm her dad come down</u>
<u n="229" who="S0198">yeah I saw him in the pictures yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0230" trans="overlap">her dad and erm her nan</u>
<u n="231" who="S0198">oh did she?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0230">yeah her nan always her nan always comes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0198">oh does she?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0230">one that one <unclear/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0198" trans="overlap">never met her</u>
<u n="238" who="S0230">oh she's lovely</u>
<u n="239" who="S0198">is it her mum's mum?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0230">yeah four children and they've all died</u>
<u n="241" who="S0198">I know how horrific</u>
<u n="242" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0198">how horrific <pause dur="short"/> imagine losing all your children how? various cancers and things?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0230">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="245" who="S0198">they were worried really it's a bit rife in her family isn't it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0198">must have some gene god forbid</u>
<u n="248" who="S0230">yet she's so healthy her nan</u>
<u n="249" who="S0198">her nan where's her dad grandad there? how old was he when he died?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0230">I don't know</u>
<u n="251" who="S0198">dear oh dear</u>
<u n="252" who="S0230">yeah she was there with her dad and her dad's girlfriend <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0198">oh yeah he's had her he's been with her for a long time now is it the same one?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0230">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0198">from the has he still got the fair down in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0198">yeah? that's where he lives</u>
<u n="258" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0198">nice they come up for the boy's birthday</u>
<u n="260" who="S0230">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was there he come straight from work so he was in <vocal desc="laugh"/> his dirty work clothes</u>
<u n="261" who="S0198">oh did he? oh bless him though I didn't even get him a card but I don't think he's used to it so I'm sure he doesn't miss it</u>
<u n="262" who="S0230">no him erm er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and her dad <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they had a game of bowls as well</u>
<u n="263" who="S0198">oh did they?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/> bowling I should say</u>
<u n="265" who="S0198">bowling yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0230"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won</u>
<u n="267" who="S0198">oh did he?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0230">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0198">did they put any money down?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0230">I don't know</u>
<u n="271" who="S0198">should have done</u>
<u n="272" who="S0230">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> her dad says yeah he cheated though he put the sides up every time he bowled <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0198">did he?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0230">no course he didn't</u>
<u n="275" who="S0198">no course not yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0198">just winding you up</u>
<u n="278" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0198">yeah ah good <unclear/> kids are there</u>
<u n="280" who="S0230" trans="overlap">he was very well organised he was much better organised than I thought he was gonna be</u>
<u n="281" who="S0198">ah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said they were really good <unclear/> easily</u>
<u n="282" who="S0230">yeah they they</u>
<u n="283" who="S0198"><unclear>he</unclear> hasn't reply since</u>
<u n="284" who="S0230">yeah the girl that <trunc>organi</trunc> was in charge of that <trunc>le</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s group she was really good with them</u>
<u n="285" who="S0198">yeah who are the girls? whose kids are they?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0230">erm I'm not sure</u>
<u n="287" who="S0198">why is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just not there? cos it was a school night or?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0230">cos she didn't want to go</u>
<u n="289" who="S0198">oh didn't she?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="291" who="S0198">ah she's getting a bit shy</u>
<u n="292" who="S0230">yeah well it's cos she don't know anybody</u>
<u n="293" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not that close to the</u>
<u n="294" who="S0230">and they'd be alright if if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was but obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna be with his schoolmates</u>
<u n="295" who="S0198" trans="overlap">friends yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0230" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0230">cos they get on really well at our place</u>
<u n="299" who="S0198">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah fair enough</u>
<u n="300" who="S0230">ah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0198">ah it's up to her I don't blame her I suppose <pause dur="short"/> normal enough</u>
<u n="302" who="S0229">what's up there? ain't no old stalls there is there?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0198">no dad all this stuff on here's just a rip-off or food which is still a rip-off touristy crap <pause dur="short"/> now now now now <pause dur="short"/> yeah got your dreads over there dad do you wanna ask for them back?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0229">ah they can keep them</u>
<u n="305" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0229">save me washing them</u>
<u n="307" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> don't really wash them do you? you've gotta get special stuff to put in them</u>
<u n="308" who="S0229">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what glue?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no they're held together with like beeswax I think actually <unclear/> dread wax I think beeswax you can do anyway <pause dur="long"/> great shorts on there <pause dur="short"/> we're at the youth <trunc>si</trunc>side aren't we?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0229">eh?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0198">all the youngsters</u>
<u n="312" who="S0230" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0198">I mean there is <pause dur="short"/> well it's nice that it's being used <pause dur="short"/> should have outdoor things to do</u>
<u n="314" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0198">it's free</u>
<u n="316" who="S0230" trans="overlap">did the <unclear/> get left here or?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0198">I wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> they must bring them from somewhere mustn't they?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0198">I kind of imagine so cos I mean that <unclear>cost</unclear> maybe you can bring your own <unclear/> I dunno</u>
<u n="320" who="S0230">well maybe</u>
<u n="321" who="S0198">yeah can't see a signpost anywhere</u>
<u n="322" who="S0229">be packed tonight and all won't you?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0230">yes I will have to won't I?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0198">that'll be a hard task no doubt <pause dur="short"/> mark my words you haven't done that before have you? packed a suitcase usual bits just don't forget your pillow</u>
<u n="325" who="S0229">still pack them all <unclear/> sheets and <unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0198"><unclear>thirsty</unclear> are you a bit?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0229"><unclear/> can tell</u>
<u n="328" who="S0230" trans="overlap">I'll I'll have to have a look exactly what's in the van I'm not sure in the way of bedding</u>
<u n="329" who="S0198">yeah I mean oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not your van is it so usually comes with some stuff do they?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0230" trans="overlap">yeah normally comes with bedding</u>
<u n="331" who="S0229">I gone up there I <unclear>take</unclear> my sheets with me</u>
<u n="332" who="S0198">years since I slept in a caravan</u>
<u n="333" who="S0230">it looks erm it's called a a Windborne and I'm sure that's what ours one was called</u>
<u n="334" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="335" who="S0230">be <unclear/> if it is our old one innit and they and they rent it out</u>
<u n="336" who="S0229">I hope not</u>
<u n="337" who="S0230">why?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0229">bloody cold in there at night</u>
<u n="339" who="S0230">well they're all bloody cold you don't think it's gonna be any different do you?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0229">might not be any heat on went <unclear>we</unclear> left some heaters in there didn't we?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0198">you left heaters in there?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0198">and all that bedding and that didn't you?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0198">let's not start that story again</u>
<u n="346" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0198">I told you so</u>
<u n="348" who="S0229">that was a waste of seventeen grand</u>
<u n="349" who="S0230">well we had a few stays in it we used it more than anybody else</u>
<u n="350" who="S0198">seventeen grand's worth?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0230">not well no but</u>
<u n="352" who="S0229">imagine the little six berth we could have had for that at <anon type="place"/> <unclear>still be</unclear> there <pause dur="short"/> anyway don't talk about that it'll only wind me up</u>
<u n="353" who="S0198" trans="overlap">wind you up eh dad?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0230">done that on purpose haven't you?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="356" who="S0230">yes you have <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0198">you're the one that was talking about caravans</u>
<u n="358" who="S0229">only got <unclear/> cornet</u>
<u n="359" who="S0198">cornet cornet's an instrument isn't it?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0229" trans="overlap">that one there <pause dur="short"/>  come on then we gonna mooch back or what?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0198" trans="overlap">Cornetto yeah we get</u>
<u n="362" who="S0229" trans="overlap">something to do not get bored sitting there</u>
<u n="363" who="S0198" trans="overlap">go back what are you doing?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0229">yeah getting bored</u>
<u n="365" who="S0198">I'm supposed to do some we've gotta cook dinner yet at some point</u>
<u n="366" who="S0229" trans="overlap">it's four o'clock</u>
<u n="367" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll be wondering where I am there goes my work for the day though have to be super-productive tomorrow Monday's gonna come round too quickly at least I get four days off eh?</u>
<u n="368" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0229">can relax then darling can't you?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0198">no no relaxing</u>
<u n="371" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear>come on</unclear> then <unclear/> brain</u>
<u n="372" who="S0230">so every week it's Thursday Friday Saturday Sunday it's good innit?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0198">yeah Monday to Wednesday I do <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> only does</u>
<u n="374" who="S0230" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does four does he?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0198">yeah but he only does an hour on erm Wednesday and one hour on Friday</u>
<u n="376" who="S0230">oh</u>
<u n="377" who="S0198">whereas on a Wednesday I do three hours I actually do an hour more than him I think overall</u>
<u n="378" who="S0230">have you made any friends yet on <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I mean we're friendly with some of the I mean we're friendly with the people on out course we all we don't always er do exactly the same thing but I mean we're such a small group that to an <trunc>ext</trunc> there's always someone that you know but I mean yeah there's an American girl there's only and the one English girl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they seem nice probably go out for something to eat or whatever but it's hard to correlate with people everyone's a bit older so everyone's kind of got lives and keeping to themselves a little bit more</u>
<u n="380" who="S0230">they're all sort of your age</u>
<u n="381" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and all busy and people some of them have got jobs and stuff as well no we're er a couple of them are younger <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> girl they're both like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just finished her undergrad at Chichester so she she's she was only twenty-one in erm August I think? and she's half Malaysian as well so she's a tiny little thing she looks really young <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s only twenty-two she's American not sure about the Dutch girl she's moody she doesn't talk to anyone the Pakistani guy I think he's probably our age and yeah the others are between twenty-five and thirty-five twenty-five and thirty so yeah mixed group definitely anyway</u>
<u n="382" who="S0229">ah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0230">can you see <unclear>any</unclear> bins?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0229">yeah where's the bin?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0198">we've got one just down there I think I mean there's bins down here ah they're a bit massive though aren't they? save <unclear/> give it here you've got a talking <unclear/> for a moment there haven't you? hang on let me pause it</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="386" who="S0198">didn't realise I oh I've got to make my money</u>
<u n="387" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0198">doesn't matter what you say does it? you've just gotta say it</u>
<u n="389" who="S0229"><unclear>could have</unclear> been Elvis</u>
<u n="390" who="S0198">yeah taking you back in time eh dad to when you was twenty-seven <vocal desc="laugh"/> fifties how old are you? hundred</u>
<u n="391" who="S0229" trans="overlap">thirty-one</u>
<u n="392" who="S0198">thirty-one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0229"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0198">no one's thirty-one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how old's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? thirty?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0198">thirty-one in March</u>
<u n="397" who="S0229">if it weren't for my leg I'd be back out at work you know that?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="399" who="S0229">without a doubt</u>
<u n="400" who="S0230">you say that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> your leg hasn't been playing up for the last nine years and that's how long you've been out of work <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> don't do an <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now for Christ sake</u>
<u n="402" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0198">has it been nine years? I suppose it has hasn't it? is that when you moved to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0230">well we've been we've been back over seven years seven years in May wasn't it? and we was in <anon type="place"/> for a a year</u>
<u n="405" who="S0198" trans="overlap">god seven years</u>
<u n="406" who="S0230">so it was <unclear/> uh well eight and a half years</u>
<u n="407" who="S0198">bloody hell</u>
<u n="408" who="S0230">and dad actually sort of finished work the January before we went so it'll be nine years this January</u>
<u n="409" who="S0198">nine years <vocal desc="laugh"/> nine years this January that's alright it's your retirement</u>
<u n="410" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0198">you've been on and off yourself mum but you've had <unclear>nan</unclear> in between all that of course</u>
<u n="412" who="S0230">yeah <unclear/> I really had <unclear/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> not quite the same</u>
<u n="414" who="S0230">same no</u>
<u n="415" who="S0198">people with their bloody shirts off it's not that warm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0230">no it's not now is it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0198">now the sun's gone down</u>
<u n="418" who="S0230">sun's gone behind that</u>
<u n="419" who="S0229" trans="overlap">that's nice now just right just right nice and cool</u>
<u n="420" who="S0198">is that how you like it dad?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear/> being there now I'm telling you</u>
<u n="422" who="S0198">might have a</u>
<u n="423" who="S0229">me and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'d go straight in there</u>
<u n="424" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would I know that not so sure about you dad</u>
<u n="425" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0229">I bloody would</u>
<u n="427" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0198">would you?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0229"><unclear>right there</unclear> Speedy Gonzalez</u>
<u n="430" who="S0198">that's what you need dad that'll be the next step won't it?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0229">oh a big one of them's <unclear/> up</u>
<u n="432" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0229">one of them for next <unclear/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0198">ah they all want a sleep she looks quite comfortable doesn't she?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear/> boozers to carry on <unclear/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0198">oh no</u>
<u n="438" who="S0229">on the way home saves driving don't it?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0198">you'll be one of those you read about in the paper goes off goes off the pier front half gatted up</u>
<u n="440" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0198">get stuck in accelerate</u>
<u n="442" who="S0229">I used to do all that <unclear>daughter</unclear></u>
<u n="443" who="S0198">I know you did need all the kids like it don't they? gonna sit here and watch it it's all er what are those shows called? the Bob the Builder and whatever</u>
<u n="444" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to love that didn't he?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0230"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0229"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0198">he used to get his screwdriver over dad's bits and pretend to poke it and do stuff on it</u>
<u n="452" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0198">they grow so quickly so fast don't they? it's a shame he's</u>
<u n="454" who="S0230">got up this morning and come up to you I think I've grown overnight again mum nan</u>
<u n="455" who="S0198">oh did he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0230">yeah he says let's have a measure</u>
<u n="457" who="S0198">is that what he says?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0230">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0198">you do a good impression of him</u>
<u n="460" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> er he is growing so fast</u>
<u n="462" who="S0230" trans="overlap">I I do honestly think in another two years time <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's gonna be as tall as me if not taller</u>
<u n="463" who="S0198" trans="overlap">as tall as you or taller yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0230">I'll have a ten-year-old grandson taller than me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0198">cor I hope he doesn't get too tall</u>
<u n="466" who="S0230">I think he's gonna I think he's gonna get bigger than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0230">and he'll end up about six foot four six foot five <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0198">bloody hell</u>
<u n="470" who="S0229">he still holds my hand when I take him to school <unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="472" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0198">he's still a little one isn't he? he's kind of soft really in some ways <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't he?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0230" trans="overlap">oh he is he is he is quite erm soft as well</u>
<u n="475" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well yeah it's having his grandad baby him and being an only child</u>
<u n="476" who="S0230">and being an only child as well probably</u>
<u n="477" who="S0198">having a mum and dad on and off all the time</u>
<u n="478" who="S0229">yeah bloody good job we are there</u>
<u n="479" who="S0230">I think it's <trunc>accept</trunc>accepted now that's permanently off</u>
<u n="480" who="S0198">oh yeah I don't think they'll go down that route again</u>
<u n="481" who="S0229">nah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0198">tried it that one last time</u>
<u n="483" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="484" who="S0198">I think they get moments of affection for their shared over <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably spares it but</u>
<u n="485" who="S0230">you never know she might marry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she really likes him</u>
<u n="487" who="S0230">yeah I know</u>
<u n="488" who="S0198">she's just got to not be too divvy and lose him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0198">he's gotta put up with her yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear/> round that way</u>
<u n="492" who="S0198">go round that way yeah he might <unclear/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0230">and I think he <unclear>isn't exactly</unclear> short of a few bob either</u>
<u n="494" who="S0198">no that's probably quite appealing</u>
<u n="495" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0198">but you'd think he'd want his own kiddies wouldn't you? but she swears she's not gonna have any more</u>
<u n="497" who="S0230">perhaps he don't</u>
<u n="498" who="S0198">it's true</u>
<u n="499" who="S0229">well if he does they're not coming down mine to bloody look after I'll stick to my little mate and that'll be it for me</u>
<u n="500" who="S0198">yeah I don't think she'd be expecting you to take in someone else's baby <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear/> either</u>
<u n="502" who="S0198">go to his <trunc>ow</trunc> other grandparents</u>
<u n="503" who="S0229">no favours</u>
<u n="504" who="S0198">if anything happens little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s getting old enough for it not to correlate</u>
<u n="505" who="S0229"><unclear/> I'm afraid</u>
<u n="506" who="S0198">I know I don't think she'd ever ask you to look after <vocal desc="laugh"/> someone else's baby different giving her started getting <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in when he was what six seven months or something isn't he?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0230">well since we moved there wasn't he?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0198">yeah did dad even change a nappy or two or was that something I made up?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0230">oh no he used to change his nappies and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will still get him to</u>
<u n="510" who="S0198" trans="overlap">wipe his bum I know that's disgusting</u>
<u n="511" who="S0230">nobody else does for him</u>
<u n="512" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no of course not <pause dur="short"/> boys are funny like that aren't they? they <trunc>ge</trunc> I remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still asking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do it until he was like way <trunc>bef</trunc> way beyond his mum or you doing it</u>
<u n="513" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0198">it's funny boys would even <trunc>as</trunc> like I don't think girls even want you to</u>
<u n="515" who="S0230">no they wouldn't</u>
<u n="516" who="S0198">definitely something different there between the sexes we're like no we can do</u>
<u n="517" who="S0230">yeah <unclear>we</unclear> never wiped any of your bums or changed any of your nappies</u>
<u n="518" who="S0198">ah no it's what being a grandparent's about grandfather anyway <pause dur="short"/> do the things you missed out on or whatever</u>
<u n="519" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="520" who="S0198">no his <unclear>favourites</unclear> he didn't do anyone else's though did he? it's not like he did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s or</u>
<u n="521" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="522" who="S0198">or any other grandkids</u>
<u n="523" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="524" who="S0198">only <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0230">but then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has spent a considerable amount of time up <unclear>here</unclear></u>
<u n="526" who="S0229">I've had him since he were a baby haven't I? even before he started crawling he before he crawled he used to <unclear/> to grab hold of me <unclear/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0198">he used to drag himself across <unclear/> with one arm didn't he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0230">his arm <unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0229">his mum'd come and pick him up he wouldn't let go of me would he dear?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="531" who="S0198">lovely little boy but yeah ah see if <unclear/> wanna have a sleepover never know I might change my mind <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0230">yeah so don't go making any arrangements</u>
<u n="533" who="S0198">oh right well I need to make arrangements don't I? oh me making arrangements with friends or with the children?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0229">the children</u>
<u n="535" who="S0230" trans="overlap">the children</u>
<u n="536" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="537" who="S0230">well not now in case you change your mind</u>
<u n="538" who="S0198">oh yeah but if I leave it too late they won't might have plans won't they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0230">oh I doubt it</u>
<u n="540" who="S0198">probably not I'll give it another week I'll think about it but I don't know how else I will <unclear/> and cos I missed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and I'm gonna miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday so I feel like I should do something with them while I'm home but I suppose they really probably don't care they're not it's not really registered on their radar is it?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="542" who="S0198">remember where we're parked dad?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0198">where are we crossing then? this one or the next one?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0229">this one right here <unclear>innit</unclear>?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0198">yeah I think so testing you that's all</u>
<u n="547" who="S0229">near the <anon type="place"/> daughter</u>
<u n="548" who="S0198">daughter</u>
<u n="549" who="S0229">it's clear and all innit?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0198">you wanna look right is it clear?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0229">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0198">oh <pause dur="short"/> alright make a point mum go as slowly as you can <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0230">I wasn't</u>
<u n="554" who="S0198">with those little legs of yours <pause dur="short"/> it's not Best Western is it? no it's a that's a different chain isn't it? Travelodge you stayed in <pause dur="short"/> like to go to Bruges myself</u>
<u n="555" who="S0229">yeah we'll have to go there together</u>
<u n="556" who="S0198">eat some of their food that brie baguette</u>
<u n="557" who="S0229"><unclear/> not expensive to go there either</u>
<u n="558" who="S0230">the brie baguette was at Antwerp I'm sure <unclear/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0198" trans="overlap">ah I'm sure Bruges has something</u>
<u n="560" who="S0230" trans="overlap">just as nice</u>
<u n="561" who="S0198"><trunc>m</trunc>measurable yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I suppose if erm find a cheap deal in a guesthouse does the ferry cost you pay for the do you pay per passenger on the ferry or just for the car?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0230">just just for the car and two people</u>
<u n="563" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="564" who="S0230">whether it'd be more for three people</u>
<u n="565" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it'd be a little more for three or four people I suppose</u>
<u n="566" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0198">but maybe nothing too dramatic something manageable I would have thought</u>
<u n="568" who="S0230">yeah I mean you <unclear>can go</unclear> for sixty something pound weren't it for the car ferry?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0198">and that's return isn't it?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0198">yeah so compared to catching a plane or whatnot anywhere cos I mean sixty quid just for one person on a cheap flight isn't it?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0230">yeah well it cost us more than that for the ferry to Isle of Wight</u>
<u n="573" who="S0198">oh you said yeah well isn't that stupid?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0229">well we've gotta go left daughter</u>
<u n="575" who="S0198">I wonder how long did the ferry take?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0230">two hours</u>
<u n="577" who="S0198">oh that guy just jumped out didn't he?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0230"><unclear/> Dunkirk</u>
<u n="579" who="S0229">nearly two hours</u>
<u n="580" who="S0198">yeah two hours long enough then</u>
<u n="581" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0198">and then you gained an hour there and then lost it on the way home is that right?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0230">no it's the other way round</u>
<u n="584" who="S0229">other way round</u>
<u n="585" who="S0230">oh yeah no no gained it there</u>
<u n="586" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah you went yeah you yeah you know what I mean</u>
<u n="587" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0198">yeah sorry I guess you lose an hour actually going there and then gain it coming back</u>
<u n="589" who="S0229">do we wanna stay left dear?</u>
<u n="590" who="S0198">yeah I mean you wanna take whatever left you can take dad this one by the looks of it</u>
<u n="591" who="S0229">that's a dead end I think darling that's a dead end</u>
<u n="592" who="S0230">no not this the next one</u>
<u n="593" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah that</u>
<u n="594" who="S0230"><unclear/> coming out</u>
<u n="595" who="S0198">you</u>
<u n="596" who="S0229">I don't think we can go up there</u>
<u n="597" who="S0198">you can someone just went up there we did this last time cos of these controlled zone signs you kept saying we can't go up there you bloody go up there</u>
<u n="598" who="S0229">oh yes we can now I know yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0198">do you remember? and we ended up driving all the way down</u>
<u n="600" who="S0229">oh the Costa Brava</u>
<u n="601" who="S0198">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0229">we're there to cushion it</u>
<u n="603" who="S0198">this is the street you parked on originally</u>
<u n="604" who="S0229">yeah <pause dur="short"/> all day overnight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0230">that erm place next to the <anon type="place"/> it is gonna be a car wash you know that was the garage that</u>
<u n="606" who="S0229">oh yeah yeah I thought it was</u>
<u n="607" who="S0198">I didn't know if you were talking to me or not there</u>
<u n="608" who="S0229">yeah oh yeah it's where we parked daughter weren't it?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0198"><trunc>ss</trunc> it's what I said dad</u>
<u n="610" who="S0229">I know you did</u>
<u n="611" who="S0198">go straight up</u>
<u n="612" who="S0229">we can't it's a dead end</u>
<u n="613" who="S0230">this is the dead end that's where you</u>
<u n="614" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no you can take a left up there can't you? what is that a dead end? why can I see cars and that up there? alright then take the next right</u>
<u n="615" who="S0230">you can't go straight up</u>
<u n="616" who="S0198">oh yeah yeah I see I see I see</u>
<u n="617" who="S0229">well you've gotta go right down here now ain't we?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0198">yeah take the next right if you can</u>
<u n="619" who="S0229">okey-dokey</u>
<u n="620" who="S0198">lemon and pokey</u>
<u n="621" who="S0229">we'll get in there don't worry</u>
<u n="622" who="S0230">pig in a pokey</u>
<u n="623" who="S0198">is it pig in a pokey?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0198">okey-dokey pig in a pokey</u>
<u n="626" who="S0230">okey-dokey pig in a pokey</u>
<u n="627" who="S0229">look at the little blonde haired girls look</u>
<u n="628" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0198">yeah cause it's pig and pokey cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> dad read some er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> read something this morning erm like you know like bric-a-brac and what you just said a pig in a pokey and</u>
<u n="630" who="S0230" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0198">odds and sods all this kind of thing there's a reason like we would never do it the other way round and it's something to do with the vowel sounds</u>
<u n="632" who="S0230">ah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0198">so it and ah pig and poke would make more sense than poke and pig it just doesn't sound right does it?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0230">no</u>
<u n="635" who="S0198">because we do the <trunc>ip</trunc> I think there's something about the <trunc>ce</trunc>certain vowel before another vowel</u>
<u n="636" who="S0230">ah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0198">I'm can't sure bric and brac pig and poke yeah I guess it's the short vowel before the long vowel maybe it just rhymes better to us so er yeah that's what we do there's are loads of them on there I can't remember them all now oh can't wait to have that wee again</u>
<u n="638" who="S0230"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0198">got to park on the just park on the yellow lines at the end of the road dad <unclear>easiest</unclear> place</u>
<u n="640" who="S0229" trans="overlap">I'm going to if there's <unclear>any</unclear> space I'll park on the corner we can walk down</u>
<u n="641" who="S0198">it's not far</u>
<u n="642" who="S0229">no no I know darling</u>
<u n="643" who="S0198">oh look at that Jeep</u>
<u n="644" who="S0229">yeah pukka ain't it?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0198">those tyres on it where are you going?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="647" who="S0198">yeah mad hatter that's what it is when we first came into here yeah thingy was fine wasn't it in Caffè Nero the chain?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0229">go on mate you can go now that's my boy</u>
<u n="651" who="S0198"><unclear/> cream on the coast that's good</u>
<u n="652" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0198">happy happy days glad I did that bit of couple of towels I washed today now hopefully they'll dry but they're not having any <unclear/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0229">where are we going straight over daughter?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0198">yeah straight up not having any direct sunlight definitely affects it</u>
<u n="656" who="S0230">do you put them on the balcony?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0198">but then it doesn't get any sunlight that side the opposite houses opposite us get the sunlight it's fine cos our back rooms get the light which in the winter is will be warming more warming</u>
<u n="660" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0198">than the bedroom but erm yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0230">are them sort of jeans still fashionable? with all the rips and tears</u>
<u n="663" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh no I mean it they're rare now it depends on the person I don't think so they were coming back a little bit in Korea and er sometimes what happens in Korea you'll see coming on here I think I don't know why just <unclear>just wear</unclear> fashion whatever but I mean I think they look terrible what's that dad?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0229">buy just buy an ordinary pair <unclear/> a hole in them</u>
<u n="665" who="S0198">I know well why would you wanna pay money on something that's already got holes in it? just wait until you've worn through a normal pair</u>
<u n="666" who="S0229">it's like with that <unclear/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's what I do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0229">buy these jeans and half the legs are missing</u>
<u n="669" who="S0198">I think you can take this left dad</u>
<u n="670" who="S0229">yeah you're right I remember doing it last time</u>
<u n="671" who="S0198">saves going back past through the the crescent</u>
<u n="672" who="S0229">roundabout and all that shite</u>
<u n="673" who="S0198">thing is can you enter my road this way? I do forget</u>
<u n="674" who="S0229">then you go right innit?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0198">yeah it's the first right sometimes it's no entry</u>
<u n="676" who="S0229" trans="overlap">this one or the next one?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0198">no this one this one <pause dur="short"/> go past it now I guess we didn't have to come round this way as just could of <pause dur="short"/> and then it's left and then right yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0198">oh a mattress</u>
<u n="680" who="S0229">oh look at that could have saved us all money there darling</u>
<u n="681" who="S0198">see has the rubbish man been down here? no er I dunno it's hard to tell with private houses cos they keep keep their rubbish in the garden you can tell when it's a flat cos it's piled high outside</u>
<u n="682" who="S0230">mm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0198">yeah down <anon type="place"/> and left down <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0229">left this bit here</u>
<u n="685" who="S0198">yeah that's our road</u>
<u n="686" who="S0229">or there</u>
<u n="687" who="S0198">but I mean our bin day is not meant to be until Monday so I can only assume that it won't happen until just park here dad</u>
<u n="688" who="S0229">right I've gotta back up now</u>
<u n="689" who="S0198">I assume the easiest the day won't be till Monday</u>
<u n="690" who="S0229" trans="overlap">your <unclear>mirror</unclear> ain't out dear</u>
<u n="691" who="S0230">you wanna park on the right</u>
<u n="692" who="S0198">no he can park this side</u>
<u n="693" who="S0229" trans="overlap">no I can park here</u>
<u n="694" who="S0198">he's gone on yellow lines so it doesn't matter does it?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0230">ah yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0198">either or on yellow lines</u>
<u n="697" who="S0230">either either neither neither</u>
<u n="698" who="S0198">done</u>
<u n="699" who="S0230">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0229">put the badge in</u>
<u n="701" who="S0198">put the badge in and we're done home</u>
<u n="702" who="S0230">and it is twenty past four</u>
<u n="703" who="S0229">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
