<text id="SDN3">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:32:30</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0428 S0432</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>train to Lancaster</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Trip to Lancaster, visit, visiting the coast, cockle disaster, fish and chips, visiting universities, masters, writing a dissertation, careers, home life, family, redundancy, </topics>
		<activity>Train trip to Lancaster</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0428">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Eastern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0432">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>White British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands/ East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Gamlingay, Cambridgeshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Chinese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0432"><event desc="sound of train"/> <unclear>from each</unclear></u>
<u n="2" who="S0428">erm so it's ten minutes from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> well just yeah just over fifteen</u>
<u n="3" who="S0432">then get a right turn</u>
<u n="4" who="S0428">but we're going north</u>
<u n="5" who="S0432">oh they're about like between ten and twenty minutes apart so it's not too bad</u>
<u n="6" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've never been to any of these places</u>
<u n="7" who="S0432">no I haven't oh it's about half an hour to the next one though isn't it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0428">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="9" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0428">shall we have a look at photos of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't I've I have no idea in my head what I think it's going to look like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0428">yeah no I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it looked really pretty</u>
<u n="13" who="S0432">yeah I still didn't think it is where it is <pause dur="short"/> for some reason I had I thought it was like Midland like in the middle and like not as far north</u>
<u n="14" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no I <pause dur="short"/> yeah I thought it was the other side of I don't really know where I thought it was actually because I</u>
<u n="15" who="S0432">I didn't think it was like so near the coast</u>
<u n="16" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wonder how big it is?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0432">yeah I dunno</u>
<u n="18" who="S0428">but it looks like really pretty this one <pause dur="short"/> we will have to go to the castle like the hills is it?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like <pause dur="short"/> it makes you feel like Sound of Music or something</u>
<u n="20" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0432">it's just like the mountains</u>
<u n="22" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <event desc="sound of train announcement"/> yeah is it actually on the sea? <event desc="sound of train announcement"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0432">I don't think so I think it's <pause dur="short"/> I only think it's like fifteen minutes by car if that so I don't think you might be able to see it the real sea from</u>
<u n="24" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> oh I see so it's a little bit like <unclear/> I think that I need to I don't have the Google app so I have to look on here <pause dur="short"/> guess I need to download the Google app</u>
<u n="25" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0432">well it's it was fifteen minutes from to <anon type="place"/> so I don't know if that's like you know I don't know if that was the closest <pause dur="short"/> type place <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what's? do you know what's at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0432">no no idea I think that was just the biggest place on <trunc>th</trunc> on the <pause dur="short"/> on that</u>
<u n="29" who="S0428" trans="overlap">on the thing so yeah it's got one of these kind of</u>
<u n="30" who="S0432">oh yeah so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="place"/> is like</u>
<u n="31" who="S0428">here</u>
<u n="32" who="S0432">yeah there</u>
<u n="33" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0432">so I don't know if that's the closest beach I don't know</u>
<u n="35" who="S0428">isn't the <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> did? wasn't there like erm like ages ago like a disaster at <anon type="place"/> of like erm like the people that were collecting cockles?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0432">oh was there? I don't know</u>
<u n="37" who="S0428">and they got <pause dur="short"/> am I totally making this up?</u>
<u n="38" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0428">like it's a place where you can collect cockles and they were like workers and they all got swept out to sea</u>
<u n="40" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="41" who="S0428">was it <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh no <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0428"><anon type="place"/> oh no</u>
<u n="44" who="S0432">is it?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why I'm looking at the map I wanted to look at pictures <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="47" who="S0432">I don't I don't like what do cockles taste nice?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0428" trans="overlap">do <pause dur="short"/> are they? <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know</u>
<u n="49" who="S0432" trans="overlap">they they sell them in the in <anon type="place"/> in the Co-op in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0428">in the Co-op?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0432">in the Co-op by the pub in like little jars and I was like what why do people eat them?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh really <pause dur="short"/> because I don't really know what they look like</u>
<u n="53" who="S0432">they're like really <pause dur="short"/> I don't know they're just like small shrimp like in small shells I think</u>
<u n="54" who="S0428">are they like because erm well maybe they kind of like <unclear>bonvali</unclear> in Italian because they that's really nice oh look it's really pretty the beach</u>
<u n="55" who="S0432">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0428">maybe it was at <anon type="place"/> bay</u>
<u n="57" who="S0432">I know there was I don't know I don't know if it was oysters there was somewhere where they stopped that's where like oysters first came from in England or something but I mean that was like down in Cornwall way</u>
<u n="58" who="S0428" trans="overlap">look <pause dur="short"/> oh okay yeah look</u>
<u n="59" who="S0432">so I'm thinking of something totally different</u>
<u n="60" who="S0428">here's yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0428">yeah no they are nice in pasta like but I'm not sure if I'd just want to eat them on their own</u>
<u n="63" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah like yeah <pause dur="short"/> snack on them</u>
<u n="64" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0428">yeah have a snack <vocal desc="laugh"/> let's have a look</u>
<u n="66" who="S0432">I don't know yet how like how many of them she sells but I can't imagine it's a lot</u>
<u n="67" who="S0428">no are they fresh?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0432">I don't know well some of the jars I'm pretty sure have been there for a while <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0428">so they're like so you buy the jar?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0432">I think they're like two pounds for a jar like that big</u>
<u n="71" who="S0428">and they come in the shells? or</u>
<u n="72" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0428">yeah here we go the two thousand and four Morecombe Bay cockling</u>
<u n="74" who="S0432">is that like the actual?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0428">the cockle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0432">it's a cockle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0428">have you never heard of that? oh well we won't go cockling then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we'll just go for fish and chips</u>
<u n="79" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0432">we are going to be like having an Indian on Wednesday with fish and chips on Thursday maybe we should have something else</u>
<u n="81" who="S0428" trans="overlap">Thursday <pause dur="short"/> international yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0432">Italian tonight</u>
<u n="83" who="S0428">international cuisine we've got the five star Michelin restaurant on Tuesday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0432">did you bring your ball gown? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I wonder what</u>
<u n="86" who="S0432">I'd laugh if we actually did and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like I thought you were joking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we never joke</u>
<u n="88" who="S0432">no we're always being serious <pause dur="short"/> serious people</u>
<u n="89" who="S0428">I looked at the map and I think the erm I think the Holiday Inn is really central like really near the station you know so when we get there we can just</u>
<u n="90" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh is it? <pause dur="short"/> I've got a map actually I don't I don't know whether it's worth getting a taxi or not</u>
<u n="91" who="S0428">I think we can walk yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0432">ah it's quite actually I should probably get it out because it's er we'll probably need it won't we?</u>
<u n="93" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah spot on Tuesday spot on man I've locked it up</u>
<u n="94" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh right cool nice one</u>
<u n="95" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah no problem</u>
<u n="96" who="S0432">I'll wait until he's <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0432">I don't know why I put them at the bottom though? well they're not they're like in the middle</u>
<u n="99" who="S0428">I always do that <vocal desc="laugh"/> like the stuff you need</u>
<u n="100" who="S0432">yeah I will just be able to see my face</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="101" who="S0428">I need to eat when we when we get there we can like find oh because of the meeting finishes at five we could have er maybe a quick like like half an hour walk around <anon type="place"/> it'd be nice to stretch our legs</u>
<u n="102" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely because we've been sat down for a long time</u>
<u n="103" who="S0428">oh like just like a normal day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I would like <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know what everything each piece was so I like highlighted the bits of information <unclear>geek</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so like there's the station <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah six minute walk</u>
<u n="105" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we can do that</u>
<u n="106" who="S0432">so that's fine and it's quite a while to the <pause dur="short"/> quite a way to the <pause dur="short"/> uni</u>
<u n="107" who="S0428">yeah I think we're going to have to get a taxi every day</u>
<u n="108" who="S0432">yeah or the <trunc>bu</trunc> I think you can get a bus</u>
<u n="109" who="S0428">yeah I think</u>
<u n="110" who="S0432">yeah by bus</u>
<u n="111" who="S0428">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said we'll just like after three of us have paid for like paid for a bus we might as well just get a taxi</u>
<u n="112" who="S0432">might as well get a taxi that's true actually</u>
<u n="113" who="S0428">a limousine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0432">definitely a limousine with champagne</u>
<u n="115" who="S0428">that's the that's the uni</u>
<u n="116" who="S0432">that's the uni map I printed off that one and I made that one</u>
<u n="117" who="S0428">oh okay</u>
<u n="118" who="S0432"><unclear/> but that's where the bus takes us if you do get out and that's where we need to be</u>
<u n="119" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yes I was like oh <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> it's quite big</u>
<u n="120" who="S0432">yeah it is isn't it? like it's got like a proper like driveway going in well a road even like separate little road set I was like it's massive <pause dur="short"/> but then I think the uni of <anon type="place"/> is like that <pause dur="short"/> whereas <anon type="place"/> because it was like a city campus and it was like all all over <pause dur="short"/> whereas that's all like one <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0428" trans="overlap">wow <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> all dotted around <pause dur="short"/> yeah <anon type="place"/> uni was a campus</u>
<u n="122" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0428">but there was it wasn't it wasn't it wasn't that big really</u>
<u n="124" who="S0432">no I don't remember there being like roads when I went to it</u>
<u n="125" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0432">like my erm <pause dur="short"/> friend went to uni of <anon type="place"/> to do Spanish and <pause dur="short"/> english I think and she left after about three weeks because one because Spanish wasn't actually like learning Spanish it was more like English lit but for Spanish if that makes sense</u>
<u n="127" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="128" who="S0432">yeah so they were just like studying plays and stuff and that's not really what she wanted to do erm <pause dur="short"/> and also because cos it was a campus and she was living on campus she couldn't like she never left like the whole three weeks you can and like <pause dur="short"/> and like other people had said like you can just get so like lost because there's like a supermarket there there's like everything you need on campus you don't actually need to leave</u>
<u n="129" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lost <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> is a bit like that it's quite weird</u>
<u n="130" who="S0432">yeah I was like I never actually knew of that one because I wanted to go to uni of <anon type="place"/> I just didn't get in and in and in the end I was actually quite glad that I didn't <pause dur="short"/> well only from like what people have said obviously a lot of people love it it is it is an amazing campus <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0428">yeah I've never been to the uni there</u>
<u n="132" who="S0432">it is really nice</u>
<u n="133" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0432">erm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0428">I don't I don't think you really put much thought into the course when you're choosing that I didn't realise like I didn't look at the courses and compare them and think oh I'd much prefer to do this than that</u>
<u n="136" who="S0432">no I didn't</u>
<u n="137" who="S0428">but I think when I went round to look I went when I went round looking at them <pause dur="short"/> some of them felt more old fashioned and kind of looked really looked <unclear/> I was like oh I'm not sure that's really for me</u>
<u n="138" who="S0432">yeah it's just I've they say like when you're when you look round them you just get a feeling as soon as you're there like this is the one <pause dur="short"/> but then don't that's like the atmosphere rather than the course and you do have to think about the course as well because that's obviously going to make such a difference</u>
<u n="139" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I really wanted to go to uni by the sea</u>
<u n="140" who="S0432">oh did you?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0428">so I applied to like all the unis on the coast like erm I applied to <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> like <anon type="place"/> which is quite close but then I ended up at <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> a few people went to <anon type="place"/> that I know and they always posted photos like even in the winter like we're just on the beach</u>
<u n="143" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0432">they had like coats and scarves and stuff but it just it's it is it was nice I only had like four choices though to do Spanish and Chinese</u>
<u n="145" who="S0428">I bet there weren't many at all <unclear>were there?</unclear></u>
<u n="146" who="S0432">there was five but one of them was at <anon type="place"/> and I didn't want to go there <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then there was like <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and then <anon type="place"/> so I didn't really have much choice and then I because I'm <trunc>f</trunc> like I know <anon type="place"/> anyway so <pause dur="short"/> might as well I've got family there and stuff I knew I kind of like ignored <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> so I just decided between those two <pause dur="short"/> but like I don't <pause dur="short"/> I remember sitting in like my friend's living room with like thousands of like prospectuses like just looking through them all not knowing where to go and what I wanted to do what was like what you needed to like prioritise</u>
<u n="147" who="S0428" trans="overlap">you wanted to go <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah what <pause dur="short"/> no I had not got a clue</u>
<u n="148" who="S0432">no</u>
<u n="149" who="S0428">and everyone was like it's your decision like yeah but</u>
<u n="150" who="S0432">yeah I don't know how to make that decision and we were in the end we were like let's all just put them in the middle one of us picks one and we all just do that and we'll just go there and do the same course <vocal desc="laugh"/> because we had no idea <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> well a lot of my friends erm <pause dur="short"/> most of them didn't go and then I think there's like six of us <pause dur="short"/> seven? six or seven of us that did go and only three of us actually <trunc>con</trunc>continued with it most of them like dropped out in like the first term</u>
<u n="151" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> really <pause dur="short"/> dropped out <pause dur="short"/> oh just didn't like it</u>
<u n="152" who="S0432">and I was like maybe I should drop out <vocal desc="laugh"/> just because everyone else has <unclear></unclear> their course you are like <unclear/> it's so weird</u>
<u n="153" who="S0428">I wanted to do a gap year erm but it I I was the last year that got in on the cheap fees and if I did a gap year I'd have to have paid so so I was kind of the whole time I was like oh it's fine I'm going to go away then after a year I'll like think about it and then it was like oh no I'm going to pay more so <vocal desc="laugh"/> quickly put in an application</u>
<u n="154" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh were you? <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought about a gap year but then I just had <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to do it with one of my friends but she wanted to go to uni and I didn't really have much money to be honest like I think I thought about it too late I didn't I couldn't save I didn't want to work I just wanted to travel so it wouldn't have worked <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's my other like I had no money and I was like I'm going to have to work in England for six months and then travel for six months or like <vocal desc="laugh"/> actually I just I don't want to do that</u>
<u n="156" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I mean I could've carried on working in the hospital because that is quite good money</u>
<u n="157" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0432">so I'd probably I probably could've done my six month work six months travelling but in the end I just don't think I would've got back into like studying after that</u>
<u n="159" who="S0428">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0432">I'd be like oh let's just keep travelling</u>
<u n="161" who="S0428">it is really hard when you like stop studying and start again</u>
<u n="162" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0428">I really <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0432"><unclear/> and even in the year <unclear/> studying</u>
<u n="165" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0432">so you aren't completely like out of habit <pause dur="long"/> do you think you will do any more studying after your Masters?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so I think I'm done now erm just write this dissertation yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> like my supervisor was like you know if you ever do a PhD I was like woah there <vocal desc="laugh"/> like stop it <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0432">you don't need to continue that sentence</u>
<u n="169" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's not gonna happen</u>
<u n="170" who="S0432">no I think my dad was like because his sister my auntie she's basically been studying her whole life I swear she's done like loads of different things but now she's like a lecturer at Liverpool university so and he's done quite a lot of studying and but so he thinks that I should carry on studying no I think I'm done now I might consider doing a Masters so like if it's going to like benefit me in my work or whatever</u>
<u n="171" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've really I've really enjoyed the Masters but I'm not sure I don't think I could do it again like I I have all these like I want to do all these plans and I'm like no I've got to stick and finish this and I'm really excited to finish it</u>
<u n="172" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it will be like such a weight off your shoulders when you</u>
<u n="173" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0432">I remember finishing uni and just like wow I feel like I can do whatever I want to do now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0432">but <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't such a relief handing in my dissertation though I thought that would be because it's such a like big part but I was still worried that I'd done it all wrong <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0428">yeah same <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0432">but like just finished uni and then wait and then I think it was more hearing what result you had got rather than finishing uni</u>
<u n="179" who="S0428">yeah that was</u>
<u n="180" who="S0432" trans="overlap">it was in that time it was still worrying if you'd actually done well enough <pause dur="short"/> because loads of obviously loads of thoughts go round your head don't they? like what if I completely failed and have to do like another year</u>
<u n="181" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I remember having dreams of like failing passing doing really well doing really badly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I can't I because erm obviously you get your results by the post or or and online</u>
<u n="183" who="S0428">oh we we'd got them on a board</u>
<u n="184" who="S0432">oh did you?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0428">yeah they were like up so everyone could see them</u>
<u n="186" who="S0432">oh no</u>
<u n="187" who="S0428">it was really weird yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0432" trans="overlap">that's horrible I wouldn't have liked that</u>
<u n="189" who="S0428">we all had to like go up to the uni and yeah it was really weird because I think that's like quite traditional I think</u>
<u n="190" who="S0432">yeah we had that in first year where just for linguistics your like student number was on there</u>
<u n="191" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0432">next to your like grade you got from particular exams we but we just had it online but erm so I was waiting for that then just got like a random phone call one day and it was like the head of department and I was like hello this is random because I knew it was a <anon type="place"/> number on my phone and then they were like we're just calling to let you know that you got a first and I was like what? and then because they rang everybody personally that got a first like before the results came out and I was like oh and like no one was at home then so I was just like jumping around in my bedroom on my own <vocal desc="laugh"/> like yay I've got no one to tell yet <pause dur="short"/> and like I think he could tell that I just wanted to like squeal in excitement because he was like you can go ahead and scream <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh that's so nice <pause dur="short"/> that's so exciting <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I really want to try and get erm a distinction in this Masters but <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't really do any work for it so in this dissertation <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0432">I'm sure you er you have done well so far though haven't you?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0428">yeah I've got distinction so far so it's just just I need a distinction you know that little thing I think I'd be really really happy</u>
<u n="196" who="S0432">yeah I'm sure you'll do well because <pause dur="short"/> because you kind of you're in the job as well</u>
<u n="197" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0432">so I think you might even if you don't think it has like made a difference to it I think it has like</u>
<u n="199" who="S0428">yeah I'm a little bit worried though because I've chosen to work and I was going to be like this is just like really obvious <vocal desc="laugh"/> by the way</u>
<u n="200" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">any further tickets for <anon type="place"/> at all?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0432">no I'm sure you'll be fine</u>
<u n="202" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0432">like if you want us to proofread it or?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0428">thank you</u>
<u n="205" who="S0432">I got my auntie and uncle to read through my dissertation I was like I'm really sorry this is going to be really boring for you <vocal desc="laugh"/> but they actually picked up on like good like obviously not like a sense of stuff but just like typos and stuff</u>
<u n="206" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> other stuff <pause dur="short"/> yeah my aunt actually on the phone last night she's like have you started? I was like no she was like I'm going to help you with it</u>
<u n="207" who="S0432">ah that's nice</u>
<u n="208" who="S0428">because she's just lost her job like she kind of she kind of knew it was happening because she's <pause dur="short"/> she works at erm <anon type="place"/> which is like like a uni place <pause dur="short"/> and she teaches like international students English but <trunc>the</trunc> they just in the business department they just have no students so they want to down she's like a she's like a lecturer and they she doesn't have an MA so they want to downgrade her <pause dur="short"/> but they it's really bad they should never have like given her the job if they thought she because she she's clearly she's clearly absolutely she's been there for like ten years so they want to make her</u>
<u n="209" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> no if they were going to down <unclear/> that's horrible <pause dur="short"/> yeah and they would have got rid of her before then if she wasn't doing a very good job <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0428">yeah exactly so they they want to make her like support staff so obviously her pay would massively decrease but she also she teaches at <anon type="place"/> which is the another uni so hopefully they'll she'll get some more hours there so she's like I have loads of free time to <pause dur="short"/> help</u>
<u n="211" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> help <pause dur="short"/> just write it for me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0428">yeah I think you need to do the whole lot</u>
<u n="213" who="S0432" trans="overlap">and have a proofread</u>
<u n="214" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> good at that <pause dur="short"/> but she's so good at that kind of thing she spent her life like teaching like academic English and that kind of thing</u>
<u n="215" who="S0432">yeah I got because my auntie erm lectures in like oh what is it? <pause dur="short"/> molecular biology like those types of lectures and stuff and she was like I'll read through yours but mine was because mine was more <pause dur="short"/> like a literature based one rather than a first experiment one which if that makes sense I don't know what they're technically called but she kind of changed she only like read my introduction and she changed bits and then I showed like both to my lecturer I didn't obviously say who'd done it but I was like which one do you prefer and she preferred the one that I'd done so she was like this one's kind of going off a little bit and not like really getting to the point of what you're trying to say so</u>
<u n="216" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she was like <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0432">yeah I felt really bad like not giving the rest of my dissertation to my auntie but I didn't want her have to go through and waste all her time like <unclear/> if I wasn't going to use it <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's great she helps with like CVs and stuff and other bits because she obviously she helps students and stuff like she helped my I mean because my older sister did a psychology equivalent <unclear/> degree so she helped her with hers</u>
<u n="218" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's really good <pause dur="short"/> like so maybe more</u>
<u n="219" who="S0432">yeah and my sister did dance but she did like a she had to do like her own like own like data <unclear>clip</unclear> or whatever you call it like she had to find out her own results from her hypothesis and stuff so she was able her able to help her <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0428">so your younger sister she's how she's like you say she's nineteen? no so she's</u>
<u n="221" who="S0432" trans="overlap">no my youngest is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0428">yeah so she's left school is she?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0432">yeah she's <pause dur="short"/> erm she's er she gets annoyed if I say it wrong but I say beauty therapist but she I think she calls it a spa therapist and she does like massages and you know and stuff she's like people think I'm stupid because of my job I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> they don't</u>
<u n="224" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh okay <pause dur="short"/> they don't <pause dur="short"/> do you like it?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0432">because she <pause dur="short"/> she had you had to be do you do have to get A star to C in like all your GCSEs people don't know that but I mean I think you can you can be a beautician I think is the word if you don't get those grades but you can be a spa therapist</u>
<u n="226" who="S0428"><unclear/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0432">I was like if it's what you want to do then don't care like what other people think <vocal desc="laugh"/> you are stupid or not cos she's not <pause dur="short"/> and like she can erm I mean she's finished college now but she can still go on to do like another year on like business management cos she wants to own her own like spa and stuff so but she's only nineteen she is not going to do it yet <pause dur="short"/> I think she wants to go on one of them on like a cruise ship and like because you earn so much</u>
<u n="228" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that would be amazing <pause dur="short"/> you should be like I mean you need lots of practice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0432">yeah we do <vocal desc="laugh"/> because she kind of erm does some for like us like she'll do our nails and she's got a couch where she does massages and stuff and wax our eyebrows and</u>
<u n="230" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's really good</u>
<u n="231" who="S0432">so she does practise and she does and people we pay her like only for the cost of like</u>
<u n="232" who="S0428">the materials</u>
<u n="233" who="S0432">the stuff she's using yeah so she can practise and every time she gets like a new colour I'll be like ah you can do my nails?</u>
<u n="234" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0432">or like yeah but quite a lot of our friends as well use her so I think she is doing okay gets quite a lot of practice but I think she prefers doing like massages and stuff rather than nails <pause dur="long"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the pregnant one</u>
<u n="236" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so she's the next one?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0432">yeah she's twenty-one almost twenty-two now and she's not doing anything <vocal desc="laugh"/> apart from having a baby</u>
<u n="238" who="S0428">yeah she's doing loads</u>
<u n="239" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0428">and then there's like you and your twin</u>
<u n="241" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0428">and what does your twin do?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0432">well she's at a estate agents now</u>
<u n="244" who="S0428">oh yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0428">so</u>
<u n="247" who="S0432">erm but she's next week or the week after she finishes there</u>
<u n="248" who="S0428">and then she'll go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0432">yeah to do whatever she is to do</u>
<u n="250" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0432">I don't really know my older sister she's erm housing needs officer so like people that need houses I guess are on benefits I'm not sure apply</u>
<u n="252" who="S0428" trans="overlap">how did she get into that?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0432">I really don't know because she because of her degree in Psychology and Criminal Behaviour <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> she <pause dur="short"/> I think she still does she wants to sort of work with there's like a youth vendor something or other <vocal desc="laugh"/> whatever it's called so and like work like in like youth prisons or something like helping teenagers and stuff but randomly erm she just saw this job as a housing needs officer in <anon type="place"/> and just applied for it and then she was like the interview went terribly I had to do all these tests and I didn't do very well but they gave her it and then but that was only maternity cover and then they basically said oh we're going to keep you on there's so much work to do but then they ended it and gave her a job in like complaints or <trunc>some</trunc> in the same like company but in complaints but now she's got another job doing the same thing but it's in <anon type="place"/> so she's a lot closer to home and still doing the same stuff I said are you not going to like do what you wanted to do the whole time? but I think she still looks for jobs but they don't come up very often</u>
<u n="254" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well maybe she yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0432">and I don't know if she needs to do anything more than just</u>
<u n="256" who="S0428">like qualification or apply I guess she's working in the right kind of sector to go into it</u>
<u n="257" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah because er like someone at I think she works from like sixteen and up as well so like some of them are teenagers obviously but that's more like housing market like rehabilitating but she wants to do and that's us all</u>
<u n="258" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's so many</u>
<u n="259" who="S0432">that's all of us</u>
<u n="260" who="S0428">it must be so nice being part of a big family</u>
<u n="261" who="S0432">yeah it's weird like now I've moved out like the home being really quiet</u>
<u n="262" who="S0428">yeah so how how many of your sisters live at home?</u>
<event desc="sound of train announcement"/>
<u n="263" who="S0432">er three and my older sister's moving out end of December so only two yeah but that's quite a and like obviously where we've moved out my house is quiet I'm not used to being like it being that quiet like used to well walking in and it'll be like chaos</u>
<u n="264" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0432">and like my boyfriend says I've got a really loud voice but I'm like I can't help it I think I've just like got used to talking over everyone because you literally have to shout to be heard <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0428" trans="overlap">so there'll be two left <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I love chaos not the chaos but I love a like a buzz in the house</u>
<u n="267" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's nice</u>
<u n="268" who="S0428">yeah we we don't like why like my immediate family is quite small there's I've just got my brother but then we've always got family around <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it's just mental</u>
<u n="269" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's good though</u>
<u n="270" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0432">like you seem to <trunc>s</trunc> go up north quite a lot as well to see them</u>
<u n="272" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I think I think just having I don't know I didn't realise until quite late on in life that actually like spending time with family isn't a given it's and like you obviously your they're like blood relatives and you care about them but when you you just actively love them <vocal desc="laugh"/> at times it's like the best thing really</u>
<u n="273" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know there's so many of us as well like you forget to like arrange to meet them and like because when you're younger obviously your parents arrange</u>
<u n="274" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so you see them anyway</u>
<u n="275" who="S0432">so you're like ah I'm going to continue seeing you this often but you don't because it's actually us that have to arrange it and like sort it out but</u>
<u n="276" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah no my cousin's we put a date in the diary and we're like right we're doing this</u>
<u n="277" who="S0432">yeah that's good I think we should start doing that</u>
<u n="278" who="S0428">yeah cos then you you know that you always do it <unclear/> like organising and things it's like Mamma Mia <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah that's good ah that's so good <pause dur="short"/> but there's so many of us it would be hard it's hard to get us all together anyway but even just like a few of us at a time but most of them are in <anon type="place"/> so they a lot of them see each other anyway</u>
<u n="280" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do both your are your mum's family and your dad's family in <anon type="place"/> or is it?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0432">yeah mostly apart from one of my mum's brother brother's is in New Zealand and then my dad's sister is in <unclear/> <event desc="sound of train announcement"/> in <anon type="place"/> and like <pause dur="short"/> two of my mum's sisters live like two doors down from each other there's like one house in between</u>
<u n="282" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh really <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> that's so funny that person must be like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then one of them is just round the corner from them as well so they just see each other well they don't see each other as much as they should seeing as they live that close to each other</u>
<u n="284" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like I'd be round all the time if I lived that close to them</u>
<u n="286" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my two aunts like one of them they both live in <anon type="place"/> which is an area of <anon type="place"/> and maybe it takes fifteen minutes to walk between the two</u>
<u n="287" who="S0432" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> to walk?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0432">oh that's yeah that is</u>
<u n="290" who="S0428">yeah so they do loads together and they erm they have like guitar lessons together and erm they they lived in <anon type="place"/> together so they're really close yeah they like they both work in the same areas they go for like the same jobs</u>
<u n="291" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0428">that's <unclear>extremely</unclear> funny <pause dur="short"/> but now one of them like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> works at <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> works at <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/> but she's just lost her job but erm she'll be fine she was like no I'm really excited like new challenge</u>
<u n="293" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah some people do take it like that which is good because you're like well I wouldn't have ever done it if I didn't lose my job but now you know just gives you like a kick up the bum <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and she yeah she's so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah and she's so like kind of she's so positive like nothing will get her down she's like I'll just go and erm grow loads of veg on my allotment <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah that's good <pause dur="short"/> accept the challenge that's good because some people get like really down don't they what am I going to do now?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no like her husband he lost well he was on like a temporary contract so then that finished and it was like deep in the recession he he's he was fifty-nine he's now sixty and he just couldn't get a job he used to be like erm like erm what's it called? like someone admittance officer to university</u>
<u n="297" who="S0432">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0428">I don't know what they're called erm maybe admittance officer</u>
<u n="299" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll go with that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0428">and he couldn't find a job anywhere and he was travelling up and down the country and he had an amazing CV so he would always get the interviews but then obviously people who were twenty-five were getting the jobs so he was going to like two interviews a week for like a year and a half then eventually he got one like all over the country like <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> I remember he went to <anon type="place"/> but he got one at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so it's like really really local really good and so he got really miserable when he didn't have a job but now he's got a job and he's still miserable and my aunt's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh cheer up what more do you want? you've got a job nice house good children <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's good <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh oh no <pause dur="short"/> where are we now? <event desc="sound of train announcement"/> oh we're in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0428"><anon type="place"/> I always thought was like in Wales are we near Wales?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0432">yeah I guess we are actually yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0432">yeah because we're going west then north aren't we?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0432">so yeah I guess we're going like towards Wales <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I've ever heard of it</u>
<u n="308" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="309" who="S0432">no</u>
<u n="310" who="S0428">I don't know why I thought it was in Wales <vocal desc="laugh"/> my cousin was at uni in Wales in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0432">oh yeah I've never been there</u>
<u n="312" who="S0428">it is so beautiful but like the train like I was on this train it was at night it was single track like really really tiny but like beautiful <pause dur="short"/> such a stunning uni and on right on the coast and it was amazing really beautiful</u>
<u n="313" who="S0432" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> is it where is is it north? or</u>
<u n="314" who="S0428">I think it's like bang in the middle</u>
<u n="315" who="S0432">oh is it?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0428">I think but I'm not too sure <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0432">I know is it <anon type="place"/>? is that in the north?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0432">and then Cardiff</u>
<u n="320" who="S0428">Cardiff and Swansea yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0432">and Swansea are in the south aren't they? yeah that's the one <vocal desc="laugh"/> range of welsh towns <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
