<text id="SDQG">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:01:48</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-08</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0329</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In the car driving to North London from East London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cars, family, TLS, digital Vs print, traffic, road rage, work, France, presents, driving</topics>
		<activity>Mother and son talking in the car while doing an errand </activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0329">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>50</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Literary Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2>French</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0326">did you lock all the doors? <unclear/> <unclear>what's wrong with</unclear> your car?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0329">if erm the car <pause dur="short"/> they're really undecided about the car</u>
<u n="3" who="S0326"><unclear/> because doesn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> say it's totally bonkers?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I sent sent <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> an email yesterday saying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says it's not appropriate to learn on and erm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0326">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he could also probably get that fixed and MOT'd</u>
<u n="6" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks he knows everything but he doesn't know everything</u>
<u n="7" who="S0326">how is how does he know it's not appropriate to learn on then?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0329">erm you know he's not as much of a hippie as we are you know if it's not like perfect where am I going? <anon type="place"/> have you got the?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0326">you know how to drive there you've driven there before</u>
<u n="10" who="S0329">er</u>
<u n="11" who="S0326">where's the map then?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="12" who="S0329"><anon type="place"/> but you've got the <pause dur="short"/> I need to know</u>
<u n="13" who="S0326">I don't have your phone</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="14" who="S0329">mm it better not fucking rain tonight</u>
<u n="15" who="S0326">why? is the party outside?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0329">it's in a <trunc>m</trunc> in a it's outside <vocal desc="laugh"/> with a marquee</u>
<u n="17" who="S0326">where is it exactly?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> exactly in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0326">are those those fields you go past on the bus?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0326">cos there was those</u>
<u n="22" who="S0329" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0326">turning cold as well</u>
<u n="24" who="S0329">well it's not cold <pause dur="short"/> it's always cold at the <anon type="place"/> party</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="25" who="S0326">are you taking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0329">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s invited but I mean he seems to have something else to do which pissed me off</u>
<u n="27" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0329">pissed me off but then I think oh fuck it I don't want him coming I can't talk to you anyway <pause dur="short"/> why don't I take you to a party and ignore you like you do to me when when our friends stay <pause dur="short"/> it's a miracle I'm going out</u>
<u n="29" who="S0326">are you sure you wanna move to France?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0329">well I am really fucking freaking out about it I do think <pause dur="short"/> if we have an argument I er that's it I can't go home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0326">just go and live with granny</u>
<u n="32" who="S0329">but I'm not really moving to France I am just I'm just mainly going to be there and I'm gonna be back in London a lot</u>
<u n="33" who="S0326">what's the point then of <unclear>like</unclear>?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0329">well the point is that I <vocal desc="sigh"/> need to rent my house out cos I've got no income</u>
<u n="35" who="S0326">you you'd have an income if you kept a job</u>
<u n="36" who="S0329">no I er I gave up my job I'd had enough of that job I couldn't do another another minute I can't do another minute I really need to <pause dur="short"/> I need to break out <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's our neighbour</u>
<u n="38" who="S0329">if someone told you you had to go to school for the rest of your life how would you feel?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I er I wouldn't mind depends on what kind of school though</u>
<u n="40" who="S0329">no the you know the the <pause dur="short"/> I've been in my mind is so constrained by er</u>
<u n="41" who="S0326">that seemed quite a cushy job though</u>
<u n="42" who="S0329">it is a cushy job but that's not the answer to life is it?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0326">yeah but I mean like try and get another job where they make you do</u>
<u n="44" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I won't ever get another job that's it forget Christmas cancelled for the rest of your life darling but I'm going to I'm I'm going to try and create something different for the rest of my just if you told me I had to spend the rest of my life at the <anon type="place"/> it would be like telling me I had to spend the rest of my life with your dad</u>
<u n="45" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0329">I'd be really depressed but if you said to me look it's gonna look a bit hairy for the next few years but <pause dur="short"/> the world's your oyster anything could happen <pause dur="short"/> I'd be excited it's an exciting new challenge and this is the time to do it I know that kids <trunc>ne</trunc>never like it when</u>
<u n="47" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I don't care</u>
<u n="48" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cares</u>
<u n="49" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a baby</u>
<u n="50" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s er and both of you care when it comes to erm you know and also I've <trunc>g</trunc> I definitely feel I've got to provide a house for you <pause dur="short"/> because <trunc>nei</trunc></u>
<u n="51" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but I sorted that one out</u>
<u n="52" who="S0329">because neither of you are prepared to go and live with your fucking dad</u>
<u n="53" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0326">well you go and live with him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0329">er you well <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc>he won't even be there <pause dur="short"/> er if you if you were prepared to to just you know park your things in his house I could make loads of money renting out my house or even sell it <pause dur="short"/> those people haven't sold their house have they?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0326">what? on our street?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0326">dunno</u>
<u n="59" who="S0329">anyway <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room it's sick isn't it?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0326">it's good yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0329">I'm gonna get him some toxic waste as well to remind him <unclear/> I once had to bribe him to move to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> he didn't want to move to <anon type="place"/> I did him a massive favour did you both a massive favour and the fuss you made about moving the trial you put me through the agony agony of doubt and recrimination <pause dur="short"/> anxiety the addiction to prescription drugs that followed</u>
<u n="62" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0329">and <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="64" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I just remember you like you having to go and lock in like when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was having a tantrum you'd lock us in the car outside the outside the <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0326">put us in the car outside the <anon type="place"/> and go in there and drink whisky</u>
<u n="67" who="S0329">yeah I mean there were a few moments</u>
<u n="68" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0329">which were were not <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember which one <anon type="place"/> is is it the one with the swimming pool on it? no that's erm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0326" trans="overlap">why are you going on Citymapper when you're in a car? that's the first question</u>
<u n="71" who="S0329" trans="overlap">well you find you find me the best way to get there <pause dur="short"/> oh and I've got to get some money <pause dur="short"/> you haven't got fifteen quid on you have you?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0326">no <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> you don't have Google Maps?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0329">I have got Google Maps</u>
<u n="74" who="S0326">no you've just got maps it's rubbish</u>
<u n="75" who="S0329">no I've got Google Maps</u>
<u n="76" who="S0326">where?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0329">somewhere <pause dur="short"/> download Google Maps</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="78" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/> what road? <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0329"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> when I was driving <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> back from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0326" trans="overlap">oh you might see might see dad</u>
<u n="81" who="S0329">when I was driving back <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> back from <anon type="place"/> we went past the bottom of <anon type="place"/> and there was a huge great big memorial <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh I've never seen that before what's that? and I said that's the Prince Albert Memorial and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> practically choked on his chewing gum and went <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's a memorial to erm to a Prince Albert? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0326">what's funny about that?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0329">well cos he'd never heard of an actual Prince Albert he</u>
<u n="84" who="S0326">he'd never heard of Victoria and Albert?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="86" who="S0326">oh what do they teach in schools these days?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0326">I can even I can even quote what Queen Victoria said after <trunc>sh</trunc> he died</u>
<u n="89" who="S0329">what did she say?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0326">the salt has gone out of my life</u>
<u n="91" who="S0329">the salt?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0329">that's witty</u>
<u n="94" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she is good though er if you see these like she's done this erm it's like a drawing published of <trunc>sh</trunc> that she did of Sappho she did her drawings in like little books and stuff she's quite a good drawer</u>
<u n="95" who="S0329">is it? <pause dur="short"/> there's erm I've just <pause dur="short"/> soon you'll be ready to start writing for the <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when it er er <pause dur="short"/> I'm sending somebody on a to review this exhibition about the grand tour <pause dur="short"/> I bet you'd do it just as well</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="96" who="S0326">do all your colleagues know that you're leaving?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0329">oh my colleagues are ghastly they're <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're all <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="98" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0329">everyone's been in er meeting after meeting after meeting all little meetings all the time <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> I'm a bit worried about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s er sorry erm and anyway now everyone's got a new job and they've got a new member of staff and they're all just <pause dur="short"/> dealing with it <pause dur="short"/> but er it's embarrassing I feel like er the whole world has been changed because of me</u>
<u n="100" who="S0326">well it er so why are you on a retainer? in case you wanna go back?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0329">no it's it's I'm on a retainer cos I will I'm not doing an office job anymore I'm but I'm so I'm a consultant editor and that means oh god this is a nightmare <pause dur="long"/> and that means <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I've got to do a number of pieces I've got to bring in all the</u>
<u n="102" who="S0326" trans="overlap">are you gonna what? do writing for it?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0329">yeah <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really squeezing a lot out of me <pause dur="short"/> but <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0326">high vis</u>
<u n="105" who="S0329">or er <trunc>h</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc> look at the little <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="106" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear>they're gonna <trunc>b</trunc> they're going off</unclear> to do building <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0329">little ones the little thingies you were like that they went to your school as well they go to your school you went to that school look this is what they turn into <pause dur="long"/> I can't say that feta cheese was very good but that salad was lush</u>
<u n="108" who="S0326">this is long man</u>
<u n="109" who="S0329">I know it is long <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0326">when you're in France you won't have to spend money on anything will you?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0329">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is really yesterday I was totally utterly utterly freaking out about money because I can't get any credit <unclear/> <event desc="sound of static"/> so how am I going to survive? <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has been so sweet he's been so sweet it makes up for the fact that he didn't talk to me at the party erm he said that I don't need to worry about it you know he's not gonna let me be high and dry ever ever ever ever <pause dur="short"/> makes me cry actually <pause dur="short"/> that's why I wanted to get him a nice present but I can't get him a good present compared to what his wife would get him cos she was rich and she bought him things like Rolexes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0329">and I've bought him a really really ordinary shirt from <anon type="place"/> but I don't like his short sleeved <trunc>s</trunc>shirts he's got this is much nicer than the ones I've seen him wear</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="114" who="S0326">where's his Rolexes now?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0326">where's his Rolexes now?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0329">on his wrist <pause dur="long"/> and I haven't got time to go I've been looking for something I mean for Christmas I got him all these little things and I don't think he really appreciated them <pause dur="short"/> he didn't wasn't interested in the body oil <vocal desc="laugh"/> perhaps unsurprisingly but it cost fifty quid erm <pause dur="short"/> and I took that to France that's still there he's not interested</u>
<u n="118" who="S0326">it's spoilt innit?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0329">yes you're right he's just spoilt <unclear/> spoilt bastard</u>
<u n="120" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="121" who="S0329">he's gonna fix up a shower unit with er and paid for it all in the bathroom with er erm Plexiglas I mean it's not gonna be a thing of beauty and the shower rail that I</u>
<u n="122" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's necessary though cos like</u>
<u n="123" who="S0329" trans="overlap">and I saw the shower that he bought it only cost forty quid <unclear/> falling apart <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and he's gonna <trunc>ti</trunc> he has to tile the unit and everything there's quite a lot of work and he's fixing up these lights he's doing a lot I cannot complain try as I might <pause dur="short"/> and I bought myself a raincoat for Scotland</u>
<u n="124" who="S0326">how much was that?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0329">it was rather expensive how much was your one? is it about a hundred quid wasn't it? reduced</u>
<u n="126" who="S0326">my red one?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0326">yeah maybe er like eighty or something</u>
<u n="129" who="S0329">the one that I wanted to <trunc>ge</trunc> to get <pause dur="short"/> erm well I got a Patagonia</u>
<u n="130" who="S0326">well that's why cos you got a designer</u>
<u n="131" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0326">Patagonia stuff is expensive cos it's <trunc>l</trunc>like a label that people like to <trunc>w</trunc> like be seen wearing</u>
<u n="133" who="S0329" trans="overlap">well they're really technical and what the guy was telling me about erm erm North Face I said I wanted a North Face Summit Series and he said they're really environmentally unfriendly they erm whereas these ones are sort of eco I can't remember all the way in which he described it <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="134" who="S0326">I'm gonna miss something exciting on cricket</u>
<u n="135" who="S0329">I think that should've been called <anon type="place"/> not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="136" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0329">then all the hipsters would go in <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/> think I know which one it is this is boring</u>
<u n="138" who="S0326"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> it's well boring</u>
<u n="139" who="S0329">I'm sorry <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> got to get the money</u>
<u n="140" who="S0326">it's hot in this car as well</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="141" who="S0329">I don't quite understand why it's so slow unless people are <trunc>ge</trunc>getting ready for this Tube strike</u>
<u n="142" who="S0326" trans="overlap">school run</u>
<u n="143" who="S0329">not yet</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="144" who="S0326">I've gotta be somewhere at four you know that?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0329">I know well I kept asking you to leave</u>
<u n="146" who="S0326">no you were sitting there doing stuff I was ready before you</u>
<u n="147" who="S0329">is it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0326">days</u>
<u n="149" who="S0329">what's happening with the lights? can you see?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0326">there's about forty-five little children who are crossing the road so</u>
<u n="151" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0326"><unclear>carry on</unclear> run them over that's alright</u>
<u n="153" who="S0329">you don't like children do you? why is that? you're so mean</u>
<u n="154" who="S0326">children are annoying</u>
<u n="155" who="S0329">if the worst comes to the worst I can always get a job in er in the bakery <vocal desc="laugh"/> can't I? oh no please don't get in front of me I can't bear it</u>
<u n="156" who="S0326">don't let him fucking hell <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0329">he's stalled anyway</u>
<u n="158" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0329">what's happening with er?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's green now</u>
<u n="161" who="S0329">he's being a total cunt</u>
<u n="162" who="S0326">honk him man</u>
<u n="163" who="S0329">I can't <pause dur="short"/> he's perfectly within his rights to do that <pause dur="short"/> oh he's changed his mind about where he's going</u>
<u n="164" who="S0326"><unclear>is</unclear> that road rage?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0329">road rage yeah I do get that</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="166" who="S0326">another red light</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="167" who="S0329"><trunc>th</trunc>they're having an argument I really really can't tolerate arguments</u>
<u n="168" who="S0326">they're not having an argument that's just <trunc>h</trunc> that's how they talk innit like with that culture <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0329">in that culture?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0326">Mediterranean culture</u>
<u n="171" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says the only time he's seen me be irritated is with my children</u>
<u n="172" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0329">yo ho ho</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="174" who="S0326">went to see quite a good gig last night it was erm had this friend's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend but I knew him before he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's <trunc>qu</trunc> sort of quite crazy German guy with really long blonde hair he's a musician and he er he's quite good at finding er sort of weird stuff and he was in Brazil in like the favelas and er found these three girls that were making like rap music and sort of took them to England they've become extremely successful and they're really cool and <trunc>c</trunc> sweet and <unclear>young</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> they do like synchronized bouncing</u>
<u n="175" who="S0329">I just had a terrible thought is your dad in the country?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0326">yeah I <trunc>sai</trunc> I told you you might see him</u>
<u n="177" who="S0329">oh man</u>
<u n="178" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0329">I don't want <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to see him I'll be ashamed</u>
<u n="180" who="S0326">oh what? er oh he's gonna be at the <anon type="place"/> party?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0326">yeah well he'll be there with his ponytail</u>
<u n="183" who="S0329">I feel sick <pause dur="short"/> why does he go?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0326">I dunno he's got</u>
<u n="185" who="S0329">he's never wanted I mean <unclear/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0326" trans="overlap">he's got <unclear/> social <pause dur="short"/> every time I go round there he's er he's like got someone over <pause dur="long"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not going anyway</u>
<u n="187" who="S0329">he must've changed his prescription</u>
<u n="188" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="189" who="S0329">and also he's got nothing to do being an academic</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="190" who="S0326">but you said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not yeah I wouldn't go I wouldn't take <pause dur="long"/> <unclear>in</unclear> boiling up <unclear>bibs</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> what are you thinking about?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0326">but you said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't go anyway</u>
<u n="193" who="S0329">no er he's he is going but er because I was so <pause dur="short"/> disappointed when you said that he wasn't coming I just couldn't believe my ears</u>
<u n="194" who="S0326">oh you're not going that way?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0329">no <pause dur="short"/> am I making a mistake?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0326">I would've gone that way <pause dur="short"/> and Google says go that way</u>
<u n="197" who="S0329">well you're the one with the fucking map</u>
<u n="198" who="S0326">I just thought it was common sense that's all</u>
<u n="199" who="S0329">anyway we we need to get some money we need to stop somewhere and I probably need to not only stop somewhere but <trunc>s</trunc> erm not only get the money out but spend the money so that I've got a five pound note she only wants fifty</u>
<u n="200" who="S0326">you're really going round the houses aren't you?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0329">and I might have to paint it <pause dur="short"/> took <trunc>a</trunc>ages to paint the other one <unclear/> <unclear>really angry about</unclear></u>
<u n="202" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> hey wait till you see the ponytail man you'll be you'll be sick <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0329">erm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0326">I was almost sick</u>
<u n="205" who="S0329">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might say oh I'm definitely coming now I wanna check this geezer out</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="206" who="S0326">yeah he was handsome when he was younger</u>
<u n="207" who="S0329">course he was <pause dur="short"/> I don't think you should let a ponytail stop you going to</u>
<u n="208" who="S0326">no wait till you see it that's all I'm saying</u>
<u n="209" who="S0329">but even so I still don't think it should actually let you stop you</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="210" who="S0326">I don't know what he thinks he's doing</u>
<u n="211" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0326">I dunno what he thinks he's doing with that ponytail</u>
<u n="213" who="S0329">erm several people are saying that about his philosophy <pause dur="short"/> or indeed all of it <pause dur="short"/> what did you go and see him for yesterday?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0326">er he got me some books</u>
<u n="215" who="S0329">when's he fucking off?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0326">er <trunc>Ju</trunc> August the eighteenth <unclear>or something</unclear></u>
<u n="217" who="S0329">and what's happening to his house?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0326">dunno <pause dur="short"/> his house is a <trunc>t</trunc> fucking building site</u>
<u n="219" who="S0329">he must have so much money <pause dur="short"/> what are they doing to it?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0326">dunno probably ruining it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0329"><unclear>well er he</unclear> may have some money but he still hasn't got any taste</u>
<u n="222" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0329">but very few people have my exquisite taste</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="224" who="S0326">oh <trunc>l</trunc> he like reshaped like the doorway so it would fit bikes but it doesn't fit bikes</u>
<u n="225" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0329">what's happening with the lights up there <unclear>blood</unclear>?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0326">I bet the builders er reckon they can take him for a ride as well</u>
<u n="228" who="S0329">I hope they do <pause dur="long"/> what's wrong with these lights? why are they so slow? they don't seem to be changing from red at all</u>
<u n="229" who="S0326">do you know er how far out of your way you went to get here?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0329"><unclear>fuck off</unclear></u>
<u n="231" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you see where that? <trunc>w</trunc>we went all the way up here</u>
<u n="232" who="S0329">well you should've you should've said</u>
<u n="233" who="S0326">I thought you knew how to drive to <anon type="place"/>? you grew up there <pause dur="long"/> I'm gonna be late for my thing and I I</u>
<u n="234" who="S0329" trans="overlap">yeah and I'm gonna be late for her</u>
<u n="235" who="S0326">yeah but I haven't got a phone so I can't text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0329">I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s number on my phone you can text him <pause dur="short"/> no it'll be quicker to get back</u>
<u n="237" who="S0326">yeah right <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0329">erm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0326">I could've finished like what I was doing as well</u>
<u n="240" who="S0329">thing is we can't go because er trucks keep driving across their red light <pause dur="long"/> oh my god we've got ages to go on this light <pause dur="short"/> we've got really ages to go on this light jesus</u>
<u n="241" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/> a really quick road as well <unclear>you should've gone</unclear> down</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="242" who="S0329">I know I I can't understand why I did that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> might have to alert her can I can you go to my emails?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0326">one second</u>
<u n="244" who="S0329">cos I'm gonna have to tell her I'll be five minutes late</u>
<u n="245" who="S0326">more than that <pause dur="long"/> where are your emails?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0329">those ones <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear>oh my goodness</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> can you write five mins late and send it?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0326">that's it? that's all you wanna say?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0329">yeah we're not friends</u>
<u n="249" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you're probably gonna be more than five minutes late</u>
<u n="250" who="S0329">erm just put five minutes late but just send it because she's she'll be downstairs now</u>
<u n="251" who="S0326" trans="overlap">alright alright <pause dur="short"/> but you'll be ten mins late and then it'll be <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="252" who="S0329">just put five mins late traffic</u>
<u n="253" who="S0326">yeah I already did that</u>
<u n="254" who="S0329">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0326">I can't believe you roped me into this are we in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="256" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0329">please never tell anybody that I made this mistake</u>
<u n="258" who="S0326">I should be driving around</u>
<u n="259" who="S0329">so funny when you see little girls like that and you can see exactly what they're going to look like when they're forty-five</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="260" who="S0326">can't believe we went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe we went to <anon type="place"/> I just can't believe it</u>
<u n="262" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear>what</unclear></u>
<u n="263" who="S0329">and part of me was thinking that <anon type="place"/> might be <anon type="place"/> and that's why I said to you get the map here's the map</u>
<u n="264" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but <anon type="place"/> is that big road in <anon type="place"/> where <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0329" trans="overlap">does it go is it the road where dad that dad's road goes off?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0329">yes right</u>
<u n="268" who="S0326">or like the one behind it like one of those two it's a road that sort of <pause dur="short"/> if you're walking from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> you have to cross</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="269" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0329">you need to find out which road it is if it's the <trunc>re</trunc> <trunc>re</trunc> ah there's cash withdrawals there <pause dur="short"/> but I can't stop</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="271" who="S0326">there's a good classics bookshop on this road</u>
<u n="272" who="S0329">well you see it's not a wasted journey after all</u>
<u n="273" who="S0326">yeah but I'm not going to it am I?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="274" who="S0329">yeah bizarre I I can't understand how I did that <pause dur="short"/> bizarre but anyway <pause dur="long"/> so I'm going to go down here and then I'm gonna turn right</u>
<u n="275" who="S0326">yeah but don't turn right <trunc>d</trunc> you just turn right straight onto <anon type="place"/> boom</u>
<u n="276" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0326"><unclear/> I could've gone back and forth on the overground about six times <unclear/> this</u>
<u n="280" who="S0329">yeah yeah I know but you couldn't've carried a chest of drawers could you?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0326">probably could of</u>
<u n="282" who="S0329">could have right I've got to get some money <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0326">there's a bank there oh that</u>
<u n="284" who="S0329">there's a bank where is the bank?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0326" trans="overlap">there's an HSBC just er past the lights</u>
<u n="286" who="S0329">left or right?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0326">to the left on the <trunc>p</trunc> right side of the road that's er for us</u>
<u n="288" who="S0329">on the left? go left</u>
<u n="289" who="S0326" trans="overlap">left hand side left hand side</u>
<u n="290" who="S0329" trans="overlap">left hand side right</u>
<u n="291" who="S0326">matey mate mate</u>
<u n="292" who="S0329">and see whether we can pull up <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0326">course you can</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="294" who="S0329">double yellow double yellow double yellow</u>
<u n="295" who="S0326">yeah but just flash the blinkers on and do it quickly</u>
<u n="296" who="S0329">I can't <pause dur="short"/> absolutely can't <pause dur="short"/> er where's Barclays? <pause dur="short"/> fucking hell</u>
<u n="297" who="S0326">maybe the post office has one</u>
<u n="298" who="S0329"><unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0326">there do it there</u>
<u n="300" who="S0329">where?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0326">there's one there er</u>
<u n="302" who="S0329">I can't <trunc>c</trunc> er</u>
<u n="303" who="S0326">that's not a double <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="304" who="S0329" trans="overlap">that's it's that's even worse that's even more illegal</u>
<u n="305" who="S0326">well you're about to go past <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0329">I'm gonna go into <anon type="place"/> there'll be somewhere I can get</u>
<u n="307" who="S0326">no there won't</u>
<u n="308" who="S0329">yes there will</u>
<u n="309" who="S0326">there's nothing on that road except the overground station</u>
<u n="310" who="S0329">job centre Oxfam is there anything here?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0326">there's a Tesco</u>
<u n="312" who="S0329">free cash withdrawals right</u>
<u n="313" who="S0326">they do fivers from that one as well</u>
<u n="314" who="S0329">how do you know?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0326">cos I know everything so just do get <trunc>y</trunc> what you want and just withdraw one fiver so do it twice see what I'm saying? and then</u>
<u n="316" who="S0329">I'll just ask for fifteen pounds</u>
<u n="317" who="S0326">yeah what about my money?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0329">get it on the way back</u>
<u n="319" who="S0326">just get sixty-five</u>
<u n="320" who="S0329">oh sixty-five yeah smart thinking <unclear>Batman</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="321" who="S0329">do fivers</u>
<u n="322" who="S0326">they do do fivers</u>
<u n="323" who="S0329">right let's get there</u>
<u n="324" who="S0326">they do do fivers</u>
<u n="325" who="S0329">they didn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0326">they do though all Tesco cashpoints do</u>
<u n="327" who="S0329">well they do but it doesn't today</u>
<u n="328" who="S0326">well they must've run out that's all it's not my fault</u>
<u n="329" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0326">what did you get in Oxfam? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s present?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0329" trans="overlap">little sign came up saying this machine only dispenses twenties and tens</u>
<u n="332" who="S0326">well it used to</u>
<u n="333" who="S0329">right this is the <anon type="place"/> is it?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0326">yes</u>
<u n="335" who="S0329">fifty-two</u>
<u n="336" who="S0326">what did you get in Oxfam? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s present? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0329">I'm so worried about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s presents</u>
<u n="338" who="S0326">when's his birthday?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0329">twentieth</u>
<u n="340" who="S0326">you've got ages why'd you get it now?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> I got it now because <pause dur="short"/> everything's in the sale and if you don't buy it now it won't be there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="342" who="S0329">I agree it's sort of</u>
<u n="343" who="S0326">what kind of shirt is it? just plain?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0329">no it's a <trunc>su</trunc> it's a <trunc>s</trunc> really simple summer simple check it's not fancy Margaret Howell summer <trunc>sh</trunc> he really likes Margaret Howell right <anon type="place"/> flats number fifty-two loading bay look out for number fifty-two <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> how do we know what the?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0326">did you put it on?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0329">I don't have an have a I put it on Citymapper</u>
<u n="347" who="S0326"><trunc>k</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> keep going it's further along it's right by the <trunc>st</trunc> er station er er fifty-two number fifty-two right?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0329">that's what she said fifty-two</u>
<u n="349" who="S0326">it's right by the station</u>
<u n="350" who="S0329">which station?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0326">the overground station which is by the bridge you might see dad if you're lucky</u>
<u n="352" who="S0329">this is I'm here all the time for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I just scurry around you can't park anywhere except in dad's street and I scurry around going <vocal desc="gasp"/> this is the arsehole of the universe though what a horrible place to live <pause dur="short"/> I don't blame you not wanting to come and live here</u>
<u n="353" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> all my days <pause dur="short"/> you know it took you forty minutes to drive here?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0329">well er I knew it took quite a long time and that's why I was saying to you can we go now please?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0326">but you went to erm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0329">and you said just this shop right flats</u>
<u n="357" who="S0326">er and then you sat there on your computer</u>
<u n="358" who="S0329">flats</u>
<u n="359" who="S0326">thirty-eight</u>
<u n="360" who="S0329">these ones?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0326">perhaps <pause dur="short"/> forty-eight fifty <unclear/> must be these ones</u>
<u n="362" who="S0329">er that's <anon type="place"/> tell you what what about these ones? fifty-seven</u>
<u n="363" who="S0326" trans="overlap">why er not do the one that was probably gonna</u>
<u n="364" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I don't know whether she <trunc>ca</trunc> it's it's like a mental this is sixty-three <pause dur="short"/> er <unclear/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0326">that one is fifty-two because it said forty-eight fifty</u>
<u n="366" who="S0329">but there's no there's nowhere to pull up she said there's a loading bay right outside okay there's <pause dur="short"/> let's erm</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="367" who="S0329"><unclear>got to drop</unclear> it at home <pause dur="short"/> where is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going to be meeting you?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0326">I dunno if you can do it anymore I've got I haven't got a phone so I've gotta check</u>
<u n="369" who="S0329">but I've got his number</u>
<u n="370" who="S0326">yeah I'll just check the computer <unclear>at home tonight</unclear></u>
<u n="371" who="S0329">okay break me off a little piece of chocolate</u>
<u n="372" who="S0326">where's your phone?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0329">in my bag</u>
<u n="374" who="S0326">do you know how to drive the way do you know the way home?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> actually don't break me off any chocolate I'm mustn't have any I'm on a diet</u>
<u n="376" who="S0326">I see the Kit Kat wrappers in there</u>
<u n="377" who="S0329">no you know perfectly well that is from your trip to to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I don't know perfectly well anything</u>
<u n="379" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you chicky chicky chicky chicky chicky so if you don't come to Scotland what about coming to France? how about that? would that be better?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0326">erm maybe</u>
<u n="381" who="S0329">I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you're not gonna be in France till when? the end of August?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0329">erm I'm going to France for a quick trip erm <pause dur="short"/> just for a week seventh to the fourteenth then I'm back and I'm back principally erm to you know move move out move in sort <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> down to <anon type="place"/> and then at some point before the end of August I er I wanna go back but we'll probably be driving back and then we'll be there your term doesn't start</u>
<u n="384" who="S0326">no but all of September I think I'm gonna be busy</u>
<u n="385" who="S0329">all of September?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0326">I'll be busy I think</u>
<u n="387" who="S0329">well it's just er I mean I can't make an arrangement with you two <pause dur="short"/> you'll be <trunc>d</trunc> busy doing what?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0326">going to Greece</u>
<u n="389" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0326">maybe the very end of August?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="391" who="S0329">well if not in the summer maybe we'll have Christmas there in the snow or in the <trunc>s</trunc> actually last <trunc>s</trunc> Christmas last New Year it was boiling <pause dur="long"/> I must get these lights get these lights get these lights get these lights come on let's go yes yes</u>
<u n="392" who="S0326" trans="overlap">do you know this this app called er Drivenow?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="394" who="S0326">basically it's an app where there's cars all over the place where you can if you're on the app you can use the cars</u>
<u n="395" who="S0329">you can what?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0326">use the cars and they charge you per minute it's like thirty P a minute or something</u>
<u n="397" who="S0329">so when er so you don't need a car?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0326">no that's not what I'm trying to tell you that's <pause dur="short"/> thirty P a minute is a lot</u>
<u n="399" who="S0329">oh I see</u>
<u n="400" who="S0326">but what people do or my friend who uses it he always uses it when he's trying to get home but he wants er he wants it to be cheaper than a cab <pause dur="short"/> so he's gotta drive home really fast <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> imagine if you were sitting in a traffic jam it'd cost you thirty P a minute <vocal desc="laugh"/> drive people mental</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="401" who="S0329">that'll be well good to put <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s socks <unclear>and knickers in</unclear> won't it?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0329">and then with the with the clothes rail and he's fucking sorted his room is gonna be so sick I don't think he'll need my <pause dur="short"/> you might want it that little filing cabinet be useful to you?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0326">no <pause dur="short"/> there's I don't have any room for it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0329">well once <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s moved into my room do they know that it the whole house is sound proofed? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0326">I don't think so actually is it?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0329">well it's sound proofed between my room and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room and between <trunc>w</trunc> er next door er not not er your bedroom but my old bedroom <pause dur="short"/> I might have told them that it was sound proofed</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="408" who="S0326">have you noticed how sort of all these adults on scooters?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0329">mm?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0326" trans="overlap">do you get that where sort of?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0329" trans="overlap">embarrassing</u>
<u n="412" who="S0326">don't you see? I always see it in like the city <vocal desc="laugh"/> like office workers scooting</u>
<u n="413" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0326">so their commute is quicker from the Tube to the office <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0329">well I'm so glad I'm not gonna be an officer worker anymore <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never gonna do that again I've had it</u>
<u n="416" who="S0326">you were barely an office worker though</u>
<u n="417" who="S0329">it's cos it was <trunc>j</trunc> I'm just not that kind of person</u>
<u n="418" who="S0326">yeah but er no one in that on on your staff</u>
<u n="419" who="S0329">no but the <trunc>p</trunc>part of the problem is that it <trunc>h</trunc>had become more and more and more corporate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> fucking cunting <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is just he's become like this mm what can I do for the corporate people upstairs?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0329">mm come into this meeting room with me</u>
<u n="422" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0329">really really horrible oh are you my boss? let me get my tongue right up your backside</u>
<u n="424" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0326">disgusting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0329">disgusting he is disgusting</u>
<u n="427" who="S0326">but <trunc>h</trunc> what do they care about? it's surely it's just er <trunc>w</trunc> how much the magazine sells? if everyone can do <unclear/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0329">no what they <trunc>ca</trunc> all they care about is numbers so they've got no interest in the product</u>
<u n="429" who="S0326">yeah I know but if the magazine is selling then what's the problem?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0329">erm because we don't make any money we don't I don't think we lose any the reason that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was so delighted that I was going to leave was that he could make an enormous saving thirty grand</u>
<u n="431" who="S0326">yeah but surely he's gotta get someone else to do your job?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0329">erm well he's mainly going to be sharing out my job to other people so er everybody else has got more work to do erm <pause dur="short"/> and he will've presented it in such a way as to make them feel fucking grateful that they've got a job at all</u>
<u n="433" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0329">so don't ask for any more money erm and he will also have said it's you know it's a whole new exciting erm <pause dur="short"/> deal for er <trunc>t</trunc> for you so you've got this new portfolio</u>
<u n="435" who="S0326" trans="overlap">do you think the the <anon type="place"/>'ll exist in twenty years?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0329">no I don't think er there'll be a print version in twenty years <pause dur="short"/> I don't think there'll be a print version in five years</u>
<u n="437" who="S0326"><unclear/> <unclear>ever</unclear> read it in a print version <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I mean I I would erm</unclear> you know just pick it up if it's lying around I'm not gonna get it on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0329">yeah you would pick it up if it was lying around but you wouldn't buy it <pause dur="short"/> whereas you might buy it if you could just have it zipped into your inbox <pause dur="short"/> oh thanks mister so the shirt I bought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a bit like that one that that guy's wearing except</u>
<u n="439" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0329">except <trunc>cl</trunc>classier short sleeved when I was going out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> one he used to laugh at men in short sleeved shirts</u>
<u n="441" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I laugh at them in <trunc>sh</trunc> I laugh at them</u>
<u n="442" who="S0329">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wears them a Margaret Howell short sleeved shirt I think is acceptable cos she's she is good looking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0326">which one?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0329">the one with the lollipop</u>
<u n="445" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0326">well <pause dur="short"/> at least you didn't er at least at least you didn't laugh at fat children <pause dur="short"/> go on then</u>
<u n="447" who="S0329">only <unclear/> only <unclear/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0326" trans="overlap">starting to drive like an old woman you know that?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0329">I'm gonna <unclear>drop</unclear> you out</u>
<u n="450" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0329">er I'm gonna chuck you out</u>
<u n="452" who="S0326">so you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> having a race across <anon type="place"/> you'd probably lose</u>
<u n="453" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0326">if you and if you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a race across <anon type="place"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="455" who="S0329">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0326">this isn't the right road is it?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0329">yes it is the right road I know my way round here <pause dur="long"/> I don't understand this <pause dur="short"/> this little shrine</u>
<u n="458" who="S0326">why?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0329">er well er it sometimes it's on that side of the road and I just wonder what happened to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0326">might've died in prison or something</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="461" who="S0329">I also bought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> some lavender water eau de cologne from <pause dur="long"/> that <unclear>be</unclear> a proper old man I mean he's gonna be sixty-two no he's gonna be sixty-one</u>
<u n="462" who="S0326">younger than dad though</u>
<u n="463" who="S0329">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> suits short sleeved <trunc>s</trunc>shirts <pause dur="long"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> he won't be disappointed he'll he'll be but I agree it's <unclear>slightly</unclear> not the world's greatest present</u>
<u n="464" who="S0326">didn't they have anything else at Margaret Howell?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0329">not that I could afford even that was <trunc>j</trunc> more money than I than I <unclear>want</unclear> you know the thing is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> buys things off Ebay so he would never ever ever spend full price this was sale price <pause dur="short"/> but I just can't oh the other thing I was gonna get him was a pair of slippers but that is just too unsexy <pause dur="short"/> he really likes my slippers <pause dur="short"/> I just I just can't <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="466" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0329">maybe for his Christmas present and I looked everywhere for the linen bathrobe so er I mean I was screwed</u>
<u n="468" who="S0326">oh mate that was just such a drag</u>
<u n="469" who="S0329">well it's only it's not even four o'clock yet</u>
<u n="470" who="S0326">so are you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> definitely gonna go to the <anon type="place"/> party?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0329">well I definitely have to go <vocal desc="sigh"/> I'm gonna phone <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and say darling</u>
<u n="472" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0329">if you don't want to go</u>
<u n="474" who="S0326" trans="overlap">phone</u>
<u n="475" who="S0329">is this my phone?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0329">if you don't want to go</u>
<u n="478" who="S0326">I think <anon type="place"/> should stay in print</u>
<u n="479" who="S0329">oh you've got Cricinfo on your phone <pause dur="short"/> anyway that's good fifteen quid <pause dur="short"/> hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> tomorrow you should receive them by Saturday but I cannot guarantee it</u>
<u n="480" who="S0326">magazines are annoying to read on Ipads</u>
<u n="481" who="S0329">I find them really good to read on the phone <pause dur="long"/> and I find the ones with the <trunc>illustr</trunc> what I think is I mean the <anon type="place"/> app is really not very good and one of the things that makes it not very good is that we <unclear/> to illustrate it <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0326">I read a <anon type="place"/> on my phone it's just not that good</u>
<u n="483" who="S0329">no the <anon type="place"/> app is absolutely rubbish it's appsolutely rubbish erm <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="484" who="S0326">how much is the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0329">well it's just a lot</u>
<u n="486" who="S0326">how much is it?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0329">erm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0326">the magazine?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0329">I don't know about four quid or something</u>
<u n="490" who="S0326">I might buy it if I was <unclear>getting</unclear> on a train or something</u>
<u n="491" who="S0329">it's so boring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's</u>
<u n="492" who="S0326" trans="overlap">that's er that's what's good about it though when I was <trunc>d</trunc>doing my exams it was the best way to get to sleep which was to read a <anon type="place"/> for like ten minutes I'd fucking pass out</u>
<u n="493" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0329">but that's</u>
<u n="495" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but I'll just read like something that I have no interest in <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0329">that's the thing er I er I when I look at it and when I read it and it's so boring and then I think well it's so boring and then I look around at my colleagues and these weird people who are so weird and boring and I think well no <trunc>w</trunc> no wonder no wonder it's boring I look at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I don't think it's that boring</u>
<u n="498" who="S0329">well sometimes we <trunc>j</trunc> sometimes we have amazing pieces I would say there's probably one piece each week <pause dur="short"/> at least and sometimes there's more than that <pause dur="long"/> I think I might have a drink tonight</u>
<u n="499" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0329"><unclear/> <unclear>hand</unclear></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="501" who="S0326">it's like you're driving me home from primary school</u>
<u n="502" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>I know</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so have you been in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0326">yeah I just messaged him to get the number of the driving guy but that's a bit <unclear/> but I don't think he's in the country</u>
<u n="504" who="S0329">oh why? did he not get back to you?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0326">no he did but I I just I got the impression I think I saw something on Facebook as well</u>
<u n="506" who="S0329">he does a lot of film work <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I think he's gone somewhere really that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't want him to go to like Syria</u>
<u n="507" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="508" who="S0329">god it better not rain for this party what am I gonna wear? <pause dur="short"/> oh I can take my new raincoat</u>
<u n="509" who="S0326">wear that with the backpack <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0329">depressed disabled person <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean she doesn't <pause dur="short"/> you know that book that was so bad that I was reading?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0329">erm I was emailing her and er we emailing about various books and things I said anyway I I've just read one of the worst books I've ever read if not the worst I can't oh it's mesmerisingly bad I got to the end cos I was just couldn't believe that somebody had allowed themselves to put one sentence after another <pause dur="short"/> like this and she wrote to me this morning saying well I read it and I <trunc>th</trunc> er I thought it was really quite good it's really interesting erm quite good as a portrait of people living in <anon type="place"/> and I just thought well that absolutely confirms it for me that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got no fucking judgement</u>
<u n="513" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0329">no taste or judgement she cannot have she cannot have</u>
<u n="515" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0329">to think that that is a <trunc>re</trunc> that you know <trunc>t</trunc>to <trunc>re</trunc> to say this was quite a deft portrait deft portrait of people who are just not like any human beings ever</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="517" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0329">funky <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> you don't smoke nearly as much as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0326">I only <unclear/> smoke when I go out <unclear/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0329">it's just such a disgusting habit</u>
<u n="521" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>kn</trunc>knocks them back</u>
<u n="522" who="S0329">he <trunc>w</trunc> he's well I like sweeties I mean he's a he's an addict <pause dur="short"/> like sugar he's got to be careful and he'll rot his teeth because he'll drink and he won't brush his teeth <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0326" trans="overlap">how many cigarettes do you think him and er him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get through? er they probably went to <anon type="place"/> cos tobacco's cheap</u>
<u n="524" who="S0329"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="525" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0329">erm I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a very sweet boy but I find him such a a difficult presence to have in the house <pause dur="short"/> I feel I've done you know ten years of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do I have to do any more?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0329">do you get me? <pause dur="short"/> what's happening here?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="529" who="S0326">look how many of them there are <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0329">how many of what? flats?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0326">flats</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="532" who="S0329">I know but I mean we it's a good place to build flats but why do they have to be so? you've been in them haven't you?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0326">yeah they're they're well they come with <trunc>furn</trunc> they come with like knives and forks <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're just for like they're I think they're <trunc>d</trunc> there's they're <trunc>d</trunc> they're built for people's parents to get their twenty young twenty something children</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="534" who="S0329">man this isn't good for the <anon type="place"/> party</u>
<u n="535" who="S0326">they are <trunc>th</trunc>they have they done it outside before?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0329">yeah <pause dur="long"/> what does it say from the weather at at <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you can check when you get home</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="538" who="S0329">I mean it doesn't seem to be <trunc>settl</trunc> oh though it's very grey <pause dur="long"/> I love the way it's <anon type="place"/>'s Cypriot Association and the menu is onion bhaji samosa</u>
<u n="539" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0326">it's funny when you it's funny when you get such odd things on erm on menus <pause dur="short"/> especially translated menus there was one where in Portugal a <trunc>men</trunc> there was a menu for selfish <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0329">for what?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0326">selfish</u>
<u n="543" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when I</u>
<u n="544" who="S0326" trans="overlap">selfish platter</u>
<u n="545" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0326">do they have something called like something there was a starry egg I don't know what that's meant to be? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>s</trunc>starry egg? that's fantastic</u>
<u n="548" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's funny cos in Europe everybody I guess that everyone has ends up having to speak English so like so if you're when we were in Greece there was like a French <trunc>Fr</trunc>French couple and then they asked in <trunc>ver</trunc> not very good English what something was to the waiter who replied in not very good English so she was like what is a veal? and he goes oh it it's beef</u>
<u n="549" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0329">well it is beef it's baby cow</u>
<u n="551" who="S0326">no it's not</u>
<u n="552" who="S0329">veal?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0326">it's it's er deer</u>
<u n="554" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="555" who="S0326">venison venison</u>
<u n="556" who="S0329">oh venison</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="557" who="S0329">have you been in <unclear/> school of dancing?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0326"><unclear>no no but</unclear> I probably never will be</u>
<u n="559" who="S0329"><unclear>I'd be over there</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0326">this place is good <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0329"><anon type="place"/> I know the guy who runs that <pause dur="short"/> is it really good?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0326">well <trunc>y</trunc> <unclear/> you should know how what it's called then</u>
<u n="563" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0326">what's it called?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0329"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0326">no it's not</u>
<u n="567" who="S0329">isn't it called that?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0326">the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0329">oh the <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I think it's absolutely horrific <unclear/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0326">it's good because er it's like</u>
<u n="571" who="S0329" trans="overlap">look at <anon type="place"/> can't wait for that to open that have you not noticed how it smells of coffee round here? roasting coffee they're gonna need a barista they're gonna need staff <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0326"><unclear>I <trunc>c</trunc> don't er think</unclear> I can't really bring myself to do that</u>
<u n="573" who="S0329">earn a lot of money have a transferable skill</u>
<u n="574" who="S0326">I can't do it at <anon type="place"/> it's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I'm gonna get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to teach me on his unbelievably expensive I tell you what if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't want to drive this car she can drive <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s coffee machine <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>high</unclear></u>
<u n="576" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
