<text id="SDTD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-05-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0422 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A car journey from St Anne's on-the-sea to Preston</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Directions, The Hay festival, Books/stories. Illness/Pregnancy, talk about the past/childhood, shopping, train strikes, exams, the Queen, moving house process, supermarkets, shops</topics>
		<activity>Family talks during a car journey to the shops</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Advising, Anecdote telling, Making Arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0422">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kosice</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Slovakia</birthcountry>
				<l1>Hungarian</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East European</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0422">right</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">I would have been here a bit sooner I had a slow puncture just after I texted from the other side of <anon type="place"/> to <unclear/> seems to be alright <pause dur="short"/> so erm what's the do you know the best way to get to <anon type="place"/>? cos it's probably not on the motorway is it? <unclear/> or is it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0421"><unclear/> is terrible <unclear/> cos it's holidays</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> along there</u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">why was it busy?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0423">no no just</u>
<u n="7" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no motorway so if you go</u>
<u n="8" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I know how to get to the motorway just get out at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0422">yeah and then I know it from there</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423" trans="overlap">then go on the <anon type="place"/>? it just seems the wrong way to do it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0422">no no not</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so I get on the <anon type="place"/> and come off there somewhere?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">alright well I'll get on there you tell me when to come off</u>
<u n="15" who="S0422" trans="overlap">the first one to <anon type="place"/> yeah I know it from there cos we used to live there so <unclear/> forward because if you go the A road and the other way it's so busy that road where my house was where I rented is best way near the hospital</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I wouldn't have thought at this time it would</u>
<u n="17" who="S0422" trans="overlap">oh it's half term isn't it? so it could be go on then <pause dur="long"/> which way are you going? it's that way</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423">do you not go through the town though?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0422">no go down here that's a quicker go down here next street to</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I've just gotta go with</u>
<u n="21" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="22" who="S0423">coming up that main road</u>
<u n="23" who="S0422"><unclear/> and then turn <unclear/> left <unclear/> or go <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> I was so sick this morning I can't <unclear>think</unclear> where they <unclear/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0423">well I thought you might change your mind cos <unclear/> is it indoors this place you're going to?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0422">it's like erm <pause dur="short"/> it's like a big Mothercare with Boots you know like a big <unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0421" trans="overlap">a retail park</u>
<u n="27" who="S0423">which one is it?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0422"><unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0423">oh that one near where your house is?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0423"><unclear>oh</unclear></u>
<u n="32" who="S0421">oh is it <anon type="place"/>? I thought it was a different one?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0422">no it's not</u>
<u n="34" who="S0423">oh I thought you wanted to go to the centre <unclear/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0422">no <unclear>no one goes there</unclear></u>
<u n="36" who="S0423">straight on here?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0422">yeah <unclear/> centre</u>
<u n="38" who="S0421">yeah see I bet you thought you were gonna be walking round all these shops <vocal desc="laugh"/> but we're just going to <unclear>see</unclear></u>
<u n="39" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> er right</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423">yeah just bring back on the second <unclear/> over to the right by there and</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I did say we just want to go to one and pick something up and you were like</u>
<u n="42" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I thought it'd be one of these you know</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">stores you know big centres in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0422">no</u>
<u n="46" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="47" who="S0423">because then I could have gone</u>
<event desc="sound of car horn"/>
<u n="48" who="S0422">who's that? <pause dur="long"/> that's the closest Mothercare there's one in <anon type="place"/> around <unclear/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0423">have you been in Aldi lately? you know they've got a load of child er stuff there</u>
<u n="50" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah probably while we're there I wanna go in and have a look at that seat because it's so <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> only got it yesterday</u>
<u n="51" who="S0423">I dunno what <unclear/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah they've got a catalogue <unclear/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0423" trans="overlap">did er the other day getting some food and some <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0422"><unclear/> the whole catalogue <unclear/> summery stuff it's too late <unclear>for me</unclear> cos I've already got it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0423">and is there nowhere is <anon type="place"/> is there nothing in <anon type="place"/>? <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0422">no there's no Mothercare or anything <pause dur="short"/> that's the problem there's no <unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0423">Hay Festival's on this week <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you know <unclear>that</unclear>?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0421">I know yeah well I've missed it I always miss it because I mean it's not too bad this year erm because I I probably well I mean I could have gone because it's half term but I always have exams <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I know I've come I've forgotten about it since we went</u>
<u n="60" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="61" who="S0423">that first year I thought oh I'll look out every year and <unclear/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well I've always looked out but</u>
<u n="63" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and I never I and then I've just heard it on the radio this morning they were there for radio <unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no yeah I always look out for it and everything but usually it's happening like a week that I'm actually at school and I mean it was half</u>
<u n="65" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is it not always on half term?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0421">no it it's sometimes like when I'm at school and I'm thinking well I can't like take the day off</u>
<u n="67" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos I don't <unclear/> on for like could be ten days isn't it?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0423">and I thought part of that cos there is a a weekend where it's for young people isn't it?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0421">yeah yeah well sometimes it like like I mean I could have gone at the weekend or something but it's always been inconvenient since we've been because of exams</u>
<u n="71" who="S0423">yeah so I think it was half term that time we went what wasn't it?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0421">er yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0423">erm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0421">but I think that was a good few years ago that like so I didn't have exams</u>
<u n="75" who="S0422" trans="overlap">come on</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">oh right it was cos of exams?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? yeah it's always in the wrong</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423"><unclear/> think you were probably about fourteen then <unclear>weren't you</unclear>?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0421">well I don't know if we went in half <trunc>t</trunc> oh yeah I think yeah it was last weekend</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">it might yeah it was at the end <unclear/> wasn't it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423">but since then I said oh I'll keep an eye out for it and erm <unclear/> on the radio station they they were there er to present the you know the five hundred words thing</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421">oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">kids short stories</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423"><unclear/> I I've heard something on the radio the other day as well they were saying oh it's they had a a presenter who said she went there first when she was a girl and bought her first <unclear/> said how good it was to go back after all those years and <unclear>had loads</unclear> of people talking about it you know <unclear/> saying <unclear/> and I just think when we went cos I didn't <unclear>know</unclear> a thing <unclear/> seemed to be a <unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0421">well yeah because erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> look out for other years to see if we can get a time when</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well we <trunc>cou</trunc> yeah well because last year we were just kind of were like oh when shall we go? oh we'll go now and we didn't book anything and all the people I wanted to see were on after we'd been and I was like</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I I was looking weeks in advance to see what</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well you didn't tell me</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423">I was I was I discussed it with you but we I <unclear/> we were restricted on dates or <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I think probably because we went at kind of at the end of half term</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423">cos you kept saying oh I can't see anyone I'm interested in and then there were maybe one or two and you said oh we're not going then</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421">well yeah there wasn't</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0421">on the day on the day we went there was like no one I wanted to see but after we went there was all these people who I was like oh I wouldn't have minded seeing them but we couldn't have gone on those days I don't think cos maybe you were working</u>
<u n="100" who="S0423" trans="overlap">if your mum or I was working mm <pause dur="short"/> but they there's a there's a Hungarian author won the booker prize this year</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421">oh did they? did they?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">yeah it's it's been translated into English</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">I thought it was erm someone Australian</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421">maybe that was last year?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I heard about that is that not a different award?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421">maybe it's a different prize yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423">yeah <unclear>and</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> and he's at the Hay Festival doing a talk as well</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421">they have erm a Hay Festival in Budapest like</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh they're all over the world</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421">yeah yeah but there's one in Budapest yeah cos on that T-shirt that I bought last year it had all the cities on that they do it in</u>
<u n="112" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> so you'll have to remind me in the future maybe or keep an eye out for anything interesting <unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well the problem is is like I struggle to find erm one day that I'm like oh yeah there's loads of things I want to see on this day it's usually like oh there's someone at the start of the week that I might wanna go and see and then someone in the middle or at the end or something</u>
<u n="114" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0423">well that's the erm <unclear/> just to <unclear/> but if you're doing English literature you might do something <unclear/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0421">what at the Hay Festival?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">no your university going down there or something</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421">I don't think so they'd be like go if you want to <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I don't think they I don't think they organise trips like that</u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> so were you not well this morning?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0422">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0423">are you feeling a bit better now?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423">and how long is it now <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0422"><unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0423">oh it is to the <unclear/> to the motorway</u>
<u n="127" who="S0422">oh <unclear/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="128" who="S0423">but then again I don't know if it might take me <unclear>on</unclear></u>
<u n="129" who="S0422">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0423">doesn't take me on right at the beginning but you don't you don't come off</u>
<u n="131" who="S0422" trans="overlap">don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0423">till <anon type="place"/> anyway do you? <unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0422">maybe <unclear/> around</u>
<u n="134" who="S0423">how many months is that?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0422">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0423">so you keep</u>
<u n="137" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> to nine on <unclear/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0423"><unclear/> told <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0422">yeah but because I'm not well I still get sick so <pause dur="short"/> like car sickness</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423">where's your dad? has he gone to the cat place?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0422">yeah <pause dur="long"/> are you gonna take <unclear/> B and Q <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423">oh yeah yeah you have to take a left <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I think I'll just use this way cos the sat nav said this way just <unclear>quick</unclear> to get to</u>
<u n="143" who="S0422">go sat nav in the <unclear/> in case you get lost in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0423">can't actually do <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know how you always get lost we've been going <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it's just one of those places where I don't know where</u>
<u n="147" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we've been going to the cinema for how many years? <vocal desc="laugh"/> we we're still sometimes an hour late</u>
<u n="148" who="S0422">well <anon type="place"/> ain't like <unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos we're just circling around the same place</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423">well you see it's funny centre of <anon type="place"/> is you take a wrong turn you get stuck in the one way system <pause dur="short"/> and that one in <anon type="place"/> it's like it's some kind of a different place</u>
<u n="151" who="S0422">I've never been to that</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423">it's er <unclear/> down by the <unclear/> in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0421">the the erm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0422" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="155" who="S0423">I was struggling to find it</u>
<u n="156" who="S0421">the other day I was walking</u>
<u n="157" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the <unclear>docks</unclear>?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0422">you go from <unclear/> that takes you there <unclear/> but then again from <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0421">I was walking to college like I don't know a few weeks ago now and erm this lady she was walking and er er she just seemed to be like crossing the road a few times <pause dur="short"/> and then she came up to me <pause dur="short"/> and she was like oh you don't happen to know whereabouts the erm are the docks near here? and I was like <pause dur="short"/> erm I don't think so right and she's like oh I must've taken a wrong turn and I'm like I I don't think the docks are around here I don't know where they are from here though <pause dur="short"/> the docks aren't near my college are they?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0422">no</u>
<u n="162" who="S0421">she must've been miles away</u>
<u n="163" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>probably</unclear> walking</u>
<u n="164" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yes she was walking <pause dur="short"/> and she was like oh I must have just taken a wrong turn I'll go back towards the centre <pause dur="short"/> and I was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't think I don't think you're going the right way <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> she had like a backpack on and stuff</u>
<u n="165" who="S0423"><unclear>she's probably been like walking then</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> see I was listening to <unclear>that</unclear> radio <unclear>Hay</unclear> Festival and then a thing come on about a book about a cyclist going through Cornwall</u>
<u n="166" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0423">so I listened to that as we're going to Cornwall aren't we?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0421">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0423">and they were saying about all the fishing villages <unclear>they went through</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> and then erm the fairytale come on</u>
<u n="170" who="S0421">oh did it?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> fairytale I don't know if you've heard of it? Baba Yaga?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0423">you've heard of that one?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0423"><unclear/> a witch</u>
<u n="176" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I've read that one yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0423">oh have you?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0423"><unclear/> I thought of you <unclear/> vampire <unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0423">cos that's something you'd you've er been told yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0422" trans="overlap">that's what <unclear>we</unclear> call a witch</u>
<u n="183" who="S0423">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0421">yeah we I think we read that in primary school</u>
<u n="185" who="S0423">did you?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0423">she eats children</u>
<u n="188" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0423">cos they were saying well really it's more like a goddess and she's portrayed as bad but she's a bit of bad and a bit of good really</u>
<u n="190" who="S0421">yeah I think it was weird yeah cos we you know in assemblies at primary school? they always used to like read us a story or something</u>
<u n="191" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0421">and I think they read us that one</u>
<u n="193" who="S0423"><unclear/> thought was <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0422" trans="overlap">I think this is the longer way you know up to the motorway</u>
<u n="195" who="S0423" trans="overlap">this is a cut-through <pause dur="short"/> oh is it?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0423">oh right well would it be better to go straight on where we instead of turning off?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0423">that's what it was signed as to go straight on <unclear>wasn't it?</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so I would have been on it by now? <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0422">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0423">so do you go on the <anon type="place"/> <unclear>not</unclear> here?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear>we've gotta come on from there <pause dur="short"/> we've gotta come from there</unclear></u>
<u n="203" who="S0423"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> is it the <anon type="place"/> we wanna <unclear>go on don't we?</unclear></u>
<u n="204" who="S0422"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/> and then after <anon type="place"/> <unclear>just at the junction</unclear> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's only about ten minutes away <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0423">so what what is there particular stuff you need?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0422">I need to pick up some blankets er for the Moses basket <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> you know the ones that have got <unclear/> like those <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah like <unclear/> type thing <unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0422"><unclear>then</unclear> it's the best quality theirs there's no point me getting cheaper ones <unclear/> and er <pause dur="short"/> I want to have a look at this <pause dur="short"/> thing in <unclear/> that big art there's a massive <unclear/> next <unclear>to it</unclear> as well <pause dur="short"/> it's very good stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0423">yeah they usually are reasonable quality there and good prices <unclear>aren't they</unclear>?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0422">yeah it's German stuff <unclear/> isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> remember when I got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that chair she used to sit in that panda one? <pause dur="short"/> cos she didn't wanna lie down anymore in her cot</u>
<u n="211" who="S0423">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="212" who="S0422">like a chair she used to sit in</u>
<u n="213" who="S0423" trans="overlap">chair?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0422">yeah like a <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="215" who="S0423">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0422">she got bored <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> after a while in the cot she wanted attention <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> that one <unclear/> sold out <unclear>online</unclear> so I'm hoping they'll have <unclear>them</unclear> at this one</u>
<u n="217" who="S0423">well they haven't got <unclear>it online either?</unclear></u>
<u n="218" who="S0422"><unclear>online</unclear> is <unclear>a different</unclear> shop though <unclear>a different outlet as well</unclear></u>
<u n="219" who="S0421">did you ring them to ask if they've got it?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0422">no <pause dur="short"/> they'll have the <unclear>white</unclear> ones so</u>
<u n="221" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="222" who="S0422"><unclear>if nothing else I can get</unclear> the white ones</u>
<u n="223" who="S0423"><unclear/> not gonna find out <unclear/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0422"><unclear/> no</u>
<u n="225" who="S0423">so it's not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="227" who="S0423">it's the next one is it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0422">yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said there may be a train strike on the date of her exams</u>
<u n="229" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0421">I know what a nightmare is that?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0423">how are you gonna get to college then?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0421">don't know</u>
<u n="233" who="S0423">what just one day?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0421">no erm three days</u>
<u n="235" who="S0423">they're striking for three days?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0421">yeah there's gonna be one strike and then like a few days later there's gonna be one for two days it's not certain yet but I think they might do something about it because the London Underground will strike as well</u>
<u n="237" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0421">yeah so I think it's about pay it's the erm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0423">I thought that was a different with the <unclear>overground</unclear> and <unclear>the trains</unclear></u>
<u n="240" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no it's</u>
<u n="241" who="S0423">it's all the same union?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0421">it's erm what was it called? the national railway or something like that and they Northern Rail's part of it and like Virgin trains and like there's a long list and it said London Underground so I'm like</u>
<u n="243" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> why they're negotiating then</u>
<u n="244" who="S0421">because it's gonna be a nightmare in London <vocal desc="laugh"/> the underground's not going</u>
<u n="245" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0421">so I'm thinking they might not care about Northern Rail not going but if the London Underground's not going they might do something so hopefully they won't strike</u>
<u n="247" who="S0423">yeah there's time to sort it out yet isn't there? <pause dur="short"/> when's your next exam then?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0421">the eleventh</u>
<u n="249" who="S0423">and your last one's the fifteenth?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0421">the nineteenth</u>
<u n="251" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="252" who="S0421">I've got one on the eleventh</u>
<u n="253" who="S0423" trans="overlap">right so they're all kind of crammed in <unclear/> sorting out <unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah one on the eleventh and then that's so that's one week and then the next week I think I've got it I think it's the fifteenth and the nineteenth</u>
<u n="255" who="S0423">it's not long really is it?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0423">you're not far off the first of June <pause dur="short"/> before you know it you'll <unclear/> <unclear>it'll all be done</unclear></u>
<u n="258" who="S0421">I know I can't wait gonna be summer nineteenth of June in the I don't know about twelve o'clock I'll be finished <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0423">that'll be a nice feeling won't it?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah and then thirteenth thirteenth of August is results day</u>
<u n="261" who="S0423"><unclear>it's what?</unclear></u>
<u n="262" who="S0421">what?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0423">results</u>
<u n="264" who="S0421">results day on the thirteenth of August</u>
<u n="265" who="S0423">do you have to go into college for them or?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0421">er yeah <trunc>be</trunc> well you can get them online but you've got to go in for your certificates</u>
<u n="267" who="S0423">oh so will you be checking online?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0421">yeah you'll be able to get them from about like I don't know like six o'clock in the morning online</u>
<u n="269" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0421">but people who <unclear>were</unclear> erm waiting for offers because universities sometimes get them before erm so they go onto UCAS to see if they've been accepted or not</u>
<u n="271" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0422">everybody seems to be waiting for August this year</u>
<u n="273" who="S0423">how do you mean?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0422"><unclear>I'm I'm waiting till</unclear> August now as well all this is over <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't wait for August</u>
<u n="275" who="S0423">have you been given a date yet?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0422">well if it's thirty-nine weeks it'll be the fifteenth of August</u>
<u n="277" who="S0423">and what's thirty-nine weeks is that the normal length?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0422">it's normally forty but they don't <unclear>want it to</unclear> start natural <unclear>they <pause dur="short"/> don't</unclear> want that</u>
<u n="279" who="S0423"><unclear>but</unclear>  you thinking taking it even a bit earlier then won't you?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no it's <unclear/> actually this is more dangerous than to go to thirty-eight weeks than thirty-nine <pause dur="short"/> sorry no thirty-seven they said rather thirty-seven than thirty-eight weird than thirty-nine it's one it's no <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was I think  looking forty-one or forty-two</u>
<u n="281" who="S0421">more I was a month late</u>
<u n="282" who="S0422">no</u>
<u n="283" who="S0423">it wouldn't have happened</u>
<u n="284" who="S0422">that much no</u>
<u n="285" who="S0421">you said I was a month late because I was supposed to be born on the twentieth of January</u>
<u n="286" who="S0422">twenty second but they calculate in weeks so</u>
<u n="287" who="S0421">oh well there you go then that'll be like</u>
<u n="288" who="S0422">almost <unclear/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> three and a half or something weeks</u>
<u n="290" who="S0423"><unclear/> well you were too comfortable where you were weren't you?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0421">I know yeah</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="292" who="S0421">I wanted to be born in February</u>
<u n="293" who="S0423"><unclear>didn't you</unclear> wanna be born in my month?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="295" who="S0423">oh why not?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0421">I don't know</u>
<u n="297" who="S0423"><unclear>didn't</unclear> want to be a Capricorn?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0421">no I wanted to be a Pisces</u>
<u n="299" who="S0423">is that what you were thinking at the time?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0421">yeah I was I was thinking I was like I wanna be born as a Pisces so gonna wait a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0423">thought you'd wanna get out sooner cos <unclear>all squashed</unclear> in there <unclear>you</unclear> were so big <pause dur="long"/> do you know if we go left or right here <unclear/>? very top <unclear/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0422" trans="overlap">go on the roundabout no and then you er</u>
<u n="303" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0422">I'll tell you which</u>
<u n="305" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0422">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0423">the queen's in <anon type="place"/> today</u>
<u n="308" who="S0421">yeah she's visiting that castle</u>
<u n="309" who="S0423"><unclear/> she's going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0422">is she?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0421">is she?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0423">she's going there's an equestrian centre cos she's into her horses isn't she? so there must be some place where</u>
<u n="313" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no going with <unclear>them</unclear></u>
<u n="314" who="S0423">well no I don't think she's going to the centre it's probably out of the centre a bit it's gonna be somewhere with <unclear>the</unclear> schools and things</u>
<u n="315" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0423">but er it's a horse place</u>
<u n="317" who="S0421"><anon type="place"/> university where erm had it on their like website yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh did they? is that how you know?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0423">saw it on <unclear/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we're like oh we're <unclear>getting</unclear> the queen to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is she going to the university?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0423">think she might <unclear/> visit there <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0422" trans="overlap">wanna be that way</u>
<u n="326" who="S0421">oh well she might do</u>
<u n="327" who="S0422" trans="overlap">that that one yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0421">who knows? <pause dur="long"/> do you think the queen can just like go down to the corner shop and buy some bread and some milk? or would people be like? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0423"><unclear/> they wouldn't</u>
<u n="330" who="S0421">they wouldn't let her</u>
<u n="331" who="S0423">if she insisted they might <unclear/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0421" trans="overlap">they might yeah but they'd have to take like guards</u>
<u n="333" who="S0423">about twenty people and bodyguards and everything else <pause dur="short"/> but er that film was out <unclear/> a week wasn't it <unclear/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0423">about the queen supposedly a very similar true story <unclear/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know but they say based on a true story and it's like</u>
<u n="337" who="S0423">well the only <unclear/> is <unclear>other people</unclear></u>
<u n="338" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah it and it would be so dramatised and</u>
<u n="339" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah they probably they probably heard a bit of the story</u>
<u n="340" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0423">made up everything about that <unclear>idea</unclear></u>
<u n="342" who="S0421">yeah like like you hear you watch films that have been like based on a true story you start thinking wow did that really happen? and then when you actually look up what happened in the true story it was not nearly as exciting as it it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah they always make more of a <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I can understand how <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yeah but</u>
<u n="345" who="S0422" trans="overlap">close to the hospital yeah so</u>
<u n="346" who="S0423">left?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0422">not just yet there's the <unclear/> and then</u>
<u n="348" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0422">you just <unclear/> a erm traffic lights <unclear/> go on <unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0423">where straight?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0422" trans="overlap">just make it no left</u>
<u n="352" who="S0423" trans="overlap">left here?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0423">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0422">and if you go that way <unclear>it's a nightmare</unclear> so <unclear/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0423"><unclear/> fair well there</u>
<u n="357" who="S0422">I know <pause dur="short"/> they're <unclear/> here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0423">well yeah the hospital wasn't far from <unclear>you</unclear> was it?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0422">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was good</u>
<u n="360" who="S0423"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> that shopping place is <unclear/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0421" trans="overlap">we could have literally walked to the hospital for something</u>
<u n="362" who="S0422" trans="overlap">oh I <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0423">oh there's the posh the posh shop there</u>
<u n="364" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0422">I don't think there's any around <anon type="place"/> <unclear>is there</unclear>?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they're all <unclear/> from across the <unclear/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0422" trans="overlap">what a shame</u>
<u n="368" who="S0423">when of course <unclear/> over there</u>
<u n="369" who="S0422">oh got some nice ones</u>
<u n="370" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it probably is in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0423">which is a bit more upmarket <unclear/> I suppose <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0422">it's a good <unclear>hospital</unclear></u>
<u n="374" who="S0423">is that where they teach in as well?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0421">yeah <anon type="place"/> has connections with it to do like the nursing programmes so although I mean <anon type="place"/>'s not well not many people want to go to <anon type="place"/> but if you want to do nursing then it's good because of the hospital</u>
<u n="377" who="S0423">yeah it's just as well you're gonna be in <anon type="place"/> cos I think <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> obtain <unclear>size</unclear></u>
<u n="378" who="S0422">well they don't have a maternity there</u>
<u n="379" who="S0423">oh they don't have one?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0422">no</u>
<u n="381" who="S0423">so <unclear/> special measures and doing that and the other but</u>
<u n="382" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no I wouldn't <unclear/> anyway <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0423">straight up?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0422">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0423">is there no progress on the house? have you not come <unclear/> a completion date on it <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0422">oh yeah I did the <unclear/> over</u>
<u n="387" who="S0423"><unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="388" who="S0422">two weeks ago so they <unclear>sent out</unclear> straightaway to the language I think that's what they make <unclear/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0423">yeah probably <unclear/> now</u>
<u n="390" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so that's also <unclear/> and you know the survey I questioned it</u>
<u n="391" who="S0423">oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0422">and erm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0423">have they got your quotes and all that?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0422">actually the estate agent they <unclear/> really they're really good the ones in in the show and <unclear/> erm and she said like she'll send the surveyor and she'll get me quotes but she had it surveyed <unclear/> and she got quotes back for me</u>
<u n="395" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0422">yeah it's very good and she didn't charge me for it</u>
<u n="397" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="398" who="S0422">and er what I did was er then I told her that they <unclear/> you know what the figures were and then I looked through it because er tax wasn't included you know the</u>
<u n="399" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>income</unclear> tax</u>
<u n="400" who="S0422">well you know the on the top there's tax as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0421">ah it's our old house</u>
<u n="402" who="S0422">erm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> what? what do you?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0422" trans="overlap">you know they give you a quote and they said plus tax? well I wanna know how much that is so I had to calculate it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0423">oh you mean VAT or the work?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah VAT yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="408" who="S0422">so erm and</u>
<u n="409" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0422">erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah and I said to her er <pause dur="short"/> I'd be quite happy to have the work done if the vendor agrees to erm reduce it by that much and then I have <unclear/> done with this company because I think they must have something out of it do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0422">because so many connections</u>
<u n="413" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and are they are they suggesting that then?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0422">she said straightaway yeah I'll I'll send it over to I'll send over the survey and I'll tell her erm you know</u>
<u n="415" who="S0423">have you heard back from <unclear>the surveyor</unclear>?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0422" trans="overlap">not yet no not yet</u>
<u n="417" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I mean if they don't then <unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0422" trans="overlap">I know waste of time yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0423"><unclear/> probably just really very expensive <unclear>is it</unclear>?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0422">well it was about seven hundred each</u>
<u n="421" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="422" who="S0422" trans="overlap">without tax</u>
<u n="423" who="S0423">you do want if they say no <unclear/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0422" trans="overlap">well when I come to</u>
<u n="425" who="S0423"><unclear/> probably say well what about meeting half way each or something?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="427" who="S0423">try to compromise as least <unclear>then</unclear> you get half of it</u>
<u n="428" who="S0422">yeah so er but then again you know the next person can come and they can do the same so if she wants to wait <unclear/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they're gonna wanna as well they're not gonna want to wait are they?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no if they wanna sell yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0423">they're gonna want to sell it they've got you there otherwise it's gonna take <unclear/> more they may as well have that back in <unclear/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0422" trans="overlap">and the estate agent's not <unclear/> cos she's gonna get something out of me anyway isn't she? from some people <unclear>so</unclear></u>
<u n="433" who="S0423">well yeah they get what a percentage of a sale they to one up to two percent probably one and a half two percent</u>
<u n="434" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no not just the house no the work as well</u>
<u n="435" who="S0423">oh right yeah she might get a so</u>
<u n="436" who="S0422" trans="overlap">they organised it yeah but they're really good really no a a I'd sell my house and I recommend them to anyone around there who wants to sell their house because you know what I'm like with estate agents the amount of times we er sold the house</u>
<u n="437" who="S0423" trans="overlap">was it right?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0422">yeah same as <unclear/> traffic lights or something <pause dur="short"/> the amount of times so <unclear/> a real pain in the backside I hate estate agents so much</u>
<u n="439" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well they usually like change a bit if they're small owned place then they have to look after their customers a bit more don't they? rather than just the <unclear/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0422">that's the worst thing of selling a house is the bloody estate agents I hate them but these ones are really good very fair but <unclear/> yeah a family business of thirty years my estate agents <unclear/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's great it's a small business they've gotta look after their customers properly</u>
<u n="442" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0421">oh there's Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="444" who="S0422">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's nice that Sainsbury's <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="446" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> your supermarkets <unclear/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0421">still I've still not been to</u>
<u n="448" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="449" who="S0421">I've still not been to that multistorey one in <anon type="place"/> that we passed <pause dur="short"/> the one with like five escalators</u>
<u n="450" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I know that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0422" trans="overlap">been going on about it for ages</u>
<u n="452" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0421">did you find it?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0422">yeah I did <unclear>it was</unclear> by the end where you if you're going <anon type="place"/> on the front it's by the end just where the road disappears and the track starts that's where you turn</u>
<u n="457" who="S0421">because I think we spotted it when we were lost <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0423">it's good getting lost sometimes innit? <unclear/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0422">it's <unclear>annoying</unclear> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so many one way streets and also it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="461" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's that's it yes <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> left isn't it?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0423">why why don't we for our holidays <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we just do a tour of the country and go visit <unclear>those</unclear> supermarkets?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0421">no because they're all the same</u>
<u n="465" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Morrisons that new one is er <unclear/> like a <unclear/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh that really nice one?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah like all black glass and everything like</u>
<u n="468" who="S0421">oh is that the one we went in?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0421">and it's like nice inside like a <trunc>war</trunc> the the converted warehouse?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0422">I don't know is it?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0421">I don't we went in one that was like a converted warehouse</u>
<u n="473" who="S0422"><unclear/> to Morrisons being a bough house style</u>
<u n="474" who="S0423">yeah surprising surprised they're building any more the getting the <unclear/> they're losing loads of money</u>
<u n="475" who="S0422">Morrisons?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0423"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> although I think also the supermarkets are</u>
<u n="477" who="S0421">wow where are people shopping?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0423">well well a lot of them are going to Aldi and Lidl aren't they?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0421">oh right yeah they're doing well</u>
<u n="480" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0423">getting a difference with</u>
<u n="482" who="S0422" trans="overlap">well they'd all started bringing the prices up as well</u>
<u n="483" who="S0423">yeah well Tesco's started bringing them down cos there's a Lidl</u>
<u n="484" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> if they're not careful</u>
<u n="485" who="S0423">there's an Aldi near Tesco and you can see they're trying to match the prices erm so they try it's on certain products not on all of them <pause dur="short"/> I mean Asda's always been a bit cheaper than Tesco anyway and there's certain things Aldi that I like to go in for I never used to go in there but</u>
<u n="486" who="S0422">the <unclear>certain</unclear> stuff is <unclear/> there</u>
<u n="487" who="S0423" trans="overlap">some stuff is really good yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0421">it's a wonder all the <trunc>in</trunc>independent market places are still going</u>
<u n="489" who="S0423"><unclear/> so <unclear/> shops are closing <unclear>down</unclear></u>
<u n="490" who="S0421" trans="overlap">who's buying? who's even who's even shopping and buying things from them?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0423">well I suppose if somebody doesn't have a car and it's just convenient to walk round the corner</u>
<u n="492" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0421" trans="overlap">all the rich people <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0423">what has your dad gone out on his bike today?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0423">has he got waterproofs and what have you? wanted to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah he does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got it him the lot <pause dur="short"/> the jackets trousers</u>
<u n="499" who="S0423" trans="overlap">did you? for a present?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0421">no I just I just got it and then he gave me the money</u>
<u n="501" who="S0422" trans="overlap"><unclear/> online</u>
<u n="502" who="S0421">yeah bought them online for him</u>
<u n="503" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="504" who="S0422">yellow vest</u>
<u n="505" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0423">oh right the high vis <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> get <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0421">oh yes</u>
<u n="508" who="S0423">I'm not sure you're supposed to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0422">she's <unclear>doing</unclear> education isn't she? <unclear/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think it gets cold in <unclear/> when <unclear/> that age</u>
<u n="511" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="512" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0421">ah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> like here's your <trunc>th</trunc>thousand to spend this month <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0423">it's in here is it to the right? yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0422">oh <unclear/> this one no can <unclear/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0423">well whenever I've driven by here there's always queues waiting to get in there</u>
<u n="519" who="S0422">well does <unclear/> to the motorway <pause dur="long"/> the <unclear/> gone</u>
<u n="520" who="S0421">it's been knocked down</u>
<u n="521" who="S0422">I hope not</u>
<u n="522" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's a right on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0423">there's a Boots over there as well</u>
<u n="526" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0423">might well <unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0422"><unclear/> on and where is it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0421" trans="overlap">are you sure there's a</u>
<u n="530" who="S0422" trans="overlap">there was one yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0423" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0422">okay it's not here</u>
<u n="533" who="S0421">there's a Mamas and Papas?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0422">no it's not here</u>
<u n="535" who="S0423">why did you think it was here? must be one in <anon type="place"/> if it's not here</u>
<u n="536" who="S0421">yeah I was <trunc>sup</trunc> you said <anon type="place"/> I'm sure it's not at I'm sure you must be thinking of another retail park cos I never thought that there was a Mothercare at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0422">must have thought there <unclear/> Mamas and Papas</u>
<u n="538" who="S0421">is Mamas and Papas no good?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0422">no</u>
<u n="540" who="S0423">don't you wanna look in that anyway while you're here?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0422">let's <unclear>wait</unclear> and come out</u>
<u n="542" who="S0423">you never know this <unclear/> there but I know that's kinda still <unclear/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0422" trans="overlap">yeah no <unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it looks posh</u>
<u n="545" who="S0422">I'll nip into Boots</u>
<u n="546" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you want to pop into Boots and then?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0422">yeah I'll nip into Aldi and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can have a look on her phone where that Mothercare is there must be another <trunc>pla</trunc> er part of <unclear/> here cos there's a massive one <unclear/> why was I so sure it was here?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0421">I I didn't think it was the <anon type="place"/> one you meant cos I <unclear/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0422">you could have said</u>
<u n="550" who="S0421">well I said are you sure it's? and you're like yeah yeah it's called <anon type="place"/> and I was like oh okay then</u>
<u n="551" who="S0423">there's more up here is it not up here?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0422">no that <unclear/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I was like I'm sure it's not</u>
<u n="554" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0422">yeah <unclear/> maybe <unclear>not</unclear></u>
<u n="556" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what's that <pause dur="short"/> motorcycle?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0421">we could go in disabled</u>
<u n="558" who="S0423"><unclear>there's</unclear> a disabled eh?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0421">no but mammy can't walk <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you need a bus though don't you? <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>these</unclear> are the docks</u>
<u n="560" who="S0423">oh no don't tell me it's there</u>
<u n="561" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0423">I'm not going there</u>
<u n="563" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we'll be like we'll be circling for hours</u>
<u n="564" who="S0422" trans="overlap">no it's not</u>
<u n="565" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't use a sat nav I didn't know this shop was there</u>
<u n="566" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's near Morrisons</u>
<u n="567" who="S0423">yeah I think there is a Morrisons down there isn't there?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0422">I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0423">oh yeah I think we've been I think I remember passing by there now</u>
<u n="570" who="S0422">oh we can go home that er that's alright can go that way home and <unclear/> away then</u>
<u n="571" who="S0421">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0422">ah <pause dur="short"/> way</u>
<u n="573" who="S0423"><unclear/> can you get out there?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0422">yeah hopefully <pause dur="short"/> I'll roll out</u>
<u n="575" who="S0421">we should have gone in the children's one</u>
<u n="576" who="S0423">yeah I <unclear/> you're getting a bit big for that now <unclear>aren't you?</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of car doors"/>
<u n="577" who="S0421">I brought my sunglasses and it's raining</u>
<u n="578" who="S0422" trans="overlap">see <unclear/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0421">oh I brought my sunglasses and it's raining it was sunny</u>
<u n="580" who="S0423">do you need an umbrella?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0421">no I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> that's new</u>
<u n="582" who="S0422"><unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I know might look in there</u>
<u n="584" who="S0421">what the? yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0423">it's what?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0421">Mamas and Papas must have mistaken it well the idea I did try to tell you I was like well I don't think it's <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> no one ever listens to me</u>
<u n="587" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I'm surprised you didn't just look it up <pause dur="short"/> well you can go into the Aldi anyway</u>
<u n="588" who="S0422">yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0423">Boots</u>
<u n="590" who="S0422">we can go on our way home <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<u n="591" who="S0422">do you need anything from Boots?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0423">well you know what I'm looking for?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0422" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0423">a spray bottle where would I get one of them? it won't be in here will it?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> for like twenty P I saw some the other day</u>
<u n="596" who="S0423">oh right yeah <unclear/> there</u>
<u n="597" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like I said to erm I said to mammy I was like can I have one of these spray bottles? she's like what for? what do you want yours for?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0423">er to spray vinegar</u>
<u n="599" who="S0421">oh <pause dur="short"/> I've got one for my bonsai</u>
<u n="600" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what did you want one?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0421">no I've got one for my bonsai</u>
<u n="602" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I can't anything you see with anything in it tends to be chemicals so I can't buy one of them and empty it or anything should be an empty one really</u>
<u n="603" who="S0421" trans="overlap">er yeah you can get empty ones in here but I I think was it <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0422">er <anon type="place"/> I think</u>
<u n="605" who="S0421">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0423">right you know what I might look in that erm <anon type="place"/> shop</u>
<u n="607" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah why don't you?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0423">rather than looking at baby stuff here</u>
<u n="609" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0423">you want to erm when you're finished in here do you want to call me?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0423">yeah?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0423">if not text me</u>
<u n="615" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0423">or whatever and I'll <unclear/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you can get some</u>
<u n="618" who="S0423">it's only next door</u>
<u n="619" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0423">so I can meet you outside yeah?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0421">yeah okay bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
