<text id="SDY6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0481</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Discussing the weekend. </topics>
		<activity>Catch-up on the way home. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, inviting, anouncing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0481">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Brommie</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Thrapston</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>w_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Business Manager Agriculture</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0481">to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0439">what so not taking nan?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0481" trans="overlap">hang on hang well I and I <trunc>sai</trunc> oh yeah but oh I suppose if I shoot down in the morning nan'll be tired won't she? I thought fucking <unclear/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="5" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so I was well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't go cos he'll be watching the cricket well England were all out for a hundred and thirty-nine</u>
<u n="6" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so I suppose well I suppose he went as well</u>
<u n="8" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0481">so no so she and she didn't see her yesterday</u>
<u n="10" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0481">I mean <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="12" who="S0439" trans="overlap">did she thank you for the wine?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0481">yeah she thanked me for the wine and <trunc>n</trunc>nan just tried to give me some money for my birthday well I <trunc>tur</trunc></u>
<u n="14" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="15" who="S0481" trans="overlap">I turned it down I said I if I want something nan I'll give you a</u>
<u n="16" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0481"><unclear/> erm and then we went to a <trunc>f</trunc> little <trunc>foo</trunc> a little food fair at the <anon type="place"/> which is a a very nice Edwardian house <trunc>op</trunc>opposite the university but it wasn't very good it wasn't my kind of thing</u>
<u n="18" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0481" trans="overlap">nothing fantastic but you know we had an <trunc>after</trunc> <trunc>d</trunc> a an <trunc>af</trunc> a a day out and she was it was like going to er <anon type="place"/> you know it's quite a long day by the time you've got there</u>
<u n="20" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0481">so I left at eight o'clock in the morning and got back at four</u>
<u n="22" who="S0439">mm that is a long day</u>
<u n="23" who="S0481">so it's an eight hour day which your mother had made two cakes</u>
<u n="24" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0481">and that was about her lot</u>
<u n="26" who="S0439">yeah I was surprised why didn't mum come and pick me up?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0481">oh I don't know I just don't I mean since Friday night when she got in <pause dur="short"/> I mean she just doesn't do anything</u>
<u n="28" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0481">this morning I got up at six made the tea did some ironing went off at eight and she she hadn't moved from bed</u>
<u n="30" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0481">I dunno it's crap absolute crap <pause dur="short"/> got in tonight so she</u>
<u n="32" who="S0439">did she come to <anon type="place"/> as well?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0481">no</u>
<u n="34" who="S0439">no?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0481">cos she <trunc>wa</trunc> go she was busy she was she was gonna do the well she hasn't touched the bloody tiling of course that bloody thing in the garage why she just doesn't she's fucking lazing around that bloody house</u>
<u n="36" who="S0439">what tiling?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0481">there's some tiling to do those strips of</u>
<u n="38" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah in the bathroom</u>
<u n="39" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah and then she comes down and says have you thrown away? I don't give a fucking shit if I've thrown away</u>
<u n="40" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0481" trans="overlap">it's not stopping you making a bloody cake or anything is it? it's just the</u>
<u n="42" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you know it just don't make any sense anyway how did you get on?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0439">good</u>
<u n="45" who="S0481">yeah?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0439">it was really good and really fun well I wouldn't well well</u>
<u n="47" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah no it was quite fun actually</u>
<u n="49" who="S0481" trans="overlap">how was your running mate was she alright?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0439">she was fine yeah she came in a little bit after me she came in like ten minutes after me but</u>
<u n="51" who="S0481" trans="overlap">well you were ran together though?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0439">well we did we got to ten miles together and then she started to drop off a bit and</u>
<u n="53" who="S0481" trans="overlap">and you <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0439">no no no I tried but it was quite difficult</u>
<u n="55" who="S0481" trans="overlap">it's quite <trunc>diffic</trunc> yeah I found it yeah it's like yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's quite difficult to run at someone else's pace</u>
<u n="57" who="S0481">I know it's the same as cycling you've just gotta go at your pace</u>
<u n="58" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0481">and erm you know it's okay if you're in a team and you're behind somebody else you'll be <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="60" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0481">but as you go on further you just can't do it can you?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah like I tried and stuff and it kind of became really annoying because people kept walking which I realised don't get me wrong <trunc>i</trunc>it is thirteen miles and it is long but they just they don't walk they don't suddenly like go to the side and walk they walk in the middle of the running and you're just like <pause dur="short"/> oh so you just end up like weaving around them</u>
<u n="63" who="S0481" trans="overlap">well no I mean I just think if you can't run thirteen miles don't do the</u>
<u n="64" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well yeah don't enter it yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0481" trans="overlap">fucking thirteen miles yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0439">yeah I I did</u>
<u n="67" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="68" who="S0439" trans="overlap">think that like there were people</u>
<u n="69" who="S0481" trans="overlap">I mean a thirteen mile walk is is anybody could do a thirteen mile</u>
<u n="70" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0481">bloody walk</u>
<u n="72" who="S0439">there were like people walking really early on and you're just like why did you enter? like I actually I did actually run all of it I didn't walk once</u>
<u n="73" who="S0481" trans="overlap">particularly as it's on a ballot is it?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0439">some of it's for charity</u>
<u n="77" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0439">some people get charity places</u>
<u n="79" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0439">but then you kind of like you're you're raising money because you're gonna run this run and you don't run it you walk it and it's a bit like</u>
<u n="81" who="S0481"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0439">what's the point? if you can't run thirteen miles</u>
<u n="83" who="S0481" trans="overlap">well no there's not point doing it yeah I know</u>
<u n="84" who="S0439" trans="overlap">don't enter the half marathon yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0481" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="86" who="S0439">but no it was really good they had loads of like Great North Run events going on on Saturday</u>
<u n="87" who="S0481">good</u>
<u n="88" who="S0439">and then this morning it was Mo Mo got his fifty-nine minutes didn't he?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0481">did he?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0439">Mo Farah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh oh dear that would have been <unclear/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah Mo Farah ran he got his personal best of a half marathon</u>
<u n="93" who="S0481" trans="overlap">what for the <unclear>ten metre</unclear> for the half marathon</u>
<u n="94" who="S0439">for the what? did you say ten metres?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0481">ten well I meant ten thousand</u>
<u n="96" who="S0439">oh I see yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0439">no for the half marathon he won the er he won it and he did it in fifty-nine point eighteen seconds</u>
<u n="99" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh did he?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0439">or something like that fifty-nine minutes eighteen seconds last year he got over he didn't get under an hour and he was a little unhappy</u>
<u n="101" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="102" who="S0439">oh <trunc>li</trunc> oh fuck off</u>
<u n="103" who="S0481">well I I got back from <anon type="place"/> and er your mother was <unclear>sitting</unclear> I thought I've gotta get some air so I got on my bike and I went out made my loop forty-six minutes ten it was I'm trying to get</u>
<u n="104" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0481" trans="overlap">under forty-five minutes for my loop</u>
<u n="106" who="S0439">what loop? how many miles is it?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0481">it's twelve and a <trunc>ha</trunc> eleven and a half miles but it doesn't matter how far it is it's the loop it's how big it's the hills involved and all the</u>
<u n="108" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know but isn't it embarrassing that well not embarrassing but isn't it weird that Mo Farah can run thirteen miles in nearly the same amount of time it takes you to cycle it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0481">he's not going up and down my hills though I tell you</u>
<u n="110" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no he's not no that's true I was thinking that today cos like by the time we cross the finish <trunc>li</trunc> the start lines like it was something like forty minutes we'd been waiting forty minutes to actually cross the start line and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like so you do know that Mo Farah's nearly finished? and she was like oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0481">how long did it take you to cross the start line?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0439"><trunc>thir</trunc> about forty minutes</u>
<u n="113" who="S0481">oh bloody hell</u>
<u n="114" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know there were thousands of people</u>
<u n="115" who="S0481" trans="overlap">how did you meet up again then <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> as you weren't stopping?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos we all</u>
<u n="117" who="S0481" trans="overlap">to go for the last part</u>
<u n="118" who="S0439">cos they have like a family reunion section</u>
<u n="119" who="S0481">right</u>
<u n="120" who="S0439">sadly none of my family were there at reunite with me but erm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0481">your mother she yeah your mother went she went to she went to Liverpool this morning</u>
<u n="122" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> god erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had agreed to meet us at the Z because you were supposed to line up where your <trunc>l</trunc> what your last name is but we thought because no one's</u>
<u n="123" who="S0481" trans="overlap">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="124" who="S0439" trans="overlap">last name is Z</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">we'll go to</u>
<u n="126" who="S0481" trans="overlap">good idea</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the zed section so we met up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came in a bit later and I met up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0481" trans="overlap">did did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not run?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> runs all the time though</u>
<u n="130" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh so how did you meet beforehand on it?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">well how did I meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> before?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439">in general? oh I met</u>
<u n="134" who="S0481" trans="overlap">no today with <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="135" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="136" who="S0481"><trunc>y</trunc> where how did you start off together?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">er I'm I met her in a café</u>
<u n="138" who="S0481">oh right</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439" trans="overlap">we met them in a <trunc>caf</trunc> well I met them</u>
<u n="140" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439">in a café in <anon type="place"/> and then we walked up together</u>
<u n="142" who="S0481">did you go out last night then?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">no dad I didn't</u>
<u n="144" who="S0481">oh didn't you?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439">I went to bed quite early last</u>
<u n="146" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh did you?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well no I went to bed at about ten last night</u>
<u n="148" who="S0481">right</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">then the youth hostel was fine</u>
<u n="150" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah you said yeah <pause dur="short"/> busy was it everyone heaving with athletes?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">actually no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0481">the smell of liniment was all over the place was it?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it really wasn't like I wandered round and I spent the day on Saturday wandering around Newcastle and I wouldn't say it was overly busy</u>
<u n="154" who="S0481">oh</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">today obviously was the</u>
<u n="156" who="S0481" trans="overlap">did you go over to the museum in Gateshead? did you go were you going over there? no? the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">oh no I went to <anon type="place"/> Centre last time</u>
<u n="158" who="S0481">oh right that's right</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I did pop in today yeah er yesterday</u>
<u n="160" who="S0481">as you do you just pop in</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">pop into the <anon type="place"/> but that's well they were having like these erm <pause dur="short"/> they called it like the Great North Games basically they I think it was like not professional professional athletes but not like Olympic athletes or something I don't know and they were having like mini competitions and they were having pole <trunc>vo</trunc> pole <trunc>vo</trunc> vaulters</u>
<u n="162" who="S0481" trans="overlap">pole oh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439" trans="overlap">pole voters? pole vaulters and erm that's not what I'm saying</u>
<u n="164" who="S0481">oh</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh no high <trunc>ju</trunc> no what's the one with the yeah the pole when you have a pole and you have to jump up really high over the beam</u>
<u n="166" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah pole vaulting yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">yeah pole vaulting and they had like and they got kids involved and did like kids' running races</u>
<u n="168" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and I think they had the junior Great North Run which was like five o'clock until like</u>
<u n="170" who="S0481" trans="overlap">very good</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I just wandered around Newcastle and <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0481" trans="overlap">was anybody else you knew running it?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure somebody</u>
<u n="174" who="S0481">it's like these you know</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439" trans="overlap">who knows?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0439">there's one every week it's like it's like music festivals innit? you can go er</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what running races?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0481">yeah you can do about</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0481" trans="overlap">half a dozen a week these days I mean</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I could run I could run a ten K every week pretty much if I wanted to</u>
<u n="182" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439" trans="overlap">from now until <trunc>ne</trunc> they go they kind of like peter off in the summer</u>
<u n="184" who="S0481">do they?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">but erm in the winter you can run one like every week</u>
<u n="186" who="S0481">oh right</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439">there's loads coming up in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah there's the cycling erm <pause dur="short"/> you can do <trunc>th</trunc>these Sportives ervery weekend and I strangely enough this year I've I I <trunc>b</trunc> I'll I I've booked I paid for two that didn't go on</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0481">I went on one I didn't pay for cos they turned up and said you needed a helmet so I thought fuck this for a bunch of <trunc>sol</trunc> I'll just follow the signs round</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0481">so I followed the signs round stopped off at the food <trunc>pla</trunc> no one bothered it at all</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0481">and then I did one but they only did half of what I originally intended to do so in future I'm not sure that it's actually <pause dur="short"/> I was planning to do the one where I did the eighty and then the hundred</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0481" trans="overlap">that day that was good but the rest of them I haven't really enjoyed <trunc>ver</trunc> if <trunc>v</trunc>very much at all</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">I think running is a bit <trunc>har</trunc> no that's not true obviously cycling is very hard but</u>
<u n="198" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439" trans="overlap">running races kind of give you a set distance and they give you the route and it means you don't have to plan it yourself</u>
<u n="200" who="S0481" trans="overlap">well that's the same whether it's the that's the same</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0481" trans="overlap">with the Sportive but they're not races</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">no no same as <trunc>ru</trunc> same as runners</u>
<u n="204" who="S0481" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">like</u>
<u n="206" who="S0481" trans="overlap">but but they time you well well there isn't a single cyclist now who needs an external timer cos they've all got</u>
<u n="207" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0481">they've all got Garmins or whatever they've got</u>
<u n="209" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know someone said to me the other day cos I said that I was running this and they're like oh have you got your Garmin ready? I'm like no and they're like oh why do you not have one? I'm like because I don't need one I run over the finish line it tells me how long it took me I'm happy with that like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has a Garmin and it tells her like her pace and <trunc>h</trunc> you know like it beeps every time she's done a kilometre and stuff and I'm just like I don't care</u>
<u n="210" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">like I don't care how fast I'm running it's not gonna <trunc>in</trunc> it's not gonna make me run any faster and it tells me when I get to a kilometre because there's a sign that says one kilometre so</u>
<u n="212" who="S0481">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439" trans="overlap">why would I need to spend sixty pounds on a</u>
<u n="214" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439" trans="overlap">watch?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0481">like mine's erm mine on the bike is four thirty quid forty quid I think to fit it on the wireless</u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0481">speedo thing I did I tell you when I was going up a hill one day and this voice said next door to me you have done sixteen point four miles an hour for the last mile?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">oh wow was that the thing?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0481">this no this bloke must have had a verbal Garmin</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="222" who="S0481">as he cycled up the hill past me <pause dur="short"/> a motivator telling him how fast he was going</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">see but they have it on the Ipod the Ipod has a fitness app and it tells you like</u>
<u n="224" who="S0481" trans="overlap">well that's probably what it was then</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">it's like when it's like you have done three kilometres</u>
<u n="226" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">it's like great thanks</u>
<u n="228" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">just in case I wasn't aware of that</u>
<u n="230" who="S0481">I know</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">but but today's run actually was okay</u>
<u n="232" who="S0481"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I generally thought I was gonna die like</u>
<u n="234" who="S0481" trans="overlap">were you?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I was really really nervous</u>
<u n="236" who="S0481" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0439" trans="overlap">about doing it and then actually I didn't get tired at all</u>
<u n="238" who="S0481">no</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">well my legs are really sore but my actual breathing was fine like I know that</u>
<u n="240" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">my lung capacity er erm I'm capable of</u>
<u n="242" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439" trans="overlap">doing it</u>
<u n="244" who="S0481">yeah I</u>
<u n="245" who="S0439" trans="overlap">my legs are just a bit <unclear>wooden</unclear></u>
<u n="246" who="S0481" trans="overlap">I factored I that I was not really I I <trunc>wa</trunc> er er <trunc>jus</trunc> you definitely go through breakthrough moments don't you?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="248" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you know you go through when I I slightly too heavier than I am but Friday</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439" trans="overlap">me too</u>
<u n="250" who="S0481">Friday night's gym was just an absolute doddle</u>
<u n="251" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0481">you know the it's a forty-five minute spin and ab</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0481">and the ab was just not an issue at all</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439">I I find with running</u>
<u n="256" who="S0481" trans="overlap">it's it's not that each exercise doesn't hurt</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">no no it's just yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0481" trans="overlap">but you're not you're not dying for two days after</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0481" trans="overlap">like you used to be you know</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439">I find with running is that you run to the distance so if you're running a ten like if I'm running a ten K I'll be really knackered by the time I get</u>
<u n="262" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah don't ask me to run another kilometre</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">but if er like today I was like okay another mile another mile</u>
<u n="266" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and then like by the time and they have like countdowns like you've got eight hundred metres to go</u>
<u n="268" who="S0481">oh right</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you've got four hundred metres it's like oh my god this is the longest four hundred metres of my entire life</u>
<u n="270" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">oh well done man cross over the the white line that you're not allowed to cross over just</u>
<u n="272" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yes you are the if it's <unclear>cashed</unclear></u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">oh okay I take it back</u>
<u n="274" who="S0481">you can do but you know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">yeah but no if you</u>
<u n="276" who="S0481" trans="overlap">what do you want to do for dinner?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">is there anything?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0481">yeah well we've got a</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="280" who="S0481" trans="overlap">chicken will chicken salad do you?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">oh yeah I'll have just a</u>
<u n="282" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439" trans="overlap">chicken salad I love chicken salad</u>
<u n="284" who="S0481" trans="overlap">well I have that <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="285" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="286" who="S0481">we have a chicken salad yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439" trans="overlap">did you not have anything at nan?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0481">oh yeah I had something at lunchtime we didn't have any</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="290" who="S0481" trans="overlap">breakfast I just had a small</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0481" trans="overlap">meal with nan and I had one of your tubes of Smarties to keep me going</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="294" who="S0481">before I went off on my bike</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">I was really naughty today <pause dur="short"/> cos like after the Great North Run you either had to get a bus back or the Metro back and I had pre bought a Metro ticket so I was like okay I'll get the Metro the queue the Metro I kid you not contained thousands of people like forty-three thousand people ran it <trunc>apparentl</trunc> or was it forty-seven? forty-seven thousand people <trunc>ra</trunc>ran it apparently but the queue for the Metro actually went all the way down a street that was about a hundred metres up the other side of the road it was horrendous so what did I do? I went to the front of the queue nipped into the erm Caffè Nero on the top of the queue bought a sandwich and then just came out and kind of just like slipped in to the queue <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0481"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">and I was like I am not waiting in this bollocks am I <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>no</trunc> no one questioned me no one said anything I was like I am not waiting</u>
<u n="298" who="S0481" trans="overlap">they're British they're British</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0481">they just tut tutted you</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">they probably did but I didn't care I was like I have to get I have to get back to Newcastle have a shower and then get on the half past five train I am not waiting in that queue</u>
<u n="302" who="S0481">how far out of Newcastle was it then?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439">South Shields?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0481">oh right</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">so it was quite far</u>
<u n="306" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">well thirteen miles apparently</u>
<u n="308" who="S0481">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="310" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yes it's not a loop then you run from</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no you run</u>
<u n="312" who="S0481" trans="overlap">Newcastle to South Shields</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0481" trans="overlap">and you have to get back</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0481">oh right <pause dur="short"/> you would have thought they'd organise that a bit better wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah the Metro was having a real problem they were having real issues with the Metro today so I don't know if it's normally like that bad but today it was horrendous</u>
<u n="318" who="S0481" trans="overlap">wouldn't have thought so</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">yeah and like the problem was like this the the Metro had to move to a station and it couldn't move on till the train in front of it had moved on from the next station so it was just this massive this really bad staggered process so</u>
<u n="320" who="S0481">oh right</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439" trans="overlap">we'd er be waiting at stations for about five ten minutes at a time</u>
<u n="322" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh so they cocked up</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0481">I mean it just be difficult I mean you</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah with that many people</u>
<u n="326" who="S0481" trans="overlap">no I mean you've been to Twickenham on the tube and</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah true yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you know and that's</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439">a pain in the arse as well</u>
<u n="330" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah that's all everybody's all crammed up together</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0481" trans="overlap">I never like doing that at all</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="334" who="S0481">I'd rather drive and wait in a carpark than try and go on the tube I didn't enjoy that</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">I've been on the the few times I've been on the tube it's been okay but it's because after the match we've normally gone somewhere afterwards for a drink just to let</u>
<u n="336" who="S0481" trans="overlap">probably</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439" trans="overlap">everything go down</u>
<u n="338" who="S0481">that takes a long time to get down though doesn't it that tube?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> go to the <anon type="place"/> and have a drink</u>
<u n="340" who="S0481">so like we waited a long time and I <trunc>g</trunc> I got back to <anon type="place"/> and they had two two blokes from Yorkshire had missed the train back to Yorkshire</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">oh shit</u>
<u n="342" who="S0481">but they <unclear/> it was pathetic</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0481" trans="overlap">on a Saturday night <unclear>out of there</unclear></u>
<u n="345" who="S0439">yeah so dad have you got your rugby tickets ready?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0481">for what?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439">the world cup I was taking the piss dad</u>
<u n="348" who="S0481">no haven't got any</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">that's neither have I <vocal desc="laugh"/> someone <trunc>sai</trunc> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad said to me he goes have you got any tickets? and I said no and he went why not? I thought you were a proper rugby supporter I'm like I am that's why I'm not paying</u>
<u n="350" who="S0481"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">eighty-five to two hundred and fifty pounds for a shit ticket to see two crappy teams play each other he was like that's not the point you're a rugby player you're a rugby supporter</u>
<u n="352" who="S0481">no</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so you should be involved and like</u>
<u n="354" who="S0481" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">no no no I am not gonna be mugged off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0481">I'm a <trunc>cust</trunc> no they're if they view me as a customer I'll act like a customer</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0481">you know <pause dur="short"/> it's like football supporters they're customers that's how they're viewed why they think they're any more than that I just do not know</u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like I'm gonna watch erm some of the matches on like on the TV but I'm not I <trunc>w</trunc> I'm not gonna like pay that much money to go and see the people who</u>
<u n="360" who="S0481">it's like it's like it's like</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't even care about</u>
<u n="362" who="S0481">you could book a ticket to watch it on the big screen at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">oh dad why aren't we there? <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no I've got no interest in it like I'll I will go watch the matches at a pub with some friends but I'm not gonna pay that much money to go to see them like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is poor spent over two hundred and fifty pounds on tickets and you're just like <pause dur="short"/> that's what?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0481"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">but how was oh how was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0481">fine your mother thought he was better than <pause dur="short"/> she'd seen him for a while his hearing when he'd had his earpiece cleared out and he said I can hear things I've never heard for years he said</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did he</u>
<u n="368" who="S0481" trans="overlap">cos he</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439" trans="overlap">give you an in depth description of how his ear was cleaned out?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0481">well</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he normally does</u>
<u n="372" who="S0481" trans="overlap">it's how everything gets cleared out</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0481">er er so we struggled to find the printing works but we found it in the end and when you found it you can understand why you'd struggled to find the printing works</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="376" who="S0481">anyway the bloke in charge er it was a letterpress printer which is</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="378" who="S0481">er so it you have to set each letter</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">oh god</u>
<u n="380" who="S0481">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> of course knew all how to do it</u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">yeah cos he worked on the newspapers didn't he?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0481" trans="overlap">and yeah and and this bloke was just doing it so that all your letters are up your your upper case are in the casements obvious why it's called</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0481">upper case the one in the bottom are called lower case they're all positioned as so well ones you use more often are close together</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah? but of course they're in reverse</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so when you set type up you have to set the word up in reverse and all the letters are reversed and this bloke could just do it like this</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0481">you know I'll just set up today's date for you he said and then you can and there it was and the things like mind your Ps and Qs comes from the fact that P and Q looked very similar</u>
<u n="391" who="S0439">and they had to be reversed</u>
<u n="392" who="S0481">and they had to be reversed</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0481">and you think how they ever bothered to print stuff but and and every letter had to be you know typed and they had some real they had six point</u>
<u n="395" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0481"><trunc>s</trunc> on the end of tiny little letters</u>
<u n="397" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0481">and this well of course we still use the word point don't we and font and all those words?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0481">and he said we found these recently upstairs and he said and they were wooden blocks and he said there was two or three of each one he said and we we couldn't quite work it out he said so we started stamping he said and then we realised that one was the letter one was the italic version and one and the others were the were the shadow</u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">oh wow okay</u>
<u n="402" who="S0481">of what now these were wooden large wooden blocks</u>
<u n="403" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0481">that people must so he said we've started using them he said to to show it and and they they used them for one of their calendars that they were trying to do</u>
<u n="405" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh so grandad liked that then?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0481">oh yeah it's er sorts of machines he hadn't used for thirty years</u>
<u n="407" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0481">you know and there he was explaining the minutiae of them this bloke said this is a nineteen sixty-five machine I said so and he said nineteen eighty er <trunc>ni</trunc> eighteen sixty-five did did I say eighteen sixty-five? and I said no you said <trunc>eigh</trunc> nineteen sixty-five is it nineteen? yeah it looked really sort of olde worlde</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0481">everything was picked up by</u>
<u n="411" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0481">by a bit of suction flicked over a but no it was a Heidelberg from eighteen er nineteen sixty-five</u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="414" who="S0481" trans="overlap">and this was a really whizzy machine and it's</u>
<u n="415" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0481"><unclear/> was there they were still using them</u>
<u n="417" who="S0439">wow</u>
<u n="418" who="S0481">predominantly small run stuff specialist</u>
<u n="419" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0481">small run stuff for other people</u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">did you see the erm Tour de France?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0481">no</u>
<u n="423" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="424" who="S0481">this it took us so long to get well to get to the <trunc>pla</trunc> not a particularly long time</u>
<u n="425" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0481" trans="overlap">but we got there half tennish rather than ten o'clock</u>
<u n="427" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0481">then we were in there for an hour and a half <pause dur="short"/> erm and we couldn't we could have gone south to catch it as it went round</u>
<u n="429" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0481">past but but going back north again I decided not to try and catch it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0481">and it was very wet yesterday morning anyway when we got to <anon type="place"/> and there was</u>
<u n="433" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah it was a bit wet in Newcastle as well</u>
<u n="434" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so it wouldn't have been particularly enjoyable er so on the way back we stopped at the first pub we came to</u>
<u n="435" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0481" trans="overlap">for lunch</u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0481">and there was a lady there playing on her computer and yes they were open the whole time there we were the only people that went in that pub</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439">oh god</u>
<u n="440" who="S0481">three of us it was really weird</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439">what was the food like?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0481">excellent</u>
<u n="443" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="444" who="S0481">absolutely excellent she cooked three meals plus starters your mother as usual had a starter and then didn't finish her main course you know</u>
<u n="445" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0481">fucking and er <pause dur="short"/> absolutely fine</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439">mm that's good did you see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or did you no?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0481" trans="overlap">no they're in Spain</u>
<u n="449" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="450" who="S0481">but er he was a bit miffed that they hadn't offered him the football tickets</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439">oh what twats</u>
<u n="452" who="S0481">cos I could have well I presume that they give them to <pause dur="short"/> what's it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or something <unclear>him and his mum</unclear></u>
<u n="453" who="S0439">you just oh I just hate them</u>
<u n="454" who="S0481"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and of course the world evolved around your mother having a haircut you know</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0481">so we had to go back into <anon type="place"/> for her to have a haircut and then he he wasn't really oh he was <unclear>looked</unclear> very good but he's not he's not he wasn't very mobile in the afternoon so we parked in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0481">and he had to walk back to the first church was like a bit of a <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> arty farty sort of stuff then I bought a book</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh what was it? open studio no?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0481" trans="overlap">it well it er well it wasn't open studios it was open buildings which was but</u>
<u n="461" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0481" trans="overlap">no no but it was a church you know they have they they use the church</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you know so the first one was a <anon type="place"/> the second one was the print show I wanted to go to and he sat there he didn't go round the print show I went round the church and had a look at the prints and then we walked back and just left him to go round to the open the car to open up and he fell over somehow</u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">oh bless him</u>
<u n="466" who="S0481">so anyway I stuck him in the car with a packet of Minstrels for his sugar</u>
<u n="467" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0481"><unclear>levels</unclear> and some water put <anon type="place"/> on the radio</u>
<u n="469" who="S0439">left him there</u>
<u n="470" who="S0481">left him there went back got your mother and said don't <pause dur="short"/> don't fanny around <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>c</trunc>come back so we came back</u>
<u n="471" who="S0439" trans="overlap">was he alright though after his fall?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0481">yeah he seemed he didn't go down heavy</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="474" who="S0481" trans="overlap">he just missed his footing and he I heard him shout before long before he hit the floor</u>
<u n="475" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0481">he sort of sat himself down <pause dur="short"/> well loads of people came and picked him up</u>
<u n="477" who="S0439">oh yeah it was really sad in the erm train station on Saturday morning this man stepped out of this the coffee area and didn't realise there was step and just</u>
<u n="478" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0439" trans="overlap">collapsed on the floor</u>
<u n="480" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">and then like and his drink went everywhere and I helped him up and this other guy came and helped him up but it's weird how like some people react and some people just stare</u>
<u n="482" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and you're just like <pause dur="short"/> I know everybody can't help him but you at least you know</u>
<u n="484" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0439">try to</u>
<u n="486" who="S0481">mm <pause dur="short"/> er so no he was alright he's a <pause dur="short"/> he did a bit of</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="488" who="S0481">did a bit of printing and what have you and but you've gotta find things that</u>
<u n="489" who="S0439">will interest him</u>
<u n="490" who="S0481">yeah you know I don't go there for my benefit although it's it's not that it's uninteresting so</u>
<u n="491" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no but</u>
<u n="492" who="S0481">I mean in two weeks' time there's another air show I think but</u>
<u n="493" who="S0439">oh right</u>
<u n="494" who="S0481">which we'll try and fit I think there's an air show coming up erm we'll try and fit one in for him so yeah erm</u>
<u n="495" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0481">well it's difficult to find things in the winter</u>
<u n="497" who="S0439">and it's basically cos you've got to sit outside so</u>
<u n="498" who="S0481">yeah well that was the problem with Tour de with with the tour you know</u>
<u n="499" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you it says well they're gonna be here the the the the road's closed twenty minutes before they come through</u>
<u n="501" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0481">well you can more or less know when they're gonna come through in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0481">but you can't guess er two hours later because you don't know what the gap is so</u>
<u n="505" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0481">so there could be er they could be either nor there the cars could be either here nor there and it it was harder to organise I've never really tried to do it so I just gave up I didn't even bother</u>
<u n="507" who="S0439">how was the weather <trunc>th</trunc> er today?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0481">it was</u>
<u n="509" who="S0439" trans="overlap">was the weather good today?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0481">yeah we were on an open top bus</u>
<u n="511" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0481">and we arrived at the bus stop and erm there was a peculiar see and anyway the some people had pre booked and I mean that well</u>
<u n="513" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah so why did you have an open top bus tour of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0481">yeah well it was open <trunc>s</trunc> it was open buildings</u>
<u n="515" who="S0439">oh okay as well</u>
<u n="516" who="S0481" trans="overlap">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0439">okay that makes more sense I just thought</u>
<u n="518" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah so we had this to go round and show you round places in <anon type="place"/> so I didn't know you could book on it so we we just we got there early and and <trunc>s</trunc> and signed up well all people were complaining that they couldn't book oh fucking hell it's free you know get on with it</u>
<u n="519" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0481">so we were downstairs and then we got there and when we came back at half past ten erm she was fannying around well some people haven't turned up so if we put people on the top they might have to come down again so we'll wait till half ten anyway we got up on the top and then he said some people then turned up who had</u>
<u n="521" who="S0439">pre booked</u>
<u n="522" who="S0481">they'd pre booked so they wanted to but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said we'll have to go back you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we don't have to go back down</u>
<u n="523" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0481">so so we stood up to go back down and the bloke said well we can squeeze her in at the back there look er and you sit down there mate you you'll you'll be okay</u>
<u n="525" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0481" trans="overlap">and you</u>
<u n="527" who="S0439">she's like</u>
<u n="528" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so so this</u>
<u n="529" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she's an eighty odd year old woman bless her</u>
<u n="530" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so this this couple a lady and her daughter</u>
<u n="531" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0481">kicked us out of our our seats</u>
<u n="533" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="534" who="S0481">me and mother</u>
<u n="535" who="S0439"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0481">you know no sort of oh bloody hell</u>
<u n="537" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0481">and then a family this this lad they had a young kid and the kid just didn't wanna do it</u>
<u n="539" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="540" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so was he got on the top of the bus and thought that no I don't wanna do this so they got off so that alleviated all the problems</u>
<u n="541" who="S0439">kids are <trunc>horro</trunc> kids are so annoying</u>
<u n="542" who="S0481" trans="overlap">and there was er a bloke doing a rather dry droll talk as we went round er an hour and twenty minutes going round <anon type="place"/> it was</u>
<u n="543" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0481">places we hadn't all around the jewellery quarter round <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="545" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0481">bits and bobs on there that I didn't I'd never been round most of the most of the tour so it certainly wasn't wasted</u>
<u n="547" who="S0439">that's cool</u>
<u n="548" who="S0481">parts of it were shit</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah but obviously</u>
<u n="550" who="S0481" trans="overlap">so <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">it's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0481" trans="overlap">then you see the</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439" trans="overlap">of course part of it's crap</u>
<u n="554" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you you see the backs of these places and good god you know</u>
<u n="555" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0481">and then it's you know it it's and you I wouldn't say he was well the point I haven't been on a bus trip <pause dur="short"/> I won't say ever but <pause dur="short"/> er and I've only been on some boat trips</u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0481">and you don't go down roads on boat trips so</u>
<u n="559" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well no obviously dad</u>
<u n="560" who="S0481">so so the number of things you see you've got longer to explain what they are</u>
<u n="561" who="S0439">yeah so</u>
<u n="562" who="S0481" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="563" who="S0439" trans="overlap">obviously on a bus</u>
<u n="564" who="S0481" trans="overlap">you've got</u>
<u n="565" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you've got less time yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0481" trans="overlap">on a bus you're closer to it</u>
<u n="567" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0481">there's a blue plaque here in the right hand side which da-di-da and that</u>
<u n="569" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and it's gone past yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0481" trans="overlap">that's it</u>
<u n="571" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0481">and so it it's it you cover an awful lot in an hour and twenty minutes</u>
<u n="573" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0481" trans="overlap">but you don't cover it in an awful lot of detail</u>
<u n="575" who="S0439" trans="overlap">detail yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0481">er so the technique of doing it is is just entirely different it I <trunc>wa</trunc> I wasn't really aware that you you've got like twenty seconds to say something about a hundred a hundred things rather than mugging up on twenty things that you can really</u>
<u n="577" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0481" trans="overlap">go into depth about you know <pause dur="short"/> but the number of trees we had to keep ducking our heads for</u>
<u n="579" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0481">oh it was surprising how er <pause dur="short"/> how leafy it was <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>his mate</unclear> come it's like said well I've read the books he said there's either six million trees in <anon type="place"/> or nine million trees in <anon type="place"/> it might just have been the same book but turned up the other way it was he was that sort of you know you wouldn't</u>
<u n="581" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so not</u>
<u n="582" who="S0481">which <trunc>h</trunc></u>
<u n="583" who="S0439" trans="overlap">particularly useful but</u>
<u n="584" who="S0481">which he</u>
<u n="585" who="S0439" trans="overlap">would be</u>
<u n="586" who="S0481">which he told me yes you know and he he was very pleasant it it wasn't the easiest of things to hear but it wasn't like you just would have got used to it after a while</u>
<u n="587" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="588" who="S0481">and an open top bus is the <trunc>sa</trunc> you know there's always noise and</u>
<u n="589" who="S0439">yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0481">but you've got a good view from the open topped bus and the weather was</u>
<u n="591" who="S0439">yeah the weather was good today</u>
<u n="592" who="S0481" trans="overlap">it was er it was a bit blowy so that was alright</u>
<u n="593" who="S0439">it was really hot er really hot running this morning <pause dur="short"/> they had special <trunc>sho</trunc> not showers but like erm well yeah showers that you could run through so you'd could</u>
<u n="594" who="S0481">oh right</u>
<u n="595" who="S0439" trans="overlap">be drenched in water</u>
<u n="596" who="S0481"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0439">obviously that's what a shower does but yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they had lots of erm drink and water stations and everything</u>
<u n="598" who="S0481" trans="overlap">oh I <unclear>the clubs</unclear> they would yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the guy on this</u>
<u n="599" who="S0439">people did collapse</u>
<u n="600" who="S0481">yeah they people have died on you know this erm this erm stupid London hundred mile cycle they do?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0481">they <trunc>d</trunc> people have died the last two years on that</u>
<u n="603" who="S0439">oh my god</u>
<u n="604" who="S0481">and <vocal desc="cough"/> whether they're just pushing or they're pushing themselves a bit too far I don't know but</u>
<u n="605" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah there were loads of like signs and stuff being like the weather is hot don't push yourself and stuff like that but erm there's like these ultra marathons you know like in the deserts and stuff and you're just like god</u>
<u n="606" who="S0481">oh I know</u>
<u n="607" who="S0439">why why would you do that?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0481" trans="overlap">I thought <anon type="place"/> had shut</u>
<u n="609" who="S0439">I think it has</u>
<u n="610" who="S0481">well it obviously hasn't they're all open</u>
<u n="611" who="S0439">well maybe it's shutting maybe it's closing down I don't know</u>
<u n="612" who="S0481" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/> might be</u>
<u n="613" who="S0439">as our conversation the other day dad I we none of us really know anything about the pubs in <anon type="place"/> so <pause dur="long"/> unless you're gonna become a pub connoisseur or whatever the word is</u>
<u n="614" who="S0481">I wouldn't waste my time on <anon type="place"/> pubs</u>
<u n="615" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0481">you know if I were a pub connoisseur</u>
<u n="617" who="S0439">a pub reviewer</u>
<u n="618" who="S0481">yeah there was loads of people this place the er the <anon type="place"/> people were moaning there was no <unclear>Bionaire</unclear> stuff er</u>
<u n="619" who="S0439">it's cos it's <anon type="place"/> people</u>
<u n="620" who="S0481" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0439" trans="overlap">don't want like</u>
<u n="622" who="S0481">arty crafty sort of the this time of <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="623" who="S0439" trans="overlap">there's a there there's certain type of person who likes arty art like that</u>
<u n="624" who="S0481" trans="overlap">and also they might they might buy the coming coming up to Christmas mightn't they?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0481">but they ain't gonna buy them in bloody summer are they? so buying bits of veg and <pause dur="short"/> this lady was trying to engage me on why people had to grow the food they wanted to grow so I said well I I do work for one of the biggest seed companies <vocal desc="gasp"/> well what a and so I said well sorry? what's what's wrong because what do you know about what I do? so she</u>
<u n="627" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what she was like rude about what you did?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0481">no but she obviously didn't know <pause dur="short"/> we didn't have any in depth discussion but obviously her understanding of how food works is is <pause dur="short"/> is limited</u>
<u n="629" who="S0439">it's like cloned animal meat we were talking cos like what was it? two or three years ago they cloned meat and said they would would people eat it? well they cloned the animal and then ate</u>
<u n="630" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0439">the meat and people were like oh I wouldn't eat cloned meat <unclear/> <trunc>becau</trunc> but they hadn't read the article they weren't eating cloned meat they were eating the offspring of a cloned animal</u>
<u n="632" who="S0481"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0439">and they were just it was just like you don't even understand what you're arguing about</u>
<u n="634" who="S0481">but potatoes are cloned</u>
<u n="635" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0481">apples are all clones <pause dur="short"/> right?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0439">yeah it's so stupid</u>
<u n="638" who="S0481" trans="overlap">they don't just don't understand what they're talking about</u>
<u n="639" who="S0439">and it's like GM food people are just like yeah but genetically modified stuff is bad I'm like okay so say hypothetically they had a gene they could extract a gene from a human that would stop them from getting cancer would you not want them to do it? and they're like <pause dur="short"/> well yes obviously well that's genetic modification and they're like oh but it's different cos we're humans like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0481">yeah yeah yeah I mean I don't understand why they're concerned I never I never understood why they were concerned because if you put in a gene to <trunc>u</trunc> er sorry a protein you're you're you're you're not susceptible to genes it's proteins</u>
<u n="641" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="642" who="S0481">you're you're you're allergic to if you go and eat a kangaroo burger I suspect there is a protein in there that you haven't actually had before</u>
<u n="643" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0481">or a fish you haven't had so the number of things that people are eating around the country I mean you know people don't peg out do they</u>
<u n="645" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="646" who="S0481" trans="overlap">cos they had a bloody kangaroo burger what's that you've got on there?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that it's my Ipod so yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0481">yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0439">I know people are just so stupid they just don't understand it's like ugh</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
