<text id="SE2C">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:27:34</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0441</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home –Kitchen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Food, friends, relationships, tv programmes, work, complaining.  </topics>
		<activity>Housemate catch-up</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, inquiring, complaining, advising, inviting, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0441">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Mental Health Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">so like what type of erm food did you eat? what was the food like over there?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0441">it was very Americanised</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0441">cos I guess they want to sort of please people don't they?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0441">they had a lot of choice</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">did you stay in like erm a a like a oh what am I trying to say? a resort? or an actual?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0441">it was really good <pause dur="short"/> I'm I want garlic bread <unclear/> when does that go off?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">if you just bought it today it should be fine today</u>
<u n="12" who="S0441">it's fine</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">fine fine or that erm don't know why this suddenly came into my head that cupboard the other day I opened it and it something hit me like this smell absolutely hit me</u>
<u n="14" who="S0441" trans="overlap">which? which cupboard?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">that cupboard going to open it and <vocal desc="misc"/> oh and like the green beans were in a bag</u>
<u n="16" who="S0441">oh shit I forgot about those</u>
<u n="17" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and they so they I binned those <unclear/> but it still kind of smells like something died in there <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was highly concerned there was like a mouse in the back of it</u>
<u n="18" who="S0441">yeah it does smell a little bit like death</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">it does doesn't it <vocal desc="laugh"/> it kind of smells just like something's crawled in there and died</u>
<u n="20" who="S0441">er can you imagine when we move out and find a mouse in the bottom?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439">I don't even yeah yeah yeah I think it's like <vocal desc="misc"/> what is that smell? I had a little look around and I was like I don't know what's in this bag? what's in this bag?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0441">sorry</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah it was fine anyway it was fine like it was in the bag anyway and everything it wasn't dripping anywhere or anything like that</u>
<u n="24" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0439">no no it's fine it was just I was just like mm yummy</u>
<u n="27" who="S0441">yummy</u>
<u n="28" who="S0439">ah <pause dur="short"/> today I had the laziest lunch I had erm I just took in some bread and pate and chutney and just had pate and chutney</u>
<u n="29" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> good lunch though</u>
<u n="30" who="S0439">it was really good I was just so lazy I was like couldn't be bothered to like cook lunch today</u>
<u n="31" who="S0441">ah I have to make a salad I hate coming back to work</u>
<u n="32" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="33" who="S0441"><unclear>make lunches</unclear></u>
<u n="34" who="S0439">Monday was just so nice so I kept thinking it was Sunday for the whole day and when I went up to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was like ah I've got to go back to work tomorrow it's Monday I hate Monday he was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's Monday today I was like what?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0441" trans="overlap">well I thought I felt like it was Monday today</u>
<u n="36" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0441">why was he there on Monday?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0439">oh cos he sometimes just goes to the <anon type="place"/> to work apparently</u>
<u n="39" who="S0441">mm oh you were at the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0439">yeah in <anon type="place"/> he just went there to work and get out of the house I think cos he still lives at home with his parents</u>
<u n="41" who="S0441">does he erm? <pause dur="short"/> does he?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0439">what are you doing to that bagel?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0441">trying to cut it but it's not it's too difficult</u>
<u n="44" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos you're just mangling it aren't you really? why don't you put it in the oven quickly?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0441">cos it takes too long to heat up</u>
<u n="46" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="47" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0439">yeah so</u>
<u n="49" who="S0441">erm <pause dur="short"/> you mean he works there like works there works there?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0439">no no no he goes in with his laptop and does like <unclear/> no no no he does like erm sports you know</u>
<u n="51" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh I see <unclear/> shift</u>
<u n="52" who="S0439">he does his emails has a coffee and does all that stuff there</u>
<u n="53" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I see that's why I was like</u>
<u n="54" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="55" who="S0441">that's weird <pause dur="short"/> he just fancied the change of scene here and there</u>
<u n="56" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> planned on doing some erm yeah some erm bartending</u>
<u n="57" who="S0441"><unclear>oh shit</unclear></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="58" who="S0439">mm he seemed fine it was nice to see him actually I haven't seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> properly in like I haven't spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for that long in ages</u>
<u n="59" who="S0441">well yeah exactly and properly without any <unclear>bother</unclear></u>
<u n="60" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="61" who="S0441">last time I properly spoke to him was when he came to your house once remember? It was like ages ago before any of your house had got redone</u>
<u n="62" who="S0439">oh god <pause dur="short"/> it was a long time ago then wasn't it?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0441">he was talking to us about bee pollen</u>
<u n="64" who="S0439">oh <trunc>go</trunc> oh yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0441">and</u>
<u n="66" who="S0439">aloe vera gel</u>
<u n="67" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0441">and I asked him <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if he told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> off for eating like normal food and he was like no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm sorry</u>
<u n="70" who="S0439"><unclear/> one of the things I asked him actually on Monday I was like ah so are you going to miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s cooking? he was like yeah her cakes are really good I was like yeah they look really good whatever she puts on Facebook he was like yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0441">he'll have to learn how to make them himself</u>
<u n="72" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah well I was thinking he would miss her personality or you know? like her company just her cakes</u>
<u n="73" who="S0441" trans="overlap">just her cakes cakes <unclear/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0439">and that isn't a metaphor</u>
<u n="75" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> bet she's really happy to hear that</u>
<u n="76" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <unclear/> some of her cakes look bloody amazing</u>
<u n="77" who="S0441">yeah I know</u>
<u n="78" who="S0439">I was like come here I want you to be my girlfriend</u>
<u n="79" who="S0441">talented cake woman</u>
<u n="80" who="S0439">yeah <unclear/> she needed something didn't she?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> she did I'm putting it in the oven now</u>
<u n="82" who="S0439">I always find the oven quite quick I know it's you know? I always find the oven quite erm quick actually if I'm honest</u>
<u n="83" who="S0441" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0439">what are you doing?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0441">hit my leg</u>
<u n="86" who="S0439">oh I did erm I've joined the yoga they do yoga in the <anon type="place"/> every Sunday so I've joined that</u>
<u n="87" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0439">the first session was really fucking hard her name's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0439">she did the one at the gym</u>
<u n="91" who="S0441">what does she look like?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0439">she's quite a erm a round woman brown curly hair <pause dur="short"/> not curly hair but like long but wavy kind of hair <vocal desc="misc"/> and she erm it was an hour and a half and it was really intense</u>
<u n="93" who="S0441">how much was it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0439">erm it's a hundred and twenty pounds for fourteen weeks course or something like that no that's why I thought because like because all of the running I'm just stiff all of the time and I don't stretch enough so I thought yoga would be a good way of</u>
<u n="95" who="S0441">it's so good</u>
<u n="96" who="S0439">and it's on a Sunday night at half past seven so it's kind of like you know it's just a nice way to end the weekend I guess</u>
<u n="97" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0439">cos I'm always here Sunday night really so</u>
<u n="99" who="S0441">what time is it at?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0439">half seven till nine</u>
<u n="101" who="S0441">oh is it?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0439">but just like some of the positions are so intense and it's just like although I think she did slightly hurt my knee cos I've got slightly bowed in knees and <trunc>m</trunc> and my knees slightly curve inwards erm and she kept trying to like make me like straighten them</u>
<u n="103" who="S0441" trans="overlap">they always tell you to straighten them out don't they?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0439">yeah and I and I had a really sore knee for the whole of last week like I genuinely was slightly worried I wouldn't be able to do the run cos my knee hurt so much like I had to strap it and take like Diclofenac and Ibuprofen and things like that but I completed it fine it was it was okay but I was a bit concerned it was going to hurt or that I wasn't going to be able to run properly and I think it was because she kept telling me to straighten my leg out without like easing into that position but just to properly straighten it</u>
<u n="105" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no that's really weird that that she did really</u>
<u n="106" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0441">that she wouldn't like do it slowly</u>
<u n="108" who="S0439">yeah but she <unclear/> she was really good but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know cos you always expect people like she was very much into her yoga and she was all about the spirituality of yoga and the the <vocal desc="misc"/> she was like if you want to join in with the <vocal desc="misc"/> the please do I was like no <vocal desc="laugh"/> but erm but then it's weird because she was quite not unfit but just she was a bit overweight erm there's this one pose where you have to kind of not do a press up but you have to lower yourself into the right position and then straighten your back out and you have to go down with your arms so it was a bit like a press up all the way to the floor and she like it's taken me a long time to learn to do this because you have to support your whole body weight and everything and I was like <pause dur="short"/> it's not that difficult</u>
<u n="109" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0439">she just seemed like slightly unfit</u>
<u n="111" who="S0441">maybe she just eats shit</u>
<u n="112" who="S0439">yeah but she was like really into her yoga and everything it was really good</u>
<u n="113" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0439">like I was sweating ridiculous amounts</u>
<u n="115" who="S0441">mm I love it</u>
<u n="116" who="S0439">yeah it was actually really good I enjoyed it <pause dur="short"/> so yeah fourteen weeks of yogaing just at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0441">mm she must be raking it in was it busy?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0439">yeah absolutely rammed I think there was about twenty-five people</u>
<u n="119" who="S0441">jesus christ</u>
<u n="120" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and the room was tiny</u>
<u n="121" who="S0441">literally just <unclear>is it</unclear> just once a week?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0441"><trunc>bli</trunc>blimey?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0439" trans="overlap">once a week for a hundred and erm a hundred and twenty pounds for fourteen weeks</u>
<u n="125" who="S0441">she must be literally raking it in</u>
<u n="126" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0441">how? so that's like what? two thousand maybe two thousand pounds two thousand five hundred pounds</u>
<u n="128" who="S0439">yeah but it is over three months</u>
<u n="129" who="S0441">true</u>
<u n="130" who="S0439">divide two thousand pounds over three months I wouldn't be very happy</u>
<u n="131" who="S0441">that probably isn't her job is it?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0439">er well she has another class on Thursdays and stuff but I actually no I think she did have another job during the week so</u>
<u n="133" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah that's a right little earner isn't it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0441">little savings pot</u>
<u n="136" who="S0439">exactly I she was really nice though cos I said to her I was like I'm not that this month I just I genuinely can't afford a hundred and twenty pound is it okay if I pay in instalments? she was like yeah that's fine I was like oh good</u>
<u n="137" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's good</u>
<u n="138" who="S0439"><unclear/> I'm so poor at the moment <pause dur="short"/> and paying by card is just so dangerous like I just put like five pounds here five pounds there it adds up</u>
<u n="139" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah it adds up</u>
<u n="140" who="S0439">and I'm like shit how did I spend a hundred quid?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0441">yeah it is bad</u>
<u n="142" who="S0439">I've got to be careful well we get paid on Friday which is fine but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s obviously come in on Sunday and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to go shopping and I just know that she's going to spend a lot of money and you know when like I don't know she'll be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go on buy it buy it and I'll be like <vocal desc="misc"/> and then like I've got to got to be strong</u>
<u n="143" who="S0441">just be strong willpower</u>
<u n="144" who="S0439">do not buy anything <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0441" trans="overlap">think of your holidays</u>
<u n="146" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0441">think of Lapland</u>
<u n="148" who="S0439">so excited about Lapland</u>
<u n="149" who="S0441">I'm excited for you for Lapland</u>
<u n="150" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> anyone I said that they're a bit like that's really cool weird but really cool <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0441">it's well I think it's cool <pause dur="short"/> I would just stop at cool</u>
<u n="152" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> although like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s still he's really peculiar like whenever I go round he just won't talk to me</u>
<u n="153" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah really?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0439">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s spoken to him about it he'll well he just no he he just wants to leave the girls to like talk about girly things I was like that's fine but it's still a bit weird it's like I'll go round and you don't even really like</u>
<u n="155" who="S0441" trans="overlap">will he not even say anything?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0439">he doesn't even really even acknowledge you like even not just me it's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's like everybody it's just that he doesn't he just doesn't really acknowledge you it's really bizarre</u>
<u n="157" who="S0441"><unclear/> like a holiday?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0439">fine that's the weird thing <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's just very peculiar</u>
<u n="159" who="S0441">it is peculiar <pause dur="short"/> what a strange child</u>
<u n="160" who="S0439">mm well he's not even a child he's a man child he's thirty years old <pause dur="short"/> doesn't look thirty years old but he is</u>
<u n="161" who="S0441">wow I'd hope to be doing something else when I'm thirty years old that sounds really horrible but</u>
<u n="162" who="S0439">talk about men <trunc>chil</trunc> well man childs men children <unclear>don't know</unclear> what that plural of that would be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I'm just so unhappy in my relationship right now I wish I was <trunc>si</trunc></u>
<u n="163" who="S0441" trans="overlap">are you still talking to him?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0439">I'm not well I send him like the odd message but he's just like been like bombarding me <pause dur="short"/> part of me maybe thinks it's funny it's like ha ha your life has like spiralled and you're unhappy</u>
<u n="165" who="S0441">he's an utter moron</u>
<u n="166" who="S0439">yeah but I was just like he was just like you know? I wish I was single sometimes it was so much nicer when I was in a long distance relationship I was like</u>
<u n="167" who="S0441">what? with you?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0439">yeah exactly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0441" trans="overlap">great</u>
<u n="170" who="S0439">I was like erm okay</u>
<u n="171" who="S0441">why is that? because he could have all the freedom that he wanted?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0439">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="173" who="S0441">great</u>
<u n="174" who="S0439">like they live him and his girlfriend live together yesterday he actually wrote that she was a mistake I'm just <unclear/> your girlfriend</u>
<u n="175" who="S0441">why doesn't he just break up with her then?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0439">yeah exactly <unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0441" trans="overlap">he doesn't have the balls to do it</u>
<u n="178" who="S0439">yeah you're obviously not happy what you why don't you just end it? he's like well I don't want to hurt her feelings I'm like</u>
<u n="179" who="S0441">shut up</u>
<u n="180" who="S0439">but writing things behind her back to your ex girlfriend</u>
<u n="181" who="S0441">yeah well he's got a a little bit of a track history of this hasn't he?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah exactly like I've I've made sure that I've not written one thing that is like anything like nothing</u>
<u n="183" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that she could come back to you and say?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah nothing I've got nothing like that erm but he like wrote me a message being like you know I I words can't describe how much you mean to me and how important you are and how amazing you are</u>
<u n="185" who="S0441" trans="overlap">fuck off</u>
<u n="186" who="S0439">I'm like yeah I'm like he actually turned around and in a text message on Sunday was like you'll always be my Eskimo and I was like and I literally went back I was like I am not yours</u>
<u n="187" who="S0441">fuck off</u>
<u n="188" who="S0439">like I have not been yours for a long time</u>
<u n="189" who="S0441" trans="overlap">what is his? what is his problem? what goes through his head?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I know I was like he <unclear/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0441">what does he think happens in the world?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0439">yeah I was I am not yours what a very peculiar thing to say to somebody that sounded so it was so possessive</u>
<u n="193" who="S0441" trans="overlap">course</u>
<u n="194" who="S0439">I was just like whatever issues you're going through you have to sort out and it is your fault if you think she's a mistake then it is your mistake you have made</u>
<u n="195" who="S0441">nothing to do with you</u>
<u n="196" who="S0439">yeah nothing to do with me I am not yours please like sort out your life because I just have this fear that I'm suddenly going to get a phone call from his girlfriend being like</u>
<u n="197" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0439">what the fuck have you done?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0441" trans="overlap">have you? have you broken up our our relationship?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> done anything like not just like no</u>
<u n="201" who="S0441">he's such a freak</u>
<u n="202" who="S0439">I know I was just like dude you can't <unclear/> it's just ridiculous</u>
<u n="203" who="S0441"><unclear/> I don't like him</u>
<u n="204" who="S0439">no no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0439">oh my god yeah but if I if I was naïve I would be like ah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really cares about me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s telling me how amazing I am</u>
<u n="207" who="S0441"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really wants me back</u>
<u n="208" who="S0439">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants me back</u>
<u n="209" who="S0441">you know? I think we're soulmates</u>
<u n="210" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> actually I'm just like what the fuck are you <trunc>tal</trunc></u>
<u n="211" who="S0441" trans="overlap">go away</u>
<u n="212" who="S0439">what are you talking about boy? like I just have this feeling wasn't it? he'll break up with his girlfriend and then come and be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I broke up with my girlfriend I'm like so</u>
<u n="213" who="S0441">so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0439">yeah what do you want me? what?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that's nice for you</u>
<u n="216" who="S0439">like I'm not going to be your girlfriend so erm if you broke up with her for me then gutted <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0439">such a <unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0439">he was like he was like you're so lucky you're so free and er you can do whatever you want to do and you do all of these amazing things and go on holiday and I was like yeah but you have a girlfriend you go home to every night and you know? you can snuggle with and have a relationship with he's like yeah I don't think that's a fair trade</u>
<u n="221" who="S0441" trans="overlap">fuck off <pause dur="long"/> it's just like even so though <trunc>wh</trunc>why has it got to be such a death sentence?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0441">it doesn't have to be like that</u>
<u n="224" who="S0439">I was like yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you've done this to yourself you moved in with her</u>
<u n="225" who="S0441">even so even if he moves in with her just go grab some balls and say look I'm going away for the weekend or something</u>
<u n="226" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="227" who="S0441">you don't have to be with her every single minute of the day</u>
<u n="228" who="S0439">and I was just like dude</u>
<u n="229" who="S0441">he's just complaining about life</u>
<u n="230" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0441">he just wants you to turn around and be like</u>
<u n="232" who="S0439">he's never happy</u>
<u n="233" who="S0441">I think he just wants you to turn around and just say oh I</u>
<u n="234" who="S0439">I love you</u>
<u n="235" who="S0441"><unclear/> same</u>
<u n="236" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0441">but you're not going to do that</u>
<u n="238" who="S0439">no he I I'm so sure that he wants me to turn around and just be like I love you I want to be with you you know you were the most amazing guy ever I can't believe <unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah I miss you so much</u>
<u n="240" who="S0439">yeah I miss you</u>
<u n="241" who="S0441">no no</u>
<u n="242" who="S0439">and I'm just not doing it and I think he's just going to keep hounding until he gets what he wants</u>
<u n="243" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no no he's going to keep hounding you until until you said that</u>
<u n="244" who="S0439">and the moment I turn around and be like look I'm not going to be like look <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know? I love you I want to be with you I can't believe we've been apart for two years he'll be like oh actually I'm going to try and make things work with my girlfriend</u>
<u n="245" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0439">you know that would happen</u>
<u n="247" who="S0441">that would happen cos that's what he wants</u>
<u n="248" who="S0439">exactly</u>
<u n="249" who="S0441">he he wants the power</u>
<u n="250" who="S0439">yeah and erm no</u>
<u n="251" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">uh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0441">what a dick</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439">I know <pause dur="short"/> just weird I just don't understand some boys</u>
<u n="256" who="S0441">I don't either they're morons</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0441">I love that word</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439">moron</u>
<u n="260" who="S0441">it's so satisfying</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439">moron</u>
<u n="262" who="S0441">moron</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0441"><unclear>fridge</unclear> is looking good isn't it?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="266" who="S0441">not</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">bit frosty</u>
<u n="268" who="S0441">gets on my nerve why doesn't she reply?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439">I know she's shit</u>
<u n="270" who="S0441">she's absolutely</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's like the whole blind thing like it's fifteen pounds for fuck sake</u>
<u n="272" who="S0441">I know I guarantee that the the landlady surely can't be that bothered about it I mean I would imagine it would cost her more money anyway</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">mm and also the only reason we're having this problem is because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> couldn't fucking organise a blind to put up so they had to put up this blind just imagine right if he'd come over and there hadn't been a blind</u>
<u n="274" who="S0441">that would've been good</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">like it would've been like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no offense why are you so incompetent?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0441">why are you shit at life?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">and she just doesn't get back to me</u>
<u n="278" who="S0441">no it is weird</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> god some people are just ridiculous at their jobs</u>
<u n="280" who="S0441">yes they are <pause dur="short"/> yeah this new whipped Philadelphia is just weird</u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">whipped Philadelphia?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0441">yeah don't really see what the difference is</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">no what is the difference?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's whipped it's just whipped it's like fluffy</u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">oh give us a look it's a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439">oh I see</u>
<u n="288" who="S0441">it's just on the front</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439">so it's a bit like <unclear>Boursin</unclear>?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439"><unclear>Boursin's</unclear> quite nice actually</u>
<u n="292" who="S0441">well yeah it is nice <unclear/> cheese actually</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0441">but still</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0441">stupid</u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">it is very good <unclear>Boursin</unclear></u>
<u n="298" who="S0441">god it's such a Christmas cheese that is</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm I just love the garlic</u>
<u n="300" who="S0441">ah it's so good</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">it's definitely not good for a date night though</u>
<u n="302" who="S0441">no avoid</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439">avoid that yeah <pause dur="short"/> bought some cheese and went we went to <unclear/> <vocal desc="misc"/> I took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> into Tesco's yesterday</u>
<u n="304" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">and got some cheese mature cheddar was like half price</u>
<u n="306" who="S0441">nice</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">I was like bargain I got a massive lump of cheddar for one pound</u>
<u n="308" who="S0441">love mature cheddar</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">I love I can't deal with weak <trunc>che</trunc> like mild cheese you need a good strong cheddar</u>
<u n="310" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no no no no no no taste something</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">exactly</u>
<u n="312" who="S0441">can't be airy fairy</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">who likes airy fairy? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0441">exactly</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">god <vocal desc="misc"/> I said I'd go over to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and watch the Bake Off but</u>
<u n="316" who="S0441">I I'm really behind <vocal desc="laugh"/> I need to watch two episodes before I watch this one</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">I love the Bake Off</u>
<u n="320" who="S0441">me too but I need to <vocal desc="misc"/> I hate being behind I hate not not knowing what's going on</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you're going to have to you're going to have to have a marathon tonight</u>
<u n="322" who="S0441">I will</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">then next Wednesday we'll all come round or I'll invite the girls round here and we can do it</u>
<u n="324" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">that's one thing <unclear/> you just like <unclear/> the Bake Off but I just don't like it as much like good god you can't complain about the fact that we like something you don't like no like we're not going to not watch it just because you don't like it I was just like er she was like I just can't get involved and then when I go round I just don't feel involved with you watching the Bake Off I'm like so</u>
<u n="326" who="S0441">so</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">then why?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just say oh I'll give it a miss this time <unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="330" who="S0441">if she's that bothered why can't she arrange something to do with you separately if she's that bothered?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">I don't know I just don't know <pause dur="short"/> so stupid it was so childish</u>
<u n="332" who="S0441">well I guess you might have to look at it from her perspective maybe she has been rejected in the past or something I don't know</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">well I can understand bloody why she's been rejected in the past if this is the way she behaves</u>
<u n="334" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">erm also I've done all the washing and everything so erm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0441">oh so do I</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">oh have you?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah okay I don't wash it I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going to come back so she's going to want the washing machine so I'll stuff everything in so I did it all yesterday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0441">no literally me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got back and we were like right let's do all my washing <unclear>did</unclear> all our washing together</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's good though</u>
<u n="342" who="S0441">it was fine</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">did you stab each other this week? or were you? no?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no we got on really well and it was a really good opportunity to have like chats about things and make plans for the future</u>
<u n="345" who="S0439">what did you chat about?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0441">so we've actually officially decided to move in together</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="348" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">and when are you going to do that?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0441">well probably in like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> two years</u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="352" who="S0441">which would give me <trunc>t</trunc> give me time to save up</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0441">but the thing is if I <trunc>ha</trunc> it's difficult cos I I don't think I'm going to be able to save up any money here</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="356" who="S0441">so I'm I <trunc>ne</trunc> I haven't asked my mum yet but I might ask if I can move home</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> when I move out I'm going to probably move out <unclear/> officially move out</u>
<u n="358" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I know I know I know I know I know <pause dur="short"/> but you know you're just sort of living for your own means aren't you?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">oh yeah like my salary <trunc>ge</trunc> I do not save</u>
<u n="360" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">I try and fail miserably</u>
<u n="362" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's really annoying I try and fail miserably</u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">I mean I do go on holiday but</u>
<u n="364" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah but that's it</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">that's the thing like this holiday was ninety-nine pounds like the one I'm going on was ninety-nine pounds like I should be able to afford a ninety-nine pound holiday</u>
<u n="366" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">and I still struggle</u>
<u n="368" who="S0441">exactly ninety-nine pounds is nothing really</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439">exactly</u>
<u n="370" who="S0441">in the grand scheme of things <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/> so I'll keep you posted with that</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439">oh yeah no it's fine</u>
<u n="372" who="S0441" trans="overlap">what's going on <pause dur="short"/> it depends it it I don't know cos he he's obviously so much further ahead than I am</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0441">and I don't like he doesn't want it to be all him I really don't want it to be all him</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="376" who="S0441">like if we put a deposit down I wouldn't want him to put</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">no when you move in move in together you mean like buy a house?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0441" trans="overlap">we need to yeah we need to buy a house and we need to we need it to be half</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0441">like half each cos I'm not</u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">yeah cos then not thinking of the negatives but if you did break up it it would be him</u>
<u n="382" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah I know I know so it was really good like because it was so chilled out and stuff and I guess normally when we're at weekends together</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439">it's a bit</u>
<u n="384" who="S0441">you can't really talk about that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="386" who="S0441">cos you don't want to like waste the sort of time talking about serious stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and if you do have an argument it's two days that you're not going to</u>
<u n="388" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah so it's just wasted so we talked about it it was really good and cos he's never really actually said to me <pause dur="short"/> yeah let's move in and let's do it</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0441">here or whatever</u>
<u n="391" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0441">it's always been sort of pie in the sky sort of thing</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0441">but this time he's actually said yeah let's make a plan let's save up and we'll move in together you'll save up I mean in all fairness with him he's been worried that I wouldn't have enough money that's why he's not really committed to it <pause dur="short"/> because he doesn't want to</u>
<u n="395" who="S0439">he doesn't want to have to support you yeah course not yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and that's absolutely fine that's clearly understandable</u>
<u n="397" who="S0439">yeah no it's like it's hard and the houses are big like they're massive investments</u>
<u n="398" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0439">like if I was with somebody and they didn't pull their weight I'd be annoyed wouldn't you? you don't want to resent somebody</u>
<u n="400" who="S0441" trans="overlap">exactly you you you'd no and you know? I don't want to be the person that sort of like just</u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">it would be it would be his house it wouldn't be your house it'd be his house so</u>
<u n="402" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="403" who="S0439">yeah no it makes perfect sense</u>
<u n="404" who="S0441">so yeah that's exciting</u>
<u n="405" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0441">but it won't be for a while</u>
<u n="407" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0441">you know like I'm twenty-four now <pause dur="short"/> and things are going very quickly life is moving on</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0441">and even he has said like he doesn't want to live with his mum like he doesn't want to be a twenty-five year old man living with his mum so</u>
<u n="411" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0441">he said he wants to get it done soon and he and we may as well sort of just cos even he said to me like I actually even this holiday he was like I I don't want to be an old old parent as well he was like I don't wanna I don't wanna sort of wait till past thirty to have kids</u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">oh my god</u>
<u n="414" who="S0441">so yeah <unclear/> getting deep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0439">if someone said to me and said I don't want to get to thirty without children I'd be like fuck</u>
<u n="416" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> shit</u>
<u n="417" who="S0439">I'm like get out the door right this moment keep your penis away from me</u>
<u n="418" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0439">there's no baby making going on in here</u>
<u n="420" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">I mean hell no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm on the next plane out of the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know what I'm like though</u>
<u n="423" who="S0439">yeah you were like you were like <vocal desc="gasp"/> babies</u>
<u n="424" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yay <pause dur="short"/> I didn't obviously let on though</u>
<u n="425" who="S0439">no no obviously not</u>
<u n="426" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just cool</u>
<u n="427" who="S0439">while your ovaries were screaming <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0441" trans="overlap">just be like oh okay cool cool man <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0439">if you if you if you want</u>
<u n="430" who="S0441">yeah sure</u>
<u n="431" who="S0439">if that's what if that's what you want</u>
<u n="432" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I don't care or anything</u>
<u n="433" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah sounds great</u>
<u n="434" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0441">so yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0439">but like one of those weird things like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> been looking for a house for a while and she's it's like fallen through a few times like it's taken her quite a long time so</u>
<u n="437" who="S0441" trans="overlap">man that's scary as well</u>
<u n="438" who="S0439">like if you like sometimes if you want to start buying a house you've got to look about a year or stuff in advance so</u>
<u n="439" who="S0441" trans="overlap">exactly so so we're we're doing that that's our plan so</u>
<u n="440" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> would you be looking in <anon type="place"/> or outside of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0441">I've said said to him I'm not I'm not living in <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0441">so perhaps</u>
<u n="444" who="S0439">like a dormitory town?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0439">like say <anon type="place"/> or something?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0441">yeah I mean I don't <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="449" who="S0441">but I I said to him like that sort of area</u>
<u n="450" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0441" trans="overlap">like <anon type="place"/> it's sort of down <anon type="place"/> up</u>
<u n="452" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0441">perhaps just above him</u>
<u n="454" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0441"><anon type="place"/> up would be fine</u>
<u n="456" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0441">I don't want to live in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0439">I wouldn't want to live in <anon type="place"/> you can't save money here bollocks if you're going to save any money in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0441">exactly <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="460" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you need to sell your body to make money in <anon type="place"/> now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> stripper</u>
<u n="462" who="S0439">I could imagine you as a stripper <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I couldn't <pause dur="short"/> I would be so awkward</u>
<u n="464" who="S0439"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0441" trans="overlap">people like <unclear/> be horrible</u>
<u n="466" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you would <pause dur="short"/> I think I would laugh</u>
<u n="467" who="S0441">it would be so awkward and I'd just lose all the no one would come to me cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or they've come to you to laugh at you</u>
<u n="469" who="S0441">yeah maybe they'd pity me they'd like throw money at me for pity</u>
<u n="470" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> come see the stripper who's the worst stripper ever</u>
<u n="471" who="S0441">I might be quite good maybe I'd literally be like a show in in itself</u>
<u n="472" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> the stripper who's not a stripper <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0441" trans="overlap">try it yeah <pause dur="short"/> the shittest stripper ever</u>
<u n="474" who="S0439">the shittest stripper that could be your tagline <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0441">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> people would flock from far and wide</u>
<u n="476" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you like a little bit of sexiness with your comedy? come see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she'll make you laugh and cum in the same half an hour</u>
<u n="479" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0441">ah <pause dur="short"/> this is just such a cheese overload but I don't care</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">love cheese</u>
<u n="482" who="S0441">so yeah I will let you know what's going on</u>
<u n="483" who="S0439">yeah no no don't worry about me I'm all good</u>
<u n="484" who="S0441">but yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0439">like I'm still debating on whether if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes back to <anon type="place"/> to go back to <anon type="place"/> with her so</u>
<u n="486" who="S0441">okay well</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439">don't worry we're all good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0441">when does she go back?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0439">next June</u>
<u n="490" who="S0441">okay <trunc>wh</trunc>what? so you'd give up your course?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0439">I actually gave it up</u>
<u n="492" who="S0441">you gave it up? I did wonder why you weren't studying</u>
<u n="493" who="S0439">I couldn't do it it was like they wanted us to do fifteen hours a month erm a week and</u>
<u n="494" who="S0441">and it was too much</u>
<u n="495" who="S0439">they'd moved the exam forward it was supposed to be the end of September they moved the exam forward to mid August and I well I was in <anon type="place"/> and I couldn't do it and they were like well you have to do it I'm like well I can't</u>
<u n="496" who="S0441" trans="overlap">can't</u>
<u n="497" who="S0439">and so I decided that I'm long distance learning was probably not working for me so</u>
<u n="498" who="S0441">did you pay for it?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0439">yeah but they give you your money back</u>
<u n="500" who="S0441">well that's good I would have thought they wouldn't give it back</u>
<u n="501" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no they gave me I think they took a hundred odd pounds for like the induction and stuff but <unclear/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh so you you you don't pay it in bulk?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0439">no no I didn't pay up front I paid like in instalments</u>
<u n="504" who="S0441">well that's good</u>
<u n="505" who="S0439">but I just couldn't do it I didn't have I didn't have the time and I was like it's not worth four thousand pounds if I don't do as well as I would've done so</u>
<u n="506" who="S0441">no but could you imagine if you like did but just didn't get very good grades?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0439">exactly</u>
<u n="508" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that would be shit</u>
<u n="509" who="S0439">exactly so I was like</u>
<u n="510" who="S0441">would be a big waste wouldn't it? a waste of money?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0439">yeah completely that's what I thought it didn't work so I will probably I want to try and look at going back full time</u>
<u n="512" who="S0441">what? to do a course?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="515" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I still I still would like to do the psychology and the become an occupational psychologist it's just when I do it</u>
<u n="516" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="518" who="S0441">well it could be a sort of a thing to look forward to or no no but plan for work</u>
<u n="519" who="S0439">yeah exactly so I've got like this year I want to do a year at <anon type="place"/> obviously</u>
<u n="520" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0439">and then</u>
<u n="522" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah no no I've got to head off in a minute to go watch the Bake Off anyway</u>
<u n="524" who="S0441" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="525" who="S0439">but like I want to do obviously finish the year at <anon type="place"/> and I want to carry on till like next definitely definitely want to carry on till like next Easter next summer because that's when all my projects come <unclear/> and I want to complete some projects</u>
<u n="526" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0439">erm so I could start uni next September or the September after I wouldn't want to leave it too late but I'm still</u>
<u n="528" who="S0441">and as well probably bit of advice <pause dur="short"/> like psychology people if if you're not just like a undergraduate learning psychology like everyone else does</u>
<u n="529" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0441">they perhaps would look for more mature people anyway</u>
<u n="531" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0441">for that sort of life experience</u>
<u n="533" who="S0439">exactly</u>
<u n="534" who="S0441">so I think it's probably better if you do wait</u>
<u n="535" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0441">not too long obviously but</u>
<u n="537" who="S0439">yeah I'm glad I tried and I did really enjoy it I just couldn't just couldn't dedicate fifteen hours a week</u>
<u n="538" who="S0441">it's a lot of hours</u>
<u n="539" who="S0439">yeah and</u>
<u n="540" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0439">full time work and then obviously I was training for this half marathon I just couldn't fit it all in and I was like I'm not going to do it justice cos I don't want to waste my money so I decided not to do it</u>
<u n="542" who="S0441">you have to literally do like an hour a night <unclear/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you have to do like two hours a night yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0439">plus like a whole weekend and I just couldn't do it I couldn't fit it in especially not with all the running and everything so</u>
<u n="546" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0439">no I'll get there <pause dur="short"/> okay I've got to go and watch Bake Off</u>
<u n="548" who="S0441">if I did move out I mean obviously we have to wait for the end of the lease anyway but what would you do in that time if I did do that?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439">I'd just find somewhere else what like next January in January?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0441">I guess</u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">yeah I'd just find somewhere else it's not a problem it's <anon type="place"/> there's always somewhere</u>
<u n="552" who="S0441">you can rent a tent in <anon type="place"/> for six hundred and thirty pounds in someone's front room as if true that's <trunc>ridi</trunc> isn't that so stupid?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439">so basically if you leave I'm gonna live in a tent?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0441">in someone's front room yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0439">great thanks</u>
<u n="556" who="S0441">for double the rent that you're paying already</u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">well then erm great nice to know that I've got a good living situation to look forward to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0441">what kind of life have you got to look forward to eh?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0439">no I'll be fine I could bond I could move in with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could you even fucking imagine?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0441">yeah life would be <unclear/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s such a copycat</u>
<u n="562" who="S0441">what's she done now?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0439">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said hi next weekend is my last weekend before I go back to <anon type="place"/> for three weeks so do you want to go to this jazz festival? and I was like mm I might be busy washing my hair and hanging out with cooler people and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like ha ha yeah I might be doing my nails fuck off have your own joke <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0441">I can sense a little bit of er bristliness going on here</u>
<u n="565" who="S0439">well that's my joke <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0441">god literally if if you two fight over everything</u>
<u n="567" who="S0439">I mean she's just such a little copycat why doesn't she have like a personality or life of her own so fuck off</u>
<u n="568" who="S0441">oh dear</u>
<u n="569" who="S0439">okay got to go got to watch the Bake Off okay but we'll see you in a bit have fun with your bagel</u>
<u n="570" who="S0441">baked beans <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0439">your <trunc>ba</trunc> your cold baked beans okay see you in a bit dear</u>
<u n="572" who="S0441">bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
